<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201804_AstroNovaTransition_LG.201804_AstroNovaTransition_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Transitioning Narrow-Format Flight Deck Printer Manufacturing and Repair to AstroNova</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
TRANSITIONING NARROW-FORMAT FLIGHT DECK PRINTER MANUFACTURING AND REPAIR TO ASTRONOVA
Dear Customer:
As part of our continuing effort to improve our service and support, we have signed a licensing agreement with a leading cockpit printer manufacturer, AstroNova, to manufacture and repair our model PTA-45B narrow-format flight deck printers. 

AstroNova has production and repair lines in place and has updated their FAA capabilities list to repair these parts. They are ready and capable of fulfilling both original equipment and repair and overhaul demand. 
The AstroNova team will contact you by 31 May to establish new contracts. After those are in place, the Honeywell team will work with you to remove the cockpit printers from existing contracts. Continue ordering from us until your AstroNova contract is executed.
Both companies are committed to minimizing any production and delivery impact. In order to minimize potential issues, please follow these guidelines: 



	- 
Effective 27 April, all new production and repair orders with due dates of April 27 or later will be subcontracted to AstroNova at the address noted below.

	- Honeywell’s MyAerospace Repair Orders Capability application will be updated on 28 May, removing Renton, WA as a repair site. 
	- Honeywell will not accept new or repair orders (or hardware returned for repair), after 28 May. To mitigate any impact in our ability to support AOG shipments, we encourage customers to plan accordingly and communicate with us to determine a proactive approach to minimize AOG requirements during this time frame. 
	- This impacts manufacturing and services operations for the product line at the Honeywell Penang, Malaysia and Renton, WA sites.  



The following information will help you plan for this change: 


	- 
Impacted part numbers and associated spares: 8055515-4501, 8055515-4502, 8055515-4503,  8055515-4504, 8055515-4506, 8055515-4507

	- 
 Please update your authorized supplier 
list and internal systems to include the new supplier location as an approved supplier:







Company Name


AstroNova Inc.




Address


600 Greenwich Avenue








West Warwick, RI








02893




Phone


United States
(401) 828-4000






	- 
Cage code:  54318

	- DUNS number:  047986898
	- Repair station certifications:


	- FAA – O60R489Y                  Status: Active
	- EASA – EASA.145.6325        Expiration:  1-Mar-2019




Please share this information with others in your company. If you have questions or require additional information, please contact either TCarll@astronovainc.com &lt;[[mailto:TCarll@astronovainc.com]]&gt; or contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager. 




Honeywell Aerospace
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt;

Please click here &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Y0GFL0sZ300D4002qIQ0hXp]]&gt; to subscribe to our email communications.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
