<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_BGANewsletter_March_Email.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Here is your March Issue of the Direct-To Aviation Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt;    |    Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;    |    View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;  Forward to a friend &lt;[[{{system.forwardToFriendLink}}]]&gt;
Enhance your Aircraft Cleaning
Proven Technology. Portable Design. 



 


The all-new Honeywell UV Treatment Wand &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-treatment-wand?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bti_hygiene&amp;utm_term=newsletter]]&gt; is our most versatile, lightweight UV system yet. Best of all, it is compact enough to go anywhere a person can go, with a battery case that can be worn or wheeled by the operator. Available soon! Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-treatment-wand?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;.
Honeywell partners with Mark Wahlberg


 


Wahlberg and his flight operations team partnered with Honeywell to upgrade the flight deck, satellite communications system, services and software solutions on his Bombardier Global Express business jet. The upgrade helps deliver a better flying experience for Mark and his passengers while also enhancing the aircraft’s value.


 






READ MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/customer-success-stories/2021/03/honeywell-creates-great-flying-experience-for-mark-wahlberg?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;
Honeywell&apos;s LASEREF series continues innovative tradition


 


Honeywell’s LASEREF family has been the standard for commercial aviation since 1997. The LASEREF series continues this innovative tradition, providing exceptionally long life with stable performance over the entire range of Aerospace environments, and was designed to safety critical Design Assurance Level A with applicable civil TSOs.


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/sensors/laseref-iv-inertial-reference-systems?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;
Quick Topic Video: Getting the Most from the Honeywell Pilot Gateway


 


By Ryan Milmoe
Have you heard about the Honeywell Pilot Gateway? It is a free customizable solution that gives pilots instant access to technical publications, videos, and other valuable resources by aircraft make, model and system.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/news/2021/03/getting-the-most-from-the-honeywell-pilot-gateway]]&gt;






 








 








 


 






Radar Corner: 8 Things You Might Not Understand About Airborne Weather Radar – Part 3


 


By Stephen D. Hammack
The RDR-4000 &amp; RDR-7000 weather radars have some unique features. This article explores the &quot;why&quot; behind the development of the new modes and the problems they solve.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/news/2021/03/radar-corner]]&gt;
Honeywell Pilot Gateway


 


This month there are SIL briefings for these platforms: Bombardier, Cessna, Dassault, Embraer, Gulfstream, Hawker, Lockheed, Pilatus. 


 






CLICK HERE &lt;[[https://performanceaccel.honeywell.com/~/media/Pilots%20App/Documents/SILs/SIL%20Briefing/SIL%20Briefing%202021%200315?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;
Honeywell Announces Winners of the Channel Partner of the Year Awards 2020


 


Through the commitment and dedication of Honeywell Channel Partners, we continued to serve and support our global customers in the most challenging of times.
 
It is therefore a particular pleasure to recognize the winners of the 2020 Honeywell Channel Partner of the 
Year Awards. Congratulations to all our winners &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2021/02/the-2020-channel-partner-of-the-year-awards?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;!

Click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us/channel-partner-locator?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt; to use the Authorized Sales &amp; Service Partner Locator.
Your Feedback is valuable


 


Every year, Aviation International News (AIN) conducts a Product Support Survey where they ask their readers to evaluate aircraft, engines and avionics products for the prior twelve months. We invite customers of our products and services to subscribe to AIN and receive the 2021 survey by following the quick 2 minute registration process using this link: www.ainonline.com/pss/honeywell &lt;[[http://www.ainonline.com/pss/honeywell]]&gt;. If you’re already subscribed to AIN and take the annual survey, then we simply encourage you to watch for and complete the 2021 survey. Your feedback to the AIN Survey will be taken seriously and our team will use the comments to identify key opportunities for improvement. Thank you!
Our most recent webinars       






 






Virtual Operators Conference


 


 


 


Watch Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Gfx9kN9aprhhAH7x1dUUCr]]&gt;


 


Access Code: 3102021


 






 








Conferencia de Operadores Virtual


 


 


 


Watch Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/RMs8Q4dcJWeY2HvEY8RrUR?]]&gt;


 


Access Code: 3102021


 






 








Conferência de Operadores Virtual


 


 


 


Watch Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/W64n9iUaqUw4FhMbrL8Bgc]]&gt;


 


Access Code: 3112021
Honeywell Forge: Not your Father&apos;s Datalink


 


Datalink technology has advanced in the last four-plus decades. Today, pilots use digital datalink channels to request and receive clearances from ATC, access the latest weather information, exchange text messages with ground operations, upload flight plans, use modern navigation technologies, and much more.


 






READ MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2021/02/honeywell-forge-not-your-father-datalink?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;
Captain Carlos Alberto de Azevedo talks increased situational awareness


 


With more than 30 years’ aviation experience, Captain Carlos Alberto de Azevedo has spent the last eight years in the corporate world and has been the chief pilot of a privately-owned Embraer Legacy 650 business jet for over six years. 

Read more about how Honeywell has helped Captain Alberto de Azevedo achieve peace of mind while flying.


 






READ STORY &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/customer-success-stories/2020/01/hazardous-landings-made-safer?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;













 






 


“The Honeywell synthetic vision system increases our situational awareness in higher risk landings at airports such as Aspen, or Sion in the Swiss Alps. It gives us comfort, safety and highly advantageous operations,” says Azevedo
How to Avoid Aircraft Maintenance Surprises in 2021


 


Dealing with uncertainty was part of the job description for aircraft maintenance teams in 2020. While aircraft were parked, maintenance teams continued to perform essential tasks, get a jump on upcoming major service intervals, install new hardware to meet mandates, improve operations or create a better passenger experience.


 






READ MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2021/02/how-to-avoid-aircraft-maintenance-surprises-2021?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bganewsletter&amp;utm_content=marbganewsletter]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;    


 


© 2021 Honeywell International Inc.  &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; 
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202


 


Subscription Preference &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt;  |  Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; |  Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; |  Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
