<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_03_March.2019_March_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - March 2019 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
March 2019
OVATION SELECT GOES DIGITAL WITH NEW UPGRADE
Honeywell&apos;s Ovation Select™ CS upgrade enables C-Series analog systems a phased approach toward a fully-digital Ovation Select transformation. This three-phase upgrade path provides a more flexible migration in both component choices and budgets...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/2019_N_08 OvationSelectCS CMS Upgrade.pdf]]&gt;
Customers and technology intersect for Honeywell field service engineer

The intersection between customers and technology is a very comfortable spot for Honeywell Field Service Engineer David Heilman. He’s a “people person” who thrives on solving technical problems... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/march/customers-and-technology-intersect-for-honeywell-field-service-engineer]]&gt;.
SmartView aids approaches in challenging conditions
Honeywell&apos;s SmartView synthetic vision system provides pilots with realistic views of surroundings day or night, and eases workload in adverse conditions with turbulence, crosswinds, mountainous terrain and busy airspace... Learn More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/smartview-synthetic-vision-system]]&gt;.
The future of integrated flight planning is here

You&apos;ve told us you want better and more sophisticated flight planning tools that save time and reduce flight-planning errors. We are delivering... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/february/the-future-of-integrated-flight-planning-has-arrived]]&gt;.
Honeywell is opening a service center in Brazil

Honeywell will be opening a repair center for avionics products later this year in Sao Jose Dos Campos, Brazil. Additional information will be coming soon.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
