<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201806_Americas_Nurture_Kellstrom_C130_mih.201806_Americas_Nurture_Email1_Kellst</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Legacy Platforms Demand Legacy Solutions</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;      &lt;[[http://www.kellstromdefense.com/]]&gt;

Total C-130 Support with Honeywell and Kellstrom Defense



Honeywell is proud to be a significant content provider for the C-130 and together with Honeywell Authorized Distributor and Service Center Kellstrom Defense, we are providing highly reliable solutions.
With aging aircraft, budget constraints and pressing needs to maintain mission viability, Kellstrom Defense provides Honeywell-based solutions that are comprehensive and extend the life of your C-130 aircraft and systems while sustaining mission effectiveness throughout and beyond its original operational life cycle.
Kellstrom’s large inventory of retrofit, modification and upgrade solutions include:


	- E2H Environment Control System (ECS)® – Flight Deck ECS System Upgrade – Provides a 233% increase in airflow, 2x increase in cooling turbine reliability (5.000 hour Meantime Between Failure (MBTF)), 2x increased service life for heat exchangers and l.3x (minimum) improvement in reliability for flow control valves.
	- Air Turbine Starter – Drop-in upgrade based on previously fielded, high reliability design and performs with all C-130 configuration starters without the need for time-consuming rise rate adjustments.
	- SHORT-POD® APU – Increases airflow for better ECS performance and expands generator capability from 20 to 40 KVA using longer-life materials for a 4x improvement in reliability.


Learn more about Honeywell’s solutions and how Authorized Distributor and Service Center Kellstrom can keep you mission ready.





UPGRADE WITH KELLSTROM  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Kellstrom_C130.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_campaign=18_channelamericas_d&amp;s]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
