<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018 Helicopter Newsletter Q2.2018 Helicopter Newsletter Q2 mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Helicopter Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HELICOPTER NEWSLETTER
June 2018
Honeywell Improves Aircraft Operations with New Flight Data Monitoring App
Honeywell has introduced a new flight data monitoring iPad application for helicopter operators equipped with Sky Connect Tracker III systems. Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2018/may/honeywell-improves-aircraft-operations-with-new-flight-data-monitoring-app]]&gt;
NorcaTec Becomes an Authorized Distributor of T53 and T55 Engines 
 
Generations of pilots have flown helicopters powered by Honeywell&apos;s reliable, powerful T53 and T55 families of turboshaft engines on all kinds of missions under all kinds of conditions. 
Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/february/norcatec-supports-honeywell-t53-and-t55-engines]]&gt;
Honeywell&apos;s RDR2000 Increases Safety for Brazilian AS350 Operator  
 

 
Unexpected and adverse weather conditions are common in Brazil. BendixKing’s RDR2000 Radar Pod is increasing flight safety for AS350 helicopter operators in the country. Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/Honeywell-s-RDR2000-Increases-Safety-for-Brazilian-AS350-Operator]]&gt;
Air Methods Uses Tracker III for Flight Data Management (FDM) and Flight Operations Quality Assurance (FOQA) Programs 
 
Air Methods is the world&apos;s largest air medical services provider, and may be dispatched to transport a patient between hospitals, roadside accident or any extreme example in between. 
Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2018/february/air-methods-uses-tracker-iii-for-fdm-and--foqa-programs]]&gt;
Connecting Customers at the Army Aviation Mission Solutions Summit   Honeywell&apos;s connected helicopter capabilities were front and center when the Arista Hawk made its highly anticipated debut at this year’s Army Aviation Association of America (Quad A) Mission Solutions Summit. Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/Honeywell-Connects-Customers-in-Quad-A-Demos]]&gt;
Honeywell Briefs Offshore Operators on HTAWS Upgrade
Honeywell’s latest upgrade to the Enhanced Ground Proximity Warning System (EGPWS) for helicopters took center stage at the HeliOffshore Conference and Annual General Meeting in Baveno, Italy, May 5-6. Read More... &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/may/honeywell-briefs-offshore-operators-on-htaws-upgrade]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
