<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017 EEMAI ASPIRE 200_Irina.Aspire 200 Email 1- June_Irina</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>WI-FI -  In the air and on the ground</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | BUSINESS &amp; GENERAL AVIATION
THE WIFI THAT FLIES TAKES YOUR OFFICE UP IN THE AIR. INTRODUCING ASPIRE™ 200 SINGLE-CHANNEL SWIFTBROADBAND SATCOM SYSTEM.
WIFI  – in the air and on the ground.



The Aspire 200 Inmarsat SwiftBroadband Satcom is Honeywell’s most economical connectivity solution offering high speed data capability. Designed to be a compact, lightweight Satcom for mid-size business jets, the Aspire 200’s high level of performance and two antenna options make it a suitable choice for all size aircraft, including helicopters, whose cabin voice and data connectivity needs can be met with a single-channel of SwiftBroadband service.

Upgrading your aircraft with an Aspire 200 Inmarsat SwiftBroadband Satcom system provides your passengers a means to always stay connected, vital in today’s ever-connected world. Passengers can use the system from the moment they board the aircraft until they disembark and therefore they are never out of touch from the office, family or friends.

KEY FEATURES &amp; BENEFITS:


	-  Most economical connectivity solution with high speed data. Crystal clear communications from multiple sources. WIFI Connectivity 
	-  Lease options available providing hardware at nominal cost on a monthly GoDirect service
	-  2 Antenna options as well as an optional HDR upgrade allows Aspire 200 to meet data requirement needs for all markets
	-  Honeywell provides worldwide support through HAPP and SPEX plans to minimize downtime
	-  The satellite-based Aspire 200 works on the ground, below and above 10,000 feet. Pilots, Crew and Passengers stay connected at all times


With Honeywell’s satellite communications systems and GoDirect Cabin Connectivity’s full suite of airtime and services, Honeywell is now the complete connectivity solution provider when it comes to satellite communications for the cabin and cockpit.

Alex Raicu
Campaign Coordinator






CLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD OUR SALES BULLETIN &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/2017 Aspire200 Bulletin_II.PDF]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
