<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201708_Americas_Email_FeedbackMatters_mih.201708_Americas_Email_FeedbackMatters_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Feedback is Important To Us</subject>
    <textOnly>YOUR FEEDBACK IS IMPORTANT TO US
Dear Honeywell Customer: 
 
  
 
 
 We value your feedback and have used it to make doing business with us easier. Our field service engineers use the latest technology to rapidly connect you with product experts and solve technical problems. We have transformed MyAerospace for real-time order management and one-stop support. Our Direct Access mobile application allows you to easily connect with technical and pilot support as well as AOG services. Honeywell’s customer support is everywhere you are, whenever you need us.
It&apos;s Survey Season! 

If you receive the Professional Pilot Avionics or Powerplant surveys by mail or email, please take a minute to fill it out and let us know how we are doing. We look forward to hearing your feedback and continuing to serve you. For additional customer and product support resources click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/customer-and-product-support-made-simple-and-easy]]&gt;.
Mobile Access Anytime You Need It 

Our Direct Access &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt; mobile application allows you to easily connect with technical and pilot support as well as AOG services.  

Download the free Direct Access &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt; tool and have Honeywell’s customer support everywhere you are, whenever you need us.
    LEARN MORE      &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/customer-and-product-support-made-simple-and-easy]]&gt;
As your Honeywell Customer Support Manager, I am available if you need any additional support. I personally want to thank you in advance for taking the time to provide valuable feedback on the industry and Honeywell surveys. We appreciate your feedback and look forward to continuing to serve you.  
   
 Gus Garayzar   Direct: 636-486-2035 
 Mobile: 480-257-8995 
 Email: Gustavo.Garayzar@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Gustavo.Garayzar@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
