<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202103_Global_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_MC.202103_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_March</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>BendixKing Dealer Newsletter March 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
Is it really March?
 Believe it or not, we’ve rolled into March 2021. We hope our friends in the Texas area are recovering from a very tough few weeks, and to those of you in other regions who have experienced severe cold weather, hang in there – the spring thaw is right around the corner. We’ve learned a lot this past year about perseverance, adaptability and remained united as we walked through tough times together. As the COVID vaccine continues to rollout and travel restrictions loosen, we are looking forward to greeting each of you in person. Until then, we hope you remain in good health and remember we’re here to help.



NEWS BRIEFS
CUSTOMER OPT IN!
Help your 
customers stay informed. Remind them to “opt-in” to receive communications and updates. 

The highly efficient, form-fit, KFC 230 (AeroCruze 230) &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ai/autopilots-and-indicators/aerocruze-230]]&gt; autopilot upgrade is now STC’d for Cessna Caravans – and many other platforms.

Help us make sure customers stay informed of the latest news, upgrades – and 
more. Share this URL: STAY INFORMED - SIGN UP HERE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/BK_Subscription_Page.html]]&gt;



CUSTOMER WEBINARS 
Let us know if you have an idea for webinar or are 
interested in co-hosting a webinar. 
Contact Lamonte &lt;[[mailto:aero.marketing@Honeywell.com?subject=Webinars]]&gt;.

SALES BULLETINS Be sure to review the latest sales bulletins for important updates. 



	- 2021BK-01 BendixKing Over The Counter (OTC) &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/content/dam/aero/en-us/documents/document-lists/sales-bulletin/bga/bendixking-dealer/2021BK-01-BendixKing-Over-The-Counter-Equipment-Sales-Dealer.pdf]]&gt;
	- 2021BK-02 BendixKing xCruze Upgrade &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/content/dam/aero/en-us/documents/document-lists/sales-bulletin/bga/bendixking-dealer/2021BK-02-xCruze-Upgrade-Sales-Bulletin.pdf]]&gt;
	- 2021BK-03 BendixKing TCAS II Change 7.1 Upgrade  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/content/dam/aero/en-us/documents/document-lists/sales-bulletin/bga/bendixking-dealer/2021BK-03-CAS-66-67A-TCAS-II-7-1-Upgrade-Dealer-Bulletin.pdf]]&gt;



SIGN UP FOR DEALER NEWSLETTER Were you forwarded this newsletter? Contact Lamonte &lt;[[mailto:aero.marketing@Honeywell.com?subject=Dealer Newsletter Sign Up]]&gt; to get on our Dealer Newsletter list.




PRODUCT SPOTLIGHT

BendixKing AeroCruze 
230
The BendixKing AeroCruze 230 (KFC 230) is now certified to support upgrades of the KFC 200. Get advanced features and improved performance out of your already great KFC 200 autopilot.  AeroCruze 230, when interfaced to digital sensors, provides safety enhancing features like Level Mode as a touchscreen controller that enables augmented mode information. For details, visit this page &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ai/autopilots-and-indicators/aerocruze-230?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_bendixking&amp;utm_content=dealer+nl+ac230]]&gt;.


TECH SUPPORT UPDATES


Australia Aerocruze 100 / xCruze Repairs Now Available – Avionics 2000 in Melbourne is now repairing the Aerocruze 100 / xCruze line of products. For more information see the Aerocruze 100 product page &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ai/autopilots-and-indicators/aerocruze-100]]&gt;.

We’ve made some changes to our Repair Partner network. Please visit this page &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/support/repair-partners]]&gt; to find your authorized repair partner today!


SHOWS &amp; EVENTS


COVID-19 continues to affect 
in-person shows and events and we will continue to evaluate each show and our participation. Organizers are also closely monitoring the pandemic and the safety of holding in person events. BendixKing/Honeywell participation at shows may vary so check with your sales team if you have questions about upcoming shows  - or to schedule an in-person demo with a customer.

SUN N FUN April 13-18, Lakeland, FL
AERO FRIEDRICHSHAFEN Germany   *New dates July 14-17</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
