<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_C&amp;PS_Announcement_A_Email_Operational.Email 2: Anniston Transition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Anniston, Alabama - Transition Plan &amp; Move Schedules</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer,  

  Honeywell Aerospace recently announced the transition of Anniston, Alabama Repair &amp; Overhaul activities to 
other Honeywell Repair &amp; Overhaul facilities. To ensure continued R&amp;O support and minimize customer impact, this transition has been planned using multiple move dates (i.e. waves, or movement of similar part families). There will be five waves during this transition, with Wave 1 &amp; Wave 2 on the same date, starting in August 2020. This transition communication addresses the schedule and parts list associated with each wave (Table 1), and the new Repair &amp; Overhaul stations information (Table 2). 

Transition Schedule






Product Line Description


Wave


New Repair Station


Anniston Last Receipt Date:


Begin Shipment to New Repair Station:




Existing Dual Capability Valves &amp; Starters


1 &amp; 2


Tempe


Aug. 20, 2020


Aug. 21, 2020




Air Cycle Machines / Fan Blowers


3


Torrance


Sept. 6, 2020


Sept. 7, 2020




Electronics


3


Phoenix – Deer Valley


Sept. 6, 2020


Sept. 7, 2020




Remaining Valves &amp; Starters


3


Tempe


Sept. 6, 2020


Sept. 7, 2020




Thermostats/Actuators


4


Tempe


Oct. 2, 2020


Oct. 3, 2020




Air Motors/Gear Boxes


5


Tempe


Oct. 25, 2020


Oct. 26, 2020








	- Wave 1 and Wave 2 include part numbers that are currently serviced at Tempe, Arizona today, along with Anniston (i.e. capabilities are listed for both sites in Honeywell ROCAPs).
	- Waves 3, 4 and 5 require moving equipment from Anniston to the future repair site, and adding capabilities to Tempe, Arizona; Torrance, California and Phoenix – Deer Valley, Arizona. 


	- This will result in a short transition period (estimated 7-14 days) while the equipment is being transferred and setup at the new repair station. We will work as quickly as possible to minimize impact to your operations.


	- As the waves progress, the Repair Site Capability list will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs. If you require a list of all parts specific to your account, please contact your Customer Support Manager (CSM) or Customer Business Manager (CBM). 


Update Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and Internal Systems
 Please ensure the new repair station is active on your authorized supplier list (ASL) and update internal systems to reflect the new supplier information by the 
transition date indicated above. 







Site


CAGE Code


Repair Station ID



Address




Phoenix – Deer Valley


58960


FAA HQ7R766N
EASA145.4539


Honeywell International Inc.
21111 N 19th Avenue
PHOENIX, AZ 85027
US




Tempe, AZ


59364


FAA ZN3R030M
EASA145.4136


Honeywell International Inc.
1300 W WARNER RD
TEMPE, AZ 85284
US




Torrance, CA


70210


FAA DO3R456L
EASA 145.4135


Honeywell International Inc.
2525 W 190TH ST
TORRANCE, CA 90504-6002
US






 What to do now?
 



	- Prepare for upcoming transition: Review the transition schedule and impacted parts list &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Honeywell_Anniston_Transition-Part-List-2020.xlsx]]&gt;, adjust your supply plan as needed, 
resolve outstanding holds to minimize transition delays, and take actions to ensure internal systems are updated to reflect the correct repair station on the correlating transition dates


	- Set/schedule updates to your internal ERP/MRP systems to support correct shipping destination per Tables 1 &amp; 2 shown above (dates/site).
	- Repair orders that are not completed prior to the transition date may require an approval prior to completion at the new repair station. Please contact your Customer Service Representative for more information on this process. 


	- Update Authorized Supplier List (ASL) as needed: Start working to add the new R&amp;O station to your approved supplier list, if not already active. If you need to conduct an on-site audit, please email Norman.Dubay@Honywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Norman.Dubay@Honywell.com]]&gt; or your Honeywell Representative. 




	- For Customers using EDI/M2M order management 


	- Please note that the link between EDI/M2M orders created to Anniston but requiring transition to the new repair site will be disconnected. These orders will need to be completed manually with any remaining actions administered through the CSR organization (AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;)
	- Your internal systems must be updated with the new repair station cage code once the transition occurs, otherwise, your order will be processed manually. 





 If you have any questions about this transition, please contact your Honeywell Business Manager, Customer Support Manager or other Honeywell representative. 
 
 Honeywell Aerospace 
 Visit MyAerospace 


Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace 
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
