<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Embraer Survey Improvements 11.10.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You spoke. Honeywell responded.</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;













 
 

 You spoke. Honeywell responded.












Hello,
In surveys and in face-to-face meetings, we asked for your opinion, and your feedback. And you answered. Honestly. Candidly. Sometimes, even bluntly.
So what happened to everything you shared? Starting with this email – followed by two more – we’ll highlight just a few examples of what you and your colleagues told us. Your comments helped us provide you with better products, services, and procedures.








Taking the Trouble Out of Troubleshooting
What you told us: Far too often, the people we talk to at Honeywell for advice can’t give us the information we need to solve the problem.
What we’ve done to correct the problem: We understand your frustration, and we’ll do everything we can to permanently solve the problem once and for all.
We’ve started by restructuring Honeywell Technical Core Teams by specific product families, staffed by people with expertise in the area. Doing that has resulted in an initial 80% rate of first-call resolutions. What does this mean to you? It means 4 out of every 5 times you call, you’ll get an answer within that one call. And we expect that percentage to climb steadily in the next year.












Delivering Dates You Can Count On.
What you told us: &quot;Honeywell delivery date promises aren’t always kept.&quot;; 
 &quot;Even if you can’t make the date, let me know so I can plan accordingly.&quot;
What we’ve done to correct the problem: Keeping Honeywell customers guessing is completely unacceptable to us. So, based on your comments, we’re changing when and how we communicate repair commitment dates.


 - Our goal is to provide an accurate initial shipment date 95%+ of the time.
 - We’re doing what it takes to reduce past-due shipment dates to 1% - or less.
 - And we’re limiting the number of shipment date changes, made per site, to less than 1 per every 100 orders.







We’re realistic enough to know that our good intentions and hard work won’t solve every problem over night. But we’re in it for the long haul. You’ve been honest with us in sharing what you need and expect from us. Now, it’s up to all of us at Honeywell to deliver.
Watch your inbox for more emails detailing what Honeywell is doing to solve the problems you’ve raised. And please – continue to share your thoughts and opinions so that together we can make Honeywell the company you’re happy to do business with.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
