<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201807_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_ClosedBeta_TM.201809_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Beta Test Invitation - Honeywell GoDirect Flight Bag Pro</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Welcome to the Exclusive Beta, {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}!   
 
 Thank you for partnering with us to be a beta tester for our new flight planning engine from GoDirect™ — powering both our next generation GoDirect Flight Services website and GoDirect Flight Bag Pro iPad 
app. We have been hard at work, developing this engine from the ground up, as well as implementing improvements to the overall experience to add more value to your flight planning subscription. 

During the beta period, our team will share updates with you via email when feature enhancements or updates are made. Additionally, GoDirect Flight Bag Pro users will receive updates via Apple TestFlight, which is the distribution method for testing iOS apps prior to release. 

As a power user of Honeywell GoDirect Flight Services products, your feedback and input during this evaluation is invaluable to help our team deliver the best solution to meet your business and operational needs. Should you encounter any issues along the way, please be sure to submit your feedback and observations to us so we can review and investigate.

Click the button below for more information about participating in the beta period and to start testing! 
 




HOW TO PREPARE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/BetaTestEmail_Directions_PDF9_18_2018.pdf]]&gt;




 Thank you for your participation,  
 
 The GoDirect Flight Services Team
Questions &amp; Support  
 
 Please contact us with questions or support at anytime, should you encounter any problems during the beta period.
  
 Email: FlightServices@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FlightServices@Honeywell.com]]&gt; 
 US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330 
 International: +1 (602) 365-7020 



If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/v0000ZXA0GqXQ0EvI020000]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
