<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_Americas_RDR-7000_Certification_Email.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>BREAKING: The RDR-7000 Weather radar is now certified</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}},

 Honeywell is excited to announce the IntuVue RDR-7000 Weather Radar System is now certified for the Falcon 900EX, Citation X and Global Express platforms!

 The RDR-7000 provides business aviation and helicopter pilots the clear and timely information they need to make safer, faster and more informed decisions before flying in bad weather and challenging environments. 

 Key Advantages:


 Next generation
 A fully automated, higher resolution weather radar system with airborne ground/sea mapping system.


 Reliable and efficient

Solid-state transmitters utilizing pulse compression provide reduced weight and power consumption, advanced coherent processing, and increased reliability over magnetron-based transmitters.


 Compact and easy to install
Best-in-class technology from our RDR-4000 IntuVue radar systems, integrated into a small, lightweight package.


 Available software upgrades
Advanced features can be added at any time, including turbulence detection, advanced mapping, target detection and additional hazard features (lightning and hail detection), and forward looking (predictive) windshear.

 Please do not hesitate to reach out if you would like to learn more information or schedule a meeting with an MSP Sales Manager.

For more information on the RDR-7000, visit our website &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/weather-radar/rdr-7000?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_americas_rdr-7000&amp;utm_content=certification]]&gt;.
LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/weather-radar/rdr-7000?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_americas_rdr-7000&amp;utm_content=certification]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
