<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202011_BK_Customer_Newsletter_Nov_MC.Internal Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Jingle all the way to a new autopilot. Upgrade your KFC 150 or KFC 200</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                            
   Newsletter - November 2020
BREAKING NEWS

 

AeroCruze 230 (KFC 230) &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/about-us/news/2020/11/bendixking-expands-aerocruze-230-certification-list]]&gt; autopilot is now certified for over 35 different aircraft!  
Check the list of supported aircraft to see if your aircraft is eligible for 
the upgrade or contact your area sales manager/local dealer &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/buy/sales-team]]&gt; for more details.

TEN REASONS YOU SHOULD UPGRADE YOUR KFC 150 &amp; KFC 200 



	- AeroCruze 230 (KFC 230) &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ai/autopilots-and-indicators/aerocruze-230?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_bendixking_aerocruze230]]&gt; is the first touchscreen-controlled autopilot
	- Designed primarily for KFC 150 and KFC 200 customers
	- Automatic Wings Level (LVL) mode corrects unusual attitudes and stabilizes the aircraft with one 
touch
	- Packed with features: Fully coupled VOR/Loc/ILS, GPSS roll steering, altitude pre-select, flight director output
	- Form-fit replacement for KFC 150 and KFC 
200
	- Use existing servos, servo mounts and 
wiring*
	- Save thousands of dollars on 
installation
	- Less 
downtime
	- Two-year warranty on existing 
servos* 
	- Capable of being a full three-axis autopilot with the addition 
of a yaw damper


          *once verified by approved dealer

THE MORE YOU KNOWWe recently provided live product demos during the MMOPA virtual convention. (MMOPA members fly PA46 derivative - Malibu, Mirage, Meridian, M-Class, JetPROP and Matrix aircraft.)
 
Check out this video AeroCruze 230 DETAILS_MMOPA &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/VJjPPvkqzKLWvgcxz3syTi]]&gt;. 
Doug Hayden, Regional Sales Manager, reviews features of the KFC 230. Even if you aren’t an MMOPA member, you might find details that help you make the decsion to upgrade.

WHAT OTHERS ARE SAYINGRick Tutt, pilot and owner of RJ Tutt Aviation, 
recently replaced the KFC 150 in his Piper with the AerocCruze 230 (KFC 230) and loves it. Read Rick’s review here &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/about-us/customer-success-stories/2020/09/touchscreen-autopilot-makes-flying-easier]]&gt; 

AN EARLY HOLIDAY GIFTRodrigo Delgado, who lives in Guatemala City, found a love for flying and airplanes as a child, where he would quickly draw any airplane or helicopter 
he saw. Radio-controlled airplanes gave him a good overview of aviation, and Rodrigo enjoyed his first flight hour in June 1985.  After that, he was hooked on flying and has since owned several Cessna aircraft - his current aircraft is a Cessna C210R.
 
   


SHOWS &amp; EVENTS 
VBACE 2020 December 2-3 
It’s no surprise that NBAA (National Business 
Aviation Association) is going virtual with &quot;VBACE 2020&quot; and we’re excited to be participating with Honeywell. For all the business jet owners and operators out there, be sure to visit Honeywell’s virtual 3D exhibit where you’ll find products, services and solutions to help business jet owners and operators stay connected and fly safer, smarter and more efficiently. Register for VBACE here &lt;[[https://nbaa.org/professional-development/on-demand-education/nbaa-go/2020-vbace/register-to-attend-vbace/]]&gt;.

WE&apos;RE HERE
Have a question? Want to schedule a demo? Need support? We’re here for you.

Locate your sales manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/buy/sales-team]]&gt;
 Locate a dealer &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/buy/locate-dealer]]&gt;
Customer and Product Support &lt;[[mailto:sales@bendixking.com]]&gt;

THANKFUL
From all of us at Team BendixKing, we want to wish all our customers, pilots, families and friends a safe, healthy and wonderful holiday season. Even through this tumultuous year, we can find so much to celebrate and to be thankful for – and we are thankful for you. Stay well and we wish you clear skies ahead!



Rodrigo recently modernized his cockpit with BendixKing avionics and now experiences a new level of flying. Here’s a snapshot of how Rodrigo, through the authorized BendixKing dealer in Guatemala, chose to update his cockpit:

Most importantly, Rodrigo wanted a new high resolution, touchscreen PFD/MFD and the award-winning AeroVue Touch display &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ifd/integrated-flight-decks/aerovue-touch]]&gt; 
was an easy choice. 

You’ll see in the photos that he also chose an AeroNav &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/nc/navigation-and-communication/aeronav]]&gt; stack so he now has increased safety, enhanced navigation and communication. 

To comply with mandates, Rodrigo also installed the KT 74 ADS-B Out transponder &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/nc/navigation-and-communication/kt-74]]&gt;.



The AeroPanel audio panel &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/audio/audio-panels-accessories/aeropanel]]&gt; let him enjoy high quality audio inside the cabin.

Rodrigo rounded out his upgrade and best utilized panel space by replacing old engine gauges with the AeroPoint 200 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/ifd/integrated-flight-decks/aeropoint]]&gt; high-resolution engine monitor.



As you can see, BendixKing open 
architecture let him choose options he liked for his cockpit. Thank you, Rodrigo, for choosing to fly with BendixKing. 

If you’d like to be considered for a future story, please reach out to your dealer or sales manager!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
