<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2015-Helitech VR Launch-EMEAI-Email.2015-EMEAI-CommHeloVRPromo-Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Come Fly with Us at Helitech</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Lights! Camera! Action!
Dear Customer,
Discover the Possibilities of Flight. Made Easy @ EBACE 2015
We invite you to join us during EBACE 2015, taking place from May 19th  - 21st at the Palexpo Convention Centre in Geneva. Take the opportunity to meet with our leadership and regional team to discover how our technologies enable the business aviation industry to realise the Possibilities of Flight.
Our booth, which is located on stand number WO89 will showcase a number of our innovative products including:


 - Ovation SelectTM – our high definition cabin management system which delivers high flying productivity and entertainment




 - Primus Elite – the latest in enhanced functionality for the ultimate ‘glass’ cockpit, delivering LCD resolution screens for enhanced situational awareness and safety




 -  Satcom – Honeywell has a suite of satcom solutions including our new JetWave (ka band) hardware to ensure that business doesn’t stop after take off




 - Virtual Reality Experience – Immerse yourself in a world of productivity, safety and connectivity with our Virtual Reality Experience. Showcasing Honeywell’s suite of RMU’s for both cockpit and cabin


In addition, our team will be on hand to answer any questions you might have regarding our aftermarket solutions include Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), Maintenance Services Plans (MSP) for engines and APU’s. 
To ensure that the relevant Honeywell representative is available to answer your queries, please use the EBACE Meeting Request Form &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/2015-EMEAI-EBACE15-Event_ScheduleMeeting.html&gt;.
We look forward to welcoming you to EBACE 2015.

  Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
                      
          
    
                 
               
                                                                                                
                            
             
          
                                                                                          
Book a meeting &gt; &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/2015-EMEAI-EBACE15-Event_ScheduleMeeting.html&gt;
  Normal 0    
 false false false  EN-US X-NONE 
X-NONE          
    MicrosoftInternetExplorer4
&lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/2015-EMEAI-EBACE15-Event_ScheduleMeeting.html&gt;
Book a meeting

Please use the EBACE Meeting Request Form by clicking the button above.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
