<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201807_Global_Email_OperationJetSet_RevealEmail_TM.201807_Global_Email_Operation</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Insider Reveal - #OperationJetSet - Technology You’ve Waited For - Contest Winners Announced</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/operationjetset#anchor]]&gt;
THE MOMENT YOU’VE WAITED FOR....IT&apos;S HERE!

For over a decade, the aviation industry has relied on the same flight planning technology and Honeywell is launching a new 
generation flight planning engine that will change the way you fly forever!

By investing in and innovating a new proprietary flight planning engine, we are advancing our GoDirect™ Flight Planning service with a new website and mobile app that helps schedulers and dispatchers create, compute and file flight plans faster and more accurate than services available now.




What this means for you

Our new engine technology will help you create, compute and file personalized flight plans faster, easier and more accurate than ever before:

• Significant time savings filing a flight plan with more direct routes
• Cost savings with plans that more accurately track fuel consumption
• Increased efficiency with higher cleared as filed rates with air traffic control




Don’t get stuck with decade-old technology, get a sneak peek of the latest in flight planning technology to be one of the first to use this new service.






I WANT NEW TECHNOLOGY &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/OperationJetSet_August_Alert.html]]&gt;




Check out our Twitter &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt; handle on July 5th to see the winners of our #OperationJetSet contest.

Thank you for your participation in the reveal and contest. If you have any questions please contact flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto: flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;.  

Honeywell GoDirect Team

If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/Ldj2XI00t0wj0QiBh0q0G0Z]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
