<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201712_JetWaveCableTechSupport_LG.201712_JetWaveCableTechSupport_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Tech Tips - Troubleshoot JetWave Transmit Cable Calibration Process</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer, 
If you have experienced a transmit (TX) cable calibration error with JetWave™, we have a solution. 
 
The TX cable calibration test is initiated upon system power-up, but if it does not complete properly, the system will show a cable calibration error until it is manually initiated and completed. Below are the steps to manually initiate the TX cable calibration:


	- After system power-up, wait 10 minutes. The auto test that starts with the system power-up (when there is no TX cable calibration data) could fail around 30%. So, waiting 10 minutes to enter the page means the first test would have failed by this time. 
	- Enter the calibrate TX cable page, then choose “Initiate”. You will likely see the error message &quot;Cable Calibration Error Not Enough Modem Power During Ramping, BUC Not&quot;. 
	- 
Wait 25 minutes. This lets the TX cable calibration test complete. The GUI status may not accurately represent the actual status. It has been reported to stick at 1% or even exit the cable calibration test page even though the calibration test is still running. 

	- 
Reset AES. Resetting the system is required once the calibration is completed. 

	- Upon reboot, check to see if “test mode” is gone. This confirms if the calibration has been completed. If the calibration data resides in the system, then you won’t see the system attempting the automatic calibration at power-up.  


Please login to the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; Portal for this supporting document - JetWave System Description and Installation Manual, D201401000049 &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/support/techpubsdeeplink?urlSearchId=DF7AD677-015F-4000-E000-DB590AC5408D]]&gt;. 
 
We also have helpful videos for an easy JetWave software load. Whether it&apos;s new software or upgrading to the latest version, these videos explain the steps to make your experience as easy as possible. These videos were published for BLv4 software but the process is the same for future software revisions. And, don’t worry if the video images don’t match the current MyAerospace view – the user interface is updated but the link names and processes remain the same.


	- 
JetWave BLv4 software load tips (1 of 2) &lt;[[https://youtu.be/iWyOfwvbcME]]&gt; 

	- 
JetWave BLv4 software load tips (2 of 2) &lt;[[https://youtu.be/bFPwstDws2Y]]&gt; 



Please refer to MyAerospace for the latest software and the service bulletin.


	- JetWave software &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/webforms?application=EMS]]&gt;
	- Software release BLv5 service bulletin &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/support/techpubsdeeplink?urlSearchId=1344E685-0160-4000-E000-EEAE0AC5408D]]&gt;


Need other technical support? Visit our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u7Z0000I0q0G0902600QXk0]]&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical publications, or to submit questions to our technical support engineering team.
 

Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
