<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201707_Spanish_Email_Followup_Rafael.201707_Spanish_Email_Followup_Rafael</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>CUSTOMER CONNECT
Dear Customer: 
 
I’m your Honeywell Customer Support Manager and your point of escalation if you need additional customer support. Please reach me at: 
 
 
 Mark Duckworth 
 
 
 Direct: 602-794-8224 
 Mobile: 602-284-8065 
 Email: Mark.Duckworth@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Mark.Duckworth@Honeywell.com]]&gt; 
 
I want wanted to share some important resources to help you get the most out of our support services.
Technical Support 
 
Our technical support global network of experts is available 24x7.
 • International: +1-602-365-6500 
 • U.S./Canada: 1-855-808-6500
 • aerotechsupport@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:aerotechsupport@honeywell.com]]&gt;
Aircraft-On-Ground Support 
 
Our world class aircraft-on-ground (AOG) team helps customers 24x7 every day 365 days a year. 
 • International: +1-602-365-3099 (option #4) 
 • U.S./Canada: 1-800-601-3099 (also option #4) 
 • AOG@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AOG@honeywell.com]]&gt; - Please include: your tail number, your next scheduled flight and the reason for the AOG. 
Operator Conferences 
 
Meet face-to-face with Honeywell representatives and fellow business aviation customers. Each conference features sessions on maintenance, operations, service, and support. Access the full schedule here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2017/march/2017-operator-conference]]&gt;.
Mobile Access Anytime You Need  
 
 

 
 The MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; Portal makes it easier to place and manage orders, arrange for repairs and access your Honeywell account. Our new search feature will help you find what you are looking for anywhere on the site quickly and easily.   
 
 
 Mobile support is also available through free apps like the Pilot Gateway &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/honeywell-pilot-gateway]]&gt; and Direct Access &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt; tools.
    LEARN MORE      &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/customer-and-product-support-made-simple-and-easy]]&gt;
It’s also    survey    season  and your participation matters. If you receive Professional Pilot surveys, please take a moment to provide your feedback. 
 
 
 
 
 
 I will stay in touch to keep you informed about your Honeywell resources. In the meantime, if you have any questions please contact me.  
 
 
 
 
  Mark Duckworth 
   Customer Support Manager, C&amp;PS Commercial Aviation   Direct: 602-794-8224 
Mobile: 602-284-8065 
Email : Mark.Duckworth@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Mark.Duckworth@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
