<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201902_N. America_UAV_Electric Utilities_JRD.201902_N. America_UAV_Electric Util</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Work With a UAV Team That Inspected More than 150 Miles of Power Lines in Only Five Days</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Hi {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}},

Did you know that Honeywell’s drone inspection and data analytics &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/uav]]&gt; team recently inspected more than 150 miles of power line inspections in less than five days?

Not only were we able to complete the 150 miles 
of inspection in record time, but of the nearly 170,000 images generated, the customer was left with less than 100 asset images which required review based on our proprietary analytics models. 

Saving our customer time during inspection meant reallocating labor to other high-priority projects, like fiber optic installations. 

Saving the customer time after inspection meant maintenance supervisors had insights into which assets required monitoring in a fast, easy way providing greater operational efficiency. 

“We’re learning what drones can do every day. The Honeywell people are really smart, and it’s fun to challenge them with new ideas and have them come back to us and say they can do it. We look forward to a long future with the Honeywell UAV program.&quot; - Clinton Foster, Right-of-Way Coordinator, Ozarks Electric Cooperative.

Read the full story here. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2018/october/honeywell-uav-team-inspects-150-miles-of-power-lines-for-ozarks-electric-cooperative-in-just-days]]&gt;

Partner with Honeywell for your drone inspection and data analytics needs. For more information or to speak to one of our regional technical managers, please contact us below.




CONTACT US &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Electric_Utilities_UAV.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_uav_gh]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
