<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Americas_Email_HOC_Survey_mih.201906_Americas_Reminder_ATRHOC_Survey_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Follow-up for Brazil Airline Operators Conference</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Your feedback is important!
AIRLINE OPERATORS CONFERENCE 
IN BRAZIL
Dear customer,

Last week you received an email from Honeywell inviting you to an Airlines Operators Conference the week of August 5th at the Grand Opening of our new Service Center in São José dos Campos/SP, Brazil. As part of that email we have linked a survey that will help us determine the topics to discuss with our Field Service Engineers and Customer Support Managers. Please take this survey at your earliest convenience so we can plan a meaningful conference. Thank you for your input on this event as your feedback matters to us.





COMPLETE SURVEY &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/FTQ953B]]&gt;





Prezado cliente,

Na semana passada, você recebeu um e-mail da Honeywell o convidando para uma Conferência de Operadores de Linhas Aéreas que será realizada na semana de 5 de agosto durante a inauguração do nosso novo Centro de Serviços em São José dos Campos/SP, Brasil. 
 Como parte desse email, vinculamos uma pesquisa que nos ajudará a determinar os tópicos a serem discutidos com nossos engenheiros de serviço de campo e gerentes de suporte ao cliente. Por favor, responda a esta pesquisa o mais breve possível para que possamos planejar uma conferência relevante. Agradecemos sua contribuição neste evento, pois seu feedback é muito importante para nós.





COMPLETAR A PESQUISA &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/H2TRS2C]]&gt;




Estimado cliente,

La semana pasada, usted recibió un correo electrónico de Honeywell invitándolo a una Conferencia de Operadores de Líneas Aéreas que se realizará en la semana del 5 de agosto durante la inauguración de nuestro nuevo Centro de Servicios en São José dos Campos / SP, Brasil.
 Como parte de este correo electrónico, vinculamos una encuesta que nos ayudará a determinar los temas que serán discutidos con nuestros ingenieros de servicio de campo y los gerentes de soporte al cliente. 
 Por favor, responda a esta encuesta a la brevedad para que podamos planificar una conferencia relevante. Agradecemos su contribución en este evento, pues su retroalimentación es muy importante para nosotros.






COMPLETAR LA ENCUESTA &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/PSN35NP]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
