<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Amer_HCE_Forge_Falcon-Connect-Portal-Launch_Email_Operational.202008_Falc</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Access the new FalconConnect Portal – Your New Platform Has Landed</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=customer}},

 We are delighted to introduce you to your new look FalconConnect Portal.

 The FalconConnect portal powered by Honeywell Forge is a new approach to providing you with a comprehensive platform of connected software solutions, services and applications. This exciting new platform makes it easier than ever for you to access the Honeywell offerings you value and use the enormous power of connected software to turn raw data into actionable information.

 What Does It Do?
 The FalconConnect portal enables you to use connected software to bring together assets, processes and people to improve operational performance 
and achieve your most important operational objectives.

 What is Included?
 Included are all the FalconConnect offerings. This includes our flight planning, flight database and cabin connectivity software, services and applications. We’ll continue to add new features in the months ahead. 

 How Does It Work?
 The FalconConnect portal is powerful, flexible and easy to use. Whether you’re operating one business aircraft or a whole fleet, you can use the intuitive dashboard to manage nearly every aspect of your business aviation operation. 

 Ready to Gain Access? 
Click the button below or type in falconconnect.honeywellforge.com to get started today. There is also a link inside your cabin, flight planning and navigational database portals that link to this dashboard.
GAIN ACCESS &lt;[[https://falconconnect.honeywell.com]]&gt;
If you have questions our team is standing by to help. Contact one of our support staff here:

 FalconConnect Customer Support 
 Phone: +1-602-365-6425 (Worldwide) or +1-833-227-3994 (Toll Free)
 Email: FalconConnect@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FalconConnect@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
