<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>September 2017 Edition.Updated September 2017 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - September 2017 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
September 2017
FLIGHT BAG PRO APP NOW AVAILABLE
Flight Bag Pro is a premier global flight planning and electronic flight bag iPad app. Using this app, flight crews can create and file flight plans, calculate and compare aircraft cruise modes for optimal performance, access up-to-the-minute weather updates and airspace information, view airport approach plates, and more! 





  LEARN MORE       &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/godirect-flight-bag-pro]]&gt;
NBAA 2017 - Honeywell showcasing its newest services and products

Visit Honeywell at Booth N5100 to see our newest connectivity and services hardware and apps, and cockpit technologies. We&apos;ll be showcasing our nose-to-tail Connected Aircraft offerings, and offering special M&amp;O sessions on Cabin Connectivity and GoDirect Services... Learn more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2017/october/see-you-at-nbaa-2017]]&gt;
DU-875 LCD display unit upgrade options now available
Honeywell is offering multiple affordable options to operators of Primus 1000 / 2000 platforms who are considering whether to replace or support DU-870 displays with new DU-875 LCD displays... Learn more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Affordable%20DU-875 LCD Display Upgrade Options.pdf]]&gt;
MyAerospace Portal makes it easy to connect with Honeywell

Honeywell’s MyAerospace web portal keeps getting better. We’ve rebuilt the site from the inside-out using input from Honeywell customers... Learn more. &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
