<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_HoneywellForge_BGA_MSP-Propulsion-Reporting-Datalink_Email.Internal send</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Propulsion Reporting: Available for MSP Customers in Honeywell Forge</subject>
    <textOnly>INTRODUCING PROPULSION REPORTING
The new feature inside Honeywell Forge that provides insight into the total engine time for any flight. This feature is available for Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) customers who sign up for datalink. Get more insights on your engine run time with this new service function. 

 Sign up for Honeywell Datalink today, and get 3 months free of service. Contact our team &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga&amp;utm_content=propulsion]]&gt; to learn more. 

 Benefits of Propulsion Reporting:



	- How does propulsion reporting work?
Honeywell uses an algorithm to compute start and shutdown time of the engine pulling from multiple data sources.
	- How long of history does propulsion reporting track?
We keep a 6-month history beginning at the activation of the tile. Time will be reported by leg, tail, and accumulated by month.
	- Is the reporting just aircraft engines?
The reporting just includes engines at this time. We are planning to incorporate Honeywell APUs in the future.
	- Can I change any of the data reported?
Users will be allowed to edit computed propulsion time.
	- Any other future integrations planned?
Yes! Our roadmap includes links to the Maintenance Service Plan (MSP), along with maintenance tracking.


Have questions on propulsion data? Getting started is easy. Contact our team &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga&amp;utm_content=propulsion]]&gt; to set up a new datalink subscription and ask us about our 2021 promotion for new customers. From there we will integrate your MSP plan into Honeywell Forge.
REQUEST NOW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga&amp;utm_content=propulsion]]&gt;
Maggie Deane
 Honeywell Forge – Inside Sales
Sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;
 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
