<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Amer_HCE_Forge_Jet-ConneX-Overage-Communication-Cabin-Connectivity_Email.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Tools to Help Control Upcoming Overage Charges</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 

 We wanted to remind you that Inmarsat will soon begin implementing monthly overage charges to all airtime service accounts that exceed their allocated data usage. This will affect all Honeywell Forge Jet Connex subscriptions. We understand policy changes like this are not ideal, so our team has developed a wide range of data management tools that will help you manage your aircraft data use to help reduce overage costs. 

 Here are some of the tools the Honeywell Forge team has provided: 



	- For the first time, you will have the option to extend the use of our popular video bandwidth control tools to all data types. You will be able to allocate bandwidth according to data type as well as manage the allowable data volume.
	- For customers who prefer a Honeywell-managed plan vs self-service option, we are preparing hassle-free options that optimize passenger experience while minimizing overage risk.


Inmarsat has also recently implemented some changes to help soften any potential impact and allow for better control of your monthly budget such as: 



	- Increasing the data allowance for JX-2 and above. Please see the current and updated allowances here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/HW_DataAllowancesChart_JetConnex_82020.PNG]]&gt;.
	- A new waiver on any accrued in-month overage charges when the customer upgrades to a higher plan. This allows users to re-size to the right level that matches your need without the risk of excessive bills.


If you would like to discuss the upcoming overage changes or solutions for your flight department, please contact your Honeywell Forge representative or the number below. We thank you for your business and look forward to continuing to serve you. 

 Thank you, 

 The Honeywell Forge Team 

 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 
sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
