<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201908_Americas_Pentastar_Jetwave Nurture_kcr.201908_Americas_Pentastar_JetWaveN</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Say Goodbye to Buffering, Dropped Calls and Wi-Fi Dead Zones!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}}, 

 At Pentastar Aviation, we believe accessibility should have no bounds. If you’ve been disappointed with the Wi-Fi on your business jet, it&apos;s time to make a change. Honeywell’s JetWave™, powered by Inmarsat’s Jet ConneX service, provides high-speed Wi-Fi with significantly fewer signal “drops.” With the seamless, rapid handover between satellites you can now enjoy connectivity in the air similar to what you experience at home.  The JetWave SATCOM solution:


	-  Provides the fastest available connection speeds for business aviation&gt;
	-  Offers service plans to fit any capacity and budget, including a new Jet ConneX Pay-As-You-Go Plan
	-  Delivers guaranteed data rate speeds


Honeywell’s suite of connectivity services and solutions can transform your aircraft cabin into an office, home theater, music studio – whatever you want. Maintain productivity, stay in touch with family, stream live TV, follow your favorite teams, kick back and watch a movie, video chat and more from takeoff to touchdown. 

 To learn more or schedule an installation, contact Pentastar Aviation, a Honeywell Authorized Avionics Dealer, by clicking below.
I WANT TO LEARN MORE ABOUT JETWAVE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/upgrade-your-in-flight-wi-fi-experience-with-jetwave?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_pentastar_jw]]&gt;
© {{my.year}} Honeywell International Inc.    This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=NA}}. If you don&apos;t want to receive these emails from Honeywell in the future, you can edit your profile &lt;[[]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://explore.honeywell.com/Unsubscribepage.html]]&gt;. Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement/ps-german]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://www.honeywellsafety.com/DE/Contacts.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
