<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201706_APAC_Email_APACHQ_July_ENG_mih.201706_APAC_Email_APACHQ_July_ENG_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell International Sarl Transition to Honeywell International Bhd Sdn</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

July 5, 2017


Dear Customer, 



Thank you for the support you have extended to us during the past few months while we are transitioning our Distribution centers from Hemel Hempstead, England to Shah Alam Malaysia. Our Asia Regional Distribution Center is now up and running and will start processing your spares orders starting on the 10th of July.

We also have moved to our brand new headquarters office, Honeywell International Sdn Bhd, Suite 25-1, Level 25, UOA Corp Tower B, Avenue 10, The Vertical, Bangsar South City, 59200, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.

We sincerely value your cooperation during this period.

In Honeywell, we are constantly seeking to improve our business processes and operations to better serve and support our customers, and a key element of this is the creation of Honeywell International Sdn Bhd. Honeywell International Sdn Bhd will simplify and enhance the ways in which you conduct business with us, this is our strategy to create an integrated business platform by creating a more efficient and effective procurement experience.

Therefore, the business activities and existing agreements currently linked with the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd facilities (Avionics R&amp;O Site at Loyang, Singapore and APU/Mechanical site at Gul Circle, Singapore) under the Honeywell International SARL will be transitioned to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd. This transition is currently targeted for Q4 2017.

To make this transition seamless, please ensure that the following steps are completed as soon as possible:





	- Update your Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to reflect supplier as Honeywell International Sdn Bhd.



The new supplier address for Honeywell Singapore Loyang and Gul Circle procurement and accounting transactions is:



Company Name: Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
Address: Suite 25-1, Level 25, The Vertical, Avenue 10, Bangsar South City, UOA Corporate Tower, Lobby B, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi
City: Kuala Lumpur
Postal Code: 59200
Country: Malaysia






	- The amended “Ship To” addresses for the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Avionics R&amp;O and Honeywell Aerospace Singapore APU and Mechanical R&amp;O sites remain unchanged:



For Singapore Loyang Site: 
Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
2 Loyang Crescent, Singapore 508976


For Singapore Gul Circle Site: Honeywell International Sdn 
BhdC/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,161 Gul Circle, Singapore 629619


For Contract Customers Only – Honeywell will be sending you a Novation Agreement or Amendment assigning existing contractual rights and obligations from Honeywell International Sarl to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd. We request your prompt attention to execute such Novation Agreement or Amendment prior to September 8, 2017. If you have any questions about the Novation Agreement or Amendment, please feel free to contact your Honeywell Customer Business Director or Contract Manager.

As we go through this transition, our Customer Support Manager or Customer Business Director will be working closely with your procurement organization and program teams to ensure that each step of the process is well communicated and effectively implemented.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us through your regular Honeywell Aerospace representative.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
