<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Global_HCE_Email_Foreflight-Dispatch-and-Forge-Free-Trial.Free Trial Emai</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>90-Days Free - ForeFlight Dispatch with Honeywell Forge</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},

If you haven’t already heard, ForeFlight Dispatch, an innovative new flight planning solution, is available inside Honeywell Forge. This integration supports our mission to bring the industry’s best to your Honeywell Forge dashboard. We are thrilled to provide this premier flight planning solution.

What is ForeFlight Dispatch?
ForeFlight Dispatch &lt;[[https://foreflight.com/products/dispatch/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; is a powerful flight planning software that delivers reliable, easy flight planning designed for business jets. By incorporating ForeFlight Dispatch with Honeywell Forge, your flight department will benefit from greater control over your fleet operations with a singular solution for all their planning, tracking, datalink, and operational needs. Contact us to try ForeFlight Dispatch with Honeywell Forge free for 90-days. Please note this option needs to be enabled and isn’t integrated automatically.

Support Packages – Available Now
 We are also excited to introduce new support packages that pair with our integrated flight planning options. Choose the specific support you want for your flight department, budget and mission profile. To view our support packages, click &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; her &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;e &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;.

Honeywell Forge Datalink + ForeFlight Dispatch – a Winning Combination  
 Already a Honeywell Forge datalink customer? Did you know, when you choose to integrate ForeFlight Dispatch you can also take advantage of flight plan uplinks with datalink? Seamlessly upload your flight plans using this option. Not a datalink customer? Learn more here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2020/12/honeywell-forge-pbcs-monitoring-tool?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; about the benefits of leveraging Honeywell Forge for datalink – now with PBCS 
notifications. Talk with our team to learn how to get this service enabled today.

Need Help or Have Questions? Our team is here to help. 
 Please contact your Honeywell sales representative or call: 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 or email sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;





GET STARTED &lt;[[https://bga.honeywellforge.com/ff?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
