<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.Executive Contact Plan 04.07.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You’re a Partner! Welcome to the Executive Contact Plan</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}:
If a disgruntled customer said that, what would we as a company do? We’d do whatever it took to get to the core of the problem, and we’d go to any reasonable length to correct it. In the process, we’d work to turn that naysayer into a loyal Honeywell customer for life.
Unfortunately, that customer is out there - and he has lots of unhappy company. It seems every time we turn around we hear some version of those words, and they’re taking a toll. They’re costing us business and money. They’re stealing our pride.

But with your help and a program called the Executive Contact Plan, 
 all that is going to change. Starting now.








You have the power to make heroes of us all.
The idea driving the Honeywell Executive Contact Plan (ECP) is to show people what we’re truly made of. It’s a rare chance to rebuild relationships that – for whatever reason – have soured. It’s also an opportunity to forge new, ongoing personal relationships based on mutual trust and respect.
To accomplish that, you and fellow AT&amp;R leaders will be assigned at least one friend. That term, “friend,” has been carefully chosen as we set about working the ECP. Because as you’re making a new friend or getting to know an old one better, you’ll be changing the conversation from “we care about your business,” to “I care about you.”








That’s not something that will be accomplished with one phone call or face-to-face.
Rather, it must become an ongoing process in which you’ll help us uncover and understand what’s important to your friend.
True, what’s on their mind might involve a problem with Honeywell - in which case you’ll have our full support as you work to make things right. But keep in mind the challenges, opportunities, frustrations, and successes of your friend involve far more than just Honeywell service. It’s business. But its effect is highly personal. 







• Work to learn what’s keeping him/her awake at night. 
• Did our last contract make him look bad because he’s measured on the number 
• of exclusions per contract? 
• What’s his idea of a job well done?           • Does she plan to retire next year? 

To launch the first phase of the Executive Contact Plan, 
 we’re focusing laser-like on five individuals at each of 30 airlines.

Reaching out through phone calls, birthday cards, sharing of interesting articles, monthly emails, face-to-face interactions and other tools listed below -- chosen to help you get to know your friend and accomplish your objectives.
These activities and their associated due dates will be added to your SFDC profile. During MOR, we’ll use SFDC to review the progress of each relationship.

We welcome you to the ECP team. We’re proud to have you representing the people of Honeywell during this critical time of history. Together, we’re going to make sure our customers become our friends. And that those friendships last a lifetime.
- Customer Experience (CX) Team
 

 

Click here  &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/honeywell3/images/SFDC Activities Training Instructions.pdf&gt;for SFDC Activities Training Instructions</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
