<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_BK_Customer_Newsletter_Mar_MC.202003_BK_Customer_Newsletter_Mar_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AeroWave In-flight Connectivity, New AeroPanel, Show Schedule and More</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Newsletter Vol III - March 
2020

SHOWS AND EVENTS ATTENDANCE UPDATE
 To ensure the safety of our people during the coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak, BendixKing has decided to withdraw from the AEA 
show in Nashville. This decision was made from an abundance of caution based upon prioritizing the health of everyone involved. 

 AEA is an important event for us, you and the industry. We remain dedicated to keeping you informed with alternative methods to share product announcements, details and training planned for the show.

 Please contact your BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; with any questions.


 

AEROWAVE 100 OFFERS AFFORDABLE UNLIMITED CONNECTIVITY
AeroWave 100 is an affordable option for unlimited text, voice and browsing for $39.99/hour. This plan offers the convenience of staying in touch on all your devices from takeoff to touchdown.

 To discuss your data requirements and plan details, contact your local Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;.

 Want more information about connectivity and AeroWave? Download our paper 
“The State of Connectivity in General Aviation”. State Of Connectivity In GA&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Aerowave-100.html]]&gt;




INTRODUCING AEROPANEL 
The technologically advanced, cost-effective, AeroPanel 100 is a feature-rich audio panel system that is perfect for the pilot, the crew and the passengers – each getting their own audio streams when and where needed! 

 AeroPanel 100 
includes the ability to pair more than one Bluetooth device at a time, such as a smart phones or video cameras through three types of music distribution modes. Additionally, the AeroPanel 100 can record up to 40 seconds from a selected input, making it easy to play back radio calls and important messages. Find Out More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropanel]]&gt;

 
   
WEBINARS &amp; TRAINING 
On-demand webinar: Who’s tracking your flights and how to 
protect your privacy? Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and Roger Dykmann from BendixKing discussed this and more in “Privacy in the Age of ADS-B”. 
View It Here &gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/xsDShFJY2Z3WQnUTwE9qZU]]&gt;
Acces Code 
902384

March 26, 7pm EST Webinar: “Automation and the Flight Envelope.” SocialFlight’s Jeff Simon and BendixKing’s Andrew Barker and Mariellen Couppee explore the levels automation and aligning with the phases of flight. 
Register&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/3477603951655777547]]&gt;

SHOWS &amp; EVENTS

AEA Convention &lt;[[http://aea.net/convention/2020/]]&gt;
 Mar 24-27, 2020
 Nashville, TN
SHOW POSTPONED
 
Sun ‘n Fun Aerospace Expo &lt;[[https://www.flysnf.org/]]&gt;
 Mar 31 – Apr 5, 2020
 Hangar A #34-36
 Lakeland, FL
SHOW POSTPONED
 
AERO Friedrichshafen &lt;[[https://www.aero-expo.com/aero-en/]]&gt;
 Apr 1-5, 2020
 Friedrichshafen, Germany
 SHOW POSTPONED

CONTACTS
Find Your Sales Rep &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTURZME16ZzFNMlZsTVRkbCIsInQiOiJ1S0szcEJxWXdZWmYyU1VKZ2VFTFkzMWdSS1VcL3Zhb1lEbkYyUXVpQnB3ZlkrNnNLSlZQRGtibmk5aWdXeDIxaFNxeE42aCtoQkU1M21KQnl2UUJYakE9PSJ9]]&gt;
Find A Dealer or Repair Partner &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/Dealer-Directory/?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTURZME16ZzFNMlZsTVRkbCIsInQiOiJ1S0szcEJxWXdZWmYyU1VKZ2VFTFkzMWdSS1VcL3Zhb1lEbkYyUXVpQnB3ZlkrNnNLSlZQRGtibmk5aWdXeDIxaFNxeE42aCtoQkU1M21KQnl2UUJYakE9PSJ9]]&gt;
More Contact Info &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTURZME16ZzFNMlZsTVRkbCIsInQiOiJ1S0szcEJxWXdZWmYyU1VKZ2VFTFkzMWdSS1VcL3Zhb1lEbkYyUXVpQnB3ZlkrNnNLSlZQRGtibmk5aWdXeDIxaFNxeE42aCtoQkU1M21KQnl2UUJYakE9PSJ9]]&gt;





AERONAV GPS 
NAVIGATORS 
The AeroNav &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigators]]&gt; series offers a full-featured touchscreen GPS/FMS/NAV/COM suite that is designed as a slide-in replacement for the GNS 430 and GNS 530 legacy navigators. AeroNav features a predictive next-waypoint entry based upon its proximity to your current location or the previous waypoint in your flight plan, reducing data entry by as much as 75%. And with the AeroNav tablet app, you can extend the navigation screens on your personal device. AeroNav also includes a wireless keyboard to make data entry flexible and within easy reach, and features built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi. Product Details Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigation]]&gt; 






AEROCRUZE 100 AND 
XCRUZE 100/110 AUTOPILOTS 
If you’re looking for an affordable autopilot for your aircraft, we have the perfect option for you. The AeroCruze 100 is STC’d for Cessna 172, 175, 177, 180, 182, 185 and Piper PA 28 and PA 32, with the choice of three standard-size form factors to fit your panel with minimal panel-revision and expense.

 For experimental aircraft, the xCruze 100 and 110 offer the same form factor choices and feature set, and interfaces with the most popular experimental EFIS displays. The compact xCruze 110 autopilot contains a PFD and displays attitude, airspeed, altitude, vertical speed, slip/skid, bank angle, turn rate and track-slaved directional gyro. Find Out More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xcruze-100]]&gt; 






AEROCORDER 100 FLIGHT DATA / COCKPIT VOICE RECORDER 
AeroCorder 100 offers a rugged enclosure, small size, lower weight, and less power consumption than traditional FDRs in a modular and flexible architecture. The additional acquisition module converts the AeroCorder into a Data Acquisition and Crash Recorder System, making this ideal for FOQA and SMS data collection. Designed and spec’d for airborne operational commercial and military environments for fixed-wing and rotary aircraft. Product Page&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocorder-fdr-cvr]]&gt;






CUSTOMER SUCCESS STORY: FRONT BURNER 
General aviation aircraft face many challenges when it comes to in-flight connectivity. Equipment installation is complex, and the cost of data can be very expensive. In addition, smaller profile aircraft have limited options for WI-FI installations because of antenna restrictions, hardware placement and weight. Front Burner’s PC-12 has AeroWave 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerowave-100]]&gt; installed, and now their Director of Aviation is able to remain in constant contact with schedules, reservations, and diversions. 

 “I would recommend the system, especially for the price, and there’s no-megabyte charge, so I don’t feel like I have to be the Wi-Fi police when using it. The total cost of the AeroWave 100 is what drove my decision to use the product.” Read Their Story&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/customer-success-stories/2019/01/patrick-collins-director-of-aviation-for-front-burner]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
