<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_Amer_HCE_Skyplan-Sunset_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Sunset Notice – Classic Flight Planning System</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 

 This communication is to inform you that we will be sunsetting our classic flight planning system on May 31, 2020. We are sharing this notice to not disrupt your service and give you ample time to be able to transition to our next generation flight planning system. This change will affect the Flight Bag Pro application as well as the flight planning website (flightservices.honeywell.com &lt;[[flightservices.honeywell.com]]&gt;). 

 
  Next Steps 
 
 We are thrilled to welcome customers who haven’t taken advantage of our next generation flight planning system to give it a try. We’ve overhauled our flight planning offering with a next generation website and mobile app that helps you create, compute and file flight plans faster, easier and more accurate than ever before. 

 Value to Customers 
 

 	- Brand new, state of the art, flight planning system developed from the ground up using FMS algorithms. 	- Updated website and user experience. 

 How to Access the New Flight Planning System 
Log into flightservices.honeywell.com &lt;[[flightservices.honeywell.com]]&gt; and start a flight plan. Both the flight bag pro and the flight planning website default to the next generation system. If you have bookmarked the classic flight planning system after May 31, 2020 you will be redirected to our new flight planning system. 

 After May 31, 2020: 
 

 	- You will no longer be able to access the classic system. 	- You will be able to see what you’ve computed in the classic system, but will not be able to edit or modify those flight plans. 

 
 Need Help or Have Questions? Our Team is Here to Assist. 

 Our 24/7 operations team is available to help at any time on the website and flight bag pro application.
Login to start flight planning &lt;[[flightservices.honeywell.com]]&gt;
US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330 
 International: +1 (602) 365-7020 
 flightservices@honeywell.com</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
