<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201710_EMEAI_Email_ATR_CONNECTED APU_PM.201710_EMEAI_Email_ATR_CONNECTED_APU_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reduce APU Related Flight Delays by 35%</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear valued customer,

Managing unscheduled maintenance events can be both costly and time-consuming for an airline, causing delays that put on-time performance at risk. That’s why Honeywell, with more than 80 product lines and nose-to-tail technologies, is using latest Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) capabilities to change the concept of airplane maintenance.
Introducing GoDirect Connected Maintenance for Auxiliary Power Units (APU)
The GoDirect Connected Maintenance service for APUs &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/connected_apu_3.html]]&gt; from Honeywell monitors APU health and performance and warns operators of impending issues. For {{lead.Company Name:default=your aircraft(s)}} it can help: 


	- Reduce APU-related flight delays by 35%

	- Highlight the most critical faults to repair, giving actionable recommendations to maintenance crew

	- Prepare for maintenance ahead of time and facilitate parts replacement before a failure occurs



Honeywell pioneered APU technology and has over 95,000 units in operation around the globe
Like other smart systems on today’s modern aircraft, the APU generates a wealth of data on just about every aspect of its health and performance. The challenge is analyzing the data quickly and determining what data is relevant for the maintenance team. Honeywell does it the best as no one understands APUs better than we do.




Interested to know more?
Honeywell’s GoDirect Connected Maintenance for APUs &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/connected_apu_3.html]]&gt; has been selected by Cathay Pacific after demonstrating 35 percent fewer operational disruptions in trial program. Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/connected_apu_3.html]]&gt; to find out how {{lead.Company Name:default=your aircraft(s)}} too can improve APU availability by identifying potential issues before they become problems.




Best regards,

Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
