<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201812_NonCPUseMyAerospace_lg.201812_NonCPUseMyAerospace_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Final Reminder: Submit Electronic Orders After January 15</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Repair Providers, Distributors and Brokers,


Using the MyAerospace Portal  &lt;http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com&gt;allows us to shorten your repair times, while the award-winning interface gives you the information you 
need when you need it. Even with these benefits, we are still receiving a high volume of manual repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) orders not sent through MyAerospace or using an electronic data interface (EDI). 

This is your last reminder that effective January 15, 2019, we will no longer accept manual orders or units at our repair sites - units will be held until an electronic order is in the system. This is consistent with our Repair and Overhaul Terms &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/terms-and-conditions-filtered?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTjJSalpHWmxZVEEzWkdOaSIsInQiOiJ5REdKaUFoYlpiNXh1R2Y3ZVwvMnZVeUEydlh0clliWWQ2Y0RSdW5cL1FydmVrT25EejIzSkJSeGlRZ2VHalFXRGNYK1FXZWRKdmJScTBieWx3blhHSm93PT0ifQ%3D%3D#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending&gt; posted on 
MyAerospace.

What do I need to know about online ordering?


	- Honeywell policy requires using MyAerospace or EDI to create orders for spares, repairs and overhaul. 
	- We reserve the right to reject, and will have no liability for, orders which were not entered through MyAerospace or EDI.


What are the benefits of online ordering?


	- Experience a fast and seamless flow into the repair cycle.
	- Reduce holds and delays with accurate order paperwork and documentation.
	- Receive immediate confirmation that the order has been placed.


How do I create a repair order in MyAerospace?


	- Access Online Ordering &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/TcZQc000w0000IS20q00GX0]]&gt; to 
place your order prior to shipping the hardware.
	- Print the Repair Order Sheet from the order confirmation page and send it with the unit.
	- Use Order 
Status &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00wI0G002000QWXcgZ0]]&gt; to monitor your order.
	- View training videos and additional 
resources &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20ascending]]&gt;, including this short video &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/P000Z0GQqI00V00c00fXw02]]&gt; describing online ordering.
	- If you don&apos;t have access yet, create an ID and password – view this quick reference guide &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/m000Ze20000Gwq00IcU0QX0]]&gt;


How do I use Electronic Data Interface (EDI)? 


	- Honeywell has partnered with Aeroxchange &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/E0G0Q00iIY00Z00X2c00q0w]]&gt;, an aviation supply chain solutions company.
	- Access information about how to enable Aeroxchange. &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/wI0XZ0GQq00000wj0002Z0c]]&gt;



Again, Honeywell requires that repair orders are sent either through MyAerospace or EDI. We look forward to working with you on this important initiative.
Thank you for your business.


Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
