<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201904_Americas_Email_IMU_3D Mapping_JRD.201904_Americas_Email_IMU_3D Mapping_V1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Partner with Honeywell’s Inertial Sensor Team and Try Before You Buy</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Hello {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}},


For decades, Honeywell has paved the way for the inertial sensor and navigation market by providing reliable, dependable and high-performing solutions for a variety of industrial applications, including 3D mapping.

Our suite of non-ITAR, MEMS IMUs and navigators are accurate, rugged and tested in real-life 3D mapping applications to provide you with the data and confidence 
you need to make the right choice. 

Whether you’re using IMUs for stabilization, guidance and control, measurement and testing or mapping, our products are designed to accommodate your size, weight and power requirements. 

If you’re flying in GNSS-denied areas, our HGuide n580 INS/GNSS navigator &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/navigation-and-sensors/hguide-n580]]&gt; provides several options to accommodate your price and performance requirements. 

If you’re just looking for a standalone IMU, our HG4930 IMU &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/navigation-and-sensors/hg4930]]&gt; is a great option and performs well in environments prone to heavy vibration. 

For a limited time, you can try a Honeywell IMU or navigator before you buy*. Contact us today to learn more. 





CONTACT US  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/IMU_V1.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_imu_gh&amp;utm_content=marketo]]&gt;







*Try before you buy program is subject to availability and execution of Honeywell’s bailment agreement. Limit one (1) product per customer. Customer must return unit in 30 days from the time the unit is received. Customers who do not return the unit within 30 days will be charged full MSRP at standard Honeywell terms and conditions.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
