<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202006_BK_Customer_Newsletter_June_MC.202006_BK_Customer_Newsletter_June_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New AeroWave 100 in-flight data plans, New Product Video Series and More</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Newsletter - June 2020

NEWS &amp; ANNOUNCEMENTS

 

AeroWave Offers Unlimited Connectivity with $399/month Flat Fee
AeroWave now offers two affordable plans: $399/month or $39.99/hour for unlimited data. Each plan offers the convenience of staying in touch on all personal devices from takeoff to touchdown. The monthly plan is a great choice for leisure users, while hourly provides the same level of connectivity for power users. Existing AeroWave customers can send an email to sales@bendixking.com &lt;[[mailto:Sales@BendixKing.com?subject=AeroWave]]&gt; to move to the new monthly flat fee plan!




We know you’re looking for something simple, 
easy to use, and mobile friendly, so we’ve done just that. 
What’s new:



	- New images and Homepage layout for a better user experience. 
	- New market categorizations.
	- New product categories and featured 
products.
	- New content such as blogs, news and events.


This new website design will leverage world-class technologies to provide our customers with a superior, single digital customer experience. 
Visit BendixKing.com &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/home]]&gt; today!



THE MORE YOU KNOW. Product Videos. The sales team continues to add more “short format” product overviews to help you stay informed and better understand upgrade options for your cockpit.

Have a suggestion for a future video or webinar? Please 
reach out to Lisa Watmore lisa.watmore@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:lisa.watmore@honeywell.com?subject=Product Videos]]&gt; or to your sales manager. 

AeroFlight electronic attitude indicator - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8]]&gt; 

HeliVue Touch - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA]]&gt; 

AeroCruze 100 proven autopilot - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS]]&gt; 

AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W]]&gt; 

AeroNav 900 GPS Nav/Com - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM]]&gt; 

AeroNav 900 (Portuguese) - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/DMVjsYrVdJTBekGqjA2T2w]]&gt; 

AeroCruze 230 touchscreen autopilot - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Wotxp12uYggtjrDqR2AN2C?]]&gt; 

AeroPanel 100 audio panel - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/ZuhUyoDWgDVAQRiiNRnvFr?]]&gt; 

AeroVue Touch primary flight display - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/DMVjsYrVdJTBekGqjA2T2w]]&gt; 

Weather Radar discussion - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Yv5bmjbwrnXQNnp4U3o6Xs?]]&gt; 

Synthetic Vision &amp; Safety - Playlist #1 How does synthetic vision help increase safety? 
- View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/vehnDHTRzkhKRHveG9fWV5]]&gt; 

Synthetic Vision &amp; Safety - Playlist #2 What products can provide synthetic vision? - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/vehnDHTRzkhKRHveG9fWV5?chapter=2&amp;autoplay=1]]&gt; 

Synthetic Vision &amp; Safety - Playlist #3 Full presentation - View Now &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/vehnDHTRzkhKRHveG9fWV5?chapter=3&amp;autoplay=1]]&gt;




 
   
WEBINARS &amp; TRAINING 
Upcoming - There’s still a few spots left 
for tomorrow’s webinar. Register today!

Webinar: From iPad to Panel: Using ForeFlight &amp; IFD100 with the AeroNav/Avidyne navigators to triple your awareness. 
Date: Thursday, June 25th, 2020 5:00pm PST / 8:00pm EST

Transitioning from flight planning to navigation has never been easier.  In this webinar, we’ll show you tips and tricks to 
seamless integration of flight planning on Foreflight and your AeroNav navigators.  Then, take to the skies and multiply your panel glass with direct Wi-Fi control from your iPads
Register Here &lt;[[https://register.gotowebinar.com/register/3092350472441892865?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0RCa01qWTFOVE5sTVRFMSIsInQiOiJzZXhcL0pjUDFwM01GTWtHYTRLZTY2OUpSOWVPcFN2eUdZNTBlaWVQWWlaMjlKYSt5ZmQ2SmlRa0RDUDBpR1lwQ1wvQ0h2NjlVRkgzdkp4bGtDc0dWUVB3PT0ifQ%3D%3D]]&gt; 

On-demand webinars - In case you missed it, check out these recent webinars:

AeroVue Touch primary flight display: Is it right for your next upgrade? 
In this webinar, BendixKing’s Simon Williams along with SocialFlight President Jeff Simon, discuss the blend of open integration combined with powerful features 
that provide a cost-effective installation strategy for avionics upgrades. Learn about this unit, including the panel planning process, installation tips and whether the AeroVue Touch might be the right choice for your next panel upgrade. 
View it Here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AeroVue_Touch_and_Integrated_PanelBK_LP_Webinar_SocialFlight_AeroVue_Touch_and_Integrated_Panel_MC.html]]&gt;
Access 
code: 748302

AeroWave 100 in-flight connectivity: New data plans to fit your needs.
In this webinar, BendixKing’s Sapan Shah provides fresh insight on the AeroWave 100 and how it provides you and your passengers the convenience of staying in touch on personal devices from takeoff to touchdown. Explore which new data plan is right for you. 
View it Here &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/rhvg4jFa9YZFCEVRk9xUWc]]&gt;

CONTACTS
Find Your Sales Rep &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;
Find A Dealer or Repair Partner &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/Dealer-Directory/]]&gt;
More Contact 
Info &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;

SHOWS &amp; EVENTS
Meet us in the “virtual” skies! EAA AirVenture 2020 in Oshkosh may be cancelled but we’ll be connecting with you 
virtually with training sessions, exciting new product announcements, product demos, show specials and more. 
More information coming in July and check our EVENTS page here &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/about-us/events]]&gt;.

Don’t forget to watch the “live look in” - short product information video snippets that are mentioned in this newsletter. 

Stay well, fly safe and we’ll see you soon!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
