<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202011_Global_ISC_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Updates and Actions Needed From Our Valued Suppliers</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Supplier, 

Despite the ongoing challenges we are facing together due to the coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak, we continue to be inspired by the resilience of our employees and our supplier partners. 

It remains a great privilege for all of us to be part of the aerospace industry, which is, pursuant to Department of Homeland Security (“DHS”) 
Guidance &lt;[[https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/Version_4.0_CISA_Guidance_on_Essential_Critical_Infrastructure_Workers_FINAL AUG 18v3.pdf]]&gt;, Department of Defense guidance &lt;[[https://media.defense.gov/2020/Mar/22/2002268024/-1/-1/1/DEFENSE-INDUSTRIAL-BASE-ESSENTIAL-CRITICAL-INFRASTRUCTURE-WORKFORCE-MEMO.PDF]]&gt;, and Presidential Directive 21 &lt;[[https://www.cisa.gov/critical-infrastructure-sectors]]&gt;, critical to infrastructure, transportation, security, and defense. As such, to the extent permitted by applicable law, it is our mutual obligation to safeguard business continuity and support our customers who rely on our products during this pandemic. As one of our valued suppliers, your partnership is crucial in making this possible. 

As a reminder, you are required to regularly communicate with your designated Commodity Manager regarding developing COVID-19 impacts to you and/or your sub-tier suppliers, your mitigation plan, and the anticipated timeline of these impacts. As necessary, you should diligently pursue alternative resources and third parties to uphold your commitments to Honeywell, on-time, and without compromising quality. As always, you must consult with your Honeywell Commodity Manager for prior approval before making any change to materials, manufacturing process, location, or subcontractors. 

With the holiday season fast approaching, your Honeywell point of contact will be reaching out to you by Friday, November 20, to document your holiday coverage and hours of operation for planning purposes. Finally, if you support U.S. government work, please be reminded to complete the Cyber-Security Assessment &lt;[[https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=JuXsln2csEiNr4uTyQpdGLVhGeRHOrxBqz61IZq6O5RUOFoxVUJXSlVIUExCWEFSNkQ2UEFVNTlJNi4u]]&gt; by November 30 in accordance with the communication you have already received. 

Thank you for all you do to ensure the health, safety, and welfare of your employees, while simultaneously supporting critical infrastructure programs. Honeywell, our shared customers, and our country are all counting on you. 

Sincerely, 

Bob Buddecke 
Vice President and Chief Procurement Officer 
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
