<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201708_APAC_Email_APACHQ_Aug_ENG_mih.201708_APAC_Email_APACHQ_Aug_ENG_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell International Sarl (Avionics R&amp;O and Mechanical/APU in Singapore) Transition to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd (HISB)</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

HONEYWELL INTERNATIONAL SDN BHD
(1164217-X)
Level 25, The Vertical, Avenue 10, 
Bangsar South City, 
UOA Corporate Tower, Lobby B, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi, 
59200 Kuala Lumpur, 
Malaysia


August 15, 2017


Dear Honeywell Customer, 



In reference to the letter sent on July 5, 2017, we would like to assure you that the transition of your transactions and existing agreements with Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte Ltd’s Avionics R&amp;O Site at Loyang and Mechanical/APU R&amp;O Site at Gul Circle (currently under Honeywell International SARL) to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd is progressing successfully.

Creating an integrated business platform via the Honeywell International Sdn Bhd organization will simplify and enhance the way in which you conduct business with us and the benefits for you as a valued customer will include a more efficient and effective procurement experience. 



To follow up on the action, we appreciate your kind validation on whether the following activities we requested previously have been completed. If not, we would appreciate your immediate attention to ensure that the below actions and changes be made as soon as possible:




	- Update your Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to reflect supplier as Honeywell International Sdn Bhd as an approved supplier.




	- The new supplier address for Honeywell Avionics Singapore Loyang and Mechanical/ APU Gul Circle procurement and accounting transactions is:





Company Name:
Honeywell International Sdn Bhd


Address:
Level 25, The Vertical, Avenue 10, Bangsar
South City, UOA Corporate Tower, Lobby B, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi


City:
Kuala Lumpur


Postal Code:
59200


Country:
Malaysia







	- The amended “Ship To” addresses for the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Avionics R&amp;O and Honeywell Aerospace Singapore APU and Mechanical R&amp;O sites remain unchanged:









For Honeywell Avionics Singapore Loyang Site:  
 
Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
2 Loyang Crescent, Singapore 508976








For Honeywell Mechanical/APU Singapore Gul Circle Site:  
 
Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
161 Gul Circle, Singapore 629619







	- Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Consignment_Goods_Manufacturing_Eng.pdf]]&gt; for more information.






For Contract Customers Only – We will be sending you a Novation Agreement or Amendment assigning existing contractual rights and obligations from Honeywell International Sarl to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd. We request your prompt attention to execute such Novation Agreement or Amendment prior to September 8, 2017. If you have any questions about the Novation Agreement or Amendment, please feel free to contact your Honeywell Customer Business Director or Contract Manager.


As we go through this transition, our Customer Support Manager or Customer Business Director will be working closely with your procurement organization and program teams to ensure that each step of the process is well communicated and effectively implemented.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us through your regular Honeywell Aerospace representative.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
