<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201902_Transition_ODY_lg.201902_Transition_ODY_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about our Wichita and Renton Repair and Overhaul Sites</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer:
As part of our normal business process, Honeywell continually looks for ways to simplify our supply chain to provide you with a more efficient process. 

After a comprehensive evaluation, we’ve decided to consolidate and centralize repair and overhaul operations into a single large facility in Olathe, Kansas by the first quarter of 2020. This means that we will close our Wichita, Kansas site by the end of the year and our Renton, Washington site by the first quarter of 2020. Overall, we expect this change to be seamless for you and are committed to zero interruptions in service. 
At this time, nothing changes and you should continue to engage with Honeywell in the same way and send your orders to your current sites. We will continue to keep you updated and will provide plenty of notice and instructions for changes that may impact you, such as adding site addresses to your approved supplier list or performing site surveys as deemed necessary by quality system requirements.
Please review this list of part numbers &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Wichita_Renton_PartNumber_List_Feb2019.xlsx&gt; impacted by this announcement. 

Our commitment to customer service does not wane during a transition. If you have questions, at any time, please feel free to reach out to your primary Honeywell contact. We’re working to always give you the quality and service you deserve. 
Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace
  

If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
