<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Constant Aviation.Constant_OvationSelect_Gulfstream.Ovation Select_Gulfstream</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Ovation Select Upgrade for Gulfstream is Finally Here</subject>
    <textOnly>THE OVATION SELECT UPGRADE FOR GULFSTREAM AVAILABLE THROUGH CONSTANT AVIATION


If you&apos;re one of the many business jet owners still flying around with an outdated cabin management system in your Gulfstream GIV/GV, G450 or G550, you&apos;ve probably outgrown the cassette player, VCR and the old technology that is still in your aircraft. 


Give your cabin a face lift and upgrade to Ovation Select™ with Constant Aviation and get a 100% digitally-driven cabin management and an in-flight entertainment solution that is specifically designed to improve your in-flight experience and complement your cabin for many years to come!


With Ovation Select, You don&apos;t have to get rid of your current configuration. In fact, with Honeywell&apos;s PED technology, you can access all of your current features from the convenience of your mobile device without all the extra costs that come with other systems - it&apos;s that simple! 


When you upgrade to Ovation Select, you&apos;ll be able to: 



 - Control lighting, temperature, shades, galley functions and audio/video from the convenience of your seat. 
 - Watch satellite TV or a high-definition Blu-ray movie with full surround sound with your new in-flight entertainment system. 
 - Review presentations, stream content and much more on high-definition monitors from your mobile device.   


Learn more about Honeywell&apos;s Ovation Select cabin management system upgrade available through Constant Aviation and see why so many business jet owners are using it today!
LEARN MORE &lt;[[#]]&gt;
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
