<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_Global_HAPP/MSP_Customer/Dealer_Email_TM.201809_Global_HAPP/MSP_CustomerV</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Updates 2018 HAPP &amp; MPP Renewal Policy</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear customer,

From all of us at Honeywell Aerospace, thank you for enrolling into our Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP). As you are aware, the service plan continues to deliver coverage to protect you from unexpected avionics maintenance cost. While we pride ourselves on the overall performance of our program plan, we want to ensure you have adequate time to renew and reinstate coverage prior to your contract expiration date.

We would like to take this opportunity to inform you of a change in policy on HAPP and MPP contract renewals.

In 
an effort to streamline and improve our renewal process, we are implementing the following changes for 2018 renewals: 



	- 60 days prior to contract expiration date, we will notify you with the details of the upcoming renewal. This lead-time will allow you to accomplish the following:



	- Resolve any questions or concerns related to contract coverage
	- Contact operator to arrange for contract signature and payment
	- If helpful to your process, provide PO to Honeywell
	- Advise if aircraft is sold or otherwise not flying


	- 30 days before the expiration date, we will send a second notification advising that the expiration date is near.

	- A final notification will be provided 10 days prior to the expiration date.

	- If no communication is received regarding the renewal of the contract it will be terminated on the expiration date.

	- Finally, please note that any requests to extend coverage dates will need to be approved before the expiration date.


For you to continue participating in this protection program, we encourage you to start the renewal process early and ahead of the expiration date reducing any chance of a lapse in coverage. If you do not supply Honeywell with a signed contract, purchase order or billing details by the expiration date you will no longer have coverage and subject to current year pricing. If you should have a failure after expiration it will result in Pre-existing Failure fees as part of new contract sign up. 

For more information or to talk to someone about these and other related topics, please contact your HAPP/MPP Sales Manager or email the HAPP/MPP Administration Team today at happ-sales@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:happ-sales@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.

Sincerely,

Paul David
Senior R&amp;O Sales Director



If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/K00djQI00qob24GBh0vZ0X0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
