<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201701_APAC_Email_APACHQUpdates_mih.201701_APAC_Email_APACHQUpdates_Eng_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell International Sdn Bhd</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;


 &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Generic_Airplane.jpg]]&gt;


January 17, 2017


Dear Customer,


As part of Honeywell’s Asia Pacific (APAC) growth strategy, Honeywell Aerospace has made the decision to set up a new aftermarket headquarters and a new distribution center under Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This will allow Honeywell to improve our product distribution in APAC and better serve our APAC customers.

The new distribution center will be called Asia Regional Distribution Center (ARDC). ARDC will streamline Honeywell’s APAC Aero aftermarket distribution operations to better support our customers in the APAC Region.

The establishment of the new aftermarket headquarters will see APAC business content that is currently managed by Honeywell International Sarl (HIS) in Switzerland transitioned to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Malaysia, with the aim to strengthen regional ownership and better delivery of services.

The optimized local distribution center will be able to serve our customers in the APAC region with quicker delivery turnaround times, and will provide exemplary aftermarket support and services.

Honeywell plans to have the new aftermarket headquarters in Malaysia to go live in Q2 2017 with the establishment of the distribution center in Q3 2017.

We expect the transition to be seamless for you as we have formed a dedicated and experienced transition team, composed of functional experts and leaders from throughout Honeywell Aerospace. The team will manage the transition process and ensure there are no disruptions to your operations; we commit that this transition will not detract from our focus of providing superior customer service to our Customers in APAC.

A follow-up notification will be sent to you with full details of changes that we may need you to execute in your systems. In the meantime, if you have any questions, please email or call Joel Miranda joel.miranda@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Joel.Miranda@Honeywell.com]]&gt; at +60172670090.



Sincerely,






            Brian Davis                                Mark Burgess                         Andy Gill

            Vice President APAC                   Vice President APAC                B&amp;GA Leader APAC

            Air Transport &amp; Regional             Defense &amp; Space                     Business &amp; General Aviation




© 2017 Honeywell International Inc.
 &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 



Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
