<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_01_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Lopez_2019_01</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
Happy New Year! I want to lead off by thanking you for doing business with Honeywell and restating my commitment to helping your business succeed. Our team of professionals is here to deliver the best customer and technical service to you and your organization every day. And with our expanded events and operator conference calendar included below, we will be going to more places to talk face to face with our operators about their Honeywell products and services. I am always available so don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance. 
-- Abel
Did You Know?


Dassault and Honeywell offer a new way to provide in-flight 
communications to Falcon operators

Dassault Aviation launched FalconConnect, a comprehensive solution designed to facilitate the use, management and control of in-flight connectivity. Powered by Honeywell’s GoDirect services, FalconConnect is designed to make connectivity as efficient and straightforward as possible for operators, crews and passengers alike... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/june/dassault-and-honeywell-offer-a-new-way-to-provide-inflight-cabin-and-cockpit-communications-to-falcon-operators]]&gt;.

Field Service Engineer Ed Leadley thinks like the customer to drive superior service

Ed Leadley knows exactly 
what it’s like to work in a busy corporate flight department -- he spent close to two decades as an aircraft mechanic and director of maintenance... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/january/thinking-like-a-customer-drives-superior-service]]&gt;.

Flying to the big football party in Atlanta and require support?

You can contact Honeywell via the Direct Access app on your smartphone or call 
1-855-808-6500... More information &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Customer Support Information.pdf]]&gt;.
 
2019 Operators Conferences schedule set

Conferences are 
scheduled throughout all regions during 2019 - we hope you&apos;ll join us to learn more about Honeywell products and services that are critical to your flight department. Download calendar. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/2019_01_Ops_Conf.pdf]]&gt;

Easy Access to Technical Support and on-demand webinars
We’re always trying to simplify your access to 
technical support. In addition to a new streamlined contact-us form &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; on MyAerospace Portal, you can also search for webinars and videos &lt;[[https://honeywellaerocommunities.force.com/SSCommunity/TSSCommunityCases]]&gt; in the portal. Review previous and upcoming webinars here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/technical-support-webinars]]&gt;.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Abel Lopez
Direct: +1-310-521-1204
Mobile: +1-310-3415987 
Email: Abel.Lopez2@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Abel.Lopez2@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
