<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201706_Global_Email_HAPP_Quoting Tool_Reminder_JRD.201705_Global_Email_HAPP Quot</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the Honeywell Services Quoting Tool for Channel Partners</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
GODIRECT SERVICES QUOTING TOOL FOR CHANNEL PARTNERS
MAY 2017

As part of the new MyAerospace Portal, the GoDirect Maintenance and Services team has created a quoting tool for channel partners, making it easier than ever to click, quote and sign-up your next HAPP or MPP customer.

Learn more about this new tool and the features that will be available to you this summer!
REQUEST A QUOTE 
 
Generating a HAPP or MPP quote is simple and less time consuming than ever before with Honeywell&apos;s new quoting tool for channel partners:


	- Simply enter your customer&apos;s aircraft and contact information

	- Select from a list of Honeywell standard and optional equipment based on their aircraft type 
	- Receive a quote, show it to your customer and sell! Easy, isn&apos;t it?
CHECK QUOTE STATUS
 
Quoting multiple aircraft? Need additional help generating a quote? No problem. Check on the status of your quote any time to see if your quote is ready - it&apos;s that simple! By using this feature, you&apos;ll be able to:


	- Monitor the status of an existing quote

	- Accept the quote/request a contract

	- Clone a quote

	- Share a quote via email
HAPP/MPP/MSP COVERAGE VALIDATION
 
Let&apos;s face it. Keeping a running list of all the aircraft types covered under HAPP and MPP is tricky. There are simply too many aircraft models covered under each of these programs and the list is always growing. With the new coverage validation feature, you can search by:


	- Operator

	- Aircraft make, model or serial number 

	- Contract number
ACCESS TO ALL YOUR GODIRECT ACTIVITIES
 
Do you manage a fleet of aircraft? Are your customers taking advantage of Honeywell&apos;s suite of GoDirect services to complement their hardware? Now is the best time to consolidate all of your customers&apos; contracts in one place. With the new &quot;contracts&quot; feature, customers can pay for their GoDirect services—from cabin to cockpit and more in one place. Now that&apos;s convenient!


	- View &amp; pay invoices

	- Manage your contracts

	- View contract details

	- View executed electronic contracts

	- View contract reporting/report usage
For more information or to talk to someone about the HAPP quoting tool, please contact your HAPP sales manager or email the HAPP team today at happ-sales@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:happ-sales@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
