<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Mar_MC.202003_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Mar_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>BendixKing Dealer Newsletter March 2020</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Dealer Newsletter - March 
2020

NEWS BRIEFS

BREAKING NEWS:
To ensure the 
safety of our people during the coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak, BendixKing has decided to withdraw from the AEA show in Nashville. This decision was made from an abundance of caution based upon prioritizing the health of everyone involved. 

 AEA is an important event for us, you and the industry. We remain dedicated to keeping you informed with alternative methods to share product announcements, details and training planned for the show.

 Please contact your BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; with any questions. 

OTHER NEWS:
We’ve added a new international distributor to our network, which now includes rotorcraft: United Aero Group. For more on how to contact them or any other distributor, please visit our website here.

 Announcing our 2020 Channel Partner Program &lt;[[https://bkdealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Documents/]]&gt; which includes updates to our experimental dealer network.

 Also updated is our 2020 Co-Op Program &lt;[[file://C:\\Users\H144988\Downloads\Co-Op-Program.pdf]]&gt;, with exciting additions, such as new product demonstration equipment as well as lobby display packages to better support your sales and marketing needs. Any questions contact Lamonte Macon &lt;[[mailto:lamonte.macon@honeywell.com?Subject=Would like more information about the 2020 Co-Op Program]]&gt;. Check out more dealer-specific programs and documents here &lt;[[https://bkdealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Documents/]]&gt;.

 KMA 30 Discontinued
 Please note the KMA 30 has been discontinued and replaced with the new slide-in replacement called the AeroPanel 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropanel]]&gt; / KMA 32. Please contact your BendixKing rep &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; for more information. 
 
   
CUSTOMER WEBINARS 
Thursday, March 26, 2020 7pm EST 
Automation and the Flight Envelope
SocialFlight’s Jeff Simon and BendixKing’s Andrew Barker and Mariellen Couppee explore the levels automation and aligning with the phases of flight. Register&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/3477603951655777547]]&gt; 

On-Demand Webinar 
Privacy in the Age of ADS-B
Where does your data go, who has access to it - and how can you protect your privacy? Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and Roger Dykmann from BendixKing discuss in this 
compelling webinar.
Watch NOW&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/xsDShFJY2Z3WQnUTwE9qZU]]&gt; Access code: 902384

SALES BULLETINS
2020BK-01 Over The Counter (OTC) Equipment Sales

2020BK-02 AeroCruze 230 Autopilot

2020BK-03 MST 67A (Trade-in Rebate) Upgrade to MST 70B 

2020BK-04 Dealer Demonstration Equipment 
Promotion

2020BK-05 RDR Weather Radar Upgrade Program

2020BK-06 CAS 66/67 TCAS II Change 7.1 Upgrade

2020BK-07 First Time Sale- Incentive Program

Complete list of BK Sales Bulletins &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ0020q0ZZpuhX40qLI00OG]]&gt; (must login to view)
Find your nearest 
BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/K00q4QI00qhQ2rGuZ0LZ0X0]]&gt;

SIGN UP FOR DEALER NEWSLETTER
Were you forwarded this newsletter? Contact Lamonte &lt;[[mailto:lamonte.macon@honeywell.com?subject=Please%20opt%20me%20in%20for%20the%20BK%20Dealer%20Newsletter]]&gt; to get on our Dealer Newsletter list.



PRODUCT FEATURE


INTRODUCING AEROPANEL 100 INTERCOM/AUDIO PANEL 
AeroPanel 100 is a convenient slide-in replacement for the BendixKing KMA 30. The music and Bluetooth capability provide unsurpassed audio flexibility throughout your airplane, and the 30-second digital recorder lets you play back any missed communications. AeroPanel 100 makes it simple to control audio throughout the aircraft including two music sources, 6-place intercom, and multiple audio inputs. Product Page&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropanel]]&gt;




TECH SUPPORT UPDATES


NETWORK ALERT: REPAIR VENDORS OLATHE UPDATE 
BendixKing has begun working more closely with its Repair Partners in the US to repair our parts that our customers send in to our Olathe facility. Repairs sent into the Olathe facility will likely see a tag issued by Duncan Aviation or Mid-Continent Instruments, with other partners to follow. Our Repair Partners have demonstrated a commitment to quality that presents a great value to both our customers and BendixKing. As always, you are welcome to reach out to these partners directly to have your BendixKing items repaired. Find Your Repair Partner &gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/repair-partners]]&gt;




SHOWS &amp; EVENTS


MARCH 2020 AEA Annual Convention &lt;[[http://aea.net/convention/2020/]]&gt; in Nashville, TN  |  March 24-27  |  POSTPONED
Due to the ever-changing landscape of this 
situation, global travel restrictions and health of everyone involved, BendixKing has decided to withdraw from this show.

Sun ‘n Fun &lt;[[https://www.flysnf.org/]]&gt; in Lakeland, FL  |  POSTPONED until May 5-10 |  Booth A-034
Please check the official status of this new date May 5-10 on the 
show’s website. 

APRIL 2020
AERO Friedrichshafen &lt;[[https://www.aero-expo.com/aero-en/]]&gt; in Friedrichshafen, Germany  |  POSTPONED 
Please check the official status and reschedule date on the show’s website.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
