<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_MyAero-Portal-Updates_Year-Program_Email_Operational.March Non-RTN Portal Use</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Portal Update – Microelectronics &amp; Precision Sensors B2B</subject>
    <textOnly>Starting today March 8, 2021 our Microelectronics &amp; Precision Sensors B2B eCommerce website will be moved to aerospace.honeywell.com and can be accessed through this LINK &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/purchase/orders/precision-sensors-ordering]]&gt;.
What features will be available? 



	- Online Ordering – Magnetic Sensors and Transducers can be placed using our Online Ordering tool for Commercial orders only.
	- Paper PO Form – Microelectronics, Precision Pressure Transducers, Barometers and High Temperature Electronics, as well as any Government orders, please submit your PO using the Paper PO form.
	- Order Status – For order status, check using our online order status tool.
	- RMA Request Form – To request an RMA, please complete the RMA request form. Do not send any hardware back to Honeywell without an RMA.


What parts can be placed using Online Ordering?


	- Magnetic Sensors and Transducers can be placed using our Online Ordering tool for Commercial orders only.


For more information about this change, please visit our FAQ page on this HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/microelectronics-precision-sensors-ordering-faq]]&gt;.
To view the individual release notes for the items listed above and to catch up on latest improvements to MyAerospace, please refer to and bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;
Please be sure to Opt-In to receive important portal enhancement update emails.
OPT-IN &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
