<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20200203_CPSTransition.CSP Transition Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about your Honeywell Aerospace Control Sensor Product (CSP) Line Transition</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

Last year, Honeywell advised of the decision to optimize our operations and better align the Control Sensor Product (CSP) line. The CSP product line will move from our 2600 Ridgeway Parkway – Minneapolis site to the Honeywell Clearwater, Florida site. This applies to Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEM) orders, spares orders, and repair units. 

A review of repair order indicates that you have sent in a part number for repair or ordered at least one of the impacted part numbers. The following table identifies the impacted part numbers and their associated last receipt dates at Minneapolis. 

View the Part Number/Wave List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/CSP PN Wave List 2.03.xlsx]]&gt; to determine when each part will move and the associated late receipt date. Locate the wave sequence number and the ‘Last Receipt Date at Minneapolis’ identified in the chart below. 





Description
Last Receipt Date at Minneapolis
Ship to Clearwater Date


Minneapolis part numbers– Wave 1 &amp; 2
Tues Mar 3, 2020
Weds Mar 4, 2020


 Minneapolis part numbers - Wave 3
Tues Mar 31, 2020
Weds Apr 1, 2020 




To minimize issues or delays with the repair of hardware, customers should follow these guidelines and actions: 

Existing Repair Orders 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Minneapolis.
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification.
	- If a modification is required, the Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact the customer to advise and coordinate the activity.


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.




New Repair Orders 



	- To minimize delays to the repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the Clearwater, FL location.
	- Part numbers received on or before the effective date will be accepted at Minneapolis, but sent by Honeywell to Clearwater, FL.
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit to Clearwater for repair.


	- A PO/contract modification may be required.
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity.




Repair Unit Shipments 



	- The customer may validate repair capability at the Repair Site Capability List &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; which is available 24x7 on the Honeywell Aerospace website.


Existing Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders



	- Honeywell is working to fulfill existing orders.
	- Depending upon inventory, due dates and lead-times associated with the order, some orders may require a purchase order or contract modification to revise the place of performance.
	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact you with the next few weeks to advise and coordinate that activity.


New Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders



	- Please view the chart to determine the last date that Minneapolis will accept new OE/Spares orders.
	- After these dates, all new hardware orders are to be addressed to Honeywell International, Inc. at the OE/Spares address provided below.
	- Depending upon inventory, due dates and lead-times associated with the hardware, some orders may require a purchase order or contract modification to revise the place of performance.
	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact.


Aircraft on Ground (AOG) Support 
There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware. 

Update Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
Customers must update their authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts. 


Honeywell Name for Repairs: Honeywell Defense - CSP
Address:                                  13350 US Highway 19 N.
City, State:                               Clearwater, Florida
Postal Code:                            33764
Country:                                   U.S.A.
MFG Cage Code:                     0BFA5

If you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Honeywell point of contact. 

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
