<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201803_EMEAI_Email_RMU_Integrated_mih.201803_EMEAI_Email_RMU_Integrated_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Make piloting easier</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Proven retrofit and upgrade solutions to make your current fleet more valuable, more efficient and more productive

By proactively responding to airline industry needs, Honeywell&apos;s products and integrated systems meet new and emerging standards and requirements, while enhancing the performance of existing aircraft functions.
Find out more about our suite of products for terrain &amp; traffic awareness, navigation and communication, to make the job of piloting easier:


	- Automatic Dependent Surveillance-Broadcast (ADS-B) &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance]]&gt; promotes greater safety by enabling an aircraft to use precise GPS data for enhanced traffic situational awareness

	- Integrated Multi-Mode Receiver (IMMR) &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance]]&gt; is industry’s only fully digital navigation receiver that integrates instrument landing systems (ILS), global positioning systems (GPS), GPS landing system (GLS) and VHF omnidirectional radio range (VOR) functionality into a single receiver

	- Datalink Services &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance]]&gt; increase the speed and enhance the accuracy of information dissemination, both to and from the aircraft  
	- Enhanced Ground Proximity Warning System (EGPWS) &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance]]&gt; reduces the risk of controlled flight into terrain by providing flight crews with timely, accurate information about terrain and obstacles in the area

	- IntuVue 3-D Weather Radar System &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance]]&gt; provides the most complete, accurate and intuitive view of airborne weather hazards



Contact us today &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/terrain-awareness-and-navigation-assistance#standards-challenge]]&gt; to know more about our retrofit and upgrade options that provide situational awareness of the aircraft and offer seamless communication between airborne and ground based systems.

Best regards

Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
