<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>New template</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Helicopter Newsletter 2016.Q4 2016 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Helicopter Newsletter for Q4 has landed!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.honeywellaidc.com/pages/SiteLanguages.aspx]]&gt;
NEWS | Quarterly Helicopter Newsletter
2016 proved to be another difficult year as the headwinds which our industry faced in 2015 continued throughout the year. Looking at the past 24 months reflects an extremely challenging market with significant headwinds inhibiting industry growth. These headwinds can be summarized by: used aircraft up for sale at near all-time highs, lower flight utilization, depressed resale values, the decline in used aircraft appraisals, oil and gas bankruptcies in the US and Canada, a year over year decline in offshore rig counts and lastly, decreased OEM production levels, primarily in the medium and heavy-twin product classes.
The outlook for 2017 reflects optimism as we anticipate industry stabilization; no more do we anticipate double-digit deltas in our leading indicators. New OEM deliveries indicate an improvement in certain product classes and equally as important, we do expect positive growth at the aggregate level. In the aftermarket, we are seeing positive signs which lead us to conclude that the tremendous decreases and/or increases in the leading indicators are behind us.
A driving force in the aftermarket recovery is anchored around the need for differentiation as well as improved safety. Both of these anchors enable operators to be better positioned within their respective operating missions in both the short, and long term.
Specific to improving safety, Honeywell continues to use fact-based analysis in identifying the top causes of accidents and incidents; this can be found in our article, Honeywell Technology Addresses 80% of Accident Causes. Honeywell’s heritage, culture and future will always focus on safety as we feel compelled to ensure the pilots, passengers, aircraft and ultimately our industry is safe. The first step in our journey to improving the rotorcraft industry safety record is through raising awareness and informing the operator base of the top causes of accidents and incidents, followed by advising the operator base that there are products and services available today which can help mitigate these causes. It is no coincidence that Honeywell has solutions to address 80% of the top causes of accidents and incidents. We encourage you to read this article and take this safety improvement journey with us.
We sincerely hope your 2016 closes successfully with the anticipation that 2017 will be the year of stabilization.


Sincerely,
Rick Angleo
Director of Strategic Marketing: Global Commercial Helicopters







Honeywell to Distribute Sikorsky S-76C++™ Helicopter HUMS Under LicenseSikorsky S-76C++™ helicopter operators have a choice when it comes to equipping their 
helicopters with the latest Honeywell Health and Usage Monitoring System (HUMS) technology. Sikorsky has authorized Honeywell and our distributors to provide HUMS hardware directly to organizations that operate S-76C++ helicopters.Continue 
Reading  https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/october/honeywell-to-distribute-sikorsky-s-76c-helicopter-hums-under-license     



Honeywell Technology Addresses 80% of Accident Causes
 Commercial helicopters are complex machines that fly low to the ground, in rugged terrain, in all kinds of weather, tackling unique 
and sometimes perilous missions. No wonder improving flight safety is the No. 1 priority for everyone in the helicopter community – from manufacturers and technology suppliers to owners, operators, end users and pilots.
 
 Continue 
Reading https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/october/honeywell-technology-addresses-80-percent-of-accident-causes



Skyforce Offers Flexible Mission Mapping – and More
 From helping an Air Evacuation pilot navigate his way to a busy urban hospital, to enabling a police officer to lock her search 
light on an accident scene, to tracking elephants for conservationists or dropping maritime pilots on ships, Honeywell’s complete line of mapping hardware and software has the capability and flexibility you need to get the job done.
 
 Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/october/skyforce-offers-flexible-mission-mapping-and-more]]&gt; 



Honeywell and Precision Aviation Offer Custom ADS-B Solutions
 The clock is ticking for U.S. helicopter operators who need to equip their aircraft with Automatic Dependent Surveillance Broadcast Out (ADS-B Out) avionics by the January 1, 2020 deadline.
 
 Continue 
Reading https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/october/honeywell-and-precision-aviation-offer-custom-ads-b-solutions



Webinar: Aspire 200 Satellite Communications System
 Have questions about Aspire 200 for Helicopters? Honeywell has the answers. Tim Roberts, senior technical sales manager for Honeywell Aerospace, conducted a one-hour informational sessions on the Aspire 200 helicopter satellite communications system and the system benefits to operators.
 
 Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/october/webinar-aspire-200-satellite-communications-system ]]&gt;




Want to fly HAPPy? Check out how.
Avionics are a big investment, worth protecting. Honeywell’s Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), covers more than 50 different platforms across commercial helicopters and business aviation. HAPP is a maintenance protection program that offers full coverage for all Honeywell avionics – and peace of mind for operators.
 
Watch the Video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/eQA79iur2Tg]]&gt;


BendixKing receives FAA approval 
BendixKing, a division of Honeywell Aerospace, announced it has received FAA approval for the installation of its KT 74 ADS-B Transponder and KGX-Series ADS-B transceivers on a broad list of popular general aviation helicopters.


Continue Reading &lt;[[http://bendixking.com/Company/News-Events/BendixKing-Receives-FAA-Approval-for-Installation]]&gt;


Platform Spotlight: Leonardo Helicopter AW139
The Leonardo Helicopters AW139 rotorcraft features leading edge technology, including a Honeywell Primus Epic fully integrated avionics system. The Epic cockpit enables operators to fly safely and efficiently and supports a variety of helicopter specific missions including corporate and VIP transport, oil and gas, law enforcement, health and emergency services, as well as search and rescue operations.


Learn 
more&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/platforms/leonardo-helicopter-aw139]]&gt;





Upcoming Helicopter Shows and Events
Helicopter Association of Canada (HAC) Convention and Trade Show 2016 – November 11-13 http://www.h-a-c.ca/convention.html
Air Medical Transport Conference (AMTC) 2016 &lt;[[https://aams.org/events/amtc/]]&gt; - December 13-15
Helicopter Association International (HAI) HELI-EXPO 2017 &lt;[[http://heliexpo.rotor.org/]]&gt; - March 6-9, 2017







Would you like to subscribe to the newsletter? You can sign up here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/newsletter]]&gt;.
 


© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.



 &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;





 



This message was sent to name@website.com.
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
