<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Amer_HCE_Forge_Email_Jet-ConneX-Overage.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>JX Overage Implementation - Effective January 1, 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 

 During the past several months, we have made sure to keep you informed about a new monthly overage charge that Inmarsat will be implementing to all service accounts that exceed their allocated data limits.

 Please be aware that this policy change took effect January 1, 2021 and will impact all Honeywell Forge Jet Connex (JX) subscriptions. 

 In preparation for this policy change, our team has developed a wide range of data management tools that will help you manage your aircraft data use to help reduce overage costs. To learn about these tools and how to enable them click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/overage-honeywell-forge?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;. 

 HOW DOES THIS IMPACT MY EXPERIENCE? 



	- Starting on the February Honeywell Forge invoice, customers will see a line item for overage and data carryover considerations for January usage (if applicable). That bill will arrive on February 15, 2021. 

	- You can set up alerts in the Cabin Connectivity Portal once a threshold of data is used. To help customers adapt to overages, we will reach out to you to and offer support on setting up alerts or you can contact Inside Sales or your Field Service Engineer. If you previously had notifications set up, your custom configurations will not change.


To understand more about the impact of this change please click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/overage-honeywell-forge?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; to see our frequently asked questions. 

If you would like to discuss overage changes or solutions for your flight department, please contact your Honeywell Forge representative or the number below. We thank you for your business and look forward to continuing to serve you. 

 Thank you, 

 The Honeywell Forge Team 

 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 
sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
