<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Americas_SpiritAero_PrimusElite_MC.201906_Americas_Email1_SpiritAero_DU87</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Don’t Risk a CRT Display Failure!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer,

Are you tired of your plane’s old CRT displays with their poor color, weak contrast, and annoying flicker? Those screens are obsolete and no longer serviceable. It’s time to upgrade!

Spirit Aeronautics, a Honeywell Authorized Avionics Dealer, is now scheduling Primus Elite upgrades and offering a variety of upgrade paths to fit your budget and operational requirements. These include:



	- One-For-One Upgrade that offers a lower-cost, building blocks approach to Primus Elite that allows you to replace one or several displays at a time.
	- Primus Elite Enhanced Features (PEEF) which replaces all your obsolete DU-870 displays, plus offers additional benefits like cursor control interface, advanced data loading with wireless options, optional XM weather, and improved situational awareness
	- Primus Elite Advanced Features, a software upgrade for operators who have a full complement of the new DU-875 that is particularly useful for reducing errors and pilot workload when flying to unfamiliar locations, in bad weather, or at night.



There are also upgrade options for Gulfstream operators that replace old CRTs with DU-885 displays with the same benefits. 


Plus, right now Honeywell is offering a $35,000 trade-in credit per display when you replace your DU-870 units, along with special Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan Avionics (formally known as HAPP) incentives.

Stop flying in an outdated cockpit! Contact Spirit Aeronautics at 614-333-8540 &lt;tel:614-333-8540&gt; or by clicking below to discuss which upgrade path is right for you.



CONTACT SPIRIT AERONAUTICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/three-options-for-upgrading-to-primus-elite?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_spiritaero_pe&amp;utm_content=customer+form+fill]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
