<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201803_Global_Email_HTF7000_Partner_mih.201803_Global_Email_HTF7000_Partner_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell HTF7000 Family Authorized Channel Partner Listing</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer, 
 

As the HTF7000 family of engines continues to mature, Honeywell has authorized HTF Channel Partners worldwide to support customer scheduled and unscheduled inspections for MSP or non-MSP covered engine maintenance. The following Channel Partners have HTF authorized locations. Honeywell recommends contacting the Channel Partner of your choice prior to scheduling maintenance to ensure they can handle the required maintenance on your type of aircraft. For more contact information, visit myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;.

(Please click on the image to view the list.)
 &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/New_Channel_Partner_Active_List_010718.pdf]]&gt;  
 

  Heavy/Overhaul Maintenance – The performance of total disassembly, inspection, repair, reassembly and functional test of an engine in the test cell    
 
  Minor Maintenance - The performance of engine bore scope inspection, on condition hot 
section disassembly and repair as necessary, reassembly and on-wing power assurance test  
 
  Line Maintenance - minor inspection, oil and filter changes, removal and replacement of engines, external LRUs, accessories and Components, plus all related services not requiring disassembly of either the engine turbo-machinery or its 
Components  
 
  Flight Line Maintenance - The performance of routine checks, inspection and malfunction rectification to return an Owner/Operator’s Authorized Equipment, limited to LRU. 


David Lopez
Honeywell Aerospace
B&amp;GA Aftermarket Americas Mechanical Director 




If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/E0G0Q0hWIkB0Z0dX2d0jq0p]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
