<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Global_Email_OvationSelect_TM.201906_Global_Email_OvationSelect_TM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Ovation C-Series Phase 1 - Upgrade Incentives</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yJOzBIINlH0&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
Greetings {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}}, 

Honeywell is offering a substantial dealer incentive for Phase 1 upgrades on aircraft equipped with Ovation Select C-Series cabin management system (CMS) through September 2019. Please contact your dealer for a quote to remove your obsolete parts. 

As announced in 2018, in the MHT Service Information Letter (SIL), the MHT 10.4” touchscreens for your CMS is no longer supported for repairs as of December 31, 2018. 

A full cabin upgrade is not required to solve your obsolescence. A phased upgrade approach is available based on your budgetary needs and convenience. Please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Ovation_CMS_Phased_Upgrade_11_5_18.pdf]]&gt; to see more information. This enables you to extend the life of your aircraft and improve your passenger experience while avoiding downtime or groundings.

We recommend reviewing various upgrade options with your preferred Honeywell dealer to inquire about scheduling an install and take advantage of the incentive. 

Please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/SERVICE_INFORMATION_LETTER_080818.pdf]]&gt; for the MHT Service Information Letter (SIL). The link lists two SIL’s, each includes two different sets of affected part numbers as listed below. If your part number is not listed, it may be because it is older and listed on previous SIL’s, feel free to further inquire with me.

Please feel free to contact me for more information.

Thank you,

Eleonora Serra
Direct Sales Manager
Honeywell Aerospace
Mobile: 714.914.0419
eleonora.serra@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:eleonora.serra@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
