<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Americas_Email_SkyConnect_LL.201903_Americas_Email_SkyConnect_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Updates and Reminders for Sky Connect Customers</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;  &lt;[[http://masco.com/]]&gt;
Sky Connect Tracker Systems Email
March 2019
Get Connected with MASCO Services and Honeywell&apos;s Sky Connect Tracker
HAI 2019 is just around the corner, March 5-7, 2019 in Atlanta, GA. Stop by and see MASCO at booth B6327 and learn more about Sky Connect Tracker System solutions and how they can elevate your flight experience.
Tracking to the Last Drop

The US Forest Service now requires more details about the water that is dropped during firefighting efforts. That includes how much water is dropped, where is it picked up, and finally where it is dropped off. Olympic Aero Services’ Series 600 Additional Telemetry Unit complies with US Forest Service Additional Telemetry Unit (ATU) requirements and uses the Sky Connect technology to meet the ATU requirements. 

With Sky Connect, firefighting operators can: 



	- Report bucket open, close gallons filled, plus gallons dropped
	- GPS data including: date, time, speed and more



Connect with MASCO to learn more about telemetry unit integration in your helicopter. 



CONTACT MASCO &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/masco-2019-campaigns&gt;
Tracker 3 Advanced

Upgrading your Sky Connect system now includes push-to-talk capabilities with Tracker 3 Advanced.  This drop-in upgrade now offers a push-to-talk feature that can shave minutes in time critical missions. Other upgrades include:



	- Data off-loading: 4G/LTE data radio
	- Barometric sensors
	- 3-Axis Accelerometer
	- Upgraded GNSS: GPS, Galileo, Beidou



Learn more about this drop-in upgrade by contacting MASCO.



LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/masco-2019-campaigns]]&gt;
Air Methods Upgrades its fleet to Tracker 3A

Air Methods is the world&apos;s largest air medical services provider, and may be dispatched to transport a patient between hospitals, roadside accident or any extreme example in between. 

They must be ready to provide the Level I trauma support the patient requires during this critical phase known as the ‘golden hour’, so tracking and monitoring this fleet is paramount to response and safety. 

Read the rest of the story and watch the video on Honeywell Aerospace. 



WATCH VIDEO &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/october/medical-operators-connect-with-masco-and-tracker-iii]]&gt;
Enhancing Sky Connect Tracker 3A Features with Truth Data

Honeywell&apos;s new agreement with Truth Data now provides FDM data collected by Sky Connect Tracker 3A to individual operators and larger fleets. Plus, you&apos;ll count on enhanced recording capabilities that allow operators to analyze and interpret data for each flight. Learn more about these capabilities by contacting MASCO. 



CONTACT MASCO &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/masco-2019-campaigns]]&gt;
See You at HAI 2019

HAI 2019 is just around the corner, March 4-7, 2019 in Atlanta, GA. Book a meeting with MASCO&apos;s sales team today by clicking on the button below.   



BOOK A MEETING &lt;[[mailto:kevinfraley@mascoservice.com; travisboyer@mascoservice.com?subject=Book Meeting for HAI]]&gt;
How Old is your Sky Connect System?

Did you know that Sky Connect Tracker installations should be inspected annually to assure good satellite connectivity? Keep your system running optimally by contacting MASCO today.



GET MAINTENANCE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/masco-2019-campaigns]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
