<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201807_APAC_Email_HAT_MC.201807_APAC_Email_HAT_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Are You Ready for the First Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) APAC Distribution Center?</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer, 

Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) is opening a new distribution center in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, by August 1, 2018. We have begun stocking critical airframe components applicable to multiple aircraft platforms for our first ever Asia Pacific distribution center offering used serviceable components. To make the transition process as seamless as possible for your organization, we appreciate your immediate attention to ensure that the following actions and changes are made as soon as possible.


	- Update your Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to reflect Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd. as an Approved Supplier.


	- Acting through Honeywell Aerospace Trading, which is a business division under Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd. legal entity.






	- The new supplier address for Honeywell Aerospace Trading procurement and accounting transactions is:





           
Company Name  
Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd.



Address
Level 25, UOA Corp Tower, Lobby B, Avenue 10




The Vertical, Bangsar South City



City
Kuala Lumpur



Postal Code
59200



Country
Malaysia





	- The amended &quot;Ship To or Pick-Up&quot; address for the Honeywell Aerospace Trading Asia Pacific distribution center is:





           
Company Name  
Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd. - Honeywell Aerospace Trading



Address
C/O CEVA Logistics (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd.




Dock 31 &amp; 32 / Lot 9A, Jalan Tiang U8/92,




Section U8, Bukit Jelutong Industrial Park



City
SHAH ALAM, SELANGOR



Postal Code
40150



Country
Malaysia





	- Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd. default currency is set up to US Dollars for quotations and invoices.
	- In accordance with the Foreign Exchange policy introduced by Bank Negara Malaysia, the Malaysia based customers can settle their invoices due to Honeywell International Bhd. Sdn. only in Malaysia Ringgit, unless they receive an exemption from Bank Negara Malaysia. If the current agreement states USD as the invoice billing currency, Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd. can maintain the current status quo, but the settlement currency will be Malaysia Ringgit.
	- All other customers outside of Malaysia will be invoiced in USD, unless the contract states otherwise.





           
For Non-Malaysia Resident Customers:  




Beneficiary Name:
Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd.



Beneficiary Account:
0-117470-059



Bank Name:
Citibank Berhad



Bank Address:
Level 43, Menara Citibank 165





Jalan Ampang 50450 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia



Swift Code:
CITIMKL



Account Currency:
US Dollar



 
 


           
For Malaysia Resident Customers:          




Beneficiary Name:
Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd.



Beneficiary Account:
0-117470-105



Bank Name:
Citibank Berhad



Bank Address:
Level 43, Menara Citibank 165





Jalan Ampang 50450 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia



Swift Code:
CITIMKL



Account Currency:
Malaysia Ringgit




As we transition, our Sales Manager and Customer Business Director will be working closely with your procurement organization and program teams to ensure that each step of the process is efficiently communicated and effectively implemented. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us.

 



CONTACT US &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/APAC_HAT.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
