<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Partner E-Blast.May Newsletter.May Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>May 2016 Honeywell Channel Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
Facebook      &lt;[[www.Facebook.com/HoneywellAerospace]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace?trk=company_logo]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[www.Twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCoEXFVPJYdvlmwyp3Sz8QRw]]&gt;
In the May issue of Honeywell&apos;s Channel Newsletter, we introduce our newest resource to you - the Channel Partner Services webpage, the Primus II Radio Upgrade and its effect on the ADS-B Out 2020 deadline, three reasons your customers must upgrade their data loaders to the DL-950 before the end of 2016 and three trends all business aviation operators should follow in 2016. 








              

Honeywell&apos;s Channel Partner Services 
We’ve created a dedicated webpage for our channel partners so that they can access articles related to their business; download helpful material about Honeywell’s solutions; and connect with the Honeywell channel marketing team to get customized co-branded marketing solutions - it&apos;s that simple.



Visit the page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/service-listing/channel-partner-services/?utm_campaign=channel-newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=newsletter]]&gt;












The Primus II Upgrade: An All-in-One Solution for the ADS-B Out 2020 Mandate 
As we start to near 2020, many operators are struggling to find a solution that fits their current aircraft configuration. For many, the answer is simple: The Primus II Radio.



Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/news-listing/2016/april/the-primus-ii-upgrade-an-all-in-one-solution-for-the-ads-b-out-2020-mandate/?utm_campaign=channel-newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=newsletter]]&gt;









Three Reasons to Upgrade to the DL-950
If you know one of the 400 operators still using the DL-900, there&apos;s a few reasons why they should upgrade before the end of 2016.


Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/news-listing/2016/march/three-reasons-to-upgrade-to-the-dl-950/?utm_campaign=channel-newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=newsletter]]&gt;









Three Trends Business Aviation Operators Should Follow in 2016 

In 2016, business aviation operators should be following these three trends that are guaranteed to improve their productivity and simplify their upgrade path.



Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/blogs/2016/may/three-trends-business-aviation-operators-should-follow-in-2016/?utm_campaign=channel-newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=newsletter]]&gt;












In Other News...


Honeywell&apos;s APU and Engine Inventory

We would like to share a great opportunity to acquire equipment from our Engine and APU inventory. For additional information on a specific solution, please contact: 
Chuck Oberfield &lt;[[charles.n.oberfield2honeywell.com]]&gt;
APUs
602.365.2034


Cory Little &lt;[[mailto:cory.little@honeywell.com]]&gt;
Propulsion
602.231.2324


Christ Jordan &lt;[[mailto:christopher.jordan@honeywell.com]]&gt;
Propulsion
602.365.5549






Q1 Shared STCs




Honeywell&apos;s Sales Advisory Board

On April 21, the Honeywell Sales Advisory Board met about several key topics including the MyAerospace Portal, pricing and ways to improve our overall efforts moving forward. The board plans to meet again in June to regroup and discuss more of these topics. If you&apos;re an SAB member and still haven&apos;t taken the survey, please take a moment to do so here &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/7238C9D]]&gt;.
















Please do not forward this email as its survey link is unique to you. Opt out &lt;[[[OptOutLink]]]&gt; of receiving surveys from this sender
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
