<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202012_Global_BGA_Email_MSP-HTF-Nacelle.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Honeywell MSP Offering – HTF Nacelle Coverage Options</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Current MSP HTF Engine Customer, 

 Honeywell is pleased to announce a new addition to its Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) solutions for Propulsion Engines and APUs. Introducing MSP HTF Nacelle, which is available for Challenger 300 (HTF7000), Challenger 350 (HTF7350), Legacy 450/500, Praetor 500/600 (HTF7500), and Gulfstream G280 (HTF7250) aircraft enrolled in Honeywell’s MSP Engines program. 

 You can now benefit from additional maintenance coverage for your nacelle system to reduce downtime, limit unexpected repair costs and gain control over maintenance needs and budgets. MSP HTF Nacelle comes packed with features that include routine inspections, treatment and repair of corrosion, and/or replacement* of nacelle components when Beyond Economic Repair (BER). 

 With MSP HTF Nacelle, you can choose from two tiers that best fit your operation. Key differences in the program tiers include:



	- MSP Preferred - Comprehensive coverage for scheduled and unscheduled maintenance including corrosion treatment, repair and replacement.
	- MSP Essential - Coverage for scheduled and unscheduled maintenance with options for corrosion treatment.


Both tiers provide predictable budget and costs, OEM-authorized repairs, replacement parts and increased aircraft availability. The program also may enhance resale and trade in value of the aircraft. The table below highlights the benefits of the tiers. 


*Corrosion-induced replacement with MSP Preferred only.

 Honeywell and the Aircraft OEMs recently released Service Bulletins (refer to table below for specific ATA 
numbers) that requires conversion to the improved thrust reverser coating within 48 months of SB release date. Honeywell is launching this MSP program to help manage expenses related to this conversion. If you experience unplanned maintenance costs and corrosion issues, MSP HTF Nacelle will cover scheduled or unscheduled maintenance including corrosion repairs to provide dispatch ability, budget control and peace of mind.







Aircraft Platform


ATA Number




Challenger 300/350


78-03-011




Legacy 450/500, Praetor 500/600


78-30-003




G280


78-30-004
Coupled with our simple-to-understand MSP Engines program, award-winning Honeywell customer service, and the Original Equipment Manufacturer (OEM) brand, the MSP HTF Nacelle is a comprehensive solution and ideal choice for your Honeywell propulsion system. 

Read the MSP HTF Nacelle brochure &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/MSP-Nacelle-Brochure_Honeywell2020.pdf]]&gt;, where you can read more about the program features and benefits and view a comparison of program tiers. 

 Please contact your Honeywell MSP Sales Manager for more details or to enroll in MSP HFT Nacelle today.
CONTACT MSP SALES &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/MSP-HTF-Nacelle-Coverage.html?utm_medium=email&amp;utm_source=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_BGA_MSP-Propulsion]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
