<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201805_SarasotaTransition_LG.201805_SarasotaTransition_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Update and Schedule Detail: Our Move to Clearwater From Sarasota</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
UPDATE AND SCHEDULE DETAIL: OUR MOVE TO CLEARWATER, FL FROM SARASOTA
Dear Customer,

In August 2017, we announced our plans to consolidate some of our operations and move all work from our Sarasota, Florida facility to our Clearwater, 
Florida location to improve service and cost efficiencies. Despite this move, product support will not change.  
Our schedule has changed slightly. We will begin moving operations on May 31, 2018 and expect to be completed by June 6. We are committed to minimizing production and delivery impact as much as possible and ask that all critical orders be submitted before May 21.
 
During this move, we will not be able to receive new orders or process repair orders at the Sarasota facility. All new and repair orders after May 30 need to be addressed to the Clearwater facility, noted below. 
 
In addition, to mitigate any impact to our ability to support AOG shipments, please plan accordingly and work with us to create a proactive approach to minimize AOG requirements during the physical move. 

Please make these changes below to help ensure a smooth transition:  



	- Update your authorized supplier list and internal systems to include the new supplier location as an approved supplier.





	- Update the “ship to” address for the Honeywell Aerospace R&amp;O site starting May 30:





Company Name
Honeywell Aerospace


Address
13350 US Hwy 19, Plant 2


City, State
Clearwater, FL


Postal Code
33764


Country
United States





	- Our cage code is 56081.


These changes only impact orders processed by our Sarasota site. We apologize in advance for any inconvenience this may cause and, as always, we appreciate your business.

Please share this information with others in your company. If you have questions or concerns, please contact us directly:
CabinMGMTRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:CabinMGMTRepairs@Honeywell.com&gt; (repairs) 
CabinMGMTSales@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:CabinMGMTSales@Honeywell.com&gt; (new part orders).  


Thank you for your business, 

Honeywell Aerospace


Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt; 
 

If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
