<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Amer_BGA_MSP-Avionics_Email.Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Releases New Extended programs under MSP Avionics</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 Experience complete peace of mind in the knowledge that you won’t encounter large unbudgeted maintenance costs by enrolling in our MSP Avionics Extended programs. These programs allow customers to reduce the risk of obsolescence and to exchange units for their newer versions upon failure.

 In addition to our current Extended programs offering that support DU-1310, DU-1080, DU-875, and Phase III we have introduced two new coverages: 



	- CD830 Extended Program &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/MSP%20Avionics%20CD830%20Brochure.pdf]]&gt;: Control Display Units 810 and 820 are facing obsolescence, CD810 is currently out of repair capabilities and CD820 will no longer have them by the end of 2020. MSP Avionics is now offering an optional Extended program allowing an unlike exchange to CD830.
	- ED800 Extended Program &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/MSP%20Avionics%20ED800%20Brochure.pdf]]&gt;: Electronic Display 800 (ED800) is obsolete and going out of repair by the end of 2020. MSP Avionics is now offering an optional Extended program allowing an unlike exchange to CMA6800.


We would value the opportunity to discuss these options in more detail. If you would like to find out more, please send us an e-mail &lt;[[mailto:MSPAvionicsSales@Honeywell.com?subject=Learn%20more%20about%20CD830%20&amp;%20ED800%20Extended%20Programs]]&gt; and we will keep you informed.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[mailto:MSPAvionicsSales@Honeywell.com?subject=Learn%20more%20about%20CD830%20&amp;%20ED800%20Extended%20Programs]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
