<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Metrics.Q2-2016</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aerospace Intellectual Property --  June Quarterly Metrics</subject>
    <textOnly>Aero Intellectual Property - June Quarterly Metrics
A Message to M&amp;PM and E&amp;T Leaders Regarding Intellectual Property Metrics

June 2015

Dear Colleagues:

Honeywell is one of the Top 40 companies in patents granted in the United States each year with Aerospace contributing about 30% of those patents. The continued creativity and submittal of invention ideas is critical for the protection of our product revenue and competitive advantage. As a result, we encourage the prompt submittal of invention ideas that support our products through the Worldwide 
Invention Disclosure System (WIDS), and are asking for your support in sharing this message across your organization.
 
 For the M&amp;PM and E&amp;T leaders on this distribution, we will be providing quarterly metrics in the areas of relevance to your organization. The intent is to inform and solicit your support to drive actions as needed for your area of influence.
 
 The appended metrics (1) Disclosure 
Submittals and (2) Disclosure Decisions (patent filings) have been prepared year-to-date through September. (June 2015 Quarterly Metrics &lt;https://teamsites2013.honeywell.com/sites/IPTracking/Wiki/2015%20Actuals/2015%20Quarterly%20Metrics/Quarterly%20Metrics_June%202015.pptx&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&gt;)




(1)  Disclosure Submittals (by IP Steering Committee YTD vs. Historical)

Purpose: Communicate quantity of disclosures received from Aerospace inventors versus 
historical averages
 Details:  Purple line indicates year-to-date 
historical average (2012-2014). Percentages indicate disclosures received as a % of the annual historical average. 
 
 Commentary: 






 - Disclosure submittals for Aero overall are 11% below the YTD historical average
 - Wheels &amp; Brakes: &gt;100% increase driven by 3D printing for carbon composite materials
 - Electric Power: 45% increase driven by EGTS inventions
 - Safety and Connectivity-CNIS: 38% increase driven by data link, data management, flight data recorder, connected aircraft inventions
 - IPSCs far below historical averages: Aerospace Services, CS-Controls &amp; Integrated Avionics, CS-FMS, Mechanical Components, Safety and Connectivity-Surveillance, Space



Who has actions: 
 &gt;&gt;&gt; E&amp;T T3 Leaders - Monitor deviations from historical averages. Is this in line with your expectations? Drive actions as needed within your organization



Note:  This metric illustrates IPSC’s which are having a significant deviation from 
historical disclosure averages.   A significant deviation is defined as those IPSC’s  that have disclosure submittals of less than 75% of the historical year-to-date (YTD) average for that IPSC.

 

(2) Disclosures Decisions (to File US patents by IP Steering Committee YTD)  

Purpose: Communicate quantity of disclosures reviewed by each IPSC steering committee. Out of those, highlight the quantity and % of decisions to File patents in the US 

Details: Total bar (green + blue) indicates the number of disclosures in which a 
decision was made (file or no file) in each IPSC year to date. Green bar indicates the quantity of those decisions that were “yes” to file
 
 Commentary: 


 - Decisions to file for Aerospace overall increased to 36%  vs. historical average (~33%, 2012-2014),

 - Far exceeding the average filing rate: Navigation (71%), Engines (48%), Wheels and Braking Systems (41%), Safety and Connectivity-CNIS (39%),
 - Far below the average filing rate: CS-FMS (12%), Lighting (20%), Aerospace Services (22%), CS-Integrated Avionics (26%). 



Who has actions: 
 &gt;&gt;&gt;  IPSC Leaders - Review the filing rate which is influenced by incoming disclosure quality and/or IPSC review standards. Is this filing rate in line with your expectations? Drive actions as needed.



Thank you for 
your continued effort to support the Aerospace Intellectual Property Program. Please feel free to contact me with any 
questions.

Thank you, 
Dan
Dan Gutfreund
IP Process Leader
Technology Strategy, Advanced Technology
21111 N 19th Ave (M/S 2J35A5)
Phoenix, AZ 85027
Phone: +1 602 436-9030
Mobile: +1 480 258-8692
Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
