<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201703_EMEAI_STC_UPDATE_JETWAVE_NJM.201703_EMEAI_STC_UPDATE_JETWAVE_NJM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell: JetWave STC Update</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear valued partners,


If you still believe that &apos;take-off&apos; means &apos;turn-off&apos; then it’s time to think again – because our customers are now expecting to stay connected wherever they are. Fortunately, the age of seamless, reliable and fast airborne connectivity is upon us thanks to JetWaveTM from Honeywell and Inmarsat’s GX Aviation satellite constellation. 
By offering your customers the JetWave solution, you’ll be enabling them with ‘office equivalent’ productivity and ‘home-equivalent’ connectivity. They’ll be able to send and receive emails, participate in conference calls or view streaming video.  They’ll also be able to access and benefit from Honeywell’s suite of GoDirect services and applications. JetWave provides a satcom solution which, not only most closely matches the on-ground-in-the-office user experience expected by today’s executive, but will support the growth of those demands into the future enabling enhanced connectivity.
Together with our partners, we continue to achieve STC readiness and certification for a range of aircraft platforms. One of the latest – and one of the biggest – is the EASA certification for Airbus A320 family of aircraft. This Supplemental Type Certificate (STC) means that our JetWave high-speed satellite communications hardware can be installed in any Airbus A319, A320 and A321 aircraft flying today. Many VIP and presidential flights operate the A320 family aircraft, so this represents a significant opportunity for growth. 
A full list of the current shareable STCs is available &lt;here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/jetwave-stc-update]]&gt;&gt;
Should you have any further queries regarding JetWave, please contact your Honeywell Area Sales Manager. Alternatively if you have any queries relating to the STC program, please contact Arnaud Renard @ Arnaud.Renard@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Arnaud.Renard@honeywell.com]]&gt;  
Marc Parizot 
 Aftermarket Program Manager, 
 EMEAI.






CLICK HERE TO VIEW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/jetwave-stc-update]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
