<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018 HELI-EXPO.2018_Event_Global_SavetheDate_HeliExpo_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Helicopter Operators Conference - Save The Date: February 26, 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HONEYWELL ANNOUNCES HELICOPTER OPERATORS CONFERENCE
MARK YOUR CALENDAR FOR THE 2018 HELICOPTER OPERATORS CONFERENCE
Save the Date:
Annual HOC Customer Reception




Date
Feb. 25, 2018




Time
6 p.m. PST





Location  
 Las Vegas, NV 






2018 Honeywell Helicopter Operators Conference (HOC)




Date
Feb. 26, 2018




Time
8 a.m. PST





Location  
Las Vegas, NV














The 2018 Honeywell Helicopter Operators Conference (HOC) will be held on Monday, February 26, 2018 in Las Vegas, NV during HAI&apos;s HELI-EXPO.
 
The conference will provide an overview of the Commercial Helicopter business and 
include technical briefings on Honeywell propulsion engines, avionics and safety equipment.

Representatives from Honeywell&apos;s Customer Business Teams, Technical Sales, Marketing &amp; Product Management and Customer &amp; Product Support organizations will be on hand to discuss our latest products and support offerings and share valuable information and experiences through a series of presentations and 
roundtable discussions.

In addition, we will host our annual HOC Customer Reception on February 25, 2018. We will be sending out a link to the HOC registration website soon, along with other pertinent event details. Please begin to plan accordingly in conjunction with HAI&apos;s HELI-EXPO Conference schedule for February 27-March 1 in Las Vegas, NV. Information about HAI and local area hotels can be found at the HAI HELI-EXPO &lt;[[http://heliexpo.rotor.org/]]&gt; website.
Happy Holidays and we look forward to seeing you at the 2018 HOC event!
 

 

Tony Gilbert 
 Customer Support Manager, Customer &amp; Product Support 
 Robert.Gilbert2@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Robert.Gilbert2@Honeywell.com]]&gt; 
 Office: 480-287-0035 










For additional information or questions, please contact your Customer Support Program Manager or the 2018 HOC coordinator:
Deta Adams
Deta.Adams@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:deta.adams@honeywell.com]]&gt;  
Mobile: 256-508-2708</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
