<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>EBACE14.EBACE 14 Customer Mailing - History</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Us @ EBACE and Witness History in the Making</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Join Us @ EBACE and Witness History in the Making

 
 Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},
 Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
 
MicrosoftInternetExplorer4          
 
 
This June, Amelia Rose Earhart will attempt to make history. By recreating and completing the infamous 1937 flight of her namesake, Amelia Mary Earhart, she will become the youngest woman to fly around the world in a single engine aircraft. Her mission will involve flying a Pilatus PC-12NG almost 28,000 miles and will include 14 stops before completing the flight that her namesake never got to finish. 
As we celebrate our centenary, Honeywell Aerospace is proud to sponsor and support Amelia Rose Earhart. Over the past 100 years Honeywell Aerospace has been at the forefront of aviation innovation – from the demonstration of the world’s first autopilot on June 18th 1914, to the lunar landing, to today’s ground breaking safety technologies - many of which will assist 
Amelia during her epic journey.  We applaud Amelia for her courage and dedication and for inspiring a new generation of aviators both.    

We are thrilled that Amelia will be joining us at EBACE 2014, taking place from May 20th - 22nd at the Palexpo Convention Centre in Geneva. We invite you to come to the Honeywell stand (6622 / Hall 6) on XX and meet this extraordinary young lady who is about to make aviation history.   

For further information on Amelia’s epic journey visit - http://www.flywithamelia.org/ &lt;http://www.flywithamelia.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&gt; 
 Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 Normal 
0     false false false  
EN-US X-NONE X-NONE       
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
Book a meeting &gt; &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/landing-pages/bga/ebace-14&gt;
 Normal 0    
 false false false  EN-US X-NONE 
X-NONE          
 MicrosoftInternetExplorer4
&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/landing-pages/bga/ebace-14&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2014 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
