<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Channel Newsletter.February BGA Dealer Newsletter.Dealer Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>February 2016 Channel Update</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
Facebook      &lt;[[www.Facebook.com/HoneywellAerospace]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace?trk=company_logo]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[www.Twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCoEXFVPJYdvlmwyp3Sz8QRw]]&gt;
Hello – and welcome to the Honeywell family! We’ve extended our commitment to our partner / dealer network to include more resources for sales and customized co-marketing materials, and keeping you in the know with what’s happening throughout Honeywell and the dealer network. For the remainder of 2016 we will bring you recaps and updates through this newsletter every other month.

Recently approved STC&apos;s
Below is a list of recently approved STC&apos;s with the platform and owners. Email BGAChannel@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:BGAChannel@Honeywell.com]]&gt; for more information. We can add you to this list as well as collaborate on co-branded campaign material to get the word out!

- FANS1/A - CL601 (Duncan Aviation/Safran) - FAA
- ADS-B Out (Duncan Aviation) Citation 560 - FAA
- CD830 (MNG/QCM) H800 - EASA
- CNX-250 (3S) PC-12 - FAA

Mandate Reminder:
TCAS 7.1 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/tcas-change-7-1]]&gt; / June 2017
ADS-B Out &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/the-ins-and-outs-of-the-ads-b-do-260b-compliance]]&gt; / January 2020

If your customers request information regarding ADS-B Out requirements, here are a couple of helpful links: The Ins &amp; Outs of ADS-B &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/the-ins-and-outs-of-the-ads-b-do-260b-compliance?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRomrfCcI63Em2iQPJWpsrB0B%2FDC18kX3RUpILWdfkz6htBZF5s8TM3DV1ZBXqFI%2BEEBS7I%3D]]&gt;, and PDF White Paper on ADS-B Mandate &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/c000200Q0qZI08GXt00yb00]]&gt;

Product Spotlight
Online quoting for Ovation SelectTM is now available &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/news-listing/2016/february/online-quoting-for-ovation-select-is-now-available]]&gt;
Ovation Select system now has a easy online pricing tool to get your customers the most accurate price available 24/7.

Operator Bulletins are NEXT
We’ve updated our Operator Bulletins. New name, new look, new layout. The new name reflects the enthusiasm of our products and services being introduced in the industry to your customers: What’s NEXT from Honeywell? Aside from the name, the redesign highlights value props for each audience, adds an “estimated downtime” section, and promotes links to helpful videos, web pages and brochures. We hope your customers will ask what’s NEXT.

Engine Rotable Assets

Model
Description
Quantity

36-100A
APU
1


RE100-LJ
APU
1


RE220-GX
APU
1


RE220-GV
APU
7


TPE331-3U-303G
ENGINE
1


TPE331-3U-304G
ENGINE
1


TSE331-3U-303N
ENGINE
2


FAQ&apos;S
Q: Why does my Sales bulletin special pricing disappear when I submit my PO?
A: Customer Service Representative (CSR) in Honeywell knows how to find the Sales/Service Bulletin (SB) in the portal. If a customer is ordering a part that has special pricing in the SB, they need to specify that in their PO, otherwise CSR will not be aware of the SB pricing. To avoid confusion and delays specify this in the initial PO. CSR will refer to SB and manually update the price in SAP. In some case, for service letters, some parts do not have price specified, CSR will contact Customer Business Manager to verify the price. When the customer is placing an order with pricing as per a SB, they should mention the same on the PO copy along with document number so that CSR can pull from technical publication section in My Aerospace portal and validate.

Q: What if I have a STC I would like included in the newsletter?
A: If your STC meets baseline Honeywell installation requirements, submit it, along with your contact information to our review team at BGAChannel@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:BGAChannel@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. As a bonus, we will also contact you for creating a co-branded campaign to get the word out!

Q: What if I have other Sales / Marketing questions?
A: Email the Channel Team at: BGAChannel@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:BGAChannel@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.


Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
