<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Direct-To.June 2015.Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>June Direct-TO Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Direct-TO Newsletter
June 2015 Issue
What’s the FMS Doing?  &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/Jun2015/FMSNavData2&gt;
How the FMS Processes Navigation Data Part II – The Enroute Segment

In part one of this series, the initial departure procedure was discussed, as were the most commonly used path terminators that deliver the aircraft to the enroute segment.  This edition will expand on those paths and terminators, and introduce a few more...

 


Engine Insights
New Condition Based Maintenance and HUMS Videos

Four new videos covering Conditioned Based Maintenance and Honeywell’s Health and Usage Monitoring System (HUMS) have been added to the Pilot Gateway and Honeywell  Aero Training TV...


Service Information Letter Briefing &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/Jun2015/SILJun2015&gt;
Leap Second Could Affect GPS

Every few years, a second is added to the clock to compensate for the earth’s gradually slowing rotation.  This “leap second” synchronizes atomic clocks with...


Global Customer Committee Update
Meetings Rock the RAILS

The GCC is an independent group of nearly 80 business aviation professionals worldwide that works jointly with Honeywell to bring about improvements in aircraft, equipment, operations and services...


Honeywell Pilot Gateway
Latest Updates

Here is a look at some of that content that was added to the Gateway since the last issue of Direct-TO...


Learn More &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/O0i0g8gX0200ZQqE0i0G24I&gt;

Technical Publications, Videos, news, events, and other resources for pilots can now be found on the new Honeywell Pilot Gateway.  Click Here &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/O0i0g8gX0200ZQqE0i0G24I&gt; to get started.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
