<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202009_Amer_BGA_CH_MSP_Textron_website.202009_Americas_BGA_CH_MSPEXT_Textron_DR</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Let Honeywell Worry About Your Obsolete CRT Displays</subject>
    <textOnly>MSP-Avionics Coverage Offers New Options for Aging CRTs
Here’s a new reason to love Honeywell’s Maintenance Service Plan – Avionics Components. MSP-Avionics has a great feature that helps you protect yourself from the unexpected cost of replacing a failed DU-870 cathode ray tube display on your Primus 1000 or Primus 2000 platform.

 As an MSP-Avionics enrolled customer you have the added option of our Extended coverage:


	- The MSP Avionics DU875 Extended program allows customers to receive an unlike exchange from DU870 to DU875 upon failure as part of their contract’s coverage.


You also have these following options so that you can select the coverage that is right for you:


	- Through the SPEX program, you can exchange the failed unit for another DU-870 at current list prices, with a one-year standard SPEX warranty. The DU-870 SPEX will end on Dec 31, 2020.
	- You’ll also have the option of upgrading to the DU-875 liquid crystal display &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/news/2017/02/honeywells-du-875-885-upgrades-display-capabilities]]&gt;, which is a drop-in replacement for the DU-870, and receive a special trade-in allowance. With this option, you can control costs by replacing one unit at a time.
	- Or, you can take this opportunity to upgrade your whole cockpit to one of our Primus Elite configurations. &lt;[[https://aerospace6.honeywell.com/en/products/cockpit-systems/primus-elite]]&gt; Primus Elite upgrade options can bring your aircraft up-to-date, increase its market value and extend its service life considerably.


Honeywell is here to help, no matter how you choose to manage the reality of DU-870 obsolescence and the move up to the LCD option, which carries with it many benefits. The DU-875 LCD provides more clarity in all cockpit lighting conditions, is substantially more reliable than the existing cathode ray tube displays and each unit saves about seven pounds of weight.

For more information, click below and an expert will contact you shortly.
I WANT TO KNOW MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/reduce-risk-from-obsolete-crt-displays]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
