<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Global_CPS_RO-Generator_Email_Operational.Email 1 R&amp;O Generators</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about R&amp;O Generator Support</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 

In an effort to better serve our customers, Honeywell has made a strategic decision to reposition the repair and overhaul of Bombardier Dash 8 generators to our Tulsa, Oklahoma site. This reposition will enable our Tucson location to increase capacity for original equipment (OE) and spares production while leveraging existing generator repair capacity at our Tulsa site. As Honeywell’s center of excellence for the repair and overhaul of generators, Tulsa is uniquely qualified to support this service. Overall, we expect this reposition to be seamless for you and do not anticipate any disruptions in service. We hope to answer any questions you may have about this change in the communication below. Please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact if you have any additional questions.
TRANSITION SCHEDULE




Product Line Description
New Repair location
Tucson last receipt date 
Begin Shipment to Tulsa on



Repair &amp; Overhaul of Bombardier Dash 8 Generators
(Part Number: 1152218-5 &amp; 1152218-6)
Honeywell Aerospace Tulsa

August 23, 2020
August 24, 2020





Information for Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems as needed to reference the new supplier information for these parts. 





Honeywell Name for Repairs 

Honeywell International Inc. Aerospace-Tulsa



Street Address 

6930 N. Lakewood Ave City



City, State 

Tulsa, OK



Postal Code 

74117



Country 

USA



Cage Code 

63389





To minimize delays with your orders, please follow these guidelines and actions: 

What to do now? 



	- Prepare for upcoming reposition to Tulsa: Review the repositioning schedule, adjust supply plan as needed, and ensure internal systems are updated to reflect the correct Honeywell location on the correlating transition dates
	- Update Authorized Supplier List (ASL) as needed: Please ensure the Tulsa repair and overhaul site is active on your ASL. If you need to conduct an on-site audit, please email your Honeywell Representative.


Repair and Overhaul (R&amp;O) Order Processing 



	- Effective August 24, 2020, all Bombardier Dash 8 generator repair orders should be placed with our Honeywell site in Tusla, OK.
	- We will work to fulfill repair orders already in process at the Tucson site.
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Tucson Last Receipt Date’ to Tulsa for repair.


	- A PO/contract modification may be required.
	- Watch for PO or contract modification request from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.


	- The MyAerospace Repair Site Capability list (ROCAPS) &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs


Original Equipment and Spares Order Processing 



	- There is no change to how original equipment (OE) or aftermarket spares are ordered.


Aircraft-On-Ground (AOG) Support 



	- There is no change to how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware.


If you have any questions about this reposition, please contact your Honeywell Business Manager, Customer Support Manager, or other Honeywell representative. 

Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
