<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Cross SBU.EGPWS TDB Subscription 2nd Customer Letter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Prepare for 6 Terrain Database Downloads/Year</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;https://ads.honeywell.com/&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Get ready for six updated releases in 2016.
With constant, rapid growth in new airports and runways, more EGPWS data more often is essential.
That’s why Honeywell created an all-new EGPWS terrain subscription that increases the frequency of update releases to six per year. So unanticipated changes can be implemented sooner, and keep your fleet smarter, and safer.
When selecting your renewal plan, your first release is always free. Then, by bundling updates 2 through 6, you’ll only pay $500 per aircraft for all five – that’s just $100/release.
For additional flexibility you can choose an “a la carte” payment of $200/aircraft per release. Or contact the helpline listed below and ask about fleet pricing options.

Prepare to lock in your six essential updates.
You’ll find the information you’ll receive well worth the subscription price. With proactive notifications on new or modified runways, changes in RAAS, SR/SL, and ROPS runway status, temporary airport modifications and more – all with the ability to customize the new information to your operator’s specific destination or alternative airports.
Take your EGPWS data to a higher level. Call us today! And don’t forget to ask about fleet pricing options.
Email DSA@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:DSA@Honeywell.com&gt;. Or call us at +1.602.436.6737, and press Option 5.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
