<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_Americas_Forge_GDT-is-now-Forge-Email_amr.Email 3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Access to Honeywell Forge – Your New Platform Has Landed</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=customer}},

 I’m delighted to introduce you to Honeywell Forge.

 Honeywell Forge is a new approach to providing you with a comprehensive platform of connected software solutions, services and applications. This exciting new platform makes it easier than ever for you to access the Honeywell offerings you value and use the enormous power of connected software to turn raw data into actionable information.

 What Does It Do?

 Honeywell Forge enables you to use connected software to bring together assets, processes and people to improve operational performance and achieve your most important operational objectives. 

 What is Included? 

 Included are all the Honeywell offerings formerly branded “GoDirect.” This includes our flight planning, flight database and cabin connectivity software, services and applications. We’ll continue to add new features in the months ahead. 

 How Does It Work?

 Honeywell Forge is powerful, flexible and easy to use. Whether you’re operating one business aircraft or a whole fleet, you can use the intuitive Honeywell Forge dashboard to manage nearly every aspect of your business aviation operation. 

 Read to Gain Access? Click the button below or type in bga.honeywellforge.com to get started today. There is also a link inside your cabin, flight planning and navigational database portals that link to this dashboard.
GAIN ACCESS &lt;[[https://bga.honeywellforge.com]]&gt;
If you have questions our team is standing by to help. Contact one of our support staff here: (602) 365-6502</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
