<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201806_Americas_Nurture_Kellstrom_C130_mih.201806_Americas_Nurture_Email2_Kellst</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Increase Reliability and Service Life for the C-130 E2H Environment Control System (ECS)®</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;      &lt;[[http://www.kellstromdefense.com/]]&gt;

Kellstrom Defense provides proven EH2 ECS® Upgrade



As platforms age, support for sustainment diminishes and end-users tasked with maintaining operational readiness are faced with critical supply chain deficit. Honeywell and Kellstrom Defense offer their military customer base legacy aircraft solutions that address these shortfalls.
Old technology requires more maintenance, has proven to have high failure rates and has low system output. With Honeywell Authorized Distributor and Service Center, Kellstrom Defense, C-130 operators can upgrade to the EH2 ECS® Flight Station, which replaces the legacy C-130 30PPM Flt. Deck ECS System.

This upgrade features:


	- Compliance with modern flight station increased avionic cooling requirements
	- Improved reliability
	- Affordable, easy installation
	- 233% increased output
	- Simplified logistics


As a respected global distributor, Kellstrom Defense will provide you an experienced service team with complete capabilities to solve your challenges. They are focused on providing complex solutions that address operations readiness maintain aging aircrafts at peak performing levels.

To learn more about this upgrade and other Honeywell solutions provided by Kellstrom Defense click below.





SEE KELLSTROM DEFENSE UPGRADES  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Kellstrom_C130.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_campaign=18_channelamericas_d&amp;s]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
