<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Global_BK_Channel_Newsletter_MC.201905_Global_BK_Channel_Newsletter_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Dealer Newsletter May 2019</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
 

BendixKing Channel Newsletter | May 2019
Channel Support 
To better support your BendixKing product marketing needs, we have created a media gallery &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/media-gallery]]&gt; 
which offers both high and low resolution options.Here are some featured new product additions that would like to update you on. 


	- AeroPower USB Charger - Charge any handheld electronic device with the panel or cabin mounted USB charger. With 2.5 amps of dedicated power per port, TSO certification, and flexible installation the AeroPower &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropower-usb-charging-device]]&gt; provides incredible value and peace of mind when using a phone, tablet, or ADS-B handheld in flight.
	- AeroNav - Fly with ease using the new AeroNav &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigators]]&gt; series navigators. Designed as slide replacements for GNS 430/530, these hybrid touch WAAS Nav/Coms provide a simple upgrade path for many customers.



 Webinar 
BendixKing recently recorded a webinar featuring our new autopilots xCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xcruze-100]]&gt; and AeroCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-100]]&gt;. Please view here &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h_egOK0EEkU&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt; and learn more about safety through autopilot proficiency. 

Technical Support Update 
Software 3.18 update for the KT 74 Transponder PN 
89000007-000001 and -000002 has been released. 

KT 74 software version 3.18 corrects an error in the software versions 3.14, 3.15, 3.16, and 3.17 which can cause the transponder to stop replying to certain Mode S interrogations. 

Publication Number D201811000035, ATA Number KT 74-34-04 

Software is available on the BendixKing Dealer portal web site, under Unit Software. 

 Need Help with troubleshooting? Knowledge Articles are short paragraphs that can help you solve the most common issues. Check here &lt;[[https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Home-Page]]&gt; before calling in, you might be able to solve your issue quicker! 





If you still cannot find the answer to what you’re looking for, call us at 855-250-7027!




We are continuously working to serve you better and we appreciate you as our valued customer. 

 You can find sales bulletins posted here &lt;[[https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Sales-Bulletins]]&gt; or on www.myaerospace.com &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.com/]]&gt;. 

Use your local Authorized Repair Partner &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/repair-partners]]&gt; in support of some of your repair needs. 

Contact us at support &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt; or call 855-250-7027 and find support at these 
extensions:</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
