<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201805_APAC_Email_HAT_mih.201805_APAC_Email_HAT_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The First Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) APAC Distribution Center Is Coming by August 1, 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer, 

We are very pleased to announce that Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) will open a new distribution center in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia by August 1, 2018. This will be the first HAT distribution center in the Asia Pacific region and will enable us to serve you in a more efficient way. 

In this new facility, we will stock a wide range of used, serviceable airframe components including APUs, avionics, mechanical components and other line replaceable units from B737, B777, A320 and other aircraft. HAT product offerings include reconditioned materials that were originally manufactured by Honeywell and other original equipment manufacturers.

The distribution center is right next door to the headquarters of Honeywell Aerospace Asia Pacific and will be supported by Honeywell’s extensive repair and overhaul network. Our team of product experts have quick and easy access to both our inventory and its corresponding records to quickly respond to your inquiries. The proximity to our headquarters office provides executive level decision-making in region on the same time zone to provide timely support. 

With this new HAT facility, you will enjoy access to the quality parts you need in a more convenient location, streamlining your distribution and improving your cycle time.

For more information or to request a quote, please contact us today.

 



CONTACT 
US &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/APAC_HAT.html]]&gt;




The new business name and address for the new facility to add to your database:
Honeywell International Sdn. Bhd.-Honeywell Aerospace Trading
c/o Ceva Logistics (M) Sdn Bhd
Jalan Tiang U8/92, Section U8, Lot 9A,
Bukit Jelutong Industrial Park
40150 SHAH ALAM, SELANG
MALAYSIA</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
