<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_BK_Event_Oshkosh_mih.201907_BK_Email3_ABTest_Event_Oshkosh_mih.Whole Emai</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Us in Oshkosh for EAA’s AirVenture Event | July 22 – July 28, 2019</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer,

We can help you bring your cockpit into the future with our innovative line up of products and services. Brand new this year are our new AeroPoint engine data monitoring products for piston and turboprop aircraft. Packed with functionality, AeroPoint will quickly become your single go-to instrument for trends, temps, leaning and detecting carbon monoxide.

We’re also featuring our three new AeroNav GPS Navigators, highlighting a superior product line up from one of our well-known and respected partners. These intuitive touch navigators will guide your flights into the future with innovative features such as geo-referenced frequencies and waypoints, built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi. They are also a slide-in replacement for GNS 430/530 legacy units. Want one more GPS, but don’t have the panel space? Stop by and ask us about the companion app for the AeroNav series navigators. 

Imagine a panel where updates are as easy as downloading from the cloud, and hardware upgrades are as simple as a subscription plan. That’s your future when choosing BendixKing avionics. 

Visit us in our Booth #292 at our BendixKing Pavilion in Oshkosh, WI, during EAA’s 50th AirVenture event July 22 – July 28 to learn more about AeroPoint and AeroNav products, discuss subscription plans for upgrades through our Total Avionics Plan (TAP) and help us celebrate our 60th Anniversary with exciting show discounts!

Spots are filling up fast, so don’t forget to register for our Annual Customer Appreciation Event where you can enjoy food and beverages with our team members and celebrate our 60th Anniversary, while learning about our experimental and certified aircraft solutions.







REGISTER HERE FOR AN EVENT TICKET &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_BK_Oshkosh.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
