<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Customer Experience (CX).CX Minute #1.CX Minute #1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the CX Minute</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.youtube.com/honeywell]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;






Give us 60-seconds &lt;[[https://corpapp.honeywell.com/sites/honvideo/Pages/Player.aspx?bctid=4835934400001&amp;UsrId=e045068&amp;ItmId=5882]]&gt; to make your job easier 
 and your customers happier. 

“The Customer Experience” is one of the hottest buzz-terms in business today. It’s a concept that has entire industries looking at corporate interactions from the customer’s point of view.
The field is so rich in untapped potential, you could spend a lifetime mining it. Fortunately you don’t have to, because the AT&amp;R CX Team is doing the hard work for you.
We’re exploring research, analyzing data, and connecting the dots to put the learning to work at Honeywell.









 

All we ask is that you give us 60 seconds a week to check out a CX Minute video &lt;[[https://corpapp.honeywell.com/sites/honvideo/Pages/Player.aspx?bctid=4835934400001&amp;UsrId=e045068&amp;ItmId=5882]]&gt;. Each installment quickly outlines problems, solutions, and opportunities to refine your customers’ experience.

 








For example, we kick off the series next week by taking a hard look at how we often communicate in writing with our customers. (Spoiler alert: We don’t come across nearly as well as we’d like to.) And as is always the case, we’ll give you the tools to do something about it.









So watch the CX Minute video series premier &lt;[[https://corpapp.honeywell.com/sites/honvideo/Pages/Player.aspx?bctid=4835934400001&amp;UsrId=e045068&amp;ItmId=5882]]&gt; now! Then, let us know what you think. 
 And how we can help you.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
