<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2020 Honeywell AERO Tech Forum.2020 Honeywell Aero Tech Forum Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We’d love to see you at Honeywell’s Tech Forum &amp; Exciting Aerospace Sessions</subject>
    <textOnly>View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/tech-forum?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=hon-corp_techforum2020&amp;utm_content=aero]]&gt;

JOIN THE #FUTURESHAPERS

 The Honeywell Tech Forum 2020 is bringing together top global innovators to provide insights and examples 
on leading the world to recovery, and into the future, through technology and innovation.  Aerospace and travel are front and center in the Tech Forum, especially the Honeywell Aerospace agenda – read on and plan to join us!

 Don’t miss these timely and critical conversations with leaders, including:


	- Peter Maier, President SAP Industries and Customer Advisory, SAP
	- Bert Natalicchio, General Manager Information Technology at Shell
	- Jonathan Roitman, Chief Operating Officer at United Airlines
	- Brian S. Tyler, Chief Executive Officer, McKesson Corporation


Honeywell business presidents will sit down with these industry titans to discuss our partnership, innovations and how we’re working to get 
everyone back to work, life and play. 

 October 15th is focused on Honeywell Aerospace where we’ll highlight:


	- Future innovations spanning the entire portfolio, including avionics, propulsion, the connected aircraft and emerging urban air mobility solutions.
	- Key technologies enabling cleaner, safer and more productive air travel, from airport to airplane.
	- A panel optimizing the connectivity experience for Business Aviation.
	- A virtual tour of products available today straight from the Honeywell hangar.





RESERVE YOUR SPOT NOW &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/tech-forum?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=hon-corp_techforum2020&amp;utm_content=aero]]&gt;







{{my.Add to Calendar:default=MARK YOUR CALENDAR FOR THE OPENING SESSION}}

© {{my.year}} Honeywell International Inc.   
This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=NA}}. If you don&apos;t want to receive these emails from Honeywell in the future, you can unsubscribe &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Email_Confirmation_OptOut.html]]&gt;.
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/contact]]&gt;
   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;     &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;     &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt; 
     &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
