<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>July 2017 Edition.July 2017 Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - July 2017 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
July 2017
PRIMUS ELITE DU-875 UPGRADE INCENTIVES AVAILABLE NOW
Primus Elite® is a unique and specifically developed LCD for CRT form/fit display upgrade providing improved safety, more efficient operations, and increased aircraft value - and upgrade incentives are available...





  LEARN MORE       &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/July-2017-Edition_DU-875-Landing-Page.html]]&gt;
Fast, Reliable Wi-Fi Here Today for G-IV Operators
Gulfstream IV operators can give their passengers the best Wi-Fi experience in the sky thanks to Honeywell channel partner StandardAero...

Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/june/fast-reliable-wi-fi-here-today-for-g-iv-operators]]&gt;.
Checkout Honeywell&apos;s JetWave at CBAA 2017 at Tradex in Abbotsford, BC, Canada
Honeywell is attending the upcoming CBAA, Booth #239, in Abbotsford. Also visit our F900 on the ramp and see JetWave Ka Satcom demonstrations all day, both days. Don’t miss your chance to see the latest in satcom technology firsthand!...
Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/jetwave-high-speed-satellite-communications-hardware]]&gt;.
Honeywell’s Flight Technical Services Team Presents the Jeppesen eChart Update Webinar


Please join us Friday, August 11, 2017 at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Daylight Time, 9:00 a.m. in Arizona and 12:00 p.m. Eastern Daylight Time for a short webinar that will provide an overview on some new eChart features such as Night Mode, Enhanced SIDs and STARs. Learn more and Register &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/eChartsWebinar.html]]&gt;
TAE Gives TPE331 Operators New Service &amp; Repair Option in North America North American TPE331 operators can now look “down under” for quality maintenance, repair and overhaul services for their engines in the U.S... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/june/tae-gives-tpe331-operators-new-service-and-repair-option-in-north-america]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
