<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_Primus_Elite_Advanced _Features_Relaunch.2019_F900_PE_SVS_Email_V2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Get Primus Elite SVS - A 3-D View and Save $30,000!</subject>
    <textOnly>Blue-over-brown. Two-dimensional. Traditional. Perfectly functional on a bright, clear day, but more challenging at night and during IFR conditions. 

 But, wouldn’t you rather see as you fly it – in color and in three dimensions? 

 Now you can!
Honeywell’s Primus Elite® upgrade now includes Synthetic Vision (SVS) and is certified for your F900EX/C. 

 Primus Elite SVS adds entirely new levels of sophistication and safety enhancements to your cockpit. SVS realistically depicts your flight path as an easy-to-understand overlay on the primary flight display, just as it would appear out the cockpit windscreen. In three dimensions, and in color – no more blue-over-brown! 

 The upgrade provides benefits and features you’ll find in the most sophisticated cockpits in operation today, including: 



	- Head up display symbology helps the crew intuitively understand where the aircraft is going
	- The Flight Path Symbol makes it easier for the pilot to directly and accurately control the aircraft&apos;s flight path without having to guess at the proper pitch attitude to maintain
	- Terrain and obstacle display enhances the pilot’s situational awareness
	- Runway markings – centerline, runway numbering and distance remaining markers present a realistic airport environment
	- Approach charts for graphical depiction of aircraft position during approach
	- Optional XM® weather for real-time weather updates
	- And more!


To make your upgrade even more valuable, Honeywell is offering incentives of more than $30,000 on our Maintenance Service Plan – Avionics when you upgrade with Primus Elite: 



	- First year of coverage is free – a $30,000 savings!
	- Receive $10,000 off regular contract price during second and third year
	- Fixed 3% escalation offered on multi-year agreements


It is no accident (pun intended) that Primus Elite Synthetic Vision has firmly established itself as one of the best safety features your business jet can have.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_Primus_Elite_SVS_Landing_Page.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
