<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018_07_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Buelow_July_2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Hello, it’s Rob again with some news from Honeywell that can help you with your everyday activities. This information will help you get the most out of our products and services. I’m here to assist you with whatever you need, so please don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance.
Did You Know?

Honeywell adds additional Customer Support Managers to better serve operators

Based on feedback received from customers, Customer 
&amp; Product Support is realigning our Customer Support Manager (CSM) assignments in the Americas region...Read more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_07_CPS_CSM_Emails_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;

Honeywell&apos;s Field Service Engineer is available at your location

Honeywell has more than 200 Field Service Engineers (FSE) around the world to help our customers quickly and efficiently resolve any issues they may encounter. Your local FSE is available to meet with you personally in your hangar to assist you...Read More. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_CPS_Programs_2018_CPS_LandingPage.html]]&gt;

Field service engineer jumps in to serve customers

In a previous life, Mitch Eldridge was a U.S. Navy Search and Rescue Swimmer, trained to jump out of helicopters to save downed seamen and others in peril. Today, as a Senior Field Support Engineer, he jumps in with both feet to solve problems for customers... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/july/field-support-engineer-jumps-in-to-serve-customers]]&gt;

Embraer and Honeywell work together to 
simplify upgrade process
The Primus Elite Advanced Features (PEAF) upgrade, like most aircraft upgrades, is challenging for operators because of the complexities involved. Embraer and Honeywell customer and product support personnel worked together to develop a program for PEAF upgrades...Read more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_07_CPS_CSM_Emails_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;

Upcoming Operators Conferences
Operators Conferences are being scheduled in all 
regions - join us to learn more about Honeywell products and services that are critical to your flight department. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/january/2018-operator-conferences]]&gt;
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Rob L. Buelow
Customer Service Manager
Office: 480-592-5860
Mobile: 480-619-1953 
Email: Rob.Buelow@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Rob.Buelow@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
