<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Feb_MC.202002_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Feb_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>BK Dealer Newsletter Feb 2020 - New Look and Format</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Dealer Newsletter - Feb 
2020

NEWS BRIEFS

ORDERING PROCESS FOR AEROCRUZE 100 AND XCRUZE 100/110
All orders by dealers for AeroCruze 100 and xCruze 100/110 will no longer be fulfilled by TruTrak Inc. 
Starting immediately, please place your orders to the appropriate distributor:



	- U.S &amp; Canada



	- AeroCruze 100 (PMA Vizion): Aviall
	- xCruze 100 (Vizion), xCruze 110 (Gemini): Edmo



	- Remaining regions, order through your local distributor.


For questions or issues obtaining product, please contact your area sales manager or sales@bendixking.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@bendixking.com]]&gt;

AERONAV WAAS GPS ANTENNA
When ordering any AeroNav system, should your installation require a GPS/WAAS antenna, please order PN AV0801. Contact your local ASM &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/o02VZ00m300M0Q000XIG0q0]]&gt; for details.

AEROVUE B200 RECEIVES EASA CERT
AeroVue achieves EASA STC for the KingAir B200. Contact your local ASM &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; for details. 

AEROCRUZE 230 AML LIST UPDATED 
We’ve updated the AeroCruze 230 AML list; HERE &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/downloads/KFC_230_AeroCruze_AFCS_AML_STC_Document_Rev_C.pdf]]&gt; is the latest version

AEROCORDER FDR/CVR INTRODUCED
Lightest and smallest data recorder available, with low power consumption. Introducing the AeroCorder FDR/CVR. Read more about this product below, and download the brochure &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/~/media/bendixking/files/n61-2361-000-000_aerocorder100_fdr-bro.pdf]]&gt;. 
 
   
CUSTOMER WEBINARS 
Wed, Feb 12, 2020 8pm EST 
Privacy in the Age 
of ADS-B
Where does your data go, who has access to it - and how can you protect your privacy?
In case you weren’t able to attend, we will be sending the link to the recording in the next newsletter. 

SALES BULLETINS
2020BK-01 Over The Counter (OTC) Equipment Sales

2020BK-02 AeroCruze 230 Autopilot

2020BK-03 MST 67A (Trade-in Rebate) Upgrade to MST 70B 

2020BK-04 Dealer Demonstration Equipment Promotion

Detailed list of BK Sales Bulletins &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ0020q0ZZpuhX40qLI00OG]]&gt;
Find your nearest BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/K00q4QI00qhQ2rGuZ0LZ0X0]]&gt;

SIGN UP FOR DEALER NEWSLETTER
Were you forwarded this newsletter? Contact Lamonte &lt;[[mailto:lamonte.macon@honeywell.com?subject=Please%20opt%20me%20in%20for%20the%20BK%20Dealer%20Newsletter]]&gt; to get on our Dealer Newsletter list.



PRODUCT FEATURE


INTRODUCING AEROCORDER FLIGHT/COCKPIT DATA RECORDER 
AeroCorder 100 offers a rugged enclosure, small size, lower weight, and less power consumption than traditional FDRs in a modular and flexible architecture. The additional acquisition module converts the AeroCorder into a Data Acquisition and Crash Recorder System, making this ideal for FOQA and SMS data collection. Designed and spec’d for airborne operational commercial and military environments for fixed-wing and rotary aircraft. PRODUCT PAGE &gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocorder-fdr-cvr]]&gt;




TECH SUPPORT UPDATES


NETWORK ALERT: REPAIR VENDORS OLATHE UPDATE 
BendixKing has begun working more closely with its Repair Partners in the US to repair our parts that our customers send in to our Olathe facility. Repairs sent into the Olathe facility will likely see a tag issued by Duncan Aviation or Mid-Continent Instruments, with other partners to follow. Our Repair Partners have demonstrated a commitment to quality that presents a great value to both our customers and BendixKing. As always, you are welcome to reach out to these partners directly to have your BendixKing items repaired. FIND YOUR REPAIR PARTNER &gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/repair-partners]]&gt;




SHOWS &amp; EVENTS


JANUARY 2020 
BendixKing attended HAI Heli-Expo on January 28-30 in Anaheim, California. We were co-located with Airwork (NZ) who are developing the STC for HeliVue. The HeliVue upgrade is a complete turnkey solution for AS 350 operators when it comes to upgrading. It’s fully scalable and centered around the AeroVue Touch and AeroNav products, along with custom fabrication.

FEBRUARY 2020 NW Aviation &lt;[[http://www.washington-aviation.org/NAC&amp;TS.html]]&gt; in Puyallup, WA  |  February 22-23  |  Booth #627

MARCH 2020 AEA Annual Convention &lt;[[http://aea.net/convention/2020/]]&gt; in Nashville, TN  |  March 24-27  |  Booth #223
We’re looking forward to seeing you 
at the AEA annual convention. We’ll have a full line of updated product solutions on display, such as the new HeliVue, as well as these training sessions:

Wednesday, March 25
8:30am – 9:30 a.m. Room: Cheekwood B
Detailed walk-through on AeroCruze 100 &amp; 230 autopilots. We&apos;ll go over insights, installation, ordering and tips and tricks for the AeroCruze 100 and AeroCruze 230 autopilots.
Presenters: Roger Dykmann / Andrew Barker

Thursday, March 26
8:30 a.m. - 10:30 a.m. Room: Cheekwood B 
AeroVue Touch, AeroWave 100 and AeroCorder. The first half of this session will focus on AeroVue Touch. The second half of this session will focus on AeroWave 100 and AeroCorder.
Presenter: Valerie Archuleta / Roger Dykmann

SAVE THE DATE!  Wednesday, March 25th, 8:00pm - Midnight  We are cohosting the must attend Renegades party.  Look for invitation to follow!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
