<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20191023_Global_Email_Greer_KFK.20191023_Global_Email_Greer_KFK</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Update Your System to Order Engine Static Component Repairs</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer,
Honeywell continually looks for ways to better serve customers more efficiently and cost-effectively. In November 2018, Honeywell announced the decision to relocate all engine repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) operations at our facility in Greer, South Carolina, to our facility in Phoenix, Arizona.  

 Honeywell remains committed to our engine product lines. We plan to continue to support repair and overhaul of the T55-GA-714, 55-L-714, LTS101 and ALF502/LF507 engine product lines for many years to come. 
 
 A review of past orders indicates that you have previously placed production or repair orders for an impacted part number. 
What is the effective date?
Effective immediately static component repair orders should be placed with our Honeywell site in Phoenix. See the site details provided below. 

What is moving now? 
This impacted part number list &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Greer- Final Move Rotating Part Number and Platform.xlsx]]&gt; represents R&amp;O services for static component repairs.

Is this the final move?
Yes, this is the final move and represents the last set of repair operations to move out of the Greer location.
 
What do I need to know about repair order processing? 
To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions.
 
      Existing Repair Orders:


	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already inducted at the Greer site. 
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification. 
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity. 


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.




       New Repair Orders:


	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to Phoenix, AZ.  
	- Parts received on or before October 23, 2019 will be accepted at Greer, but transferred to Phoenix for the actual repair.
	- Parts that are currently in transit and received after October 23, 2019 will be transferred to Phoenix for repair. 
	- Repair orders will need to reflect the Honeywell Sky Harbor address as the place of repair performance.


	- Your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate this activity. 


	- The Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs.


       Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems

        Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include
        the new supplier information for these parts.





Company Name
Honeywell Aerospace


Address
1944 E Sky Harbor Circle


City, State
Phoenix, Arizona


Postal Code
85034


Country
United States






What has already moved?


	- Engine Repair Orders: Instructions on submitting engine level repairs have been previously communicated. This data is now available on the Repair Site Capability List on the Honeywell Aerospace &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt; website.
	- LTS101 engine repairs will be serviced by our channel partners, Intermountain Turbine Services and Airwork NZ.
	- T55-GA-714 and 55-L-714 engines will be serviced by our Honeywell Sky Harbor site at the address listed above.
	- R&amp;O Services for rotating components and parts that require outside processing.


What is not impacted? 


	- There is no impact to Honeywell’s Original Equipment (OE) production operations.
	- AOG Support


	- Our dedicated support service teams are available to assist you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week worldwide.
	- Make sure you have the required AOG information ready when calling.
	- Information needed: aircraft make, model &amp; serial number, aircraft tail/registration number, operator/end-user name &amp; address, location of ground aircraft, next scheduled Flight/Minimum Equipment List (MEL) expiration, any additional details regarding the aircraft&apos;s current situation.
	- United States or Canada, call 1-800-601-3099
	- International customers, call 1-602-365-3099




If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell representative. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 
Honeywell Aerospace
Customer and Product Support

Visit Honeywell Aerospace &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt;


  &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/n0Qh0VU02dZq0XI0BD00Gmj]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
