<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Cross SBU.Tango Transition Update Customer Letter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace-Mississauga Site Transitions to Celestica</subject>
    <textOnly>March 6, 2015
 

Dear Customer,  


Last year, we shared news that Honeywell was shifting manufacturing and aftermarket production
work from Aerospace-Mississauga to Celestica. Here is an update on our progress.

The transition is on schedule and will be completed by April 2015. As part of the transition,
 the Mississauga site will also migrate to SAP - an enterprise resource planning and
 communications system.  

Past experience has proven that the best way to minimize order disruptions or escapes during the
 changeover is to designate a &quot;freeze&quot; period for outbound shipments and incoming orders.
 
 Here are the dates of the software upgrade - and details on how this could affect you: 



 - Starting March 26th at 4pm (Eastern Daylight Time) through April 13th, Honeywell will be
unable to receive new orders or process existing orders. Orders received during this time
 will be placed in a queue for processing after April 13th. 






 - Orders received between March 1st and April 30th may experience up to a two-week turn 
around delay. 






 - During this time, we will continue to manually process orders for AOGs. Our contact numbers
 are:
 1-800-601-3099 US/Canada
 1-602-365-3099 International
 00800-601-30999 International Land Line Toll Free 





 - The Estimated Ship Date (ESD) function in the myaerospace.com customer portal will not
 operate during this time, and will not reflect updated shipping data until the migration
 is complete.     



Following the transition, Honeywell will continue as the design and manufacturing authority over all
 impacted parts. However, the Manufacturing Repair &amp; Overhaul functions will now be performed by
 our service provider, Celestica, under the supervision of Honeywell. 

To support this transition, certain customer information will of necessity be shared with Celestica,
 including but not limited to purchase orders, contract requirements and detail available via direct
 access to our customer portals.  Honeywell and Celestica have signed a Non-disclosure agreement
 and take necessary steps to ensure continued protection and confidentiality of your data.       


Above everything else, we are committed to making this a smooth transition for you and your
business. Your Honeywell contacts remain the same, and we&apos;ll continue to provide you outstanding
customer and product support.

If you have any questions or concerns during this shutdown period, please send an email to
customerservicescommunications@honeywell.com &lt;mailto:customerservicescommunications@honeywell.com&gt;

Best Regards,

 Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
