<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_BK_Dealer_Email_With_Overview_Video_Links_MC.202004_BK_Dealer_Email_With_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing BendixKing&apos;s new product overview video series</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
To our Dealer Network, 
 
 Introducing the BendixKing Overview video series. These short-format videos provide you and your customers four minutes of all the pertinent information about our latest offerings, from features to functionality and pricing. The links can be forwarded to your customers but are also a great primer for your new avionics’ technicians and sales team members. 
 
 We will be adding more videos in the coming weeks to this list and expanding the subjects to include how to use the Aerospace portal, tips on ordering parts and more. 
 
 AeroCruze 100 affordable autopilots: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS]]&gt;
 
 AeroFlight / KI 300 attitude indicator and KA 310 autopilot adapter:
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8 &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8]]&gt;
 
 AeroNav 900 GPS navigation series: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM]]&gt; 
 
 AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W]]&gt;
 
 HeliVue Touch touchscreen PFD/MFD for helicopters: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA]]&gt;
 
 Where to find these links other than this email:


	- Dealer Newsletter – new section has been created with list/links updated monthly
	- BendixKing Dealer Portal – new section has been created with entire list/links available 24/7


If you have a suggestion for a topic or wish to provide feedback on any of these videos, please reach out to your sales manager directly, or locate your sales manager here &lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;.
 
 Thank you for being part of the BendixKing family. Stay safe and healthy. 
 
 BendixKing</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
