<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Global_ATR_Email_Q1-Newsletter.Internal Send</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Quarterly Airline Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt;    |    Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;    |    View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;  Forward to a friend &lt;[[{{system.forwardToFriendLink}}]]&gt;


Happy New Year! In our second edition of the Honeywell Aerospace Airline Newsletter, we cover the recently announced UV Treatment System and CHOC 4 Combined Hydrocarbon Ozone Catalyst, new MyAerospace Portal announcements, and information about upcoming events &amp; webinars.
New UV Treatment System


 


Portable ultraviolet-c light (UVC) system designed to reduce various viruses and bacteria on targeted surfaces within passenger transportation systems. Click here &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/94TXjpXPGsMWUV1kQB3Nz7?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;, to watch it in action!


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-treatment-system?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;
Customer Support Updates


 



We have created reliability presentations for all significant issues that are updated every 30 days on the investigation&apos;s status, root cause analysis, solutions, and schedule. You can access and download these from the Technical Support &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services-and-support/support-center/technical-support?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt; page. In 2021, we are driving a further 50% reduction in the cycle time it takes to get solutions to market on the Top 10 issues under investigation. This initiative has support at the Honeywell CEO level. If you would like to learn more about this initiative, please reach out to your Honeywell Field Service Engineer.  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/field-service-engineers-americas?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;



 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services-and-support/support-center/technical-support?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;
Online Ordering and Spares Quote Status have been combined


 


In order to make the Spares Quoting process simpler, from finding a part to quote, to acting on that quote and ordering the part, Honeywell has moved the Quote Status functionality within our Online Ordering application.


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes/2020/quote-status-online-ordering?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;
Join our MyAerospace Portal User Forum and be the first to test new functionality on our portal.


 






Sign Up &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/NYHXC7Q]]&gt;
Fresher Cabin Air 
with CHOC4


 


This catalyst is an aftermarket upgrade for ozone converters and can significantly reduce odors from bleed air, ensuring cleaner cabin airflow for safer, more reliable operations.


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/air-and-thermal-systems/combined-hydrocarbon-ozone-catalyst?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;
737MAX Return to Service Information


 


Honeywell is pleased to see the 737MAX back in revenue service and to see that Boeing has begun delivering new 737MAX airplanes to operators in the Americas. To ensure we provide 737MAX operators with the best support possible during aircraft re-entry, we’ve assigned focals from our Aerospace Technical Support organization to each airline to work closely on your return to service plan and answer any questions you have.


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/737max?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter]]&gt;
Our Blockchain Dot Finally Found its Friend


 


Honeywell integrates the GoDirect Trade &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt; marketplace to Blockchain quality document data which bypasses the need to upload quality documents. With $1B in excess inventory loaded in the month of December (~25,000 listings), this saves over 365 full workdays of downloading / re-uploading quality paperwork!




 






Learn more &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/blog/post/dots/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;






 








 




 





 


 






Join Us at the 2021 MRO Americas Event!


 


With 2020 in the rearview mirror, planning is underway for MRO Americas 2021 and a return to live events this year in Orlando, Florida. Starting April 27th - 29th  the event represents the perfect platform to connect with 5 attendees and develop your business in this lucrative sector. Suppliers and more!

Click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/events?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt; to see our 2021 event schedule.



 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/events]]&gt;
Honeywell, Sichuan Airlines Inc. Historic Deal on Auxiliary Power Units


 


As part of a five-year agreement, Sichuan Airlines has selected the 131-9A APU for its 93 new A320 aircraft that will enter service by 2025.


 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2021/01/honeywell-sichuan-historic-deal-apu?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_airline_newsletter&amp;utm_content=newsletter-january]]&gt;
In Other News…


 


Honeywell has selected Piedmont Aviation &lt;[[https://piedmont.tat-technologies.com/]]&gt; Component Services, LLC, located in Greensboro, North Carolina, USA to be an exclusive 331-500 APU Rental Provider for Honeywell customers on MSA, NTE and other repair contracts. As part of this 10-year agreement, Piedmont acquired all of 331-500 rental APUs in the Honeywell Engine Rental Bank, and will own, manage and rent the APUs to Honeywell customers and other operators. 

Honeywell signed a ten-year agreement with AAR, a leading provider of aviation services and channel partner, to be the sole channel partner licensee for component repair and overhaul services for the OEM’s suite of Electronic Bleed Air Systems (EBAS) covering 15 components on the B737 MAX aircraft
While you are here, why not take a moment to opt-in &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;. We want to be sure you don’t miss out on the latest news, industry insight and special offers from Honeywell.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;    


 


© 2021 Honeywell International Inc.  &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; 
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202


 


Subscription Preference &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt;  |  Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; |  Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; |  Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
