<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Email Project.TP Access Info Required - 2nd Request</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Request is Missing Info {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Tech Pubs Access: Response Required










 







Hello {!Contact.FirstName},

We’re anxious to start working on the {!Case.Subject} inquiry you asked us about. But we can’t until we hear from you.

Before we can start, we need the following information from you.

Signed US Export Compliance End User Certificate (Attachment)

Once you’ve sent us the certificate, we’ll get right to work processing your request. So help us speed the process by sending us the missing information today.

To do that, please reply to this email and include your signed certificate. Here’s your unique tracking number: {!Case.CaseNumber}. You can use this number to track our progress.
For Case Related Questions?


We’ll connect all of your inquiry details through the subject line of this email. So, when you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.


We’ll be on the lookout for your email.

Thanks again! We appreciate your business,
{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
 Honeywell Aerospace
 Technical Publications Team
 Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZ4X06jG0000H0bl20qXQn]]&gt;
 1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099
ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
 {!Case.Subject} 
 {!Case.Description} 
 {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}
This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
