<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201712_APAC_Email_BGANewsletter_mih.201712_APAC_Email_BGANewsletter_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell APAC Business Aviation Newsletter - December Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
APAC BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
December 2017
TAKE OFF
Honeywell Expands Connected Aircraft Support at New GoDirect Service Center   
 
New Connectivity Integration Lab within GoDirect Service Center provides around-the-clock technical support to keep business jets connected... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/september/honeywell-expands-connected-aircraft-support-at-new-godirect-service-center]]&gt;
Honeywell Enhances Customer Experience With New MyAerospace E-Commerce Website  
 
 Customer feedback helps build a more intuitive online experience that provides the industry’s best solution for managing aircraft repair and overhaul... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/october/honeywell-enhances-customer-experience-with-new-myaerospace-e-commerce-website]]&gt;
Honeywell Engines Reach More Than 225 Million Flight Hours  
 
Honeywell’s strong legacy in engine technology continues to evolve with its HTF7000, TFE731 and TPE331 engines... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/october/honeywell-engines-reach-more-than-225-million-flight-hours]]&gt;
Honeywell&apos;s Business Aviation Forecast Projects 8,300 Deliveries Valued at $249 Billion Through 2027 
 
 2018 deliveries are projected to be slightly higher than 2017, with low single-digit growth supported by new models’ entry into service...  Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/october/honeywell-s-business-aviation-forecast-projects-8-300-deliveries-valued-at-$249-billion-through-2027]]&gt;
Honeywell Launches UAV Industrial Inspection Service, Teams With Intel On Innovative Offering  
 
 New commercial UAV inspection service will be offered through a collaboration with Intel Corporation, helping infrastructure industries grow and serve customers faster in the digital age... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Upcoming Event 

 

 Maecenas sed ante pellentesque, posuere leo id, eleifend dolor. Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos... 
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
