<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Americas_StandardAero_JetwaveObjections_KCR.201903_Americas_StandardAero_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Don’t Let Your In-Flight Wi-Fi Service Costs Soar</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.standardaero.com/]]&gt;

Create a Great Passenger Experience without Breaking the Bank

Fast, reliable in-flight Wi-Fi was unimaginable just a few years ago. Now it’s a reality. But, as with any new technology, there’s a premium cost associated with sending emails, surfing the net, videoconferencing or live-streaming video at 30,000 feet. 

You want to manage data use, control costs and still offer passengers a great in-flight Wi-Fi experience. We know how. Honeywell’s GoDirect services and applications let you make the most of your investment in our JetWave satellite communications solution and Inmarsat’s Jet ConneX network. 

It all starts with GoDirect Connectivity Consultation. Our expert team of engineers works directly with you to choose software configurations and data plans tailored to your specific needs. With our help you can improve the speed, efficiency and cost-effectiveness of inflight Wi-Fi services without breaking the bank. 

GoDirect Data Control gives you the power to allocate data use on the aircraft and make sure that bandwidth is available for all onboard voice, network and data traffic. By controlling the data used by video-streaming and other heavy-bandwidth applications, you’ll be able to choose a less expensive data plan. 

GoDirect Filter helps you ensure that all of the data sent and received from your aircraft cabin is used productively, not for background updates and the like. You control the kinds of applications used on the airplane to make the most of the data you’re consuming and reduce delays caused by an overloaded network. 

Get the Wi-Fi you crave without breaking the bank. Contact StandardAero to learn more or request a quote.



LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/StandardAero_JetWave.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_stda_jw]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
