<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018_08_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails_RW.Azevedo_August_2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Hello, it’s Rafael again with some information that will help you get the most out of our products and services. I’m here to assist you with whatever you need, so please don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance.
Did You Know?

Honeywell extends maintenance intervals on TFE engines 

Honeywell recently announced an extension of 
TFE731-20/-40/-50/-60 engine intervals to maximize operators’ time on-wing... Read more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_08_CPS_CSM_Emails_RW_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;.

Global Customer Committee to meet in fall 2018

Honeywell’s Global Customer Committee regional advisory boards will 
meet this fall in Vienna, Phoenix and Hong Kong. We want to hear from you... Read More &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_08_CPS_CSM_Emails_RW_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;.


Pilatus PC-12 training videos now 
available 


Honeywell has released a series of maintenance 
training videos for troubleshooting the Honeywell APEX cockpit system. The training videos include informative system overviews and best practices for line maintenance work.
PC-12NG / KSG 7200 ADAHRS Diagnostic Tools-Usage &lt;[[https://youtu.be/5kGkVXp59pw]]&gt;
PC-12 CMC Aircraft Diagnostic and Maintenance Systems 1 of 2 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/IgMeb1i-uRA]]&gt;
PC-12 CMC Aircraft Diagnostic and Maintenance Systems 2 of 2 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/97mXmTgpdWI]]&gt;

Thank you for 
recognizing Honeywell&apos;s Customer Support Managers on the AIN Product Support Survey

It&apos;s an honor that you, our customers, recognized the passion and commitment we have in supporting you every day. Link to Above and Beyond: Product Support Survey 2018 &lt;[[https://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/business-aviation/2018-08-01/above-and-beyond-product-support-survey-2018]]&gt;, scroll down to Honeywell.

Upcoming Operators Conferences
Operators Conferences are being scheduled in all 
regions - join us to learn more about Honeywell products and services that are critical to your flight department. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/january/2018-operator-conferences]]&gt;
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Rafael Azevedo 
Gerente de Suporte ao Cliente, América do Sul 
Celular: + 55 12 99122-1600 
Email:  Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
