<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201912_Global_CH_ATR_Airline-Discount-Priced-Parts_amr.AT&amp;R Notification - Use o</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AT&amp;R Notification – Use of Discounted Net Priced Parts</subject>
    <textOnly>Date: November 30, 2019 

 Notice: AT&amp;R Notification – Use of Airline Net Priced Parts 

 Reference: 1. Honeywell International Inc. Conditions of Sale &amp; General Terms dated October 25, 2018 Rev. 4. 


 To Impacted Parties, 

As we near the end of the year, we wanted to send a reminder that also serves as notification regarding restrictions for using parts purchased at airline net pricing from Honeywell under our Honeywell Condition of Sale, which is available on aerospace.honeywell.com. As noted in the next paragraph, airlines aren’t permitted to sell those parts to any third party, nor provide service to third parties using those parts. 

 “In the event the Buyer receives airline net pricing from Honeywell, such purchases of Product at airline net pricing are for the exclusive use of Buyer and Buyer agrees said Products will not be (i) used in the overhaul or service of third party equipment, or (ii) sold, traded or otherwise transferred by Buyer to a third party without Honeywell’s prior written 
consent. Buyer hereby agrees to produce documents and allow for audits as reasonably required to ensure adherence to this section. Should violations to this section be found, Buyer agrees to pay liquidated damages for the unauthorized use, sale, transfer, or trade of Product in the aggregate amount of the difference between the price Buyer paid and Honeywell’s then-current price for such Product.” 

 Please ensure that all relevant people in your organization that may use these parts are aligned 
with our policy. Similarly, if parts are purchased at discounted pricing on Purchase Agreements, Product Support Agreements, or other agreements with discounted pricing, you are responsible to ensure those parts are utilized appropriately and are not distributed or used in services beyond the allowance provided for in your agreements. 

 Thank you for being a customer and helping us in this area.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
