<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_Global_Internal-Comms_Supplier-Concessions_Email_Operational.Email 1 - Su</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aerospace Partnership Response Requested</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Supplier}}, 

 The COVID-19 coronavirus pandemic has created an increasing number of hurdles which many businesses across the globe are encountering, resulting in new and dynamic economic pressures. As such, our customers have come to us for support to balance the impacts across their supply chain and we are asking our supply chain partners for similar support. 

 Your company has been recognized as a leading supplier of critical components and services in support of Honeywell platforms and product lines that are vital to our success. As we greatly value our business relationship, Honeywell is now asking that you partner with us in support of both of our companies’ long-term goals. 

 Effective immediately, we are asking our suppliers to provide combinations of the following to implement now: 



	- 30% across the board pricing reductions on unit costs
	- Extend pay terms by 60 days over current contractual terms
	- Immediate resolution of all outstanding claims per Honeywell’s requests


We understand that the ask can be difficult, but we also recognize that inaction will create a more challenging environment than what we are currently experiencing. Our ability to continue to serve our customers directly translates into growth and opportunities for your business. With acceptance of the above request, Honeywell will prioritize your company for future sourcing events that align with your capabilities so long as performance levels continue to meet our standards. 

 Please kindly respond directly to your Honeywell global commodity manager—with specific detail to the action requests stated above—by Monday, April 6, 2020, as Honeywell will amend all contracts and purchase orders by Friday, April 10, 2020. All existing purchase orders will be retroactively updated to the new accepted unit price position. 

 We greatly value your continued support and look forward to your response. 

 Sincerely,
 
 Honeywell Global Procurement and Sourcing Leadership Team 

 
Robert Vislosky, Chief Procurement Officer 

 Rick Bruno, Chief Procurement Officer, 
PMT
 Robert Buddecke, Chief Procurement Office, AERO
 Galen Chin, Chief Procurement officer, SPS 
Jeff Gajda, Chief Procurement Officer HBT</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
