<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201812_CPUseMyAerospace_lg.201812_CPUseMyAerospace_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Final Reminder:  Submit Electronic Orders</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Honeywell Partner, 
 
Honeywell channel partners are members of a carefully selected and outstanding group of partner companies chosen because of their unique market reach, bias for growth, and a strong record of performance, integrity and compliance. One of the compliance areas is utilization of electronic ordering for repair and overhaul orders. Using the MyAerospace portal allows Honeywell to provide faster repair turn times by reducing non-value added time.  

This is the third reminder that our policy requires using the MyAerospace portal to create repair and overhaul orders. Starting January 15, 2019, we will no longer accept orders which are not created electronically through MyAerospace or Electronic Data Interface (EDI).
 
To facilitate and enhance the communication, productivity and profitability of this network, we created a new Channel Partner Guidebook &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Documents/Channel Partners/Channel Partner Guidebook.pdf?la=en]]&gt;. This guidebook consolidates the latest information into a single source and is available on the MyAerospace Channel Partner Resource Center.  &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/channel-partners]]&gt;
 
What do I need to know about the policy? 


	- This is not a new policy.
	- Section 2 of Honeywell’s repair and overhaul terms and conditions &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/terms-and-conditions-filtered#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending]]&gt; states that we reserve the right to reject, and will have no liability for, orders which were not entered through the MyAerospace portal or EDI.  
	- Honeywell has previously advised your company of this policy. 


 What must I do differently?


	- Create all repair orders in MyAerospace prior to shipping the hardware. Failure to create an electronic order will result in hardware being held at receiving.
	- Print the repair order sheet (found on the order confirmation page) and send it with the unit.


What are the benefits?  


	- Creating repair orders electronically facilitates a timely and seamless flow into the repair cycle.
	- Your repair order will already be waiting in our system for receiving your hardware, ensuring no disruption into our repair cycle.
	- Order documentation is created directly from your inputs, eliminating holds and delays.
	- Receive immediate confirmation that the order has been placed.


 How do I create a repair order in MyAerospace?


	- Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZhA0n5G0000C02020qXQB]]&gt; to access Online Ordering to place your order.
	- Use Order Status &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/order-status/!ut/p/b1/04_SjzS0NLQwMzI0NzbQj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQwMXI1cDDzDzIyNLTzNDA0sjIEKIoEKDHAARwNC-r30o9Jz8pOAVoXrR4EV4zHLzyM_N1U_NyrHIlvXUREAg1-eQg!!/dl4/d5/L2dBISEvZ0FBIS9nQSEh/pw/Z7_UM5L8F5400E2D0IV6338I610O3/act/id=X65IZUmetPA/p=action=showSearch/397315615062/-/]]&gt; to monitor your order.
	- View training videos and additional resources &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20ascending]]&gt;, including this short video &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Video%20Tutorials/Online%20Ordering%20Update.mp4]]&gt; about ordering online.


Do you have a question about your order?  


	- Use MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZhA0n5G0000C02020qXQB]]&gt; to ask questions about your order so we can quickly direct it to the right person. 
	- Log into MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZhA0n5G0000C02020qXQB]]&gt;, navigate to Order Status, search for your order, then click on ‘Contact Us’.


How do I learn more about Electronic Date Interface? 


	- Honeywell has partnered with Aeroxchange &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Fn2Iq00270Q0A2BC000XGZh]]&gt;, an aviation supply chain solutions company, to provide a solution that automates the exchange of documents and information for commercial transactions.
	- As a Honeywell channel partner, we recommend implementing EDI with high volume customers.
	- Contact your Honeywell Customer Support Manager to get more information. 


Thank you for your business and continued support.


Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
