<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>NorcrossSAP_13SEpt2017.NorcrossSAP_13Sept2017</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Information About Honeywell&apos;s Norcross, GA Facility</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Honeywell Customer, 
 
Honeywell Aerospace is in the process of implementing our enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, SAP, across all our facilities. This globally-integrated business platform will allow us to provide greater speed, accuracy, and consistency in meeting your needs. In addition, it allows our sites to integrate into the order and repair management applications available on the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;. This is great news for you – allowing you to track order status and order repairs on-line anytime. 



Our Norcross, GA site (supporting EMS Technologies) will implement SAP on October 9th, 2017. While we are committed to making this process as seamless as possible for you, the following details will help you plan your orders and repairs:


	- The site will start transitioning on October 2nd. During this transition, we will move data to the new system and verify system functionality. To create a static data environment, we will need to stop shipments on September 30th, resuming again on October 9th.   
	- In many cases, we have pre-built product to fulfill specific customer requirements. 
	- Where previously arranged, we will ship these products before September 30th. 
	- Units that arrive at the Norcross site during this transition period will be held in receiving inspection to be inducted post-transition. 


We have been working for several months to facilitate a successful ERP transition. If we need to accommodate a critical shipment, such as to support an aircraft-on-ground, we have created a plan to continue to meet that need until our new system is operational. 
 
Once we are on the new system, you will see some—largely cosmetic—paperwork changes. These create a consistent standard message across Honeywell - EMS Technologies. It should not impact the way you work with our site. Please contact your contract or program representative if you have any questions about the new paperwork.
 
In addition to now being able to order your repairs directly from MyAerospace, Honeywell is simplifying our repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) pricing; transitioning from time and material quotations to published universal flat rates (UFRs). This pricing policy enhancement streamlines the repair process and helps you better predict, manage and budget your R&amp;O expenses. We’ve included all the resources you need for MyAerospace Portal training here &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20ascending]]&gt;. 
 
These universal flat rates were calculated using your current discounted repair pricing as the baseline. Thus, we expect very little impact to average repair prices you are currently paying. Moreover, we will hold your UFR pricing flat through 2018. Using UFRs will also simplify and shorten your purchasing process by eliminating excessive requests for quotes, waiting for pricing confirmation, and extra administrative tasks. The expectation is that lead times for pricing and repair turn-around times will be significantly reduced.   


Specifically, these details will help you transition to the new structure: 


	- Once Honeywell receives your funded purchase order (PO) at the published UFR price, we automatically proceed with the requested work scope and will send the unit back to you immediately after completion with the service report attached. No additional customer effort required.
	- The purchase order funding must match the requested work scope (funded PO). 
	- You will still receive an automated message from Honeywell if you have not funded your PO with the correct UFR for the requested work scope. The email will contain the following content: “In order to proceed with induction of your unit, we kindly ask you to provide an amended PO funded with Universal Flat Rate.”
	- To ensure best delivery performance, please respond with any requested PO amendments within 5 days. If no response is received within 5 days a minimum return-as-is/evaluation fee may be assessed and the unit may be returned uncertified.


This change does not impact our current processes regarding how we determine if a part is covered under UFR or how we handle those parts. Flat rate covers minor modifications, ORIs and service bulletins which do not require a change of material number. These will be incorporated without extra charges above the flat rate. 
 
Please share this communication and future information with others in your organization. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact your regular Honeywell - EMS Technologies customer service representative or your Customer Business Manager.
 
We are committed to providing you with world-class support. Thank you for your patience as we work to enhance the way we do business with you. 


Thank you and best regards,
 
George Assoian
Site Director
Honeywell Aerospace
EMS Technologies - Norcross
Thank you for your business,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
