<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_07_July.2019_July_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Biz Av News - Honeywell Deals!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
July 2019
THREE REASONS WHY MAINTENANCE SERVICE PLANS MAKE SENSE
Honeywell offers three customizable maintenance options designed to make it easy for you to control the unexpected... 





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/maintenance-service-plan-business-aviation]]&gt;
Save with Honeywell&apos;s Primus Elite with Synthetic Vision upgrade bundleWe are offering terrific savings when you purchase Primus Elite Enhanced Features and Primus Elite Advanced Features with Synthetic Vision package. And you have the option on including SmartRunway and SmartLanding at a 50 percent discount.
Savings details for Falcon 900EX/C operators &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_Primus_Elite_Advanced_Features_Relaunch_2019_Landing_Page.html]]&gt;
Savings details for Global Express operators &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_Primus_Elite_Advanced_Features_Relaunch_2019_GEX_Primus_Elite_LP.html]]&gt;
Savings details for Legacy 600 operators &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_Primus_Elite_Advanced_Features_Relaunch_2019_L600_Primus_Elite_LP.html]]&gt;
Hawker 800/1000 Operators - Discount Package Pricing on ADS-B &amp; FMS 6.1
Honeywell has a special discount pricing in effect when you combine ADS-B Out and FMS 6.1 upgrades. The package includes an ADS-B capable RM-855 exchange unit for either existing RM-855 or RM-850 Radio Management Units, and an ADS-B capable RCZ Communications Radio Unit exchange for existing RCZ unit. The FMS 6.1 software upgrade provides access to the latest approaches and increased efficiency in the cockpit. Contact your preferred Honeywell Authorized Service Center for a complete price quote.
Field Service Engineer has physically laid hands on every single mechanical part in the HTF7000 engine

Michael Cox knows the HTF7000 turbofan engine like the back of his hand. He spent more than a dozen years as a member of the HTF7000 engineering team... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/july/field-service-engineer-puts-htf7000-experience-on-the-line?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTWpjeU1HUTBNMlJrTjJGaiIsInQiOiJFN0JTeVk2QTEwUG00SnpvUmRLZjJ2NXk2MlBjOUpIdGtLY2s3UnVwMjkzSE0yeEVhdnVIQmlLR2duT3Y2Tk9tenBPVFYrcjB0SEF0UmpzVVNIZXNcL3c9PSJ9]]&gt;.
Why you need better cabin technology
Business jet 
passengers have high expectations these days. If you’re an aircraft owner or operator, you need to offer more than a comfortable seat, good food and the right beverage selection. You need to provide a “third place,” away from home and office... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/july/three-reasons-you-need-better-cabin-technology]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
