<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_C&amp;PS_Wellington-Wiper_Email_Operational.Wellington Wiper Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Upcoming Changes To Honeywell’s Aerospace Wiper Business</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

In March 2020, Honeywell advised of the exclusive perpetual licensing agreement for our wiper business to Ontic Engineering and Manufacturing, Inc. (Ontic). The transition teams are engaged and details for the transition has been finalized into an overall project plan. As a reminder, the wiper products affected by this transition include: View Wiper Product Line Part Numbers. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Wiper Part Numbers.xlsx]]&gt; 

Customers were asked to establish Ontic on 
their approved source list for the impacted part numbers. The information to update the Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal customer systems is also provided below. 

 ASL Information: 

Company Name:               Ontic 
Engineering and Manufacturing, Inc.
 Address:                            1176 Telecom Drive 
 City, State: 
                        Creedmoor, North Carolina 
 Postal Code: 
                     27522 
 Country: 
                            USA 
 Cage Code: 
                      8G4X8 
 DUNS Number:                 11 736 2367 
 Contact Name:                  Derek Ashcroft 
 Contact Email Address:     dashcroft@Ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:dashcroft@Ontic.com]]&gt;
 Desk Phone:                      919-956-4390 
 Mobile Phone:                    919-337-5950 

Contact List






Area
Name
Email Address
Phone




1) Quotes &amp; Orders: Spares or Repairs
2) Order Status
3) General
4) AOG

Neal McKinnon
nmckinnon@Ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:nmckinnon@Ontic.com]]&gt; 


919-956-4212



5) Escalations
Brittany Moore
bmoore@Ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:bmoore@Ontic.com]]&gt;
Desk: 919-956-4213 
Mobile: 919-603-8264 


6) Technical Questions and Documents
Neal McKinnon &amp;
Carldetta LeMay
nmckinnon@Ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:nmckinnon@Ontic.com]]&gt;
clemay@Ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:clemay@Ontic.com]]&gt;
919-956-4324




Schedule






Description
Honeywell: Last Receipt Date
Ontic: Start Date




Repairs: Hardware/Orders


June 5, 2020
August 3, 2020


Spare Part Orders
June 30, 2020
July 1, 2020


Technical Ops/Tech Pubs
June 30, 2020
July 1, 2020


AOG
June 30, 2020
July 1, 2020





To minimize issues or delays with the repair of hardware, customers should follow these guidelines and actions: 

 REPAIR ORDER PROCESSING &amp; SHIPMENTS 

 Existing Repair Orders 
 



	- June 5, 2020: Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders received on site at Urbana, Ohio.
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a purchase order or contract modification due to change in place of performance. 
	- After June 5, 2020: Honeywell will work with Ontic to transfer both the administration, and repair of orders received on site after this date.


	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact the customer to advise and coordinate this administrative/contract activity. 
	- Watch for PO/contract modification correspondence on these orders.




New Repair Orders  



	- After June 5, 2020: Due to turn-around-time constraints in the repair process, Honeywell will not be able to fulfill repairs orders received after June 5, 2020 before the cutover to Ontic on July 1, 2020.
	- After June 5, 2020: Orders are to be sent to Ontic Engineering. 
	- To enable repair support during the June/July time frame, we are advising Customers to consider the following when planning. 


	- Typical repair turn times will expand by approximately 4-8 weeks as Honeywell and Ontic physically relocate the manufacturing and repair lines. 
	- Honeywell is providing some buffer stock to cover customer demand during this transition period. 
	- Honeywell repairable exchange asset stock availability will determine turn times. 
	- Now: Eliminate/minimize this additional turn time: 


	- Send repairs to Honeywell before June 5, 2020 to ensure completion before the line transfer. 
	- Review your routable stock levels to determine if you have sufficient stock to meet demand during the cutover period. 


	- After June 5, 2020: Ensure that new repair orders are sent to Ontic. 


	- MyAerospace Repair Site Capability List &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send repairs.


Ontic Repair Capabilities  



	- By August 3, 2020: Ontic expects to have repair and overhaul capability established per FAA and EASA guidelines


SPARE PART ORDERS

 Existing Spares Orders 



	- In case of stock unavailability, the Honeywell Customer Business Manager will contact you to cancel the order and ask that the order be placed directly with Ontic Engineering.


New Spares Orders  



	- After June 30, 2020, Honeywell will no longer accept new spares orders.
	- To minimize delays to your order requirements, ensure that new spares orders are sent to Ontic Engineering at the address provided above.


TECHNICAL OPERATIONS &amp; PUBLICATIONS 

After June 30, 2020: Technical Documentation and questions shall be submitted to Ontic’s customer service representative (CSR) noted above who will obtain answers from the appropriate technical focal.

 AOG SUPPORT

 After June 30, 2020: AOG Support questions shall be submitted to Ontic’s customer service representative (CSR) noted above who will obtain answers from the appropriate business function(s).

 If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact.

 Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace
 
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
