<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Nov-Dec 2018 Edition.Nov-Dec 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - Nov-Dec 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
November - December 2018
MSP OFFERS REBATES
FOR PREFERRED ENGINE OPERATION
Honeywell will pay you for taking it easy on your engine. We are changing our signature Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) to what is believed to be the business aviation industry’s first usage-based protection program...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2018/november/msp-offers-rebates-for-preferred-engine-operation]]&gt;
Field Service Engineer Larry Lindsey has customer support in his blood 

&quot;If you take care of the customer, everything else will take care of itself&quot;... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/november/field-engineer-takes-proactive-approach-to-customer-support]]&gt;.
Special trade-in pricing is available on LASEREF IV retrofitThe LASEREF® IV replaces the aging LASEREF II and III, which will become obsolete at the end of 2019, so trade in and trade up... Learn more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/2019_N_07 LASEREF IV Replacement Program.pdf]]&gt;.
2019 Honeywell Operator Conferences and events schedule – coming soon

Honeywell hosted more than 2000 customers this year at 60 events worldwide. During these events, customers met with our technical and business teams to discuss the latest information regarding their Honeywell products. We will have new types of events at different locations in 2019 to make it more convenient for our customers. Thank you for your support in 2018, and be on the lookout for our upcoming 2019 schedule.
The final countdown for Mandates compliance is approaching

2019 is now days away and with the turn of the New Year, opportunities for upgrading your aircraft tick away...  Read more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/ADS-B_Upgrade.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
