<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Portal_Release_Virtual_Chatbot_Email_MC.202010_Portal_Release_Virtual_Cha</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Assist - Meet Our New Virtual Chat!</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Assist – Virtual Chatbot - Honeywell Assist is our new virtual chatbot. All logged in MyAerospace users will have access to Honeywell Assist to help pull the following information:


	- Order Status
	- Part Availability
	- Pricing Information
	- Technical Solutions
	- FAQ


At this time, the chatbot can only help pull the information from the areas listed above. For more detailed information related to Order Status, Part Availability or Pricing Information, please use the Online Ordering and Order Status within the portal as you normally would. 

Honeywell Assist will be available to use on the following pages (via a floating icon on the right side of the page):


	- MyAerospace Portal Homepage
	- Online Ordering
	- Order Status
	- Technical Support
	- Contact Us


For more information, please visit our training topic page on the chatbot HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/dca-chatbot]]&gt; which includes a demo video recording. 

 A few reminders…
 
Pricing Exception for Spares Orders – Within Online Ordering, if you would like to add a pricing exception for your Spares order, please refer to the training topic page HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/online-ordering-pricing-exceptions]]&gt;.

 Reports and Notifications – To receive reports and notifications for your orders via email, please visit the training topic page on how to turn this functionality 
ON and modify per your needs: How do I receive orders reports &amp; notifications &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/order-status/reports-notifications]]&gt;?

 Website Search, Sales and Service Partner Lookup and Portal Overview – View THIS VIDEO &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Zfd5DeYmJzExSENBgocaxX]]&gt; recording – with helpful links - as we review frequently asked questions about searching on our website, our Authorized Sales &amp; Service Partner Lookup Tool as well as portal functionality.

To view the release note 
for the virtual chatbot and to catch up on latest improvements to MyAerospace, please refer to and bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;
Please be sure to Opt-IN to receive important portal enhancement update emails. 









   OPT-IN  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
