<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Amer_BGA_MSP_Nurture.2.BGA Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Making Aircraft Maintenance Coverage Easier – Hear From A Customer</subject>
    <textOnly>Our Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) provides rapid part supply and replacement to ensure that your aircraft is never grounded for long periods and your investment is secure. A successful example &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/customer-success-stories/2019/12/maintenance-program-provides-rapid-supply?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_bga_msp&amp;utm_content=nurture]]&gt; of our plan’s agility and capabilities is the story of Pro Tork – Latin America’s largest motorcycle parts manufacturer. 

 The company invested in a Pilatus PC-12 NG turboprop aircraft, relying on Honeywell MSP to remove financial shocks from future avionics repairs and maintenance. Pro Tork’s pilot, Captain Luciano Gabriel de Lima, takes up the story: “While taxiing, a primary flight display went blank. I stopped the aircraft, got in contact with Honeywell and less than 24 hours, we could safely continue our flights.

 “If the aircraft had been grounded for longer, it could have generated a significant loss.” He concluded: “If I have Honeywell by my side, I know the aircraft will be repaired quickly, my software will always be up to date and I will also have a 
predetermined cost.”

 The main customer advantages with Honeywell MSP: 



	- Efficient, predictive maintenance
	- Speedy parts supply and service
	- Enhanced productivity
	- Long-term financial predictability


Choose Honeywell MSP – Avionics Components &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/services/maintenance-and-service-plans/maintenance-service-plan-avionics-business-aviation?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_bga_msp&amp;utm_content=nurture]]&gt; and remove any financial uncertainty from 
future avionics repairs and maintenance.
Choose MSP &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/services/maintenance-and-service-plans/maintenance-service-plan-avionics-business-aviation?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_bga_msp&amp;utm_content=nurture]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
