<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201909_Americas_StandardAero_PEEF_PEAF_kcr.201909_Americas_StandardAero_PEEF+PEA</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Special Discounts When You Bundle Primus Elite with Synthetic Vision</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;  &lt;[[http://standardaero.com/]]&gt;

For a limited time, Honeywell is offering customers the chance to save when you upgrade your cockpit with the latest technology: Primus Elite Enhanced Features (PEEF) and Primus Elite Advanced Features (PEAF).


PEEF provides improved situational awareness capabilities and safety enhancements, including the electronic display of Jeppesen charts and maps, XM® graphical weather overlays, and video inputs, all enabled through a cursor control interface.


Additionally, PEAF is a software upgrade that includes a Synthetic Vision System (SVS). SVS provides 3D color images of runways, terrain, and obstacles, giving pilots a clear view of the virtual flight path. This increased level of situational awareness is particularly useful for reducing errors and pilot workload when flying to unfamiliar locations, in bad weather, or at night. In addition to SVS, XM Meteorological Aviation Reports and Terminal Area Forecasts, and TCAS flight awareness layers are added to the enhanced map display.


Want even more? In addition to a receiving a special discount when you bundle PEEF and PEAF, you&apos;re eligible to purchase SmartRunway and SmartLanding at a 50% discount! 


Contact StandardAero today to learn more about these exciting opportunities to upgrade your cockpit with the latest state-of-the-art avionics technology.





CONTACT STANDARDAERO &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/StandardAero_PEEF_PEAF.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_stda_peef-peaf]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
