<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201907_N_America_Nurture_UAV_Oil_Gas_MC.201907_N_America_Nurture_UAV_Oil_Gas_Ema</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Improve Your Plant’s Efficiency with Honeywell’s Drone Inspection Service</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

&quot;Helping you stay on time and on target during critical shutdowns&quot; 
 

Hi {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}},

We understand that you&apos;re constantly looking for ways to keep your site running safely and efficiently. 
 
 Honeywell’s UAV drone inspection service &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/uav]]&gt; efficiently and accurately prepare you for scheduled turnarounds with ample time to order the parts and services you’ll need to stay on time and on budget during this critical time. 
 
We&apos;ve partnered with our Honeywell colleagues at UOP and UOP Callidus ® to offer on-site field inspectors and engineers for a complete inspection solution, combining our century of knowledge in aerospace safety best practices and oil and gas technology. 
 
 Our on-site UOP engineers, field technicians and drone pilot can expertly inspect flares, piping, burners and furnaces without needing to shut down your operations. 
 
Improve your plant&apos;s operational efficiency today with Honeywell. For more information or to speak to one of our regional technical managers, please contact us below. 
 






CONTACT US  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/UAV_Oil-and-Gas_North_America.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_uav_gh&amp;utm_content=north+america+oil+and+gas]]&gt;






Disclaimer:

This email was sent by PMMI Media Group, publisher of Packaging World, Automation World, Healthcare Packaging, Contract Packaging, OEM and ProFood World. PMMI Media Group is a division of PMMI, owner and producer of the global portfolio of PACK EXPO shows. You are receiving this communication because of your subscription to one or more of PMMI’s newsletters, prior attendance at one of PMMI’s webinars or trade shows, or prior download from PMMI’s website. By engaging with PMMI, you have provided your consent for PMMI to process and store your personal information for purposes of communicating with you. Your consent for PMMI to retain and use this data will remain active until expressly revoked by you. All questions regarding data privacy policies, practices, or portability, as well as requests to revoke consent can be addressed to dataprivacy@pmmi.org &lt;[[mailto:dataprivacy@pmmi.org]]&gt;. All content in this email is sponsored and was not developed by PMMI Media Group. PMMI Media Group may share your contact information with sponsors as detailed in our privacy policy, but we will NEVER share your contact information with a sponsor whose content you have not viewed. However, PMMI may also make use of your data for other communication purposes, such as to inform you of other important industry developments, programs, or publications that may be relevant.
PW Privacy Policy: https://www.packworld.com/privacy &lt;[[https://www.packworld.com/privacy]]&gt;
PW Opt-Out Variable: @{confirmunsubscribelink}@</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
