<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_BTI_Hygiene_BGA_UV-Treatment-Wand_Webinar_On24.UV-Treatment-Wand.Subject Line</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>WEBINAR: Exclusive Invite | Unveiling the UV Treatment Wand</subject>
    <textOnly>Last year, Honeywell launched the groundbreaking UV Treatment System – a portable UV cleaning system specifically designed for transportation systems. It has now been demonstrated or deployed around the globe, helping passengers and employees travel with more confidence. Now, we’re offering our most portable and versatile UVC solution yet. 

 Introducing the Honeywell UV Treatment Wand &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/events/2021/02/honeywell-uv-treatment-wand-webinar?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_BTI_Hygiene]]&gt;: a lightweight, simple, affordable solution for operators of any size who 
want to enhance their cleaning protocols. The wand features high-intensity 254nm UVC, which has been found in clinical testing to be effective at reducing various viruses and bacteria on targeted surfaces when properly applied.1 Signify and Boston University have reported that high-intensity 254nm UVC can deactivate SARS-CoV-2, the virus which causes COVID-19.2

 For an 
exclusive first look, please join me for a webinar on Tuesday, February 23, 2020, at 10:00 a.m. EST. I’ll share the latest updates on this exciting new product which is expected to be available in March. The webinar will last approximately 60 minutes, and you are welcome to share the invitation with colleagues if you’d like. To register, please click the link below. 

 Sincerely,
 Ryan Hannaford
 Offering Management, Safety Systems
REGISTER NOW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/events/2021/02/honeywell-uv-treatment-wand-webinar?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_BTI_Hygiene]]&gt;
[1] These product concepts are currently under development. No testing has been done specifically as to protection against COVID-19. As with all of our products and services, Honeywell will adhere to its commitment to integrity and compliance within its global supply chain; meet relevant legal, scientific and industry standards; substantiate claims; and obtain necessary regulatory approvals as products progress through the development process. 

 [2] Boston University has reported achieving a 99% reduction of SARS-CoV-2 on targeted surfaces with a UVC dose of 5 mJ/cm2 in its testing.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
