<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS Newsletter 2014.June 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>June Direct-TO Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Newsletter Title
December  2013 Issue






 



Honeywell Flight Technical Services
Temperature Compensation - Part 3 of 3
In the previous November &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_newsletters.php?flag=november_2013_desc&gt; and February &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_newsletters.php?flag=february_2014_desc&gt; editions, temperature compensation, why it is used, and a basic &quot;how to&quot; was discussed. Part three of this series will look at the calculator function of the FMS temperature compensation feature. As discussed in part two, the FMS will modify the encoded altitudes for waypoints on a segment of an approach, or in some installations on a departure. Here the RNAV Rwy 15 into Bangor Maine, KBGR is used as an example; the temperature at the airport is -18 degrees C.....Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_2014_temp&gt;.
 
Temperature Compensation - Par 
Using the Place/Bearing/Distance (PBD) method is a simple way for flight crews to insert a pilot-defined waypoint at a bearing and distance from another waypoint in the navigation database. For example, if a pilot wanted to put in a waypoint 30NM from PXR at the 064 degree bearing, they would enter PXR/064/30... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_2014_place&gt;.






Tools of the Trade 
Increasing Situational Awareness  
In 2003, Honeywell developed the Runway Awareness and Advisory System (RAAS). It was the first system providing improved flight crew situational awareness to help minimize the potential of runway incursions and excursions. ... &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_14_tools&gt;Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_14_tools&gt;  







Engine Insights
Effect of Spinner Shape on Ice Collection
Editor’s Note: The Direct-TO Newsletter is excited to announce a new section devoted to Honeywell Engines and APUs. Featuring articles written by Honeywell Test Pilot and Pilot Advisor Helmuth Eggeling, Engine Insights will tackle mechanical issues from a pilot’s perspective.....Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_2014_effect&gt; 






Service Information Letter Briefing
PC-12NG - GPS Initialization Times with Apex Builds 8.6 and 8.7
Honeywell has published Service Information Letter (SIL) D201312000062 to address longer-than-expected initialization 
times for some PC-12NB aircraft loaded with Apex Build 8.6 or 8.7. Upon start-up, the GPS receiver may not receive the present position data needed, so GPS initialization can take longer than expected.  ... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_2014_service_info&gt;    






Service Information Letter Briefing
Heading Legs on Departure Procedures and Missed Approaches  
In 
an effort to inform pilots about FMS heading versus track behavior, a Honeywell Service Information Letter (SIL) has been published. SIL D201210000071 discusses how departure and missed approach procedures with “fly heading” or “climb heading” legs are flown by business and general aviation aircraft using Honeywell FMS.... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_feb_2014_service_info&gt;   




Events and Training
2014 Events and Training
Honeywell&apos;s Flight Technical Services team travels all over the world to bring pilots the latest information on regulations, technology, and Honeywell product updates. Through pilot breakout sessions at Honeywell operator conferences, one-on-one training, entry into service support and live webinars, Honeywell pilots are on a mission to keep operators informed...Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_mar_2014_event_training&gt;
Upcoming Events &amp; Training &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=nov_events_and_training&gt; 

Online Pilot Training Webinar &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/cpsfltops_training.php?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRow5%2FmYJoDpwmWGd5mht7VzDtPj1OY6hBoqILyJK1TtuMFUGpsqOOGRDwcJBJVtzF8%3D&gt;
Tech Ops Center &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/%21ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQzc3UONDTzNQ7zN3AICDA0sjPULsh0VAb6AM7A%21/&gt;   

Direct-TO Archives &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_newsletters.php?flag=all&amp;mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRow5%2FmYJoDpwmWGd5mht7VzDtPj1OY6hBoqILyJK1TtuMFUGpsqOOGRDwcJBJVtzF8%3D&gt; 

Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
