<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201811_EndUseCertification_LG.201811_EndUseCertification_email_nonChannel</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Complete the End-Use Statement of Certification Form by 17 December</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer: 
Processing your repair order quickly is important to all of us. To enable the fastest possible repair turn times, it is critical that we have the required end-use and end-user information to process your order. These are not new requirements. Completing this updated statement of certification form will allow the order to proceed directly into the repair cycle. 
This requirement complies with import/export government regulations. The easiest way for customers to provide this information is to complete the updated end-use &amp; end-user statement of certification form as described below.
Why are we using this updated certification form?



	- It is easier to provide the required data. 
	- If you do not provide third-party repair support, it eliminates the need to include the aircraft information on each purchase order. 
	- Repair orders are not held or delayed due to missing end-use and end-user data. 




How long is the certification valid for?



	- Certifications will be applicable for a two-year period when the certification has the required information and signatures.


What type of products does this certification apply to?


	- 
Spares

	- 
Original equipment

	- 
Technical publications

	- 
Software

	- 
Technical data

	- 
Repairs: For your own fleet or when all repairs are for ‘stock’ or ’shelf replenishment, not direct returns to a customer

	- 
Repairs: For 3rd parties – identifies if additional information is required on each purchase order



What is the timing? 
Effective immediately, incoming repair orders will be required to have:


	- A certification on file indicating that they do not perform third-party repairs, OR
	- Third-party repair orders will require the following mandatory information on the purchase order: Company name, address, platform and/or tail number.


What about existing orders? 
If existing orders do not have the required information, a Customer Support Representative will contact the requestor. 
What if the certification is not on file? What if Honeywell does not know whether a company does third-party repairs? What if the PO is missing the mandatory information?


	- The incoming repair orders may be delayed until the required information is provided or the end-use &amp; and end-user certificate is on file.
	- Honeywell must contact the customer to validate that the repair is not for embargoed or sanctioned countries. 


What else do I need to know? 


	- If a part requires an export authorization, a separate end-use and end-user document may be required. 
	- As applicable under the exporting country’s law, additional export documentation may be required.
	- One form is required for each customer buying entity (i.e. ordering address for your account) OR if all buying locations provide the same type of repair activity, one form can be submitted as long as all addresses are captured in the space provided on the form. For example, if three buying entity addresses all submit repairs to Honeywell for their own fleet, one form is acceptable with all three addresses listed in the boxes provided on the form.


What do I need to do? 


	- All repair customers should use the ‘Honeywell Customer End-Use and End-User Statement of Certification’ to certify their end-use, end-user information, and adherence to United States and local export regulations. 


	- Download the AF-0974, Rev. 4 certificate &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/My%20Account/End_Use_and_End_User_Certification.zip&gt; file. 
	- Open the .zip file and &quot;Export Compliance Form&quot; folder.
	- Select &quot;AF-0974 Honeywell Customer End Use and End User Statement of Certification&quot;.
	- Accurately and completely execute the certificate.
	- 
The form can be electronically completed and digitally signed with a system viewer (Adobe), OR printed, completed, signed and scanned.



	- 
Save the form and email it to EndUseCert@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:EndUseCert@Honeywell.com]]&gt; by 12/17/18.

	- If you are a third-party repair provider:


	- Complete and return the form indicating that you request repairs for other third-parties. 
	- Include the mandatory information on all repair orders sent to Honeywell: Company name, address, platform, and/or tail number     




Thank you for using Honeywell for your repair needs. This document is critical to enabling an unrestricted order flow into the repair cycle. 


Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
