<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201710_Global_Email_Aerospace Directory_Channel Partners_Reminder_JRD.201710_Glo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reminder: Please Update Your Contact Information for Aerospace Directory</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Valued Channel Partner:



Last week, you were sent the following message. If you have not done so already, please make sure to send us the preferred email address you’d like to provide on file for your company to receive sales leads. 


---------------------------------------------

In an effort to promote our channel partner network and connect you with customers, we&apos;ve created a tool that will accomplish these objectives faster than ever before. 

Through the new Aerospace Directory, customers can contact Honeywell’s area sales managers, the customer and product support team and our channel partners immediately by visiting any of our product pages via the Honeywell Aerospace website &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/product-listing/satellite-communications]]&gt; and selecting “locate/directory” or from the MyAerospace portal “contact us” page &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;.

For a demo of the Aerospace Directory, please watch this video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/quCde0xGOR0]]&gt;. You can also access a list of frequently asked questions here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/FAQ_Aerospace Directory.pdf]]&gt;. 

ACTION FOR CHANNEL PARTNERS:
Please visit the Aerospace Directory by using the links provided above to ensure your information is listed correctly by October 30, 2017. It is critical we provide customers with the correct contact information in order to engage in every sales opportunity provided to us created by this new tool. 

Once the tool goes live, your team will start receiving leads and someone from the channel marketing team will contact you to follow-up on the status of these leads. 


If you&apos;d you like to update the email address we have on file for this tool, please send your updated contact information to channelmarketing@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:channelmarketing@honeywell.com]]&gt;. If we do not receive an updated email from you, we will use the one we have on file provided to us in your agreement.



This tool will go live October 30, 2017.


We appreciate your support and look forward to working with you to make this an effective tool for our customers.


Sincerely,

The Honeywell Aerospace Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
