<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Global_Internal-Comms_Supplier-Comms-FM-Response_Email_Operational.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Action Required: Honeywell Response to Your Communications</subject>
    <textOnly>March 31, 2020 

 Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Supplier}}, 

 Honeywell acknowledges receipt of your communication regarding what you recognize as impacts of the COVID-19 situation on your operations. Honeywell is committed to working with you, as one of our valued suppliers, to maintain continuity of supply. We will assess any appropriate support needed given the dynamic global environment and your particular circumstances. 

 We share with you the great privilege of being part of the aerospace industry, which is critical to infrastructure, transportation, security, and defense. With this privilege comes a responsibility. As a Honeywell supplier for commercial or government aerospace products and services, you are an essential business and part of the Critical Infrastructure of the United States, pursuant to Department of Homeland Security (“DHS”) 
Guidance &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/DHS Letter.pdf]]&gt;, Department of Defense guidance &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Defense%20Industrial%20Base%20Essential%20Critical%20Infrastructure%20Workforce.pdf]]&gt;, and Presidential Directive 21 &lt;[[https://www.cisa.gov/critical-infrastructure-sectors]]&gt;. Under this guidance, you are expected to remain open and maintain normal work schedules. If you have orders rated under the Defense Priorities and Allocation System (DPAS), you are required to prioritize materials and production and deliver in accordance with applicable law and pursuant to recent DPAS guidance &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/DIB%20Memo%20Final%20Coord%20Copy%20for%20Sig%2020%20Mar%2020%201750.pdf&gt; from the Department of Defense. 

 Honeywell has a responsibility to meet its customer commitments to secure these parts of Critical Infrastructure. Our expectations for you remain unchanged: deliver on your contractual commitments, including with respect to quality, delivery, and cost. 

 Please review carefully the following immediate actions required to continue meeting the needs of our shared customers, while caring for the health and safety of all our workers. We can, and we must, do both. 



	- Maintain the delivery schedule of Honeywell orders and prioritization of Honeywell orders
	- Continue to prioritize materials and production capacity and flow down DPAS rated orders to your suppliers, in accordance with federal law
	- Complete the Honeywell Continuity of Supply Risk Assessment &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DQLTP7L?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTmpFNE1qSmpOelJqTnpBNSIsInQiOiIyUHJFbFFCUVBEUmdKZ3N5eWdTMXczTHpQOURyWkJxUVZIb1p0YmlcL2s0UitVRlwvN3VOdkFZaEYrN3VwVXZJc0dhVDhxNXZwcEJUeWpyWjFGYmo0ZENnPT0ifQ%3D%3D]]&gt; sent to you on March 20, 2020, if 
you have not already done so
	- Communicate regularly with your designated Commodity Manager regarding evolving COVID-19 impacts to you and/or your sub tier suppliers, your mitigation plan, and the anticipated timeline of these impacts.


As necessary, you should diligently pursue alternative resources and third parties to complete your deliverables to Honeywell on-time, provided such alternatives do not compromise the quality nor functionality of your deliverables. As always, you must consult with your Honeywell Commodity Manager for prior approval before making any change to materials, manufacturing process, location or subcontractors. 

 Thank you for all you do to ensure the health, safety, and welfare of your employees, while simultaneously supporting critical infrastructure programs. Honeywell, our shared customers, and our country, are all counting on you. 

Sincerely, 

 Bob Buddecke 
Vice President and Chief Procurement Officer 
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
