<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201704_APAC_Email_APACHQFollowUp_ENG_mih.201704_APAC_Email_APACHQFollowUp_Eng_mi</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell International Sdn Bhd</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

April 12, 2017




Dear Customer, 



Honeywell Aerospace has decided to set up a new aftermarket headquarters and a new distribution center under Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The new distribution center will be called Asia Regional Distribution Center (ARDC). ARDC will streamline Honeywell’s Asia Pacific Aero aftermarket distribution operations to better support our customers in the Asia Pacific Region.

The establishment of the new regional distribution center will see APAC business content that is currently managed by Honeywell International Sarl (HIS) in Switzerland transitioned to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Malaysia. The optimized local distribution center will be able to serve our customers in the Asia Pacific Region with quicker delivery turnaround times and will provide exemplary aftermarket support and services.



The new headquarters office in Kuala Lumpur Malaysia will open in Q2-2017 while the Asia Regional Distribution Center will be in Q3 2017.



In order to make this transition process as seamless as possible for you and your organization, we kindly ask for your assistance with the following critical actions:




	- Ensure that Honeywell International Sdn Bhd is set up in your system as an &quot;Approved Supplier&quot;

	- Appoint a freight forwarding agent in Malaysia that is registered with the Royal Malaysian Custom

	- The invoice “Pay To” account must change to the Honeywell International Sdn Bhd




We would be grateful to receive a notification from you when this action is completed via the following contact: joel.miranda@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:joel.miranda@honeywell.com]]&gt;

Advance Notice for Contract Customers:

If you currently have a contract with Honeywell, such agreement may be assigned or novated as required. Please anticipate an additional communication from our Contracts department.

As we go through this transition, we want to assure you that we have your best interests in mind. For frequently asked questions, please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/ARDC-FAQ 90 Days April 5.pdf]]&gt;. If you have any further questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us via your account leader or customer manager.

Thank you for your support as we work to enhance the way Honeywell Aerospace does business with you.

Sincerely,</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
