<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>BAN 2015.February.Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Business Aviation Newsletter: February 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Business Aviation Newsletter: February 2015
In-Flight Voice Recognition for Future Cockpits  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/honeywell-testing-in-flight-voice-recognition-for-future-cockpits&gt;

We have begun testing voice recognition inside aircraft cockpits using a recently developed rapid prototyping system that allows emerging technologies like voice recognition control to more easily integrate...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/honeywell-testing-in-flight-voice-recognition-for-future-cockpits&gt;


Success Story: Sunrise Jets &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/success/sunrisejetsstory&gt;


When Sunrise Jets of Long Island was trying to complete the sale of a Cessna Citation 560XLS, a routine pre-purchase inspection suggested that there was foreign object damage (FOD) to the impeller...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/success/sunrisejetsstory&gt;


Engine Health Monitoring Offers One-Stop-Shop &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/enginehealthmonitoring&gt;


Our partnership with CAMP Systems is in full swing to provide TFE and HTF operators with Integrated Engine Services (IES) for monitoring engine health to improve the life of our propulsion systems...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/enginehealthmonitoring&gt;



 GCC Meets in Istanbul, Phoenix and Hong Kong  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/globalcustomercommittees&gt;


The Global Customer Committee (GCC) is an independent group of nearly 80 business aviation professionals worldwide that works jointly with us to bring about improvements in aircraft, equipment, operations and...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/globalcustomercommittees&gt;


Ovation Select Scores Cabin Management Award &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/cabinmanagementaward&gt;


What&apos;s the best new corporate jet development or idea to enhance the VVIP (Very VIP) experience? Envelope please. And the  winner is... Ovation Select, our all-digital, high-definition, state-of-the-art cabin management...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/cabinmanagementaward&gt;


Join our Business Aviation Operator Conferences  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/operator-conferences&gt;


Join our Customer Support Managers as they host business aviation operators conferences in 40 locations around the world this year. These conferences are designed to provide maintenance personnel,...

Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/operator-conferences&gt;



Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
