<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202102_APAC_Newsletter_MC.202102_APAC_Newsletter_Images</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Connect with Andrew Wong</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell’s solutions have supported many critical industries that underpin the global economy throughout the pandemic. From aerospace to building technologies to manufacturing process controls to worker safety, as well as vaccinations distribution.
The Honeywell UV Treatment System makes flying safer and helps passengers feel more confident flying again. It can treat an aircraft cabin effectively with clinical-proven UVC light in less than 10 minutes between flights. 

Recently, a smaller version innovative backpack design with a UV treatment wand &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-treatment-wand?utm_source=website&amp;utm_medium=public_relations&amp;utm_campaign=21_bti_hygiene]]&gt; was released to the market to serve beyond airplanes, such as buses and trains.



 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-treatment-system]]&gt;
Honeywell’s Healthy Buildings solutions provide a holistic view of a building’s health and make buildings healthier through air quality, safety and security technologies along with advanced analytics.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/press/2020/05/honeywell-launches-solutions-to-help-improve-building-health-and-reassure-occupants]]&gt;
Honeywell Remote Operations offerings support the remote operation of critical infrastructure.






 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://www.honeywellprocess.com/en-US/online_campaigns/remotesolutions/Pages/solutions.html]]&gt;
Public-private partnership in our headquarters’ state of North Carolina, supporting the goal of 1 million vaccinations distribution in the Charlotte metropolitan area by July 4.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/press/2021/1/public-private-partnership-targets-1-million-vaccinations-by-july-4]]&gt;
Honeywell continues to strengthen our business growth and innovation capabilities to better serve our customers in the aerospace industries.



	- Forming a new business unit dedicated to unmanned aerial system and urban air mobility.
	- Recent acquisition: Ballard Unmanned Systems &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/us/en/press/2020/10/honeywell-acquires-ballard-unmanned-systems]]&gt;.








Recent Announcements on Honeywell Aerospace.
Honeywell to bring next-generation inertial sensors to unmanned vehicles segment


 


Recent findings show the accuracy of new sensors is improved by greater than an order of magnitude over current offerings.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2021/01/honeywell-bring-next-gen-inertial-sensors-to-unmanned-vehicles]]&gt;






 








 




 





 


 






Honeywell, Curtiss-Wright receive EASA Certification for 25-hour cockpit recorder for the Air Transport Market


 


New Cockpit Voice Recorder receives EASA Technical Standard Order.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2021/01/honeywell-curtiss-wright-receive-easa-certification-cockpit-recorder]]&gt;
Honeywell launches next-generation digital cabin pressure control and monitoring system for aircraft


 


Latest version of the system is 30% lighter, more reliable and customizable for a wide range of aircraft.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2021/01/honeywell-launches-next-gen-digital-cabin-pressure-control-monitoring-system]]&gt;






 








 




 





 


 






Honeywell, Sichuan Airlines ink historic deal on Auxiliary Power Units


 


Five-year agreement includes a new selection, plus a retrofit for the entire A320 fleet.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2021/01/honeywell-sichuan-historic-deal-apu]]&gt;
Honeywell introduces next-generation catalyst to address “Smell in Cabin” events


 


Advanced catalyst technology will help reduce delays, cancellations and unscheduled maintenance.




 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2020/12/next-gen-catalyst-addresses-smell-in-cabin-events]]&gt;






 








 



 





How Honeywell can help you to be more cost-effective and competitive:


	- The Smarter Way of Material Provisioning
 Now is a good time to invest in material that you will need in the near future. Please note that this is a limited period offer and parts are subject to availability and on new orders only. Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/material-provisioning]]&gt;
	- GoDirect Trade
 The first aviation online marketplace for new &amp; used aerospace products, leveraging Blockchain technology. Learn more &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;    


 


© 2021 Honeywell International Inc.  &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; 
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202


 


Subscription Preference &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt;  |  Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; |  Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; |  Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
