<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Metrics.Oct_YTD 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aerospace Intellectual Property Process --  October Quarterly Metrics</subject>
    <textOnly>October Quarterly Metrics
A Message to M&amp;PM and E&amp;T Leaders Regarding Intellectual Property Metrics

November 18, 2013


Dear Colleagues:

Honeywell is one of the Top 30 companies in patents granted in the United States each year with Aerospace contributing about 40% of those patents. The continued creativity and submittal of invention ideas is critical for the protection of our product revenue and competitive advantage. As a result, we encourage the prompt submittal of invention ideas that support our products through the Worldwide Invention Disclosure System &lt;https://wids.honeywell.com/Index.aspx?err=logout&gt; (WIDS), and are 
asking for your support in sharing this message across your organization.

For the M&amp;PM and E&amp;T leaders on this distribution, we will be providing quarterly metrics in the 
areas of relevance to your organization. The intent is to inform and solicit your support to drive actions as needed for your area of influence.

The appended metrics (1) Disclosure Submittals and (2) Disclosure Decisions (patent filings) have been prepared year-to-date through October. (October 2013 Quarterly Metrics &lt;http://teamsites.honeywell.com/sites/IPTracking/Wiki/2013%20Actuals/2013%20New%20Quarterly%20Metrics/Quarterly%20Metrics_October%202013.pptx&gt;)


(1)  Disclosure Submittals (by IP Steering Committee YTD vs. Historical)

Purpose: Communicate quantity of disclosures received from Aerospace inventors versus historical averages
Details:  Purple line indicates historical year-to-date average. Percentages indicate disclosures received year-to-date as a % of the historical annual average.

Commentary: 


 - Disclosure submittals for Aerospace overall are up 8% over the historical average 2011 / 2012.
 - There is variation among the IP Steering Committees, as shown below, some far exceeding historical averages and some far below



Who has actions: 
 &gt;&gt;&gt; E&amp;T T3 Leaders - Monitor deviations from historical 
averages. Is this in line with your expectations? Drive actions as needed within your organization.
 


(2) Disclosures Decisions (to File US patents by IP Steering Committee YTD)  

Purpose: Communicate quantity of disclosures reviewed by each IPSC steering committee. Out of those, highlight the quantity and % of decisions to File patents in the US 

Details: Total bar (green + blue) indicates the number of disclosures in which a decision was made (file or no file) in each IPSC year to date. Green bar indicates the quantity of those decisions that were “yes” to file

Commentary: 


 - Disclosure submittals for Aerospace overall are 29% of all decisions made. This is down from 32% in 2012, 35% in 2011.
 - There is variation among the IP Steering Committees some far exceeding the average and some far below.




Who has actions: 
&gt;&gt;&gt;  IPSC Leaders - Review the filing rate which is influenced by incoming disclosure quality and/or IPSC review standards. Is this filing rate in line with your expectations? Drive actions as needed.




Thank you for your continued work in driving our IP protection program. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.

 

Thank you, 
Dan
Dan Gutfreund
IP Process Leader
Technology Strategy, Advanced Technology
21111 N 19th Ave (M/S 2J35A5)
Phoenix, AZ 85027
Phone: +1 602 436-9030
Mobile: +1 480 258-8692
Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
