<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201808_Email_Global_MSP_Early Scheduled Maintenance_CustomerTFE731.201808_Email_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Extends Maintenance Service Intervals for Certain TFE Engines Covered By Our Maintenance Service Plan</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | BUSINESS AND GENERAL AVIATION
HONEYWELL EXTENDS INTERVALS FOR ENGINES COVERED UNDER MSP
Dear Valued Customer,
Honeywell will release an update to extend TFE731-20/-40/-50/-60 engine intervals to maximize operators’ time on-wing. Honeywell is extending maintenance intervals for the TFE731-20/-40/-50/-60 engine from 3000 / 6000 hours to 3500 / 7000 hours. This interval extension is effective immediately.
Note that engine model TFE731-40AR-200G, which is used on the Gulfstream G150 aircraft, is under an MSG-3 maintenance program and therefore subject to a Maintenance Review Board (MRB) process as defined by the FAA. That engine model will therefore not be eligible for the interval extension until the MRB committee approval is received. 
We continue to refine MSP so that operators can schedule maintenance with our industry-leading service center network while minimizing unplanned maintenance costs. Customers enrolled in MSP can take advantage of features including foreign object damage (FOD) gap protection, the ability to sign bailment agreements electronically and the option to use rental assets in regions where they operate. 
 
 Your authorized service center will work with you to reach the maximum designated interval. As a result, this helps Honeywell continue to extend other engine maintenance intervals, balance work scopes, and reliability and keeps your investment economically viable.
We look forward to working with you as we continue to increase the benefits of MSP and other programs alike. We appreciate your business and thank you for your continued support.
Sincerely,
 
 Bill Hurst 
 VP, Business Aviation



If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/NI005QdG000uhzX08Zj0B2q]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
