<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Monthly Metrics 2017.201706_Global_Monthly Metrics_dpg</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>IPSC Performance - May 2017</subject>
    <textOnly>Email Title
July 2015

Dear Colleagues: Appended are the monthly Intellectual Property Steering Committee (IPSC) performance metrics for July 2015. The intent is to track our ability to make timely decisions on invention reviews and assist troubleshooting issues. This effort has taken on additional importance with the US first inventor to file patent system. The appended metrics will provide a rolling three month trend. (July 2015 Metrics &lt;https://teamsites2013.honeywell.com/sites/IPTracking/Wiki/2015%20Actuals/2015%20Monthly%20Metrics/IPSC%20Performance%20Metric_July%202015.pptx&gt;) 

Purpose: Communicate why disclosure decisions are delayed to IPSC stakeholders and highlight where actions need 
to occur to resolve the problem.

Commentary: 


 - Overall: Inventions reviewed 110; performance flat – 37% inventions delayed, several IPSCs in “Red”
 - High Attendance Delays (P, M) -15 total
 - High Delinquencies (D) – Engines-15, Thermal Systems (ECS)-4
 - Engines IPSC – 5 month trend below 50% inventions reviewed



Who has actions: 

&gt;&gt;&gt; IPSC Leaders - Review &amp; take action as needed to address: Delinquency (D), PPM Absence (P), and Unjustified Holds (U)

&gt;&gt;&gt; M&amp;PM Leader (Vaish) - Review and take action as needed to address:  MPM Absence (M)

&gt;&gt;&gt; IP Process Owner (Gutfreund) - Monitor Transfers (T) and Justified Holds (J), escalate issues



Inventions Delayed - Reason (Detailed Definitions) &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/dG0q64fZKv0XR00I6d020Q0&gt;

Comments about the IPSC performance metric: 


 - Intended for distribution to IPSC members, distributed on a monthly basis (mid-month for the prior month) and reviewed as needed at IPSC meetings
 - The metric is not a grade, but a way to track IPSC decisions on inventions and assist in troubleshooting an issue that may be an ongoing trend 
 - The IPSC should not be overly concerned with the scoring of an individual month, it is the trend that will need to be monitored (e.g. if an IPSC is not getting 50 percent of the inventions decided over many months, this is an issue and the metrics will support more detailed investigation into the causes)



Additional Aerospace IP processes and information are available at the Aero IP Community Wiki &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/jveI042qQ006R06ZXGg0K00&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&gt;.
 
 Thank you for your continued work in driving our IP protection program. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.

Thank you, 
 Dan 

Dan Gutfreund
IP Process Leader
Technology Strategy, Advanced Technology
21111 N 19th Ave (M/S 2J35A5)
Phoenix, AZ 85027
Phone: +1 602 436-9030
Mobile: +1 480 258-8692
Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/m000Zx2060vG3q6RIIC0QX0&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
