<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_BK_Webinar_SocialFlight_AeroVue_Touch_and_Integrated_Panel_MC.Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AeroVue Touch and Integrated Panel</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for attending our recent SocialFlight webinar “AeroVue Touch and Integrated Panel”. In a few days, we will have this posted online for on-demand viewing and will send you the link. 

 As a seminar special, we are offering a 10% discount on our products when you secure your products through our free My Avionics &lt;[[https://apps.apple.com/us/app/my-avionics/id1367559967]]&gt; app found on the App Store for iPhone and iPad products. Easy to use; download the app and upload a photo of your panel or take a photo through the app, complete the information and you’ll receive a 10% discount in your inbox!

 As we mentioned in the presentation, our AeroVue Touch &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerovue-touch]]&gt; PFD/MFD display is a simple and powerful. It comes standard with all flight indicators, the industry-leading SmartView synthetic vision, a vertical situation display that shows flight path over terrain, and ADS-B In weather and traffic. The HeliVue Touch package is built around this display, specifically for helicopters.

 If you’re not sure of where to start with an upgrade, contact us &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;. We’re happy to listen, make recommendations and help you find a dealer/installer. And to discuss the AeroVue Touch for helicopters in our HeliVue Touch, please email me: simon.williams2@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:simon.williams2@honeywell.com?subject=AeroVue Touch and Integrated Panel]]&gt;

 For more information about the other products discussed with the AeroVue Touch during the webinar, please visit these pages:


	- AeroNav GPS Navigators &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigation]]&gt;: Slide-in touchscreen replacement for legacy GNS 430, 530
	- AeroCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-100]]&gt;: Affordable autopilot offered in three convenient form factors
	- AeroCruze 230 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-230]]&gt;: Touchscreen autopilot packed with features
	- AeroFlight &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeroflight]]&gt;: Compact digital attitude indicator
	- AeroPoint 200 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-200]]&gt;: TSO’d as primary instrument for single engine aircraft
	- AeroPoint 300 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-300]]&gt;: Designed for twin-engine aircraft, with pre-wired harness
	- Confidence Plan &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/productitems/bendixking-confidence-plan]]&gt;: Insurance plan for your new avionics
	- Total Avionics Plan (TAP) &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/total-avionics-plan]]&gt;: Unique alternative in financing your new panel as a subscription


If you have any feedback or questions, please email us at sales@bendixking.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@bendixking.com]]&gt;


 Sincerely,
 Simon Williams 
BendixKing</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
