<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Amer_HCE_Propulsion-Reporting_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Propulsion Reporting – BETA Analytics – Honeywell Forge</subject>
    <textOnly>Introducing Propulsion Reporting
The new BETA feature inside Honeywell Forge that provides insight into the total engine time for any flight. This feature is available for datalink tails only, for both fleet and aircraft view. Get more insights on your engine run time with this new service function. 

 Benefits of Propulsion Reporting: 

 How does propulsion reporting work?
 Honeywell uses an algorithm to compute start and shutdown time of the engine pulling from multiple data sources. 

 How long of history does propulsion reporting track? 
 We keep a 6-month history beginning at the activation of the tile. Time will be reported by leg, tail, and accumulated by month. 

 Is the reporting just aircraft engines?
 The reporting just includes engines at this time. We are planning to incorporate Honeywell APUs in the future. 

 Can I change any of the data reported?
 Users will be allowed to edit computed propulsion time. 

 Any other future integrations planned?
 Yes! Our roadmap includes links to the Maintenance Service Plan (MSP), along with maintenance tracking with CAMP. 

 Have questions or propulsion data isn&apos;t showing up in your dashboard? Contact our team, we are here to help. 

 If you have feedback, we’d love to hear from you. Click the small question mark in the top right corner of the Honeywell Forge dashboard, fill out the short form and click submit.

 Honeywell Forge Flight Services
 US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330
 International: +1 (602) 365-7020 
flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;
Log In &lt;[[https://bga.honeywellforge.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
