<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Amer_BGA_CH_DU-875-Upgrade_Pentastar_Email.202006_Americas_DU875_Email3(a</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Honeywell DU-875 Display Upgrade for Falcon 900 is Here</subject>
    <textOnly>The DU-875 Display Upgrade for Falcon 900C/EX 
 by Honeywell and Pentastar Aviation
Improve your pilot’s view and add instant value to your aircraft with the DU-875 upgrade for Falcon 900C/EX by Honeywell and Pentastar Aviation.
Replace one or all of your CRT DU-870 displays with this simple “plug and play” replacement, that allows for quick and easy installation using the same connector without additional wiring. 
When you upgrade your cockpit, you also receive many benefits: 


	- Reduced cost of ownership, represented by increased display reliability (2x more than the old CRT&apos;s) and system weight reduction (each display is 7lbs lighter than the existing DU-870 and the cooling system is no longer required) 
	- Maintains full cockpit integration – no need for pilot training due to retention of current display formats, symbology and color sets 
	- Growth plan that takes advantage of future technologies and applications – Primus Elite 


Avoid obsolescence and save up to $175,000* when you take advantage of this limited time trade-in credit. 

Contact Pentastar Aviation for more information about the DU-875 upgrade for Falcon 900C/EX and inquire about having them come to you for the install to further eliminate your aircraft downtime.
UPGRADE NOW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/upgrade-your-views-with-du875-display?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_ch_du-875_bga_pentastar]]&gt;
*Savings are based on operator upgrading up to five (5) DU-870 display units to the DU-875 LCD display units</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
