<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201902_Americas_Nurture_SpiritAero_HAPP-MPP_mih.201902_Americas_Nurture_Email2_S</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Protect Your {{lead.Type of Platform:default=Aircraft}} Beyond Its Factory Warranty Through Spirit Aeronautics</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; &lt;[[http://www.spiritaeronautics.com/]]&gt;

Dear {{lead.First Name:default=customer}},

Your avionics are a big investment – an investment worth protecting. Our records indicate that the factory warranty on {{lead.Aircraft Tail Number:default=your aircraft}} expires in 2019. Honeywell&apos;s Maintenance Service Plan is the perfect solution for Gulfstream operators who want to keep their aircraft flying and control their annual maintenance budget with the industry’s premier fixed-price protection plan.

When you sign up for Honeywell&apos;s Maintenance Service Plan, you’ll have access to Honeywell’s global network of authorized service centers so 
that you never have to worry about being stuck on the ground. With more than 600 service center locations worldwide, and 24/7 support, your Honeywell avionics and environmental control systems are always protected.

Save on Unexpected Repairs

Along with Honeywell’s worldwide coverage, the Maintenance Service Plan can help you save money when you come across those unexpected and inconvenient repairs. According to our research, operators who have the Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan save more than $60,000* on their avionics and environmental control system repairs. This allows maintenance crews to better predict their annual costs, making it easier for everyone onboard to make better decisions with the extra savings.

Get the peace of mind that comes with having world-class protection plans on your side. Contact Spirit Aeronautics to protect your Gulfstream today with the Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan.




CONTACT US &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/SpiritAero_HAPP-MPP.html]]&gt;




*Annual cost does vary per airframe and flight hours.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
