<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>AESS 350.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>A350 AESU EGPWM Terrain Database Release Notification version 585</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}
 
 

  
 
Honeywell has just released Service Information Letter D201610000018 detailing a new worldwide Airbus A350 AESU EGPWM Terrain Database - version 582. This version is an update to previous version 581 and adds a number of new airports, runways and obstacles while improving terrain mapping and resolution. 
  
The database and supporting documentation (Service Information Letter and a Certificate of Conformance) can be downloaded by visiting ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/]]&gt; (login required).  EGPWS database search tools and change info are located there (no login required), look under the Search tab and the Change Info tab. 
  
Please click here &lt;[[mailto:dsa@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWM A350 Query contact us]]&gt; if you have any technical questions concerning the database. 
  
The URL www.egpws.com &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/enhanced-ground-proximity-warning-system]]&gt; will take you directly to the new Honeywell EGPWS page.  From there you can view product Information, or jump to the EGPWS Technical Data Site &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/new_egpws]]&gt; (login required) or the Aerospace Software and Database Services site &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRoju6vPZKXonjHpfsX76%2B0sWaC0lMI%2F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CSMBgI%2BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFTLTEMbFpwrgEWhM%3D]]&gt;. We encourage you to visit the website today and explore. 
  
Please click here &lt;[[mailto:myaerospaceportalissue@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWM A350 Website Query contact us]]&gt; if you have any questions concerning operation or access to Honeywell websites. 

 
Best regards, 
 
 The Honeywell EGPWS Team
This email was sent by: Honeywell
21111 N 19th Avenue Phoenix, AZ 85027 USA
View Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;
View Our Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
