<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Global_Email_RealTimeCurtailment_mih.201906_Global_Email_RealTimeCurtailm</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Real-Time Curtailment Now Available with GoDirect Flight Bag Pro</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Weight and Balance with Real Time Curtailment Now Available with GoDirect Flight Bag Pro 
 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Update your Honeywell Electronic Flight Bag (EFB) Pro application today to achieve the most accurate weight and balance calculations specific to your aircraft cabin and baggage compartment.



	- TAILORED: Actual aircraft cabin positions and weights are used to determine the amount of curtailment applied (dashed line)
	- PROTECTION: Computed weight and balance values are checked against and displayed within curtailed envelope
	- ACCURACY: APG curtailment protects CG integrity, always ensuring operation is within CG
	- REGULATORY COMPLIANCE: APG fixed curtailment is FAA and EASA compliant. Complies with regulatory requirement AC 120-27F (5/6/2019) applies to 14 CFR part 91K, 121, 125, and 135 operations


The new feature calculates the effect of each movement individually to determine the amount of &quot;curtailment&quot; needed and then applies this to the original equipment manufacturer (OEM) CG envelope, generating new CG Limits. Simply update to the newest app version to get started. 






UPDATE MY APP &lt;[[https://apps.apple.com/us/app/godirect-flight-bag-pro/id1232722107?ls=1]]&gt;




If you are interested in activating real-time curtailment within your aircraft profile, please contact the GoDirect team for additional information about this feature.

GoDirect Flight Services 
(888) 634-3330 
flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
