<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201709_Email_Global_MSP_Early_Scheduled Maintenance_JRD.201709_Email_Global_MSP_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Extends Maintenance Intervals for Engines Covered Under MSP</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | Business and General Aviation
HONEYWELL EXTENDS MAINTENANCE INTERVALS FOR ENGINES COVERED UNDER MSP
Dear Valued Channel Partner:


In an effort to sustain maintenance service plan (MSP) enrollment and support our authorized service center network, Honeywell is making policy changes to its maintenance intervals for MSP customers.

In the coming months, Honeywell will release two updates to extend engine intervals in order to maximize operators’ time on-wing performance. The first update is to Honeywell TFE731-5BR-1H series engine intervals and the second update is designed for all other propulsion engines enrolled in Honeywell’s MSP program.

This change is a direct result from feedback Honeywell’s received from operators and service centers to extend maintenance intervals and help customers reduce operating costs. This effort will keep engines in-service and flying under MSP which is a significant benefit to the authorized network. All MSP customers will be serviced by Honeywell service centers.

Today, the window for performing maintenance at the major periodic interval or compressor zone inspection for customers under MSP is around 100 hours. Honeywell is working to maintain MSP hourly rates by utilizing the full operating window by only performing maintenance when due per the maintenance manual or applicable service bulletin. We ask that our service centers do not tell customers that they will not be charged if they come in early.

Honeywell continues to look for ways to maintain MSP enrollments to support our authorized service center network. One example of this is improving the benefits of MSP to better meet operator needs and minimize unplanned maintenance costs (CAMP, GOLD, FOD gap).

We look forward to working with you as we continue to increase the benefits of MSP and other programs alike. Thank you for your continued support and partnership. For questions, comments or concerns, please email me directly &lt;[[mailto:bill.hurst@honeywell.com]]&gt;. 

Sincerely,

Bill Hurst 
VP, Business Aviation</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
