<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Amer_BGA_MRM-ABM-Engagement_Nurture.2.2.2 Time Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thinking about downtime during downtime</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello again,

Right now, while the entire world experiences unprecedented downtime, many people are considering how to optimize their organization’s flight experience. Some see this as an opportune time to think about and schedule needed upgrades.

We know you care about efficiency, security, equipment and systems that won’t let you or the organization down. So while equipment is idle, we urge you to consider learning more about products that can help your people use time well in the air and help you find the greatest efficiencies.

Our “Time is Critical” &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Time_Landing_Page.html]]&gt; e-book 
collection focuses on evolving technologies that could make your life and the lives of your organization’s employees more productive, easier and more efficient. Learn about technologies that allow you to know that transactions and information are secure on board, that allow you to customize connectivity by the seat and flight, and that make for smoother flights and fewer issues.

So while you and your planes are in the air less frequently, or not at all, you might consider learning about new technologies for the best use of time in the air. Our “Time Is Critical” &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Time_Landing_Page.html]]&gt; e-book collection focuses on evolving technologies that help you do that.

GET THE E-BOOKS &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Time_Landing_Page.html]]&gt;

We hope to see you in the air soon!

With warm regards,

{{lead.ABM Sales Rep:default=Kyle Vitzthum}}
{{lead.ABM Sales Rep Phone:default=(623) 336-0312}}
{{lead.ABM Sales Rep Email:default=Kyle.vitzthum@honeywell.com}}

Let&apos;s Connect! &lt;[[https://calendly.com/honeywellaerospace]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
