<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202104_Supplier-Comms_Agile-Training-Invite_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Register Today | Honeywell New Product Development Training</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell is accelerating our New Product Introduction development efforts, what we call NPI, by strategizing to dramatically reduce development cycle time while sustaining quicker lead times for new parts entering production. This transformation is an opportunity for both Honeywell and our suppliers to better serve our customers through increased speed to market, getting world-class products in the hands of our customers faster than ever before. 

 To support this initiative, Honeywell will be hosting a training session for key suppliers to learn best practices and expectations for competing and winning new business through new development programs. The training will identify the conditions that must be satisfied to be considered for new business opportunities and the Supplier support required for Agile and Design for Manufacturing (DFM) initiatives. 

 The scheduled training times and days are below.



	- Thursday, May 6: 9:00 a.m. – 11:30 a.m. PST &lt;[[https://honeywell.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_916NlZF7RQGflkTqZcjozg]]&gt;
	- Tuesday, May 11: 9:00 a.m. – 11:30 a.m. PST &lt;[[https://honeywell.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_hpKc15CxTJmuEPLRonrbbA]]&gt;


This training is targeted to business and engineering leadership, but we encourage you to extend this invitation to anyone else in your organization that would benefit from the training. Please register in advance for the session that works best for your schedule. The content shared is the same in both sessions. Please note that all attendees will need to register individually to attend. 

 Thank you in advance for your participation. We look forward to meeting with you! 

 Bobby Sohi
 Honeywell Aerospace 
 Sr. Director, ISC NPI Sourcing</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
