<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>21_CH_EMEAI_HTF7000_DR.202103_EMEAI_Email_HTF7000_DR</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Trust the Power of Jet Aviation for your Honeywell HTF7000 engine</subject>
    <textOnly>As an owner / operator of the Honeywell HTF7000 engine, you will have become familiar with its renowned reliability, durability, and maintainability. The engine has logged well over 1.7million flight hours providing operators with outstanding performance and industry-leading fuel efficiency.  However, even the best engine is only as good as the maintenance and care it receives. As an authorized Honeywell Service Centre, no-one understands or knows the HTF7000 engine better than Jet Aviation in Basel. As an approved Minor Maintenance service center, Jet Aviation can perform all routine minor HTF 7000 inspections up to the 8,000-hour maintenance.    Jet Aviation has completed over 120 HTF7000 engine events from their state-of-the-art facility in Basel, Switzerland, and through their dedicated Mobile Repair Team who are trained, equipped, and authorized to provide troubleshooting, emergency warranty and maintenance services, anywhere in the world.  Trust Jet Aviation to maintain your HTF7000 engine and benefit from their over 50 years of experience in supporting business jet operators worldwide. With world-class maintenance, repair and overhaul services, operators have come to rely on Jet Aviation to ensure their aircraft remain airworthy, while minimizing the impact on aircraft availability, performance and passenger satisfaction caused by unplanned maintenance events.
To find out more, click below. 
LEARN MORE ABOUT JET AVIATION  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2021/03/trust-power-of-jet-aviation-for-honeywell-htf7000-engine]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
