<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201811_YeovilOrdering_lg.201811_YeovilOrdering_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Order Yeovil Parts from Regional Distribution Centers</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer: 


To better support your orders for commercial spare parts designed in our Yeovil, United Kingdom (UK) site, Honeywell Aerospace will soon ship these parts from our three regional distribution centers. We are committed to improving our processes to help us deliver superior and consistent customer service.
 
This change goes into effect on January 7, 2019. Please see the list of impacted part numbers here &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Yeovil_Impacted Part Number List_Nov2018.xlsb&gt;. 
 
What is the change? 


	- Orders for impacted commercial spare parts designed in Yeovil, Somerset, UK should no longer be ordered from that facility. This excludes orders for non-commercial military and OEM orders.
	- Order directly from one of the distribution centers identified below through the MyAerospace Portal.  &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
	- Please do not email the direct Yeovil email address (yeovil.spares@honeywell.com) – this will no longer to be used.


 
Why are we making this change?   


	- Regional distribution centers maintain stock to better support your needs, resulting in faster delivery times. 
	- It’s easier to order from regional distribution centers because they are fully integrated into the ordering and order status applications on MyAerospace.
	- Orders placed on MyAerospace or through Electronic Data Interface (EDI) are automatically routed to the closest regional center for fulfillment. 


 
What about my existing orders? 


	- There is no impact to orders received before January 7, 2019. They will be processed and shipped through the current process. 


 
What do I need to know about placing new orders and obtaining new quotes? 


	- New quote requests and purchase orders issued on or after January 7, 2019 should be sent to the regional distribution center instead of to our Yeovil, UK site.
	- The regional distribution centers are fully integrated with the MyAerospace order application. 
	- Use MyAerospace to request a quote, place your order, view order status, confirm identified delivery dates and obtain way bill information.


 
What information do I need to establish these sites as new suppliers?
 
Europe Regional Distribution Center - Europe, Middle East, Africa and India




Purchase order address:
Honeywell International Sarl
Zone d’Activités La Pièce, 16
1180 Rolle
Switzerland
Cage code: SCY35
Sita Code: IATA address PRGHWCR
DUNS number: 483642950


Physical warehouse address:
Aero HIS Hemel Hempstead
Honeywell International Sarl.
Unit 2 Chevron, Eaton Rd.
Hemel Hempstead
Hertfordshire HP2 7UB
United Kingdom




 
Asia Regional Distribution Center




Purchase order address:
Honeywell International Sdn Bhd 
Level 25, UOA Corp Tower, Lobby B
Avenue 10, The Vertical 
Bangsar South City 
59200, Kuala Lumpur
Malaysia
Cage code: Y0306
Sita Code: IATA address KULASXD
DUNS number: 534416079


Physical warehouse address:
CEVA Freight Holdings (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd
Lot 9A, Jalan Tiang U8/92, Section U8 
Bukit Jelutong Industrial Park
40150 Shah Alam 
Selangor Darul Ehsan
Malaysia
 




 
Americas Regional Distribution Center 




Purchase order address:
Honeywell International Inc
1944 E. Sky Harbor Circle
Phoenix AZ 85034
United States of America
Cage code: 7X000
Sita Code: IATA address PHXASXD
DUNS number: 081323407


Physical warehouse address:
Honeywell Distribution Center
1720 E. Grant Street
Phoenix AZ 85034
United States of America




 
 
As always, we are committed to providing you with world-class products and service. Thank you for your support as we work to improve our customer service. If you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Honeywell contact. 
 
 
Honeywell Aerospace


Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
