<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Americas_Email_LASEREFIV_WJA_DR.202010_Americas_Email1_LASEREFIV_WJA_DR</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Let’s talk about your LASEREF system!</subject>
    <textOnly>LASEREF family is the industry standard for Inertial Reference System since its entry into service in 1997 and It continues this innovative tradition, with the LASEREF IV upgrade. The gyro compassing eliminates the need for magnetic sensors, and supports Heads-Up Display (HUD), Synthetic Vision System (SVS) and high-bandwidth SATCOM installations. It also meets prerequisites for Required Navigation Performance with Authorized Required approaches segments (RNP AR)  with 100% availability, and the inertial reference unit serves as a Global Navigation Satellite System (GNSS) denied solution with complete on-aircraft autonomous navigation capability in the event of GNSS interruption or jamming. Since the end of last year, Honeywell stopped supporting the aging LASEREF II and LASEREF III systems. The MSP Avionics plan also no longer convers those aging units and, you might be paying more for repairs to keep them up and running than you would if you upgraded to LASEREF IV. When you upgrade, in addition to knowing your new LASEREF IV is covered by Honeywell’s MSP Avionics plan, you will notice the following benefits: 

 	- Improved cost of maintenance with a modular design and assembly 	- MTBF (Mean Time Between Failures) consistently exceeds 40,000 hours 	- MTBUR (Mean Time Between Unscheduled Removals) more than 20,000 hours since service entry in 1997 	- 35% lighter than aging versions 	- 30 percent improvement in demonstrated reliability 

 
Want more information? For a limited time, Honeywell and Western Jet Aviation are offering attractive promotional pricing and a $52,500 Honeywell trade-in credit per unit for operators who install the LASEREF IV by Dec. 31, 2020. Don&apos;t miss this exciting savings opportunity! 
Click below to get in touch with Western Jet Aviation for more information, available STCs or to request a quote.
I WANT TO LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/upgrade-laseref-iv-western-jet-aviation]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
