<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Announcements.APG Weight and Balance</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>APG Weight and Balance Analysis Tools</subject>
    <textOnly>MyGDC Flight Planning v2.0 Beta Now Available!

For the past several years the Global Data Center has been acting upon customer suggestions requesting increased efficiencies in our flight planning website as well as expanded capabilities for flight planning, flight tracking, global strategic weather and ground-based services. We are pleased to inform you that we have streamlined the GDC flight planning interface, rewritten our software to improve performance, simplified the navigation through work-flow improvements, and are actively increasing the number of overlays that are available, to include flight tracking map improvements.

We are excited to share these improvements with you; beginning on Wednesday, August 29th the Global Data Center will make available beta access to the new flight planning experience through www.mygdc.com &lt;http://www.mygdc.com&gt;. This beta website will run in parallel with our existing website allowing you to experience the new improvements on your time frame and provide feedback to the GDC. At the conclusion of this multi-month beta period we will discontinue the old flight planning environment.

We trust that you will be impressed by these new improvements and are confident that the continued incorporation of direct customer feedback is the best way to drive value in your flight planning experience. We invite you to try the new features as you plan future trips by simply pressing the blue “Log into New GDC Beta” button after entering your GDC credentials on the www.mygdc.com &lt;http://www.mygdc.com&gt; home page.

For questions regarding the operational usage of our current websites, or other GDC features, or sales inquiries, do not hesitate to contact us at (425) 885-8100, option #1 or at gfo@mygdc.com &lt;mailto:gfo@mygdc.com&gt;.

Best Regards,



The Global Data Center Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
