<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201909_Americas_StandardAer_PEEF_Lear45.kcr.201909_Americas_StandardAero_PEEF-Le</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Have You Updated Your Learjet 45 Cockpit Technology?</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; 
 &lt;[[http://standardaero.com/]]&gt;
Upgrade Your Learjet 45 Cockpit with Primus Elite and Save up to $140k! 
 
 
 It’s time to retire the 25-year-old Cathode Ray Tube (CRT) screens on the Learjet 40/45 and brighten your vision with Honeywell&apos;s Primus Elite DU-875 displays with StandardAero.  
 
  Honeywell’s Primus Elite display upgrade was named Flying magazine’s choice for a retro-fit flat-panel solution. Upgrading to the state-of-the-art Primus Elite flight deck provides pilots with added capabilities that improve safety and comfort through increased awareness. These enhanced features and benefits include: 
 

 	- Cursor Control Device for easier scrolling on displays 	- Airport charts for visual awareness on the runway and taxiways 	- Geo-referenced departures and arrival charts for graphical depiction of aircraft position 	- Integrated maps for 2-D depiction of flight plan, weather, traffic, geographical boundaries and more 	- Integrated maps for 2-D depiction of flight plan, weather, traffic, geographical boundaries and more 	- Optional XM® Weather for real-time weather updates along the route and at destination, alternate airports, etc. 	- Increased aircraft value! 

 Want to know the best part? The Primus Elite upgrade does not require additional pilot training or cockpit modifications and in most cases, can be installed in ten working days. Upgrade before 12/31/2019 and save up to $140k* thanks to Honeywell trade-in credits and qualify for special savings on your Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan. Click below to contact StandardAero and learn more.
CONTACT STANDARDAERO &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Primus_Elite_StandardAero_201903.html]]&gt;
Not ready to upgrade to a Full Primus Elite System but still want to replace your obsolete DU-870 display? Ask about the one-for-one upgrade path, which offers a building blocks approach to Primus Elite. 

 
 
 *Trade-in credit is $35,000 per DU-870 display. The $140k savings is based on upgrading all four displays on the Learjet 45. Customers opting for the Primus Elite upgrade for all display units are eligible for one free year of MSP after the installation has been completed, and a $10,000 discount off years 2 and 3 when signing a three-year contract with Honeywell. Offer ends 12/31/2019
© {{my.year}} Honeywell International Inc.    This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=NA}}. If you don&apos;t want to receive these emails from Honeywell in the future, you can edit your profile &lt;[[]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://explore.honeywell.com/Unsubscribepage.html]]&gt;. Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement/ps-german]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://www.honeywellsafety.com/DE/Contacts.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
