<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202102_C&amp;PS_Change-Management_Loyang-to-Penang-Transition_Email-Operational.Emai</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about the Honeywell Loyang to Penang Transition - Action Before April 15th</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 

 As Honeywell advised in October 2020, we have decided to optimize our operations and close our Loyang, Singapore facility by end of 2021, with all products transitioning to our Penang facility in Malaysia. As a reminder, the product lines affected by this transition include:



	- Air Data Inertial Reference Unit (ADIRU), Air Data Computers, Airplane Information Management System (AIMS I), Radar, Recorders, Control Panel, Flight Management Computer System, Traffic Collision Avoidance System (TCAS), and Weather Radar.


For each product line transfer, dates have been provided below as to when units should no longer be sent to the Loyang facility, when units should start to be sent to the Penang facility, and where support can be obtained until the Penang facility is certified for repairing each product. The initial products will stop being received by our Loyang facility in April 2021, and all products are expected to have repair certification in Penang by March 2022.

 As listed in the transition schedule below, the first phase of part numbers will stop being received into Loyang effective April 15th, the second phase of part numbers by July 1st, and the final phase for Nov 12th, 2021. It is important to prepare for repair support during the time that our Loyang facility is de-commissioned, and the Penang facility is approved to perform repairs.

 Transition Schedule
Move 1: Repair and Overhaul Services

 
  

Product Line Description 

Loyang Last Receipt Date 

New Supplier 

Begin Shipment to New Supplier on 

Notice   

Air Data Inertial Reference Unit (ADIRU)
 Air Data Computers
Airplane Information Management System (AIMS I)
Radar
Recorders
Click Here for Parts List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Loyang-to-Penang_Transition_Part-Number-Cutoff-Dates_2-2021.xlsx]]&gt; 

April 15, 2021 

Honeywell Penang – Penang, Malaysia 

March 31, 2022 


For repair and overhaul support between the last receipt date at Loyang, and the certification date at Penang, please refer to our Repair Capabilities Locator below for available site information.
Move 2: Repair and Overhaul Services

 
    Product Line Description   Loyang Last Receipt Date   New Supplier   Begin Shipment to New Supplier on   Notice     Control Panel
 
 Flight Management Computer System
 
Traffic Collision Avoidance System (TCAS) 
 
Weather Radar
 Click Here for Parts List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Loyang-to-Penang_Transition_Part-Number-Cutoff-Dates_2-2021.xlsx]]&gt;   July 1, 2021   Honeywell Penang – Penang, Malaysia   March 31, 2022   
For repair and overhaul support between the last receipt date at Loyang, and the certification date at Penang, please refer to our Repair Capabilities Locator below for available site information.
Move 3: Repair and Overhaul Services

 
    Product Line Description   Loyang Last Receipt Date   New Supplier   Begin Shipment to New Supplier on   Notice     All Remaining Products

 Click Here for Parts List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Loyang-to-Penang_Transition_Part-Number-Cutoff-Dates_2-2021.xlsx]]&gt;   November 12, 2021   Honeywell Penang – Penang, Malaysia   December 17, 2021   
It is requested for customers to send any units requiring repair support in this Phase to Loyang by November 12, 2021, and resume all future orders to Penang by December 17, 2021.
Repair Capabilities Locator 

 As identified in the transition schedule above, alternate service locations will be required for specific product repairs until Penang is fully certified across all part numbers. You may reference all repair support information for a given part number at MyAerospace Repair Capability (ROCAPS) &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt;; available 24x7. 

 For this transition, Honeywell has pre-identified the Basingstoke, United Kingdom facility as the preferred location to be utilized based on capability and certification availability. Therefore, when multiple sites are identified as options within ROCAPS for a given part number, please select the Basingstoke UK facility to be used. It is expected the Basingstoke UK facility will have CAAC certification for their capability list associated with this transition on or before April 1st, 2021. ROCAPS will be updated to reflect based on official approval.

 Action Required 

 This notice is to remind you of the upcoming changes required before April 15th, 2020. To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions. 

 What to do now?



	- Prepare for upcoming transition: Review the transition schedule and impacted parts list provided above, adjust your supply plan as needed, resolve outstanding holds to minimize transition delays, and take actions to ensure internal systems are updated to reflect the correct Honeywell location on the correlating transition dates


	- Set/schedule updates to your internal ERP/MRP systems to support correct shipping destination per the table shown above






	- Update Authorized Supplier List (ASL) as needed: If Penang is not already on your ASL, start working to add the new supplier to your approved supplier list. Please note that for part numbers listed below in Phase Move 1 and Phase Move 2, you will need to identify an alternate repair location that meets your workscope and certification needs, until the Penang site is certified. This alternate location will also need to be updated in your ASL. If you need to conduct an on-site audit, please email your Honeywell Representative.




	- New Supplier Information: 





Honeywell Name for Repairs:
Honeywell Aerospace
Avionics Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.


Street Address:
3057, Tingkat Perusahaan 4A, Kawasan
Perusahaan Bebas St Plant 4


City, State:
Perai, Penang


Postal Code:
13600


Country:
Malaysia


Cage Code:
YA696




 Existing Repair Orders



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already in work at Loyang.




	- Some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification.




	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager, or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity.




	- Watch for PO or contract modification request from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:aerorepairs@honeywell.com]]&gt;.


New Repair Orders



	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the new location in accordance with the transition schedule.




	- Phase Move 1 part numbers received on or before April 15, 2021, will be accepted at Loyang Singapore.




	- The MyAerospace Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; (ROCAPS) will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs


Aircraft-On-Ground (AOG) Support



	- There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware.


Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 

 Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace
 Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
