<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20181_TechnicalOnlineForm_LG.20181_TechSupportWebForm_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Simplify your Technical Support Request</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customers,
It’s now easier and faster to request technical support from Honeywell. Our simple MyAerospace contact form collects the critical information we need to start solving your technical issue immediately. This reduces back-forth communications, helps us connect you with the right expert, and even displays suggested solutions for immediate resolution. And, as always, you can track your inquiry status on the MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support&gt;. 




If you are already a MyAerospace registered user, simply login from the contact us page &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/forms&gt;, choose &quot;technical issue&quot; or learn more about our online technical support &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt;. You can also access the technical form 
directly &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/forms/technical-issue/commercial&gt;. If you haven&apos;t started taking advantage of MyAerospace yet, please follow this easy registration process &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Updates%20Training%20Materials/MyAerospace%20-%20How%20To%20Register.pdf]]&gt;. 




Use this MyAerospace technical issue contact form to streamline your support:


	- Enter only your aircraft, product, and technical issue - there’s no need to enter your contact information again after login.
	- Attach any relevant files, such as BITE download files, photos, or screen shots that will help us understand your issue and shorten our response time.
	- View real-time solutions as you enter your technical problem description.
	- Track your request online so you always know the latest status.


 
Our goal is to solve your technical issue as quickly as we can while also making it easy for you.






Visit 
MyAerospace  &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;








Please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Subscription_Page.html]]&gt; to subscribe to our email communications.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
