<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201802_Global_Email_APU_131-9A_mih.201802_Global_Email_APU_131-9A_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>6 Reasons for {{company.Company Name:default=your airline}} to Retrofit Honeywell 131-9A APU</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},
 
 Retrofitting an Auxiliary Power Unit (APU) is not an easy decision and we understand this. Cost approvals, operational hassles and satisfactory performance of existing APU are good enough reasons to keep you from venturing into an uncharted territory.  
 
 Honeywell&apos;s six-point, power-packed proposition that will drive you to consider 131-9A APU retrofit:



	- 131-9A APU scores much higher over competing systems in power, ease of maintenance, cost of ownership and noise &amp; emissions. It’s an APU with superior performance (not just satisfactory)
	- 

With 131-9A’s fuel saving advantage, lower start cart cost, higher reliability, easy &amp; cost efficient maintenance, and new engine warranty, recover the retrofit costs much earlier than you expect 

	- Given our long standing experience in APU integration, we ensure smooth and hassle free retrofit with minimal operational disruption. Further, with Airbus Service Bulletin 49-1055, retrofit can be easily accomplished

	- 

We are offering special pricing + an exchange offer on your existing serviceable or non-serviceable APU for new 131-9A APU

	- 

Globally, there are number of airlines which are selecting and retrofitting 131-9A. Recently Asiana and Air New Zealand chose to retrofit 131-9A over their existing APU. So many airlines cannot be wrong! 

	- 

131-9A opens door for adopting Honeywell GoDirect Connected Maintenance Services that reduce APU related operational disruptions through predictive maintenance notification




 Standard APU for Airbus 320 family, superior performance, quick cost recovery, smooth transition, access to connected services, and a special offer – 131-9A APU retrofit proposition couldn’t have been more compelling.   
 
 So, what are you waiting for? Talk to our sales team today &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/131-91-apu-2.html]]&gt;. 
 
 
 
 Best regards

Graham Davies
Honeywell Aerospace 
 
 





Talk to Honeywell sales team &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/131-91-apu-2.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
