<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_02_February.2019_February_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - February 2019 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
February 2019
&quot;HONEYWELL SUPPORT...
SIMPLE AS ORDERING A PIZZA&quot;
Services are available for many Honeywell products, including mechanical, avionics and environmental control systems. Learn why NASCAR Champion Brad Keselowski and his pilots rely on HAPP and MSP...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://youtu.be/Q60ijIkuXGo]]&gt;
Field Service Engineer John Braidich is energized by avionics mysteries
 
Field Service Engineer John Braidich has always loved a good mystery. When a Honeywell customer reaches out, Braidich digs in like a seasoned detective to assess the situation, gather evidence, analyze the problem and find the right solution as quickly as possible... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/february/avionics-mysteries-energize-long-time-field-service-engineer]]&gt;.
SPEX option for ADS-B Upgrade available for PC-12NG operators
The window of opportunity is rapidly closing to upgrade your transponders to comply with the 2020 ADS-B Out mandate. If you haven&apos;t upgraded yet, Honeywell has a way to expedite the process. You can utilize our SPEX program to exchange... Learn More &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/ADS-B Mandate - PC12NG SPEX Offer.pdf]]&gt;.
The dirty little secret about Ka vs Ku frequencies

There’s a running debate about the merits of the Ka and Ku frequency bands. But here’s a dirty little secret. Your passengers couldn’t care less... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/january/ka-band-vs-ku-band-the-difference-between-ku-and-ka-band-frequencies]]&gt;.
Are you looking for the latest service bulletins?

There&apos;s an easy way to get the data: log in to our MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[myaerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt; and go to Technical Bulletins.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
