<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2020_Primus_Elite_SV.2020_F900_Primus_Elite_SV_Email_B</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Primus Elite Synthetic Vision Now Certified for F900C/EX - Buy Now &amp; Receive Up to $65K in MSP Savings!</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell’s Primus Elite Synthetic Vision Is Now Certified for Your F900 C/EX!
More than 50 percent of F900 C/EX operators have upgraded their cockpits with new Primus Elite DU-875 liquid crystal displays. If you haven’t upgraded yet, the time is right. Honeywell has special pricing incentives in place. 
If you have already upgraded, now’s the time to add Primus Elite Synthetic Vision and get an entirely new view.



Wouldn’t you rather see as you fly it – in color and in three dimensions – rather than the old tradition blue-over-brown? 
Synthetic Vision adds new levels of situational awareness by realistically depicting your flight path as an easy-to-understand overlay on the primary flight display, just as it would appear out the cockpit windscreen. In three dimensions, and in color – no more blue-over-brown! And we have pricing incentives in place for you too.The upgrade provides benefits and features you’ll find in the most sophisticated cockpits in operation today.

To make your upgrade even more attractive, Honeywell is offering incentives that could save you nearly $65,000 on your multi-year Maintenance Service Plan – Avionics when you upgrade with Primus Elite SV: 



	- First year of coverage is free – an estimated savings of $45,000 to $50,000
	- Receive $10,000 off regular contract price during second and third year
	- Fixed 3% escalation offered on multi-year agreements


If your aircraft isn&apos;t flying during these troubled times, this is the perfect opportunity to upgrade without impacting flight schedules.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cockpit-systems-and-displays/primus-elite-875-885?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_americas_bga_primuselite]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
