<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>March 2017 Edition.March 2017 Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - March 2017 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
March 2017
DON’T BE LATE FOR YOUR ADS-B DATE
The ADS-B Out Mandate requires you to have your aircraft upgraded by December 31, 2019, and your big date draws nearer each day. Get ready now!







 READ MORE       &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/march/don-t-be-late-for-your-ads-b-date-book-your-upgrade-today]]&gt;
Low Vis? No Problem with Primus Elite’s Advanced Features Synthetic Vision Option We’ve all been there, approaching an unfamiliar runway, ceiling less than 1000 feet, with visibility less than three miles. Would’ve been easier with a better view...
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/march/low-vis-no-problem-with-primus-elite-s-advanced-features-synthetic-vision-option]]&gt;
Protected Mode - Controller Pilot Data Link Communication Can&apos;t fly over there in 2020 without. Upgrade now...
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/FANS-mandates]]&gt;
GoDirect Flight Sentinel gets you there  GoDirect Flight Sentinel makes life easier for corporate flight departments and improves the flying experience for passengers. Powered by Honeywell’s Global Data Center, GoDirect Flight Sentinel takes critical flight planning, flight following and problem mitigation tasks off your shoulders... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/flight-sentinel]]&gt;
Honeywell JetWave connects Falcon 900 passengers to the &quot;best internet in the sky&quot;  JetWave hardware is the only system that enables business aviation aircraft to connect to Inmarsat’s Jet ConneX network - the fastest broadband service in the sky for business aviation... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2017/february/honeywell-jetwave-connect-falcon-900-passengers-to-the-best-internet-in-the-sky]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
