<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>July 2018 Edition.July 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - July 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
July 2018
CUSTOMER SUPPORT MANAGER REALIGNMENT ENHANCES CUSTOMER CONNECTIONS
Honeywell Customer and Product Support has realigned Customer Support Managers (CSM) in the Americas to better serve operators. Operators who have newly assigned CSM were notified by email. Our Direct Access app has CSM and field service engineer contact information...





DIRECT ACCESS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt;
Field service engineer jumps in to serve customers 
In a previous life, Mitch Eldridge was a U.S. Navy search and rescue swimmer, trained to jump out of helicopters to save downed seamen. Today, as a senior field support engineer, he jumps in feet to solve problems for customers... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/july/field-support-engineer-jumps-in-to-serve-customers]]&gt;
Upgrade improves 36-150 auxiliary power unit reliability
A new hydrodynamic seal and other configuration changes have improved the reliability of one of Honeywell&apos;s most widely used auxiliary power units... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/july/upgrade-improves-36-150-apu-reliability]]&gt;
Save 50 percent on SmartLanding® and SmartRunway®
Yes, you read this correctly: for a limited time save 50 percent when you upgrade to the leading safety solutions that reduce the white-knuckle approaches and takeoffs at challenging airports...
Read more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/SmartRunwayLanding.html]]&gt;
GoDirect Maintenance Advisor now available
Honeywell&apos;s new maintenance application, GoDirect Maintenance Advisor, is free to customers who have a current Honeywell Avionics Protection 
Plan contract... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/godirect-maintenance-advisor]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
