<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS.FMS Dec 2016</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Quick Answers to Your FMS Technical Questions</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
QUICK ANSWERS TO YOUR FMS TECHNICAL QUESTIONS


Do you need quick answers to support your flight management system (FMS)? Visit our new FMS support web page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/airline-fms-support]]&gt; to access immediate answers to your most common questions. 
On this single page, link to all essential files, such as technical publications, service bulletins, and service information letters. Need some tips on how to load a navigation database? It’s all here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/airline-fms-support]]&gt;. 
We have also answered your frequently asked questions covering topics from how to check battery life to understanding memory capacity. We will continue to update troubleshooting information, so keep checking back. 
And, if you need us to troubleshoot your flight management system and support a BITE analysis, view the page that walks you through that process and download the files we need. 
This is the first of many product-specific support pages that we will launch over 2017 on the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;. The Portal is your home to access technical solutions and open or track cases. 





Thank you for your business,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support





© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
 &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=]]&gt; 



Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
