<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201804_Global_Email_EGPWM-Threat _mih.201804_Global_Email_EGPWM-Threat _mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>EGPWM Threat Terrain Database Release Notification - Version 602</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},
Honeywell has just released a new EGPWM Threat Terrain Database - version 602 – for aircraft equipped with the Honeywell Primus Epic cockpit. This latest terrain database version is an update to the previous version 601 and adds several new airports, runways and obstacles while improving terrain mapping and resolution.

NOTE:



	- This notice is applicable to INDS customers as well. The EGPWM update is available now via the INDS website or via the IDM application. It will be automatically included on your next data delivery.


The database and supporting documentation such as loading instructions and a certificate of conformance can be downloaded by visiting ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiWkdZelpqZGhPR016TmpabSIsInQiOiJHRVNjZlJhV0VMdnVUdEswYWtxeldRRFwveGdha2x2aTkwWTBmcHRwSHg5UXJqMHZ3cjlwSklBeWF2Sm15eGlKTTVWb01SRGJ4bFJyRXlvUUtIaHlmeXc9PSJ9]]&gt; (login required). EGPWS database search tools and change info are located at that same address (no login required). Look under the search tab and the change info tab. A letter of acceptance (LOA) document is located under the documents archive tab for applicable configurations. A release statement, located under the updates tab, may be referenced to confirm the status of the LOA.

Database download and media creation capability for all EGPWS products now available in the OneNav+ tool, version 1.21.0 or a higher version needed (no license required), additional OneNav+ features are being developed for EGPWS databases and 
will be available in future releases.

Please click here &lt;[[mailto:dsa@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWM Query]]&gt; if you have any technical questions concerning the database.

Please click here &lt;[[mailto:myaerospaceportalissue@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWM Query]]&gt; if you have any questions concerning operation or access to Honeywell websites.


 Best regards, 
 
 The Honeywell EGPWS Team


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2017_Email_Confirmation_OptOut.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
