<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202012_Global_MSP-TES_Email.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>36-100/150 BGA APU Rental Bank sold to Turbine Engine Specialists (TES) &amp; Announcement of TES RE220GX Overhaul Capability</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 

 Honeywell has recently sold their Business and General Aviation 36-100/150 APU rental bank to Turbine Engine Specialist (TES) located in Fort Worth, Texas. In addition, Honeywell has authorized TES Overhaul Capability on the Bombardier RE220GX APU product line. TES has been a Honeywell authorized Channel Partner for almost 20 years and will continue to provide 36-100/150 APU rentals noted in Table 1 below for both MSP and retail customers. 

 There will be no change to your current process on how you request a rental APU. Should you need an APU rental engine, contact your Honeywell authorized Channel Partner who will request a rental engine from TES on your behalf. 

 MSP customers will continue to pay their normal MSP rate when using a rental APU from TES. There will be no additional charge for MSP customers. 

 For anyone currently renting a 36-100/150 rental engine, no change in rental paperwork will be necessary. The current rental bailment will remain in effect until your APU is complete and rental removed. Utilize the Honeywell Channel Partner that installed the rental engine to remove the rental engine. 

 TES will work in the coming months to ramp up their overhaul capability and readiness to support customers on the RE220GX and we will provide further information closer to program “go live” date.

 Honeywell continues to optimize MSP so that operators can schedule maintenance with our industry-leading service center network worldwide while minimizing unplanned 
maintenance costs. As part of this transition, TES plans to continue to locate APUs worldwide in the same or similar locations that are used today in order to provide maximum availability. 

 Over the coming weeks Honeywell &amp; TES will continue with the transition of all APU assets. In January 2021 Honeywell will provide additional information regarding this full transition with TES including TES contact details and other applicable information. 

 We look forward to working with you as we continue to increase the benefits of MSP and other programs alike. We appreciate your business and thank you for your continued support. 

 Sincerely, 

 Bill Hurst 
 VP, Business Aviation
Table 1. BGA 36-100/150 Rental Models transitioned to TES 
 
 
 
 
     Model   Aircraft     36-100A   Falcon 50     36-100E   CL 600/601      36-100G   G-II/III/IV     36-100H2   HS-125 series     36-150BD   C300/C350     36-150CL   CL 601/604/605/650     36-150CX   Citation X     36-150DD   DO 328     36-150EMB   Cit Longitude/Legacy 450/500     36-150F   Falcon 900/900EX     36-150F2M   Falcon 2000/2000EX     36-150FN   Falcon F7X/8X     36-150G   GIV/G300/G400     36-150GIV   G-IV-SPX     36-150HH   Hawker 4000     36-150IAI   G200/280     36-150M   BAe 146-300     36-150W   Cit III/VI/VII, Astra SPX, Hawker 750XP,800XP,900XP,Falcon20</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
