<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202011_Portal_Update_November_Email_MC.202011_Portal_Update_November_Email_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Portal Updates – November 2020</subject>
    <textOnly>Same Day/Next Day Shipping – For Business &amp; General Aviation and Airlines MyAerospace users, parts MAY ship in as little as 24 hours from the time of order as inventory and contractual agreements permit. ONLY on make-to-stock parts. Currently this is only available for Sky Harbor and the GMS distribution center (Deer Valley Plant 1009).

 Exchange Order Core Return Tag – You can now download the Core Return Tag within Order Status for Exchange orders.

 Honeywell Assist – Virtual 
Chatbot – In our last communication we shared the launch of our virtual chatbot, Honeywell Assist. This chatbot, is a virtual assistant and not a live person. Currently, the chatbot is still learning and can only help pull up quick, summary information in the following areas as you go through the prompts within the chat.


	- Order Status
	- Part Availability
	- Pricing Information
	- Technical Solutions
	- FAQ


Honeywell Assist is not meant to be a replacement for how you would normally use our MyAerospace Portal. If you need more detailed information regarding your order, part and pricing availability please go to the Order Status and Online Ordering pages within the portal as you normally would.

 For more information, please visit our training topic page on the chatbot HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/dca-chatbot]]&gt; which includes a demo recording. 

 A few reminders…

 Pricing Exception for Spares Orders – Within Online Ordering, if you would like to add a pricing exception for your Spares order, please refer to the training topic page HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/online-ordering-pricing-exceptions]]&gt;.

 Reports and Notifications – To receive reports and notifications for your orders via email, please visit the training topic page on how to turn this functionality 
ON and modify per your needs: How do I receive orders reports &amp; notifications &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/order-status/reports-notifications]]&gt;?

 To view the individual release notes for the items listed above and to catch up on latest improvements to MyAerospace, please refer to and 
bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;
Please be sure to Opt-IN to receive important portal enhancement update emails. 









   OPT-IN  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
