<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Americas_SpiritAero_HoneywellMSP_kcr.201905_Amer_SpiritAero_HoneywellMSP_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the New Maintenance Service Plan from Honeywell</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;  &lt;[[http://www.spiritaeronautics.com/]]&gt;

New Name, Same Great Protection You Trust

Protect your aircraft with the new Maintenance Service Plan from Honeywell. The Maintenance Service Plan is an umbrella of offerings that incorporates the legacy Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) and Maintenance Protection Plan (MPP) Programs. 

The Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan - Avionics (MSP Avionics, formally HAPP) offers flexible coverage options, allowing you to pick the right coverage for your needs. Benefits and features of MSP Avionics include:



	- 24/7 Aircraft on Ground (AOG) emergency service

	- Factory-backed support identical to your original factory warranty
	- Field system support and access to a global network of authorized sales and service centers
	- Full coverage on exchange and repair services
	- Fully transferable maintenance agreements
	- No charge loaners
	- Full content coverage
	- Targeted obsolescence coverage*


Rest easy knowing you are benefiting from more than 40 years of experience. To learn more and enroll, contact Spirit Aeronautics today at (614) 344-9195 &lt;tel:614-344-9195&gt; or online by clicking below!





CONTACT SPIRIT AERONAUTICS ONLINE! &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/control-the-unexpected-and-keep-your-aircraft-where-it-belongs-in-the-sky?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_spiritaero_msp-avionics&amp;utm_content=customer+form+fill]]&gt;






** Targeted obsolescence coverage is an optional upgrade for MSP Avionics and MSP Avionics Gold that can be selected based on your operational needs.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
