<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201808_global_BK Channel NL_LM.201808_global_BK Channel NL_LM_v2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>August BendixKing Channel Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;


BendixKing Channel Newsletter | August 2018
&lt;[[http://www.bendixKing.com]]&gt;
Channel Partners, 

The half-way point of the year is behind us and BendixKing appreciates your support through the final 4 months. We have incorporated additional repair partners, new products, and improvements to our website. These resources will provide you the best opportunity to finish up strong and reach your desired goals. Here are some updates and important reminders from your BendixKing family.
Channel Partner Program 
 Earlier in the year we announced our Channel Partner Program that talked about the commitments from BendixKing 
and the requirements of a BendixKing Channel partner. https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Dealer-Newsletters &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZhx0uzG0000r0Zw20qXQJ]]&gt; 
 
 Audits and Repair  
 We have been, and will continue to, audit channel partners for violations of their agreed upon repair capability. This honors our commitment to protect the investment by those of you who have opted in to level 3 repairs.  As a friendly reminder, verify whether you opted in or out of the level 3 field approved repairs (this is the $3,500 annual fee present in the signed Avionics Dealership Agreement). Violators of this agreement will be subject to penalties as detailed in the signed AvDA and General Term Agreements. For any BendixKing LRU you are no longer authorized to repair, please ensure that you remove mention of your repair capability from your promotional materials, including websites, to avoid violations.
We ask that you review this and if you have any concerns or questions, please reach out to your area sales manager or send an email to sales@bendixking.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@bendixking.com]]&gt;.
 
 KA 61 L-Band antenna 
A new L-Band antenna is available for purchase that will be a direct replacement for the KA 61 antenna in most cases. Please see the Service Information Letter for more information - document number D201805000010 in Honeywell Technical Publications &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/MZ0X0r0ZQMhuG00Cq0xI0w2]]&gt;.

 QUICK LINKS
 Repair Partners
 &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/a0200q0urQ0Z00BXyIZJhxG]]&gt;Current Promotions &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/NI00vQrG000uxMX0BZh0Z2q]]&gt;
 AeroWave 100 $5000 rebate promotion &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/T2ZQM0x0u000ZIW20qhrGX0]]&gt;


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/v0SD0ZWp0GqXQuTuI02t000]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
