<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201706_Global_Email_MediaNewsletter_Honeywell_LES.201706_Global_Email_MediaNewsl</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Stay Connected with Honeywell - Connectivity Newsletter Q2 2017</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HONEYWELL CONNECTIVITY MEDIA NEWSLETTER
Q2 2017
STAY CONNECTED WITH HONEYWELL
The second Honeywell connectivity media newsletter is here! Tune in every quarter for the latest Honeywell connectivity news and updates for the aviation industry.
EXECUTIVE VIEW: MAKING THE CONNECTED AIRCRAFT A REALITY
The Connected Aircraft isn’t just an idea; we’ve brought it to life with our Boeing 757 test aircraft that just kicked off The Power of Connected world tour. We’re developing and implementing connected solutions with airlines and aircraft operators around the world to streamline decision-making and reduce operational costs at every phase of flight. Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/june/making-the-connected-aircraft-a-reality]]&gt; from Michael Edmonds, president, Connectivity and Services.
ROCKING THE POWER OF CONNECTED WORLD TOUR


We&apos;ve kicked off the Power of Connected World Tour to showcase our latest technology, applications and services on the Honeywell Boeing 757 Connected Aircraft to media and customers. The first few whirlwind days were just the start of a tour that will run all summer and span the globe. After a couple of busy stops in New York and London, we&apos;re off to Paris for the world’s biggest air show. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/june/rocking-the-power-of-connected-world-tour]]&gt;
POWERING THE SKIES AND PREDICTING THE FUTURE
Mechanical components and software are converging and are no longer operating separately. With Honeywell’s experience in aircraft auxiliary power units (APUs), engines and automotive turbo chargers, we can strike a balance between mechanical and software expertise, so customers can continue extending the value of their aviation assets. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2017/june/powering-the-skies-and-predicting-the-future]]&gt;
WHY GREEN IS THE NEW BLACK
According the International Air Transport Association (IATA), global jet fuel prices have risen 10 percent over the past year. While that may not seem like a big jump, fuel costs account for somewhere between 20 to 40 percent of any airline’s total expenditures. A 10 percent jump is a significant cost that any smart airline needs to battle against. How do airlines fight back against rising costs? It can be as simple as software. Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/june/why-green-is-the-new-black?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0dZd01UazNPR0ZpWVRBMyIsInQiOiJZQ1I1aWZFWTY4OVBYdWoyTzdXMmdWM2wrYldJdFpWc2JcL3JKTWR0TE40a0pRMEtEUHh4MWRSXC9EaStGbWJsNFM0MG83QjZldlZyWWFyTzN2cEl1NkdRPT0ifQ%3D%3D]]&gt;. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/june/why-green-is-the-new-black?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT0dZd01UazNPR0ZpWVRBMyIsInQiOiJZQ1I1aWZFWTY4OVBYdWoyTzdXMmdWM2wrYldJdFpWc2JcL3JKTWR0TE40a0pRMEtEUHh4MWRSXC9EaStGbWJsNFM0MG83QjZldlZyWWFyTzN2cEl1NkdRPT0ifQ%3D%3D]]&gt;
IN CASE YOU MISSED IT: RECENT CONNECTIVITY NEWS FROM HONEYWELL
Connected Aircraft Lifts Off &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/connected-aircraft-lifts-off-honeywell-s-power-of-connected-world-tour-coming-to-a-city-near-you]]&gt;
Top OEM&apos;s Pick Honeywell Connected Aircraft Solution &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/yi2Q000Z0G0qXIU00Q00020]]&gt;
Dassault Selects Honeywell&apos;s JetWave System as Preferred High-Speed Wi-Fi Option for New Falcons &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/dassault-selects-honeywell-s-jetwave-system-as-preferred-high-speed-wi-fi-option-for-new-falcons]]&gt;
Connected Aircraft: Embraer Jets to Fly with Honeywell&apos;s JetWave System for High-Speed Wi-Fi &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/connected-aircraft-embraer-jets-to-fly-with-honeywell-s-jetwave-system-for-high-speed-wi-fi]]&gt;
Hainan Airlines First to Adopt Honeywell&apos;s Groundbreaking GoDirect Maintenance Service &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/hainan-airlines-first-to-adopt-honeywell-s-groundbreaking-godirect-maintenance-service]]&gt;
Honeywell, Cathay Pacific Connected Aircraft Test Program Delivers Substantial Savings in Flight Operations Maintenance &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/honeywell-cathay-pacific-connected-aircraft-program-delivers-savings]]&gt;
Thomas Cook Airlines Scandinavia Chooses Honeywell Software to Improve Fuel Efficiency &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/may/thomas-cook-airlines-scandinavia-chooses-honeywell-software-to-improve-fuel-efficiency]]&gt;
Honeywell Features GoDirect Suite of Aviation Services at Asia’s Largest Business Aviation Event &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/april/honeywell-features-godirect-suite-of-aviation-services-at-asias-largest-business-aviation-event]]&gt;
Honeywell Selected by Jiangsu Jet to Provide a VVIP-Class Flying Experience &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/april/honeywell-selected-by-jiangsu-jet-to-provide-a-vvip-class-flying-experience]]&gt;
Honeywell Introduces New Lightweight Satellite Communications System for Cockpit Safety &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/april/honeywell-introduces-new-lightweight-satellite-communications-system-for-cockpit-safety]]&gt;
Honeywell Unveils the Power of the Connected Aircraft at Aircraft Interiors EXPO 2017 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/april/honeywell-unveils-the-power-of-the-connected-aircraft-at-aircraft-interiors-expo-2017]]&gt;
AirAsia Upgrades to JetWave &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Q02X00I0QV2q00ZiG00R000]]&gt;
Honeywell Puts GoDirect Cabin Connectivity Services in the Hands of Business Jet Operators to Control the In-Cabin Experience &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ002000Z0S02X00qiI00WG]]&gt;
Inmarsat’s GX Aviation In-flight Broadband Enters Commercial Service with Lufthansa Group &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/P000Z0GQqI00X00200TXi02]]&gt;
Qatar Airways to Offer Next Generation Inmarsat GX Aviation In-Flight Broadband Service &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/p0000Q0iUX000YZIGq00022]]&gt;
To keep updated on the latest connectivity and Honeywell news, please watch this alias or visit the Honeywell News page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
