<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201908_Global_Helo_Customer_Connect_Newsletter_Lorenzo.201908_Global_Email_Helo_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Here Is Your August Issue Of Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer,
I have a lot of updates to share this month. Along with these updates, I would like to invite you to join Honeywell’s online social community. Connect with over 400k followers to discuss the latest articles, announcements and unique stories covering everything from business aviation, to urban air mobility. 

Follow our channels:  
  &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;
Did You Know?

If you are a Bell407HP Operator, this Utah Operators Conference is for youHoneywell will be holding an HTS900 Operator’s Conference on October 16, 2019 in Lindon, Utah. This conference will bring together the HTS900 engine operators with the Honeywell Product Support Team for technical discussions and collaboration. Also, participating will be our partners: Eagle Copters and Intermountain Turbine Services. If you are a Bell 407HP operator and would like to attend, please contact deta.adams@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto: deta.adams@honeywell.com]]&gt; for information on how to receive an invitation. 

FSE Creates ‘Wow’ Moments for Latin American Operators Field Service Engineer Fernando Vasquez Orellana has spent 20 years solving problems for 
Honeywell customers in Latin America. Currently based in Toluca, Mexico, Fernando works with business aviation operators in Mexico, Central America and the Caribbean to get them the solutions they need. Here is his story on how he works with customers in Mexico to create those “wow” moments. Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/august/fse-creates-wow-moments-for-latin-american-operators]]&gt;. Technical Support Video of the Month In this months’ Technical Video segment, we’re featuring the most watched video on Condition Based Maintenance and Honeywell&apos;s Health and Usage Monitoring System - HUMS. Honeywell&apos;s Condition Based Maintenance solutions and services have been matured through over 20 years of world class applications.  
CBM and HUMS &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pIKFXufkBo&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ002000Z0L0bX00qFI00jG]]&gt; to access the Technical Knowledge Center&apos;s thousands of articles and videos to help you solve technical issues, parts ordering, your 
order status and much more. Spanish and Portuguese Technical Support Numbers Your 
requests have been answered! The Honeywell Customer and Product Support team is excited to launch technical support phone numbers in the Central and South American regions. Starting in August, Honeywell will now have support for Spanish and Portuguese speakers. Here are the new phone numbers: 
Mexico - 528004360128
Colombia - 018000125387
Chile - 800395072
Brazil - 080000474059
Technical support made easy and personalized with Direct Access Latest 
Update It just got easier! Direct Access is one of Honeywell&apos;s customer support mobile apps that is available to Business &amp; General Aviation pilots and flight 
departments. The app is a customer service one-stop-shop that provides aircraft-on-ground (AOG) support, order status information, helicopter support and includes an interactive map of the nearest dealers and service centers. In update 9.0, Honeywell introduced a convenient and personalized mobile experience making it easier to contact technical support and register for the local Operator Conferences. Click here for more information and to download the app &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt;.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:

María L. Lorenzo
 Customer Support Program Manager
 Office: (787) 658-1985
 Mobile: (787) 675-4957
 Email: Maria.Lorenzo@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:maria.lorenzo@honeywell.com]]&gt;

Need immediate support? Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
