<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>September 2018 Edition.September 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - September 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
September 2018
PIONEERING THE DATA-DRIVEN FUTURE AT NBAA 2018
Visit us at Booth #2600 to learn how Honeywell is pioneering the collection and use of data from all aircraft systems to control costs on the ground and in the air, prolong systems viability and performance, and improve safety...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/october/nbaa-business-aviation-convention-,-a-,-exhibition-]]&gt;
Just call Jack 

 

 Field Service Engineer Jack Wolf&apos;s job is all about getting customers the right answer as quickly as possible... 
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/august/veteran-fse-sees-almost-everything-change]]&gt;.
GoDirect Flight Sentinel is your personal support staff
  From start to finish, the Flight Sentinel team monitors the position and progress of your flight while looking ahead for weather hazards, traffic 
congestion, ground delays...  View video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/tnQ7cmHsW-4]]&gt;.
The GoDirect router - small, light, and fast

GoDirect Router offers big performance in a small package. In the most important advancement in router technology in years, Honeywell has reinvented the airborne router... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/godirect-router]]&gt;.
Take advantage of new 100 percent tax write-off for component upgrades 
 
One of the more than 100 changes to the U.S. tax code signed into law in 2017 is that the purchase price of a new and used airplane, or component retrofit / upgrades, by a company can be written off 100 percent against its earnings. Install now and save on your 2018 taxes.
Sign up for free webcast - GoDirect™ Jet ConneX Service Plans.

Join us for our webcast on Wednesday, October 10 at 8:00 a.m. PT / 11:00 a.m. ET and find out how GoDirect and Jet ConneX service plans allow passengers and flight crews to experience home-like wi-fi in the sky!



REGISTER NOW &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/GoDirect_Webinar.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
