<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Global_Email2_GoDirect Trade_Seller_Nurture_Campaign_mih.Subject Line Tes</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>88% of your customers prefer e-commerce, even if the part is more expensive</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/sellers?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;Source Study: Positioning Strategic e-commerce in a Digital-First World, The 2019 B2B Buyer Report
Buyers value a digital channel and efficiency over price!

A recent report revealed that online B2B buyers are not shopping based on price. They’re looking for the best overall experience with full product information and transparency being a top priority. In fact, “the vast majority of B2B buyers between the ages of 18 and 25 prefer online shopping processes, compared to 70 percent of those aged 36 and above.&quot;

GoDirectTrade.com online is a cutting edge aerospace marketplace that provides a unique, frictionless buyer experience!At GoDirectTrade.com we&apos;re not 
surprised with the report &lt;[[https://www.avionos.com/2019-b2b-buyer-report/]]&gt; findings!
Our online marketplace is built around quality listings that make it easy for buyers to choose YOUR products. We’re truly driving innovation and efficiency into the purchasing process, one listing and one order at a time. Our creative structure, requiring images, documents and price online for every part listed allows buyers to find what they want and checkout immediately.  A no hassle, frictionless buying experience is what we’re all about.
Become a seller on GoDirectTrade.com today!
Please contact us to learn more about starting your own storefront at our online marketplace. With over 2000 active buyers from 820+ companies, we can help you sell more online, reducing your cost to sell by utilizing our proven approach.




INQUIRE ABOUT OUR EXCLUSIVE OFFER FOR SELLERS &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/sellers?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
