<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201909_Customer_Connect_Newsletter_Meza.201909_Email_Customer_Connect_Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Here is your September Issue of Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>CUSTOMER CONNECT SEPTEMBER 2019

Dear Honeywell Customer,


This month, I’ll highlight the latest field service engineer profile, the technical support video of the month and other pertinent customer support updates. As always, if you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.
Did You 
Know?

Former Mechanic Still Focused on Customer Fixes 
Honeywell Field Service Engineer Efrain Villafane knows aircraft engines from the inside out. He spent a big part of his 20-year aviation industry career working as a mechanic for legendary aircraft manufacturers Cessna and Bombardier. He doesn’t turn wrenches much anymore. But Efrain is still “Mr. Fixit” when it comes to business aircraft operators with engine problems. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/september/former-mechanic-still-focused-on-customer-fixes]]&gt; 

Technical Support Video of the Month 
In this months’ Technical Support Video segment, 
we’re featuring the most watched video on SATCOM, Honeywell&apos;s in-flight Satellite Communications system. In this day and age of increased global connectivity, Honeywell&apos;s SATCOM system provides passengers and flight crews with world wide data and voice communications in both the air and on the ground. Watch the overview video: 


SATCOM &lt;[[http://youtu.be/t6jd-s0zUik]]&gt;

Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ002000Z0L0bX00qFI00jG]]&gt; to access the Technical Knowledge Center&apos;s thousands of articles and videos to help you solve technical issues, parts ordering, your order status and much more. 

Your Honeywell Field Support Representatives are 3 Clicks Away 
In the latest update, Honeywell introduced a convenient and personalized mobile experience to contact your Honeywell Representatives on-the-go. With 3 easy clicks, you can contact your local Field Service Engineer from anywhere in the world. Your dedicated Field Service Engineer will automatically appear as you select “talk to a technical expert” on the app. Download the app and try for yourself! &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/direct-access]]&gt; 



Getting Around the Pilot Gateway Just Got Easier  
 The Honeywell Pilot Gateway has been going through some big changes. While users still have the most up-to-date information on aviation events, news, and technology at their fingertips, now it’s easier than ever to find just what you’re looking for! Read about some of the new features here. Read more. &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Y0GwA0uZK00sr002qIQ0tXG]]&gt;
Jazmin A Meza 


Customer Support Manager
Mobile: + 52 686-119-3062 
Email:  Jazmin.Meza@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Jazmin.Meza@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
