<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global Newsletter.May 15, 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aero Express Americas: A350 from concept to reality, IDS update on flow, Site HSE awards, Army VIP visits engine site, 50-year employee, White House &apos;Joining Forces&apos; award, volunteer profile and more...</subject>
    <textOnly> 

 










May 15, 2013
Americas Edition















Airbus A350: Taking the concept to reality
In the coming weeks, a historic milestone will occur – the first flight of the Airbus A350 XWB aircraft. The A350 – Airbus’ new long-range wide-body aircraft – represents one of the largest development programs in Honeywell Aerospace history. When it takes to the skies for its inaugural flight, it will be equipped with Honeywell’s HGT1700 auxiliary power unit, environmental and cabin pressure control systems, supplemental cooling, ventilation and fans; bleed air systems; and wing anti-ice systems. Honeywell also will provide the A350 with its proven flight management system and aircraft environment surveillance system. Making history… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/AirbusA350Takingtheconcepttoreality.aspx&gt;

 





New IDS podcast gives update on flow transformation
Listen to this Integrated Delivery System (IDS) podcast &lt;http://ez.com/IDSPodcast26May2013&gt; for the latest on our flow transformation progress and what’s ahead. Mark Howes, IDS Vice President, and T.J. Castle, Honeywell Operating System (HOS) Vice President, also discuss the relationship between flow deployment and HOS implementation. Reminder: previous IDS podcasts are on the IDS home page &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/ids/Pages/IDShome.aspx&gt;.









3 sites win 2012 HSE Excellence, Process Improvement awards
Health, Safety, Environment &amp; Facilities (HSE&amp;F) has selected the 2012 Aerospace HSE Excellence and Process Improvement award winners. Top honors for HSE Excellence go to Boxgrove/Broadstairs in the small site category and Greer, S.C., for the large site, pictured here. The first Process Improvement Award goes to the Aguadilla, Puerto Rico, site. In this video &lt;http://bcove.me/so5mz4un&gt;, Integrated Supply Chain Vice President Mike Owens explains what set these locations apart. HSE awards… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/3siteswin2012HSEExcellence,ProcessImprovementawards.aspx&gt;









Assistant Army Secretary views engine assembly line, HPW3000 test facilities in Phoenix
Katherine Hammack, Assistant Secretary of the Army for Installations, Energy &amp; Environment, got a first-hand look at the first HPW3000 helicopter engine when she visited Aerospace facilities in Phoenix May 9. She was accompanied by Lt. Col. Daniel Roberts, Army ROTC Professor of Military Science at Arizona State University. They toured the Honeywell production assembly line and the development assembly area where the HPW3000 demonstrator engine is being built. HPW3000 engine tour… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/AssistantArmySecretaryvisitsPhoenixtolearnmoreaboutHPW3000engine.aspx&gt;









SPEX Dashboard Team applies Human Factors to support parts availability
The SPEX Dashboard Team had a big challenge from Adrian Paull, Vice President of Customer &amp; Product Support. Could they apply a Human Factors perspective to a dashboard for the Aerospace spares and parts exchange, called SPEX, so operators would be assured of support for their entire airplane anywhere in the world? And could they make it happen in 40 days? Members of the C&amp;PS e-Biz Team and the Information Technology Order Management Build Team met those goals, becoming finalists for the Honeywell Team Performance Award for their efforts. SPEX Dashboard… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/SPEXDashboardTeamappliesHumanFactorstosupportpartsavailability.aspx&gt;









HTSI wins $72.4 million US Army contract for heavy vehicle maintenance
Honeywell Technology Solutions Inc. (HTSI) has won a three-year, $72.4 million maintenance and training contract from the U.S. Army for Total Package Fielding Army Modernization Training. It provides mission-capable vehicles and training to safely operate and maintain heavy tactical vehicles. More… &lt;http://www.honeywellnow.com/2013/05/14/honeywell-aerospace-wins-72-4-million-heavy-vehicle-maintenance-contract-for-u-s-army/&gt;









Ralph Borkman celebrates 50 years at Honeywell
It was 1963 when a friend told Ralph Borkman about a job opening at then-Sperry Aerospace at what is now the Aerospace-Deer Valley site in Phoenix. His original plan was to work there for one year before moving on and pursuing other passions. Obviously, life had a way of changing even the best laid plans. 50-year career… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/RalphBorkmancelebrates50yearsatHoneywell.aspx&gt;









Special event for veteran hiring takes Dorsett to White House
When Colin Dorsett represented Honeywell Aerospace at the White House April 30, he found himself in the East Room, where President Barack Obama, Michelle Obama, Vice President Joe Biden and Dr. Jill Biden were on the podium. Dorsett, Director of Program Management for Defense &amp; Space in Glendale, Ariz., was there with other veterans representing companies that support the “Joining Forces” initiative to hire and train veterans and military spouses. White House visit… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/SpecialeventforveteranhiringtakesColinDorsetttoWhiteHouse.aspx/&gt;









April brings Honeywell volunteers with helping hands
Spring was a very busy time for Honeywell employee volunteers who repaired and refurbished low-income homes and nonprofit facilities in their communities. Honeywell Aerospace sponsored 12 projects this spring with more than 300 volunteers, including this group in South Bend, Ind. Community projects and image gallery… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/AprilbringsHoneywellvolunteerswithhelpinghands.aspx#http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/PublishingImages/13April_HHS-RT/Tulsa.jpg&gt;









Volunteer profile – Jon Connor Foster 
When Jon Connor Foster left Phoenix to join Honeywell in Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, two years ago, he wanted to make the most of his time in Mexico. He actively sought an organization in the region that needed volunteers, specifically a place where he could make an impact in his new community. Now Foster spends every Saturday teaching fourth-sixth grade students English, Spanish, math, science, geography, art and health. Making a difference… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/Volunteerprofile%E2%80%93JonConnorFoster.aspx&gt;



 
HTSI plays part in Blount Island Command earning Marine Corps safety achievement award
The U.S. Marine Corps’ Support Facility Blount Island Command in Jacksonville, Fla., where Honeywell Technology Solutions Inc. (HTSI) is the largest civilian contractor, has received a Marine Corps Achievement in Safety Award for 2012. “HTSI employees supporting the Marine Corps Support Facility at Blount Island Command play a critical role every day in driving safety throughout the facility,” said Carey Smith, HTSI President. “We take safety seriously, and we are proud to support the Blount Island Command.” Safety award… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HTSIplayspartinBlountIslandCommandearningMarineCorpssafetyachievementaward.aspx&gt;


D&amp;S President Mike Madsen joins NBC education summit in Phoenix
When NBC News opened its Education Nation Summit in Phoenix May 3, Defense &amp; Space President Mike Madsen was at the forefront of the discussion about math, science and technology education. He served on a panel (watch the video &lt;http://video.msnbc.msn.com/msnbc/51767160#51767160&gt;) about preparing Arizona’s present and future workforce to compete in a global economy. NBC education summit… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/DSPresidentMikeMadsenjoinsNBC-sponsorededucationsummitinPhoenix.aspx&gt;


FM&amp;T sponsors events to encourage interest in science, math careers
How do you encourage teens to pursue careers in science, technology, engineering and math (STEM)? Honeywell Federal Manufacturing &amp; Technologies (FM&amp;T) in Kansas City, Mo., furthered their efforts by sponsoring two events to make such studies fun and interesting. As part of FM&amp;T’s outreach with the “Introduce A Girl to Engineering Day” put on by the Kansas City section of the Society of Women Engineers, FM&amp;T’s Sr. Project Manager Kristin Ehlers was featured in a local TV broadcast &lt;http://fox4kc.com/2013/05/02/trying-to-get-more-girls-interested-in-engineering/&gt;. Their sponsorship of the regional contest for the National Science Bowl resulted in an article &lt;http://www.kansascity.com/2013/04/30/4210746/in-the-science-bowl-the-answers.html&gt; in the Kansas City Star.


More Headlines…


Featured Product and Video: Ovation Select cabin management system



Honeywell receives ESGR Seven Seals Award for Reserves support &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywellreceivesESGRSevenSealsAward.aspx&gt;



D&amp;S May 1 Business Update with Mike Madsen &lt;http://ez.com/dsupdate20130501&gt;



Engineering &amp; Technology May 2 Town Hall with Bob Smith &lt;http://ez.com/AEROETTH20130502&gt;










In the News
APEX Blog –

May 9, 2013
Roll out of NextGen is progressing slowing but surely. Should passengers care? &lt;http://blog.apex.aero/passenger-2/roll-nextgen-progressing-slowing-surely-passengers-care/&gt;


Bloomberg –

May 8, 2013
Honeywell wins $6 billion of orders for business jet engine &lt;http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-05-08/honeywell-wins-6-billion-of-orders-for-business-jet-engine-1-.html&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 7, 2013
Honeywell synthetic vision for helicopters on the horizon &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ainalerts/2013-05-07/honeywell-synthetic-vision-helicopters-horizon&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 3, 2013
Inmarsat, Honeywell partner with Ka-Band &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/aviation-international-news/2013-05-03/inmarsat-honeywell-partner-ka-band&gt;


Avionics –

May 1, 2013
Connectivity’s next step &lt;http://www.aviationtoday.com/av/business-and-general-aviation/Connectivitys-Next-Step_79108.html#.UYXoAr3n-P8&gt; 


Reuters –

April 29, 2013
U.S. Army sees savings on upgrades for Vietnam-era helicopter &lt;http://www.reuters.com/article/2013/04/30/usa-army-helicopter-idUSL2N0DG25J20130430&gt;








© 2013 Honeywell International Inc.

Aero Express is produced for internal use only and is not for distribution outside the company.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
