<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>HoustonHarvey_Aug29_2017.HoustonHarvey_Aug29_2017</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News About Honeywell&apos;s Houston, TX Facility</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Honeywell Customer,
 
We’re sure, like us, you’ve been shocked and saddened by the devastation Hurricane Harvey has caused on the Texas Gulf Coast. The unprecedented flooding has affected thousands of people in the area, including many of our employees who work at our Houston repair and overhaul facility. We wanted to give you a brief update since you do business with that site:


	- 
Our first priority is the safety and well-being of our employees. We are currently trying to account for all of our employees and ensure they are safe.

	- 
The Houston R&amp;O facility closed yesterday. We are optimistic operations will resume this week, but that will depend upon the weather and the ability of our employees to safely access the site. We will keep you updated. 

	- 
As of Tuesday morning, all work headed to the Houston site was re-routed to our Memphis, TN and Kingman, AZ facilities. We will continue to send work to these sites until Houston reopens to minimize customer impact. 




We have the ability to monitor the Houston building and, at this time, the flood waters haven’t reached the building. Power is still on and there is no apparent damage to the facility. In short, we expect to resume operations as soon as the weather permits and it is safe for our employees to travel. We will provide another update by Thursday.

If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell account leader. If you do not know who that is, please visit the MyAerospace contact us page &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;.


Thank you for your business,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
