<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017_EMEAI_MYMAINTAINER_Irina.2017_EMEAI_MYMAINTAINER</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing MyMaintainer -12 months free trial</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | BUSINESS &amp; GENERAL AVIATION
Introducing MYMAINTAINER: your go-to app that facilitates rapid maintenance decisions
Valued HAPP Customer, 





We come with great news! You have been selected as the beneficiary of a unique offering: 12 months free of charge trial of MyMaintainer *.

What it is: MyMaintainer is an app and a web-based system which helps maintenance teams reduce costs and improve troubleshooting time, enabling faster return to service. This ground-based platform was built to analyze and troubleshoot fault and operating data generated by Honeywell EPIC systems. This is done by effectively leveraging mobile technology, analytics and secure connectivity solutions in a form factor that suits the modern day maintainer.
How it works: The App reads FHDB (Fault History Data Base) and translates it into fault history in real time. Within the App you can view the fault history by date/ATA chapter etc. It allows you to mark faults, so other users can review and see what you have highlighted. It as well allows you to flag spurious massages and keep them hidden from view, so you have easy readout of data and fault trends.

The data resides on Honeywell server, so our ATC (Aero Technical Support) help-desk can access the data real time and use it to troubleshoot. As well the data can be accessed remotely, so you can log into the web based tool/App wherever you are, upon need. 




     CLICK HERE TO READ THE FACTS SHEET       &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/MyMaintainer_Fact Sheet.pdf]]&gt;




How to register: click here  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/MYMAINTAINER_HAPP.html]]&gt;and add your details and we will get in touch with you shortly.


Best regards,
Petar DUMICIC

HAPP Sales Manager



*After the first 12 months you can decide if you want to continue with paid subscription or drop off without any associated fee.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
