<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_BK_Webinar_SocialFlight_Automation_and_the_Flight_Envelope_MC.Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Automation and the Flight Envelope</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for attending our recent SocialFlight webinar “Automation and the Flight Envelope.” In a few days, we will have this posted online for on-demand viewing and will send you the link. 

 As a seminar special, we are offering a 10% discount on our autopilots through our My Avionics &lt;[[https://apps.apple.com/us/app/my-avionics/id1367559967]]&gt; app found on the App Store for iPhone and iPad products. Easy to use; either upload a photo of your panel or take a photo through the app, complete the information and you’ll receive the discount in your inbox. 

 As we mentioned in the presentation, our AeroCruze 230 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-230]]&gt; autopilot is a slide-in replacement for the KFC 150, STC’d for several aircraft platforms &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/downloads/KFC_230_AeroCruze_AFCS_AML_STC_Document_Rev_C.pdf]]&gt; and well-suited for those that fly IFR on a regular basis, while our AeroCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-100]]&gt; is an affordable option for Cessna and Piper owners that tend to typically fly in VFR conditions. If you’re not sure of where to start with an upgrade, contact &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt; us. We’re happy to listen, make recommendations and help you find a dealer/installer.

 Understanding your autopilot and automation starts with the learning the “Mindset of the Box”. I know this well, coming from the perspective of owning/operating TruTrak for many years. Being a pilot, engineer, aircraft builder and end user, these are amazing tools when you take a bit of time to learn them as they are intended and designed. Push with intent, verify and communicate (with the system).

 We design the interfaces to be “at-a-glance” to know the modes and displays, but learning the nuances takes practice. Aside from studying the Pilot and Flight Guides, flight instructors appreciate the opportunity to learn different equipment, and together you can create a custom transition flight review specific to your equipment.

 If you have any feedback or questions, please email &lt;[[mailto:Andrew.Barker@Honeywell.com?subject=Questions about Automation and the Flight Envelope webinar]]&gt; me.

 Sincerely,
 Andrew Barker
 BendixKing</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
