<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202012_Global_DFARS-Cybersecurity-Compliance_MC.202012_Global_DFARS-Cybersecurit</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Immediate Action Required | DFARS Cyber-Security Compliance</subject>
    <textOnly>December 10, 2020



References:



(1) 
DFARS Case 2019-D041 &lt;[[https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2020/09/29/2020-21123/defense-federal-acquisition-regulation-supplement-assessing-contractor-implementation-of]]&gt; dated 9/29/20, effective 11/30/20.


(2)  
DFARS 252.204-7020 &lt;[[https://www.acquisition.gov/dfars/part-252-solicitation-provisions-and-contract-clauses#DFARS-252.204-7020]]&gt; (Nov 2020) NIST SP 800-171 DoD Assessment Requirements.






Dear Valued Supplier, 

As of December 9, our records reflect that you have not taken action related to compliance with DFARS 252.204-7020 &lt;[[https://www.acquisition.gov/dfars/part-252-solicitation-provisions-and-contract-clauses#DFARS-252.204-7020]]&gt;. As previously stated, Honeywell is unable to place future POs with your company supporting government related work. In addition, you are running the risk of disqualification from future Government subcontract awards until proof of compliance is provided. 

This may be our final attempt requesting that the steps below are immediately completed to avoid impending business interruptions. 



	- Step 1: Complete Assessment: You must have completed at least a Basic Assessment in accordance with NIST SP 800-171 DoD Assessment Methodology &lt;[[https://www.acq.osd.mil/dpap/pdi/cyber/docs/NIST SP 800-171 Assessment Methodology Version 1.2.1 6.24.2020.pdf]]&gt; within the last three years for all applicable covered contractor information systems. A Basic Assessment is a self-assessment. If DCMA has already conducted a Medium or High Assessment for your organization and you have received a score, you have satisfied this step.
	- Step 2: Post Assessment Score: If you completed a Basic Assessment, your summary-level score and other information required by 252.204-7020(d), must be submitted into SPRS &lt;[[https://www.sprs.csd.disa.mil/default.htm]]&gt; or by sending an encrypted email to webptsmh@navy.mil &lt;[[mailto:webptsmh@navy.mil]]&gt; for posting to SPRS. If you have a Medium or High Assessment score, ensure your score is posted to SPRS for all CAGE codes covered by your System Security Plan.
	- Step 3: Tell Honeywell You’re Done with Steps 1 and 2: Please complete the Honeywell Cyber DFARS Questionnaire &lt;[[https://forms.office.com/Pages/ResponsePage.aspx?id=JuXsln2csEiNr4uTyQpdGLVhGeRHOrxBqz61IZq6O5RUOFoxVUJXSlVIUExCWEFSNkQ2UEFVNTlJNi4u]]&gt;.



Please also ensure that you are taking similar steps to inform your sub-tier suppliers about these new requirements in order to avoid supply chain disruptions.

Thank you in advance for your cooperation regarding this matter. Please do not hesitate to reach out to your Commodity Manager with SupplierResponsibility@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:SupplierResponsibility@honeywell.com]]&gt; on copy with any questions or concerns.

Sincerely,
 
 Bob Buddecke
Vice President and Chief Procurement Officer</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
