<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201801_Email_Global_2018_HAPP_MPP_Policy_Update_Dealers_JRD.201801_Email_Global_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Updates 2018 HAPP &amp; MPP Annual Billings Policy</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | Business and General Aviation
UPDATES TO 2018 HAPP &amp; MPP ANNUAL BILLINGS POLICY
Dear Valued Channel Partner: 
 
To improve and automate our annual billing process, Honeywell is implementing the following changes to the 2018 Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP) and Mechanical Protection Plan (MPP) policy: 



	- We will notify you with the details of the upcoming annual billing 60 days prior to contract anniversary date,. This lead-time will allow you to accomplish the following:



	- Resolve any questions or concerns related to contract coverage
	- Review new features/options available for each plan
	- Contact operator to arrange for payment
	- If helpful to your process, provide PO to Honeywell
	- Advise if aircraft is sold or otherwise not flying


	- During the expiration month, we will send a second notification advising that billing will occur on the anniversary date.
	- A final notification will be provided 10 days prior to anniversary date.
	- If no communication is received regarding changes or updates to the contract, billing will occur on anniversary date.


Finally, please note that any requests to extend a billing date will need to be approved before the anniversary date.

 If you do not supply Honeywell with a purchase order or billing details by the anniversary date, you will be automatically invoiced on that date. Failure to pay invoice within 30 days could result in credit hold.

For more information, please contact your HAPP/MPP sales manager or email the HAPP/MPP team at happ-sales@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:happ-sales@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. 



Sincerely,

Frank Muscolino 
Senior R&amp;O Sales Director</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
