<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201702_Global_Email_Test_mih.201711_Global_Email_Test_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Helicopter Newsletter for Q4 has landed!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
QUARTERLY HELICOPTER NEWSLETTER
Q4 2017
THE Q4 EDITION
Stabilization Should Lead to Growth in 2018
As anticipated 12 months ago, we are truly seeing stabilization in the commercial helicopter sector. In short summary, commodity prices have rebounded from their lows, the number of used aircraft up for sale has been trending downward for nearly 6 consecutive months, Brent Crude oil prices have experienced positive growth in 2017, and OEM order velocities are stabilizing. 
The above-mentioned points bring not only optimism, but a reality that 2018 will realize positive growth with pent up demand, stabilization in exchange rates are anticipated and overall healthier economic growth is forecasted.
In this edition of the Helicopter Newsletter, you will learn more about:


	- Honeywell’s first dedicated T53 engine service center in the Middle East and Africa, Jordanian Aeronautical Systems Co. (JAC)
	- Our HUMS systems are rapidly becoming smarter and more intuitive for our customers through efforts like the US Army ASTRO Program
	- Helicopter Express highlights how the T53-17 engine’s reliability and capability to operate under high/hot conditions meant continuous heavy lifting capabilities without any performance degradation and increased production
	- An opportunity for you to hear from our experts on how helicopter connectivity can enhance your operational efficiency (Rotor &amp; Wing Webinar Replay)


I wish you a successful close to 2017 and we look forward to meeting with each of you at HAI 2018.

Sincerely, 
Rick Angelo
Director of Strategic Marketing: Global Commercial Helicopters
Honeywell&apos;s Iconic T53 Engine Gets a Regional Lift   
For over 50 years, Honeywell&apos;s T53 turboshaft engine has been powering some of the world&apos;s most iconic helicopters, including the Bell UH-1H Huey, Huey II and AH-1H Cobra. In that time the engine has accumulated more than 62 million flight hours.  
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/september/honeywell-s-iconic-t53-engine-gets-a-regional-lift]]&gt;
Making HUMS Smarter for Helo Operators 
 Smart machines that learn on their own are making all of our lives easier. Smart machines hold enormous promise for making helicopters safer and more efficient, while improving asset availability and mission effectiveness.  
 
 Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/october/making-hums-smarter-for-helo-operators]]&gt;
Helicopter Express&apos; Kaman K-MAX K-1200 Helicopters Get Serious Lift with Honeywell T53-17 Engine 
 

Helicopter Express was founded in 1995 as a single call-when-needed helicopter operation for the United States Forest Service. The seasonal contracts have since grown to a fleet of 22 mission-specific workhorses, and are dispatched worldwide for fire-fighting to heavy lifting, disaster relief, charter operations, aerial cinematography, and heli-skiing.
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/october/kaman-k-max-k-1200-helicopter-powered-with-a-honeywell-t53-17-engine]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/october/honeywells-connected-aircraft-hardware-certified-to-bring-high-bandwidth-wi-fi-to-helicopters]]&gt;Honeywell Connected Aircraft Hardware Certified to Bring High-Bandwidth to Wi-Fi Helicopters 
The helicopter industry can now take advantage of higher-speed onboard Wi-Fi, video transmission and telemedicine capability in Europe and North America using Honeywell&apos;s Connected Aircraft solution, the Aspire 200 system. 
Read more  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/october/honeywell-s-connected-aircraft-hardware-certified-to-bring-high-bandwidth-wi-fi-to-helicopters]]&gt;
New Webinar Now Available On-Demand! 
 

Aircraft connectivity is no longer a luxury in the rotorcraft industry. Take an hour out of your day to learn from the experts at Honeywell how connectivity can enhance your operational efficiency. Topics include the hardware and software necessary for connecting, what applications connectivity can enable, and considerations for selecting the right satellite communications.  
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/the-dawn-of-the-connected-helicopter-brought-to-you-by-honeywell]]&gt;
Upcoming Helicopter Shows and Events  
Helicopter Association of Canada &lt;[[http://www.h-a-c.ca/convention.html]]&gt; 
HAI Heli-Expo &lt;[[http://heliexpo.rotor.org/?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTURneFpXSTNPRGMyTjJFeiIsInQiOiJHZmZOSFNlS0JxYWY3Y0JFQTU5MHpZUCtQTzdtbU13a1kwenVyZXIwU2JKXC9PeHVCU1VyYXNQcVBPNkpET1FyMlpEc2ZtaHRkc1N5aEFOWDVIQVpxQ0E9PSJ9]]&gt;
Subscribe to the Honeywell Aerospace Newsletter
 
Subscribe now and we will keep you updated on latest helicopter news and information. 
   CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
