<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Inmarsat F2 Satellite Launch Mailing.Inmarsat F2 Satellite Launch Customer Maile</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We’re Counting Down to Global Connectivity</subject>
    <textOnly>Ka Band Connectivity Reaches Next Milestone
 







 &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/&gt;   &lt;#&gt;

 



 

Ka Band Connectivity Reaches Next Milestone


 







Dear  {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},

We are delighted to announce the successful launch of the Inmarsat I-5 F2 satellite from the Baikonur Cosmodrome in Kazakhstan.

The ILS Proton M launch vehicle safely transported the F2 satellite to a supersynchronous transfer orbit following lift-off on Sunday 1st February 2015. Satellite separation from the launch vehicle occurred approximately 15½ hours after lift-off. For more information about the Launch Mission (click here &lt;http://hwll.co/2skw&gt;).

I-5 F2 will be positioned in geosynchronous orbit 36,000KM above the earths surface to serve the Americas and Atlantic Ocean Region. As full global coverage for GX is expected early in the second half of 2015, airline operators worldwide and their passengers can start counting down to the launch of the GX Aviation solution and with it unparalleled connectivity and the highest committed information rates in the industry.

To find out more or to arrange a meeting with one of our connectivity experts, please click here &lt;http://hwll.co/2skw&gt;.









What does this means for us?

• With two of the three GX satellites now in position, we are now able to commence ‘hand over’ testing between coverage areas to ensure seamless connectivity

• In flight testing of the Honeywell JetWave hardware will commence in Q2 and remains on track for certification in Q3 2015

• We are on target for Commercial Services Introduction of our GX Aviation service, JetConnex in Q4 2015

What does this mean for you?

• You will soon be able to offer your customers the fastest, most reliable data connection in the air - anywhere, anytime, always

• Don’t let your competitors leave you in their wake – the countdown to high speed global connectivity has begun

 






 

©2015 Honeywell International Inc. All Rights Reserved.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
