<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>November-2015.Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Supplier Update - December 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Honeywell Aerospace Supplier Update - March 2015
Continuous Improvement Collaboration
Dear Valued Supplier,
 
 Honeywell Aerospace competes in a highly competitive market environment with increasing customer expectations on cost, quality and delivery.To meet these expectations, our Integrated Supplier Chain mission is to “continuously improve our safety, quality, delivery, inventory, productivity and customer performance.
As the Sourcing and Procurement organization, we keep focus on:


 - Quality – Drive the ZERO defects to support our factory to eliminate scrap, rework and escapes.
 - Delivery – 100 percent On Time to Request (OTTR) supplier delivery performance in order to meet all customers’ need on time.
 - Productivity – Seeking for all the possibility to reduce waste and cost, and increase efficiency, including, but not limit to, cost reduction and value engineering proposal.


In order to accomplish these challenges, Honeywell relies on our suppliers&apos; success and their performance heavily. We know our process and products, and our suppliers know their processes and products. Therefore, we need to collaborate to successfully deliver top quality products, at a competitive price, on time to meet our customers’ expectations.
 

In Asia Pacific, we deliver the overall Sourcing and Procurement organization results together with the Global and other regional teams.

We focus on:


 - Supply Market intelligence in Asia Pacific
 - Global sourcing strategy deployment in Asia Pacific region
 - Local sourcing strategy defining and implementation
 - Managing supplier contracts in Asia Pacific region
 - Managing supplier quality and delivery performance


Together, let us leverage each other to deliver top quality results.
 
 Sincerely,
 Owen Zhu
 Director, Sourcing and SPM (APAC)

Supplier Performance Management
“Self Release by PN” Program Go-Live is Monday March 16, 2015
 

As we have previously communicated, we are transforming the Honeywell Self Release Program from a Supplier-based to PN-based approval system. In preparation for the March 16 Go Live, we trained over 1,000 Suppliers during February. There are two different training modules, both important to impacted* suppliers:
 

Part 1 Training Module: Self Release by PN Overview: What is changing in the SR Program? How will SR be granted on a Supplier and PN basis?
 Part 2 Training Module: Self Release by PN HASP Reports: How is the SR data tracked in HASP?
 

For those who could not attend, we’ve scheduled more makeup sessions in March, as shown below. If you still need training, please ask your FQE to forward the meeting invites to you.
For other questions, you may contact Tina.Smith@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto://tina.smith@honeywell.com&gt;
*Who are the impacted suppliers? ONLY those Suppliers who have Purchase Orders with SPOC149 “Product Release” flowdown requirement. Others are not affected and do not need to attend training.

Supply Chain Collaboration Portal (HASP)
 

Tired of waiting for your Supply Chain Collaboration (HASP) Portal account to be unlocked or password reset?
 

We’ve heard your concerns and we’ve responded. Please take a few minutes to complete 8 simply security questions. The next time you forget your password OR your account is locked you can regain access IMMEDIATELY.
 

To take advantage of this functionality the next time you log into your HASP account, https://hasp.honeywell.com/irj/portal &lt;https://hasp.honeywell.com/irj/portal&gt; follow these quick steps:
 

Click REGISTER SECURITY QUESTIONS on the HASP Overview screen:



Then the next time you forget your password or your account is locked click FORGOT PASSWORD, answer 3 security questions successfully and you will be granted IMMEDIATE access.





Honeywell Supplier Council


Honeywell is focusing on fundamentally changing the relationship with our suppliers and becoming the customer of choice. The Supplier Council, which was formed in early 2010, is one of the forums that Honeywell has been leveraging to drive this strategic vision.

In May, 2013, Jim McQueeney was appointed as Vice President and Chief Procurement Officer for Aerospace Sourcing &amp; Procurement. Part of his vision in this role included modifying the Supplier Council operating system in order to add more value to the meetings and enhance supplier relationships. Since that time, the Supplier Council has grown into an important event aimed at obtaining supplier feedback and gaining alignment on strategic initiatives. There are 13 Mechanical and 10 Electrical supplier council seats that were chosen which aligns to the overall Aerospace supply chain landscape. Suppliers were chosen based on their area of their expertise and were managed by visionary leaders and change agents who believe in providing candid and honest feedback.
Supplier Council Objectives:


 - Collaborate on relevant issues
 - Create better alignment
 - Captures ‘Voice of the Supplier’ which provides candid feedback
 - Problem solving action planning
 - Focus on strategic issues, threats and problems
 - Sharing of growth opportunities and best practices



The Council To Best Represent the Needs of the Entire Supply Base
Within the council are four Supplier co-chair leaders whose purpose is to manage the ‘Voice of the Supplier’ and help gather topics of interest among peers. Ideas are consolidated, prioritized and actions taken as appropriate to drive results to improve business relationships. If you have ideas for improvement submit to your Supplier Council co-chair leaders.

Honeywell Wants to Hear Your Topics for Improvement. Include:


 - Problem statement with title
 - Solution and proposed recommendation
 - Potential benefit to Honeywell
 - Supporting information, if available


Electrical Supplier Council Co-Chair Leaders:


 - Jim Anderson - james.anderson@plexus.com &lt;mailto://james.anderson@plexus.com&gt;
 - Pete Wortendyke - pworten@celestica.com &lt;mailto://pworten@celestica.com&gt;



Mechanical Supplier Council Co-Chair Leaders:


 - David Camilleri - david.camilleri@noranco.com &lt;mailto://david.camilleri@noranco.com&gt;
 - Mike Holmes - michael.holmes@aerodesignmfg.com &lt;mailto://michael.holmes@aerodesignmfg.com&gt;



 


 

Aerospace Global Sourcing Economist Update
 


Note: The following financial and economic information is Honeywell’s summary of publicly available information and is to be used for general information purposes only—it should not be used as a basis for making financial or business decisions. Honeywell suppliers are responsible to complete their own due diligence with respect to financial and economic risk analysis with respect to any business decisions related to their business with Honeywell.
 


Commodities, Currencies and Global Economic Growth
 


Crude Oil Link to Global Economic Growth
 


Tumbling oil prices may increase world economic growth by 15-20% this year, according to the head of the World Bank. Historical estimates suggested that a 30% decline in oil prices—as projected for 2015—could be associated with an increase in the size of the global economy by approximately 0.5%.
 


Following four years of stability at ~$105 per barrel, oil prices have plummeted 47% since June 2014 to current (WTI) price of $51.16/barrel.

The World Bank forecast that the world economy would expand by 3.0% in 2015 (after growing 2.6% in 2014) before growing by 3.3% in 2016 and supported by low oil prices, as well as continued recovery in the US, a gradual improvement in the euro area and receding domestic headwinds in slower-growing developing countries.
 


The blended rate of GDP over the past five years is approximately 2.2%.
 


The United States recorded fourth-quarter real GDP growth at a 2.6% annual rate which was driven down from the third-quarter’s 5.0% pace by reduced defense spending and an import surge. IHS Economics highlights that low oil prices and a rising dollar are two profound transformations that are affecting the U.S. economy.
 
 According to Bloomberg, analysts are mixed on whether low oil prices will prove to be a net benefit to the economy and global growth.
 


Currencies, Exchange-Rates and Economics
 The consensus among economists and policymakers seems to be that the top risk to the global economic recovery is low inflation, which has been exacerbated by the dramatic plunge in oil prices.
 &quot;We are in currency wars,&quot; Goldman Sachs President and COO Gary Cohn told a panel discussion at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. &quot;The prevailing view is that the easy way to stimulate economic growth is to have a low currency.&quot;
 


According to CNBC, &quot;currency war&quot; was a phrase coined by former Brazilian Finance Minister Guido Mantega in 2010 to complain about developed market central banks, such as the Federal Reserve, weakening their currencies through policies like quantitative easing.
 Interest rates cuts are so popular among governments around the world that about 40% of developed world economies are experiencing negative interest rates, according to Societe Generale. The US 10 year treasury yield is near 2.0%.
 


The current result of various rate cuts has the U.S. dollar index, which measures the U.S. dollar’s strength against a trade-weighted basket of six other major currencies, sitting at a near 12 year high (on February 26, 2015) of 95.37. The Euro, for example, is down more than 18% against the dollar from its value last year at this time. The “buying power” of the United States, reflected by the U.S. dollar index, increased just over 13% in 2014.
Honeywell in the News

To read the latest news from Honeywell, click here &lt;http://click.e-honeywell.com/?ju=fe2c17737c600575751774&amp;ls=fdc11572706c067e7010797660&amp;m=fefc1575766002&amp;l=fe5e15777c61007e7716&amp;s=fe2810757261037c7d1472&amp;jb=ffcf14&amp;t=&gt;.

We Want to Hear from You

The Honeywell Supplier Update is a newsletter to send timely and relevant information to our suppliers. If you would like to suggest a topic to include in a future issue of the Honeywell Supplier Update, please send a message to Aero Supplier Communications &lt;mailto:%20AeroSupplierCommunications@honeywell.com&gt;.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
Honeywell
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;
 Confidential</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
