<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Global_RTA-44D_Repair_mih.201906_Global_Email_RTA-44D_Repair_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace VHF Data Radio Product Line Update</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Honeywell Aerospace recently announced the site closure of the Renton, Washington location. As a result, the Repair &amp; Overhaul activity for the RTA-44D VHF Data Radio is moving to the Honeywell Olathe, Kansas facility. The Olathe facility currently houses both a repair line and the OEM spares production line. The additional equipment from Renton will augment and expand the current repair volume. The teardown of the Renton line begins June 29, 2019. 

A review of the repair history for the past 2.5 years indicates that you have sent in a part number for repair for at least one of the impacted part numbers.

IMPACTED PART NUMBERS 



Material
Material Description


064-50000-0101
RTA-44D VHF DATA RADIO


064-50000-0110
VHF DATA RADIO RTA-44D


064-50000-0202
RTA-44D VHF DATA RADIO


064-50000-0303
RTA-44D VHF DATA RADIO


064-50000-0505
VHF DATA RADIO RTA-44D


064-50000-2000
VHF DATA RADIO RTA-44D


064-50000-2001
VHF COMM TRANSCEIVER


064-50000-2031
RTA-44D VHF DATA RADIO


064-50000-2032
VHF COMM TRANSCEIVER


064-50000-2032R
VHF COMM TRANSCEIVER


0064-50000-2051
VHF DATA RADIO RTA-44D


064-50000-2052
VHF DATA RADIO RTA-44D



REPAIR UNIT SHIPMENTS 


	- The last date that Renton will receive hardware for repair is June 28, 2019. Through June 28, Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Renton.
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification. 
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity.
	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.


To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow the following guidelines and actions.  
 
 Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems  



	- Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts.





Company Name
Honeywell International Inc.


Address
23500 West 105th Street


City, State
Olathe, Kansas


Postal Code
866061


Country
United States


Cage Code
22373


DUNS Number
614705783




 If you have any questions about this transition, please contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager or point of contact. The MyAerospace Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; is available 24x7 to validate where to send units for repair. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve.   
 

Sincerely,
 
Honeywell Aerospace
Visit MyAerospace


 &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Umr805X0qI0QGo02tZ000Zq]]&gt;
If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
