<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Technology Library Spotlight Newsletter December 2013</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>TL Spotlight.December 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Spotlight Newsletter: Library Services</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Email Title
December 2013

The Technology Library is a corporate-wide resource for research assistance and document delivery services. The Library team is available to assist employees in any aspect of their search for information. Services include technical and business research, current awareness updates and article/document retrieval.







Technical &amp; Business Research   

Library Web Site &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/index.htm&gt; – Access websites and databases to search for company information, technical literature, market 
research, government sources, and more. Sites listed are a combination of free, prepaid, and fee-based databases. Contact a librarian &lt;mailto:library-mn10@honeywell.com&gt; for help in searching or to conduct a customized search that may require access to fee-based databases.

Training Opportunities &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/Training/default.htm&gt; – See the schedule for upcoming database training dates and links to replays of past training events. Periodic library-run webinars on research resources are listed here as well. If you can&apos;t attend the live webinar, view the NEW TUTORIAL &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/Tutorials/ResearchResources/player.html&gt; to guide you through the various research resources available to 
you.


Current Awareness Alerts 

A current awareness alert is a regular update of 
publicly available information on a specific topic.   Current awareness alerts can help you track news on competitors or keep you up-to-date with developments in a particular subject area of interest. See examples of Library team generated customized Current Awareness &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/Services/alerts.htm&gt; updates on a variety of topics. You can request to be added to the distribution list for any of the alerts. 


Article/Document Retrieval 

Several of the research databases available on 
the Library web site allow users to download full text articles from selected publications. For a fee, the Library staff will order copies of articles that are not available in our electronic or print collections from a document delivery vendor.


For more information on resources or services the Technology Library provides, please email the Technology Library at library-mn10@honeywell.com &lt;mailto:library-mn10@honeywell.com&gt; or call 
763.954.6000. 




Spotlight Archives &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/Spotlight/default.htm&gt; |   &lt;http://library-technology.honeywell.com/rss/spotlight.xml&gt;







Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
