<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Global_ATR_Q4_Airline_Newsletter_Email.Internal Send</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Quarterly Honeywell Airline Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt;    |    Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;    |    View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Forward to a friend &lt;[[{{system.forwardToFriendLink}}]]&gt;


Welcome to the first-ever Honeywell Aerospace Airline Newsletter!
This will be a quarterly newsletter highlighting the top trends in the Airline Market. While you are here, why not take a moment to opt-in &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;. We want to be sure you don’t miss out on the latest news, industry insight and special offers from Honeywell.
Enhanced Customer Support – &quot;The Hub&quot;


 


Aptly named &quot;The Hub,&quot; we have recently enhanced our customer support by building a single, 24/7/365 call center in Phoenix, Arizona, to co-locate parts AOG, Technical Support Engineers, Support Pilots, In-Service Engineering, and Connected Aircraft technical support. What this means to you is that we’ve placed all the people responsible for resolving urgent issues in a single room and created a single phone number, single case system. For technical issues that cannot be resolved remotely, we have a robust network of Field Service Engineers distributed around the globe who can be dispatched to assist. You can connect with The Hub by clicking the button below. 



 






CONTACT US &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;
Technical Support Updates


 


We have also revamped the Technical Support page under &quot;Service &amp; Support&quot; on www.aerospace.honeywell.com &lt;[[http://www.aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; to bring you more 
self-service tools. We have a knowledge library of over 11,000 articles &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services-and-support/support-center/technical-support]]&gt; written by our technical support team to document previous issues and what resolved them. We are expanding our video library &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/videos]]&gt; to include a large number of &quot;how-to&quot; videos for common problems, and you can subscribe to Aero Training TV on our site to get notified when new videos have been added. We have created comprehensive information packets on all of the top reliability &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/secure/downloads/service-request-updates]]&gt; drivers that get updated every 30 days that you can access anytime to know the latest status and expected completion timelines.

We have an exciting pipeline of other 
enhancements to our technical support planned that we will share in future issues.
New Podcast: Environmental Control Systems


 


As we look to rebuild passenger and crew confidence, Honeywell is developing technology to improve cabin air, monitor ECS status remotely, and anticipate maintenance needs. Learn more about these new offerings in this episode of Aerospace Unplugged.

To listen to our previous episode on the Air Cargo industry and how it&apos;s rapidly evolving to meet today&apos;s fast-paced shipping, click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/podcasts/air-cargo]]&gt;.



 






LISTEN NOW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/podcasts/environmental-control-systems]]&gt;






 








 








 


 






Trade-in and upgrade your existing Emergency Locator Transmitter (ELT)


 


The pending end of support for the further repairs on the legacy RESCU 406AF/AFN and RESCU 406SE products coming December 2021. Spare sales for these legacy products have ended.  Honeywell no longer produces them or allows replacements of batteries in repairs.








 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/smaller-lighter-safer-elts]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/tech-forum]]&gt;
MyAerospace Portal Updates


 


GoDirect Trade Integration - Full integration with GoDirect Trade, Honeywell’s online marketplace for used Aerospace parts. Once logged into Aerospace.Honeywell.com, customers can access Honeywell’s extensive used serviceable material with real-time availability and pricing.

Warranty Claims - Airlines Multiple Claims Form - Airlines are now able to submit multiple serial number claims within the same request on the portal HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/secure/contact-us/forms/warranty-claims/multiple-claims]]&gt;. 

Warranty Self Service - A new tool for MyAerospace users to check their warranty coverage for parts by entering the Part Number, Serial Number and Malfunction Date. Please click HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/secure/services-and-support/warranty-coverage-check]]&gt; to access our Warranty Self Service tool.

Online Ordering – Aircraft on Ground (AOG) - We have fully automated the Aircraft on Ground (AOG) order process. Customers may now submit orders for Spares, Exchange Parts and/or Repair Services via the Online Ordering in support of an AOG.

Product Reliability Updates – MyAerospace Users can get the latest information on in-service product improvements addressed by Honeywell, summarizing the issues and including the program schedule. Go to Technical Support &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services-and-support/support-center/technical-support]]&gt; to learn more.

Want more information on the MyAerospace portal?



	- Click Here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt; to access our release notes and stay up to date on the latest improvements to MyAerospace portal.
	- Click Here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt; for training topics pages related to the portal.
New Blog: How AI is Changing the Aviation Document Game


 


Artificial Intelligence is all the rage. Now it’s transforming quality document management for aviation.


 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/blog/post/alfred/]]&gt;
While you are here, why not take a moment to opt-in &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;. We want to be sure you don’t miss out on the latest news, industry insight and special offers from Honeywell.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;    


 


© 2020 Honeywell International Inc.  &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; 
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202


 


Subscription Preference &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt;  |  Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; |  Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; |  Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
