<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_CPS_Cosmos-Move_Email_Operational.Coon Rapids - 10.27 Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about the Honeywell Coon Rapids Transition- Action Before November 6</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 
 
 As Honeywell advised in 2019, we have decided to optimize our operations and close our Coon Rapids, Minnesota facility by Q1 2021. As a reminder, the product lines affected by this transition include: 


	- Commercial Inertial Reference Units (IRU), Data Acquisition Units (DAU), Yaw Damper, and Flame Sensors are moving to the Clearwater, FL site.
	- Digital Analog Adaptor (DAA), Air Data Computer (ADC), Air Data Management (ADM), and Fuel Probes are moving to the Deer Valley, AZ site. 
	- Control Sensor Products (CSP) have transitioned from our Golden Valley site to the Clearwater, FL site.



As we approach the end of 2020 the Coon Rapids transition will be coming to an end and will be completed with our final 2 moves of remaining products to the Honeywell Clearwater Facility. 

Action Required: This notice is to remind you of the upcoming changes required before November 6, 2020. To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions. 
What to do now?


	- Prepare for upcoming transition: Review the transition schedule and impacted parts list provided above, adjust your supply plan as needed, resolve outstanding holds to minimize transition delays, and take actions to ensure internal systems are updated to reflect the correct Honeywell location on the correlating transition dates


	- Set/schedule updates to your internal ERP/MRP systems to support correct shipping destination per the table shown above


	- Update Authorized Supplier List (ASL) as needed: If Clearwater is not already on your ASL, start working to add the new supplier to your approved supplier list. If you need to conduct an on-site audit, please email your Honeywell Representative. 



Transition Schedule





Product Line Description 
Order Type
New Supplier
Begin Shipment to New Supplier on
Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date


10 MCU - Balance

MEMS 1.5

4 MCU (3of4)

Click Here for Parts List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/11-09-2020 Clearwater transiiton part list.xlsx]]&gt;

Repair and Overhaul Services

Honeywell Clearwater – Clearwater, Florida
November 9, 2020
October 16, 2020









Product Line Description
Order Type
New Supplier
Begin Shipment to New Supplier on
Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date


Flame Sensors

4 MCU (4of4)

MEMS 2.0

Click Here for Parts List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/12-07-2020 Clearwater transiiton part list.xlsx]]&gt;

Repair and Overhaul Services
Honeywell Clearwater – Clearwater, Florida
December 7, 2020
November 12, 2020





Information for Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
 Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems as needed to reference the new supplier information for these parts. 


            Honeywell Name for Repairs:             Honeywell International Inc.
                                                                        Clearwater Commercial Service Center
 
            Street Address:                                     3051 66 th St Plant 4
            City, State:                                           Largo, Florida
            Postal Code:                                        33779
            Country:                                               USA
            Cage Code:                                         8F7U8



Effective December 07, 2020 all hardware orders are to be sent to the Honeywell International, Inc, Clearwater (see address provided above). 

Existing Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders: 


	- Honeywell is working to fulfill existing orders.  
	- Depending upon inventory, due dates and lead-times associated with the order, some orders may require a purchase order or contract modification to revise the place of performance.    
	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact with you during the next few weeks to advise and coordinate that activity. 



New Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders: 


	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact with you during the next few weeks to advise and coordinate that activity. 
	- For order status, use the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt; portal.


Existing Repair Orders


	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already in work at Coon Rapids. 
	- Some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification. 
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager, or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity. 


	- Watch for PO or contract modification request from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. 




New Repair Orders


	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the new location. 
	- Part numbers received on or before September 27, 2020, will be accepted at Coon Rapids. 
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date’ to Clearwater for repair. 


	- A Purchase Order/contract modification may be required. 
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager, or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity. 


	- The MyAerospace Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; (ROCAPS) will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs


 Aircraft-On-Ground (AOG) Support


	- There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware. 


Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve.  

Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace
 Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
