<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201710_AspireTechSupport_LG.201710_AspireTechSupport_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Tech Tips - Troubleshoot Aspire 100 Cordless Handsets</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Have you experienced power-down problems with your Aspire® 100 cordless handsets (part numbers 1492-F-020X-01 and 1541-F-020X-01)?
 
Recent testing and field experience have revealed issues with the latest Cabin Service Unit (CSU) software V.234 and handset firmware 903-003 revision 013. This firmware can cause the cordless handset to remain on, instead of powering off, after 10 minutes of inactivity. It stays powered and continues to reboot every 140 seconds after de-registration with the CSU until the battery is drained. 
 
The handset will start charging the battery from zero percent on the next aircraft cabin power-up. This rebooting occurs because the back-up file on the SATCOM Configuration Module (SCM), PN 1492-E-8120, is erased shortly after being loaded. 
 
While we work on a permanent solution, please refer to the recent Service Information Letter (SIL) D201707000039 for instructions on how to configure and back-up the SCM. This 
also references the procedure in SB-90406597 Rev A on how back-up your configuration into the SCM. 
 
Please visit the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; portal to easily search for the following support documents. If you aren’t a registered user, follow these instructions &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Updates%20Training%20Materials/MyAerospace%20Portal%20-%20How%20To%20Register.pdf]]&gt; to get started. These documents are located on the Technical Publications site &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Ftechnical-publications]]&gt; (login required) within MyAerospace:


	- SIL D201707000039
	- Users&apos; Manual - D201308000046
	- Aspire 100 Software Update - SB-90406597 Rev A
	- Aspire Handset Software Upgrade (MOD 11) - SB-90406598 Rev A


Still need help? Please visit our Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical 
publications, or to submit questions to our Technical Support Engineering team on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;. 
 

Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
