<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_NonCPUseMyAerospace_LG.201809_NonCPUseMyAerospace_LG</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Use MyAerospace for your Repair Orders</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
ACCESS 2019 PRICING ON MYAEROSPACE
Dear Repair Providers, Distributors and Brokers,  
We continue to enhance our MyAerospace portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; to make it easier for you to place and monitor your orders. Using MyAerospace allows us to shorten your repair times, while the award-winning interface gives you the information you need when you need it.
Even with the benefits offered by this intuitive web portal, we still receive many manual repair &amp; overhaul (R&amp;O) orders that are not processed through MyAerospace or Electronic Data Interface (EDI). As advised in a prior communication (January 11, 2018) and per our terms and conditions, we do require that all orders be submitted through MyAerospace or EDI. 
Please follow this Honeywell policy. As of January 15, 2019, Honeywell will no longer accept manual orders/units at our repair sites. Units will be held until an electronic order (through MyAerospace or EDI) is in the system.
Why use MyAerospace?


	- 
MyAerospace is available 24/7 and offers convenience, dependability, speed, and ease-of-use.

	- 
We are continuously improving functionality and features. View a summary of enhancements &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-release-notes&gt; that include: 



	- 
Order Status: Download scrap certificates and additional shipment tracking information and functionality to ease the shipping process and avoid disputes.

	- 
Online Ordering:  Search freight forwarders, view additional repair order capabilities for our licensed channel partners, and access updated cost status messaging for pricing and quotes.





 
Why use MyAerospace to place repair orders?  


	- The Online Ordering &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Fonline-ordering]]&gt; tool provides the fastest possible order entry - the repair order goes directly into our system for hardware receipt, ensuring no disruption. 
	- Data is directly inputted into our system so the paperwork and documentation is 100% accurate, eliminating holds and delays.    
	- Orders are created with the correct flat rate repair price, enabling timely receipt and induction to the repair cycle.  
	- Receive immediate confirmation that the order has been placed.
	- Track order status from your PC or mobile device. 
	- Review and approve repair status and open quotes. 


 
What do I need to know about the policy? 


	- 
This is not a new policy - it has been in place and customers have previously been advised. 

	- 
Section 2 of Honeywell’s Repair and Overhaul terms and conditions gives Honeywell the right to reject, and will have no liability for orders, which were not entered in MyAerospace or through EDI. Read the terms and conditions here &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/terms-and-conditions-filtered#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending]]&gt;.

	- 
Effective January 15, 2019:



	- 
Honeywell Aerospace will no longer accept orders which are not created electronically through MyAerospace or EDI. 

	- 
Units will not be inducted into the receiving process, but will be held at receiving until an electronic order is received.





 
What must I do differently?


	- Access the repair capabilities and locations tool on MyAerospace - this allows both the order and hardware to be sent to the correct site location, minimizing incorrect shipment and product returns. 
	- Create repair orders on MyAerospace or through EDI, prior to shipping the hardware - failure to create an electronic order will result in hardware being held at receiving.  
	- Print the Repair Order Sheet (found on the Order Confirmation page) and send with the unit. 
	- Use the MyAerospace contact-us forms for questions about your orders. This is the fastest way to receive a response, including estimated ship date and order status.



	- Log into MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;, navigate to Order Status, search for your order, click on ‘Contact Us’.
	- Starting January 1, 2019, we will only accept inquiries about your order through MyAerospace. We will no longer accept emails.





How do I use MyAerospace for my repair and overhaul orders?


	- Create an ID and password – view this quick reference guide &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Updates%20Training%20Materials/MyAerospace%20-%20How%20To%20Register.pdf]]&gt;.
	- Access Online Ordering &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Fonline-ordering]]&gt; to place your order – view this short video (7 min) &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Video%20Tutorials/Online%20Ordering%20Update.mp4]]&gt;. 


	- Repairs:  Repair, overhaul, test, inspect, and modify
	- Spares:  New, used (HAT), exchange, and rental 


	- Use Order Status &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/order-status/!ut/p/b1/04_SjzS0NLQwMzI0NzbQj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQwMXI1cDDzDzIyNLTzNDA0sjIEKIoEKDHAARwNC-r30o9Jz8pOAVoXrR4EV4zHLzyM_N1U_NyrHIlvXUREAg1-eQg!!/dl4/d5/L2dBISEvZ0FBIS9nQSEh/pw/Z7_UM5L8F5400E2D0IV6338I610O3/act/id=X65IZUmetPA/p=action=showSearch/397315615062/-/]]&gt; to monitor your order.
	- View training videos and additional resources. &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20ascending]]&gt; 


 
How do I use Electronic Data Interface (EDI)? 


	- Honeywell has partnered with Aeroxchange &lt;[[https://www.aeroxchange.com/aexportal/home.jsp]]&gt;, an aviation supply chain solutions company.
	- Access information about how to enable Aeroxchange. &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/forms]]&gt;


 
Honeywell requires that repair orders are processed either through MyAerospace or EDI. This follows our &quot;Repair and Overhaul Terms&quot; posted on MyAerospace. Thank you for your attention to this – it will help us more quickly respond to your orders and provide additional benefit. 
 
As always, thank you for your business.
 

Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support 
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt;   
 


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/AB0000QI20ZGs0000q0l00X]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
