<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Flightstar.20BR_2016_Upgrade.20BR_Flightstar_Upgrade</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Save Now with Our Year-End ADS-B Out Special for Learjet 40/45</subject>
    <textOnly>   &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;                                                   &lt;[[http://flightstar.com/]]&gt;
THE ADS-B OUT AND 20BR ENGINE UPGRADE AVAILABLE FOR LEARJET 40 and Learjet 45


For a limited time, you can save up to $100,000* with Flightstar’s ADS-B Out STC for Learjet 40 or Learjet 45.Get the latest upgrade available for your Primus 1000 equipped aircraft and choose from one the 
following options before the end of 2016:


Option #1: ADS-B Out and HAPP Offer


If you’re one of the many Learjet operators still waiting for a solution to meet the ADS-B Out deadline, look no further. With Flightstar’s flexible and affordable ADS-B out upgrade, you’ll receive one of the most cost-effective solutions offered today. And, when you redeem this offer, you’ll receive up to $59,000** off your new or existing Honeywell Avionics Protection Program!

Option #2: ADS-B Out, HAPP Offer and 20BR Engine Upgrade

You 
didn’t think it could get any better? Well, it just did. When you upgrade your Learjet 40 or 45 with Flightstar’s ADS-B Out STC, you’ll receive the same HAPP offer and a Merchandise Credit Voucher (MCV) for a 20BR engine upgrade! With this upgrade, you’ll experience a better climb, better fuel efficiency and more power from your engine. And, you can save up to $100,000* with option 2 for a limited time.


Contact us today and take advantage of this exclusive offer by December 31, 2016!
CONTACT US &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/save-more-with-flightstar-ads-b-out-upgrade]]&gt;
 
*Savings are only available to Learjet 40 or Learjet 45 operators who use Flightstar’s STC. Customer must have 20AR engine to be eligible. Upon purchase of the Lear 40/45 ADS-B Out upgrade via Flightstar STC, a MCV in the amount of $49,000 will be created and available for use up to 9 months from the ADS-B Out install date. 20BR upgrades to be completed by Bombardier.

** Savings are variable and are based off of flight hours and tier pricing. The 20BR MCV is exclusive to Flightstar’s ADS-B Out STCs. This offer will be extended to any authorized dealer purchasing Flightstar’s ADS-B Out STCs.
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 
This message was sent to name@website.com. If you don&apos;t want to recieve these emails from Honeywell in the future you can edit your profile &lt;[[#]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Unsubscribelandingpage.html]]&gt;
Terms of Use &lt;[[#]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[#]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
