<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>SATCOM1 Newsletter Feb 03.2016</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>SATCOM1 Newsletter Feb 03.2016.SATCOM1 Newsletter Feb 03.2016</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>SAT2U: Satellite Communications News by Satcom1</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://twitter.com/Satcom1_tweets]]&gt; &lt;[[http://www.linkedin.com/company/satcom1]]&gt;
SAT2U: Satellite Communications News by Satcom1
Message from the Executive Management


Since our last edition, the biggest news is that Satcom1 is now a Honeywell company. The acquisition was final in December 2015 and since then we’ve been working together on our combined, full suite of connectivity offerings spanning satellite communications equipment, software applications and global airtime services. With Honeywell, we now have a worldwide sales and support presence and can provide customers a greater variety of voice and data solutions. Watch for more exciting news to come from the acquisition.

Speaking of exciting, we are entering 2016 with a special focus on having JetConneX Ka-band &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/airtime-services/global-xpress/]]&gt; installed on major VVIP aircraft and business jets. We are thrilled to provide this solution, which will deliver higher guaranteed bandwidth in the connected cabin than we have ever experienced before.

This year is going to be exciting for the helicopter market as well. The High Data Rates (HDR) satcom hardware and airtime will make cabin communications operational under rotary wings a reality.

Finally, Inmarsat Swiftbroadband &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/airtime-services/inmarsat/swiftbroadband/]]&gt; Safety technology is expected to launch to end-customers in 2016. That means, the Inmarsat Aero Classic services will be no longer the only approved services to use for cockpit satcom communications. Swiftbroadband &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/airtime-services/inmarsat/swiftbroadband/]]&gt; (SBB) Safety will be also able to receive ICAO approval, in order to be ready to support new installs or cockpit upgrades.

Satcom1’s core focus in 2016 is the commitment to assist our customers in all technology changes, from network design to installations support. We will continue to provide airtime and airtime related services. In addition, together with Honeywell we have an ambitious plan to develop new services to follow new technologies like Ka-Band &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/airtime-services/global-xpress/]]&gt;. Watch for more customer oriented services onboard with use of the Satcom1 AvioIP software suite &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/avioip/]]&gt;, managing the onboard networks.


Trending Topic


Airborne RoutersSatcom1 started developing its unique router software – AvioIP &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/avioip/]]&gt;, back in 2004 in order to manage the onboard network. We noticed the need in the aeronautical satellite communication market and predicted how the industry needs would develop toward more customized and advanced solutions onboard aircraft. It was a good decision to invest our resources in the AvioIP Software Suite &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/avioip/]]&gt; development over this time. The Suite is installed on major airframes today and the need in the market for our software keeps growing.

Today, Satcom1’s AvioIP Software Suite &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/avioip/]]&gt; is leader in the aerospace industry when it comes to router software. The software provides features like high-speed internet and user management, among others. It is built from modules, which means a lot of flexibility when it comes to choosing the best solution customized for your aircraft. In practice, that means each router with a Satcom1 AvioIP software &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/avioip/]]&gt; license installed on it comes with a different set of hardware-dependent and software-dependent features. This way, Satcom1 provides the solution to any VVIP and business jet, but also to helicopters and smaller jets worldwide.

The Satcom1 engineering development team is proud to retain our strong partnerships with major router manufacturers on the market and to adding more to our portfolio. We have prepared a little summary of “new-comers” when it comes to hardware platforms with Satcom1 AvioIP Software Suite installed.


CNX-250, Honeywell &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/router-management/]]&gt;



A new aircraft router from Honeywell offers higher Wi-Fi speed potential and growth to 4G LTE on-ground capability, among other benefits to both passengers and crew.

The CNX-250 Cabin Gateway is a multi-port network router that acts as the communications hub for all aircraft data links, enhancing the performance of both Honeywell&apos;s current Aspire 200 and MCS Series SwiftBroadband and the forthcoming JetWave™ Ka-band satcom systems.

Because of the stronger Wi-Fi signal inside the aircraft, passengers will immediately gain faster data transfer rates. In addition, using the wired gigabyte Ethernet port capability, passengers and crew can gain even higher speeds devices.

Another advantage of the CNX-250 over its CNX-200 predecessor is &quot;smart routing&quot; to obtain the best available network through the system&apos;s multi-WAN (Wide Area Network) capability.

While on the ground, the upgraded router gives passengers the same 3G/4G service they cur-rently enjoy with their cell phones and this will transition to the latest 4G LTE when available. Currently, the CNX-250 is shipping with an EASA Form1. We are working to update this existing certificate to include AvioIP software license into the CNX-250 router. Satcom1 AvioIP Software Suite v 3.0 is expected to be installed on the CNX-250 in Q3, 2016. We are all very committed to complete this engineering project as soon as possible due to many customer requests.


PGA Platform – a global entertainment server and full control IP system &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/router-management/]]&gt;



French company PGA signed late in 2015 a partnership contract with Satcom1 for AvioIP software license to be included in their new total satcom network solution system for connectivity (precisely for the core platform for the router and router management part).

Their hardware platform for connectivity IFE/CMS systems has Satcom1 AvioIP Software Suite installed which makes the PGA platform even more VVIP focused, besides their Ka-Band capability incorporated in the hardware.

• Cabin Management / In-Flight Entertainment

• Adding router features in the same server unit

• Porting of AvioIP2.6 in progress

• Next versions already planned for high/speed networks

If you would like to know more about PGA platforms range of products, please consult direct, Mr. Marc PIAULET, email: Marc.PIAULET@pga-avionics.com &lt;[[mailto:Marc.PIAULET@pga-avionics.com]]&gt;


JetLAN AS270 &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/cabin-cockpit-solutions/router-management/]]&gt;



Satcom1 has been proudly collaborating with Cobham since 2005, providing software for their server/router called AS/AR250. We are thrilled to announce that the contract for the new evolution of hardware, JetLAN AS270, was signed in the end of 2015 between Cobham and Satcom1.



This compact and powerful advanced airborne server is an ideal solution for a variety of applications. Embedding various I/Os and utilizing an Intel® i7 Quad-core processor with a large storage capacity, the AS270 allows maximum resources for:
• Network management.

• IFE/IFC connectivity.

• Data acquisition, processing and analysis.

• Communication application hosting.

• Content management.

• Cabin management.


For more technical specifications like dimensions, weight, processor, OM and more. Kindly contact direct: Christelle BOEMO,email: christelle.boemo@cobham.com &lt;[[mailto:christelle.boemo@cobham.com]]&gt;


Wheels-up time! Satcom1’s Technical Lab is up and running in Paris (and Copenhagen)

As many of you already know, Satcom1 has its engineering base and satcom lab located in our office at Le Bourget business airport in Paris, France. Besides hiring many new members to our excellent engineering team working on various R&amp;D, support and consultancy projects, we have also been expanding our lab quite significantly. We are excited to show you around as well as to show off our latest hardware additions –JetWave™ &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/jetwave/mcs8000/]]&gt; aeronautical hardware, which just arrived in our labs in France and Denmark.

Satcom1 has a tail mount antenna in the Paris lab and a fuselage mount in Danish lab, which makes our engineering team familiar with both Honeywell JetWave™ &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/jetwave/mcs8000/]]&gt; hardware solutions available.

In addition, a Ka-band modem from Viasat has also arrived to our Paris lab, to ensure we can make AvioIP software operative with Inmarsat and Viasat Ka-band technology.



Part of the engineering lab in the Satcom1 Office in Paris, Le Bourget.
We like receiving big shipments like this one!






(From the left: KANDU, MODMAN Modem Manager, Fuselage Antenna). Learn more about JetWave™ here &lt;[[http://www.satcom1.com/jetwave/mcs8000/]]&gt;.
Fuselage mounted Antenna (JetWave™)






KANDU and MODMAN up close.
 







Over the coming months Satcom1 engineering teams are constructing full testing labs, finalizing ground infrastructure, developing new value added services based on the Ka-Band.


New addition to Satcom1 Consultancy &amp; Engineering team:
 Welcome to Alban Ngoma



Satcom1 consultancy and support department is continuously adding more engineers to our support team to service our customer base fleets but also to ensure we are ready to support the Ka-band bandwidth era in terms of new technology coming to our customers. We are happy to announce a new addition to our Technical Team in Paris – Alban Ngoma.

Alban will be working as a Support &amp; Consultancy engineer. Many of you might deal with Alban in the future as his main missions are the remote configuration of equipment during the activation of new aircraft, resolving any problems and challenges reported by our customers, as well as carrying out the technical solutions.


Quiz

Congratulations to the winner in the last edition of SAT2U! For a chance to win another Danish Design Prize, email the following answers to Satcom1 &lt;[[mailto:marketing@satcom1.com]]&gt;

• What is the name of the SATCOM service especially suited for helicopter market?

• What’s the name of the new router by Cobham?

• How many types of antennas the JetWave™ set include?
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
