<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201910_Global_Email_October 2019 Newsletter_JRD.201910_Global_Email_HGuide Octob</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>HGuide Highlights: Aiding Resources, News Products and More</subject>
    <textOnly>View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Hi, {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}We&apos;re pleased to announce the start of Honeywell&apos;s HGuide Highlights. In each issue, we strive to provide you with brief, engaging and timely updates about our HGuide inertial sensors and navigators business. For more information about our products and services, please send a note to HGuide.Sales@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:HGuide.Sales@honeywell.com]]&gt;.

INTEGRATION AND AIDING SUPPORT FOR HGUIDE CUSTOMERS
We&apos;re here to help our customers integrate our HGuide products into their applications. Here, you&apos;ll find an exhaustive list of all our aiding resources available to customers. Learn more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/201910_IMU_Aiding Resources_v3.pdf]]&gt;

HGUIDE TEAM ADDS TWO NEW INERTIAL MEASUREMENT UNITS
“Honeywell is committed to expanding our inertial sensor and navigation offerings to meet the needs of new industrial customers with our HGuide i300 and HG4930 S-Class 
IMUs,”... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2019/september/honeywell-expands-navigation-offerings-to-meet-evolving-requirements-for-industrial-applications]]&gt;.
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TtD50Cd7ilY]]&gt;
HGUIDE N580 NAVIGATOR PROVIDES NAVIGATION ACCURACY FOR 3D MAPPING
“Sometimes we work in valleys where signals are blocked by mountains, but we find that the operation of the HGuide n580 INS/GNSS remains very precise and accurate. Read 
more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2019/march/honeywell-navigator-delivers-precise-location-accuracy]]&gt;
TELL US ABOUT YOUR EXPERIENCE
We&apos;re always looking for feedback from our customers who are using our products in their applications. If you&apos;ve had a positive experience, we&apos;d love to feature your company in our next customer success story. Tell us more about your experience using our products to be considered here &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/H6HS59N]]&gt;.
FEEDBACK FOR IMPROVEMENT
HGuide Highlights were designed to keep our customers in-the-know about what we&apos;re doing to continually drive value to their business. Let us know if there are topics we&apos;re missing or if there&apos;s something we can do to improve this communication &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/PKCZ2P6]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
