<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Global_internal-Comms_Supplier-Zero-Defect-Plan-Reqs_Email_Operational.Em</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Supplier Zero Defect Plan Requirements</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Supplier, 

 At Honeywell Aerospace, on-time delivery with perfect quality to our joint-end customers is our top priority, and we depend on you, our valued supplier partners, to strive for the same. 

 As a reminder, the core quality requirement for all deliverables is to comply 100% to specifications. If your processes lead to performance below this threshold, Honeywell expects you to pursue measurable continuous quality and delivery improvement actions. Honeywell Aerospace’s Quality Requirements are a material part of your contractual agreements with Honeywell, including Section 1.3 of the Supplemental Purchase Order Condition (SPOC) Manual, which defines the following minimum performance expectations: 

 Quality: 100 PPM or lower based on a three-Month Moving Average (3 MMA)
 Delivery: 98% On-Time to Requirements (OTTR) 

 When a supplier does not meet its contractually required performance minimums, Honeywell may take a variety of actions to help our suppliers regain top performance. Once such action is requiring suppliers to engage in an aggressive improvement project called the Zero Defect Plan, or ZDP. ZDPs are coordinated by the supplier’s leadership and relevant Honeywell stakeholders, focusing on implementing sustainable improvements to the supplier’s processes to achieve the expected quality and delivery performance. 

 Consistent with the ZDP instructions in HASP &lt;[[https://scc.honeywell.com/irj/portal]]&gt; (SI-ZDP-01), Honeywell Aerospace will require suppliers whose performance falls below contractually required performance minimums to utilize robust process improvement tools, including key elements of APQP such as PFEMA’s and Control Plans. Additionally, Honeywell will partner with suppliers to conduct frequent reviews to ensure the effective use of these tools and to monitor performance improvement. 

 If your performance does not meet the minimum standards required by your contract, you will be contacted by a Honeywell stakeholder to immediately implement a ZDP to drive the required improvements. 

 Thank you for your continued partnership and for adhering to these important requirements. 

 Scott Hillpot
 Honeywell Aerospace Global Sourcing &amp; Procurement 
 Vice President and Chief Procurement Officer</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
