<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Customer Experience (CX).CX New Hire Email 3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>CX Tips – When You’re on the Frontline</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Use these tips to keep Honeywell customers smiling.

One thing is clear: the customer you’re working with has a problem. And even though he hasn’t slowed down enough to tell you what that problem is, he’s clearly unhappy about it.



 





So what do you do? The first step is to restore calm. Most of the frustration a customer feels in that kind of situation stems from their mistaken belief that the company won’t work to correct it. It’s up to you to prove that at Honeywell, that’s not the case.

 









Upset callers will often assume that the company representative they’re speaking with is completely familiar with the problem – which is seldom the case. So, calmly work with the caller to find out what’s at the source of the frustration.

 









In many cases, there may be little you can do immediately to take care of the problem. The key is to put yourself in the customer’s situation. At the very least, you’d want to know that the person on the other end of the phone is listening to your concerns, recognizes your frustration, will do everything possible to correct the problem, and will keep you informed.

 




Here are a few suggestions from the Honeywell Customer Experience Team to convey your helpfulness to the customer:
Assume that your customer has a right to be angry.
“I can see why you’re upset, I probably would be too in your situation.”
Let them know you’re listening – by telling them what you’ve heard.
“I understand you’re not happy about the change to the XYZ program.”
Take the blame for any misunderstanding.
“I apologize that we didn’t do a better job of explaining the process to you.”
Don’t wait ‘til you have the perfect answer to let them know you’re working on the issue.
“I’ll send you an update within 24 hours.”








Now, what can we do for you?
The Honeywell Customer Experience Team is here to do everything we can to make your job easier, our customers happier, and our company more responsive and successful.
To do what, we need to hear from you. What are your points of frustration when you’re working with a customer? Or, just as importantly, what’s working for you that might benefit others in your same situation?
We’ll work to find answers to your question, and share your suggestions. Watch your email for more.
The Honeywell Customer Experience Team is on your team.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
