<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201804_Global_Email1_GoDirectDatalink_mih.201804_Global_Email1_GoDirectDatalink_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>GoDirect Datalink and PFM Team Up to Deliver an Improved Connected Experience for You</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.pfmsys.com/]]&gt;

Big news from Honeywell GoDirect™ Flight Services &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/service-listing/flight-services]]&gt;! We’ve integrated our aircraft datalink data with Professional 
Flight Management (PFM) &lt;[[https://www.pfmsys.com/]]&gt; operations management services. 

Now you can link your datalink position &amp; OOOI reports to PFM systems to import flight times into PFM, send flight following notifications and follow your flight on map in real-time! 

What this means for you:



	- Improved efficiency for your operation - share meaningful data between your two most important systems 

	- Reduced flight log errors and inaccuracies by avoiding human errors 

	- More situational awareness – real-time location reporting lets you track your aircraft through all phases of flight 

	- Send enhanced flight notifications – keep your team (flight operations, passenger’s executive assistants and security) updated for better planning



To take advantage of this integrated offering you must be an active GoDirect Datalink &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/godirect-datalink]]&gt; and PFM subscriber. Not set up today? Contact our accounts team via email FlightServices@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FlightServices@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. Our Honeywell Flight Services representatives will assist in the account set up to enable this data forwarding service. 

Honeywell GoDirect Team

Email: FlightServices@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FlightServices@Honeywell.com]]&gt;
US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330 extension 1
International: +1 (602) 365-7020 extension 1</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
