<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Amer_LATAM_CH_BGA_Dassault_JW-MarkII-Easy2_Email.202008_Americas_Email_JW</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Upgrade to JetWave and Save!</subject>
    <textOnly>As well as being a powerful business tool, your business jet is often your home away from home. 
Saying that, we know that a powerful internet connection is key when you are flying – on business or on leisure. 
We know that there are some things we cannot change. But others, we can! So, take advantage of this time on ground to upgrade your aircraft with JetWave. JetWave is the in-flight Wi-Fi for today&apos;s business executive. With JetWave, you can connect with the Inmarsat Jet ConneX Ka-Band network, the best broadband service available for business aviation. Only JetWave delivers global, secure, high-speed Wi-Fi that’s as good as you get at home or in the office.  
And now, it’s even better! You can choose from one of the time-limited special offers below to enjoy the best in-flight connectivity and save up to US$150,000.
Offer One * Offer Two ** Bonus Offer     Buy JetWave and get: - $100,000 cashback from Honeywell - AND 6 months of free JX-1 services (valued at $50,000)  Install JetWave now and get: - $50,000 cashback from Honeywell - AND 6 months of free JX services (any package) $10,000 More Credit - What’s more, install the latest 
Honeywell Forge Router and you’ll receive a further $10K credit from Honeywell.
Dassault Aircraft Services can install and activate your plan easily as 1, 2, 3.
Click in the link below and get a quote from a Dassault Aircraft Services near you.
I WANT A QUOTE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/all-your-upgrades-available-in-one-place?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_ch_latam_bga_jw_dfj]]&gt;
* Offer subject to activating the JetWave terminal with a 3, 4 or 5-year airtime service agreement. This limited time offer is available to Falcon 2000 and Falcon 900 operators.
** This offer is applicable on all certified JetWave aircraft and applies to any JX plan with a three, four or five-year service agreement</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
