<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_Global_Nurture_GoDirect_BGA_mih.201908_Global_Nurture_GoDirect_BGA_Email4_M</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Boost your Viasat Connected Experience with Honeywell</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Making the Most of Your SATCOM Investment with GoDirect
Thinking about buying a Viasat Ka-Band or Ku-Band satellite communications system to upgrade your business jet? A GoDirect Router and GoDirect Cabin Connectivity services from Honeywell can complement your purchase and help you deliver a much better Wi-Fi experience for your passengers.
The GoDirect Router &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/godirect-router]]&gt; can replace your current router or be installed as part of a new router installation that delivers all the speed, performance and reliability you need to complement your new SATCOM system. It’s also the perfect fit for your aircraft – 65 percent smaller and 45 percent lighter than a conventional router, with a price tag 70 percent below that of previous-generation routers.
Our GoDirect Routing Software &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/may/free-routing-software-update-sends-godirect-cabin-connectivity-to-new-heights]]&gt; lets you configure your onboard satellite communications system for optimum performance and automatically choose the best available network and service. It also allows for more sophisticated features such as GoDirect Access per-device billing for charter operations and fully enabled the GoDirect Network App providing detailed device and usage data to maintenance personnel on the ground.
With GoDirect Cabin Connectivity &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/godirect-cabin-business-aviation]]&gt;, we give you the tools you need to reduce data costs by up to $100,000 annually per aircraft while still providing a great connected experience for your passengers.




GET CONNECTED &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/Setting-New-Standards-for-In-Flight-Connectivity?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_godirectcabin_bga&amp;utm_content=marketo]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
