<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_APAC_AIN_Survey_MC.202004_APAC_AIN_Survey_Email2_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your Experience Matters | Register Today For The AIN Survey</subject>
    <textOnly>Help us improve our products and services by completing the AIN survey 

 Dear Valued Customer,

 We appreciate our relationship with you and your constant feedback. This helps us continuously improve our products and services, building long lasting relationships with you as our valued business aviation customer.

 Every year, Aviation International News (AIN) conducts a Product Support Survey asking their readers to evaluate aircraft, engines, and avionics products with which they have had experience during the prior twelve months. The survey is released during the month of May.

 As both an engines and avionics manufacturer, Honeywell takes this survey seriously. We use the information from the results to improve our products, services, and support. Our goal is to gather as much feedback from our customers worldwide, make improvements, and achieve top marks in the surveys. To make this happen, we need your support and feedback in the upcoming AIN survey. 

 In order for you to take the survey, you must be registered with AIN prior to April 24, 2020. You can register for free here &lt;[[https://www.ainonline.com/aviation-international-news-subscribe?ain_promo_code=honeywell]]&gt;. If you are already subscribed to AIN, please let us know and watch for and complete the 2020 survey.

 If you have any questions on the survey or think it would be valuable for others in your organization to take part, please let me know.

 Thank you in advance for your feedback on Honeywell!

 Customer &amp; Product Support Team
 Honeywell Aerospace


 More info: Aviation International News is a print and digital publication that covers all aspects of aviation: business, military, and transport. Subjects include aircraft, engines, personnel, acquisitions, accidents, safety, security, and training. According to the AIN website, “AIN’s Product Support Survey ask readers to evaluate aircraft, engines and avionics products they have had experience with during the prior twelve months. This in-depth survey asks readers to evaluate aircraft and engines across ten different categories and avionics across seven different categories. The survey is traditionally conducted during the month of May and results are released in the August (aircraft), September (avionics) and October (engines) issues of Aviation International News.” To learn more about the surveys and AIN, click here &lt;[[https://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/prodsupport-survey]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
