<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201703_Global_Email_MediaNewsletter_mih.201703_Global_Email_MediaNewsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Stay Connected with Honeywell - Connectivity Newsletter Q1 2017</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HONEYWELL CONNECTIVITY MEDIA NEWSLETTER
Q1 2017
STAY CONNECTED WITH HONEYWELL
The first Honeywell connectivity media newsletter is here! Tune in every quarter for the latest Honeywell connectivity news and updates for the aviation industry.
EXECUTIVE VIEW: THE POWER OF THE CONNECTED AIRCRAFT 
The aerospace industry is going through a tremendous change right now, driven by the connected aircraft. What started as a revolution in the passenger experience has now forced airlines to re-examine what amenities are a must-have on each flight to stay competitive. Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/march/the-power-of-the-connected-aircraft]]&gt; from Michael Edmonds, vice president, Connectivity and Services.
JETWAVETM PROGRAM UPDATE


The past year has been monumental for Honeywell’s JetWave connectivity hardware, which connects to Inmarsat’s Global Xpress Ka-band network and provides true broadband service around the world. Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/march/jetwave-program-update]]&gt;
HONEYWELL CONNECTED HELICOPTER TAKES OFF
Access to global connectivity is changing the very nature of the helicopter industry. Honeywell’s experience in connectivity and communications gives helicopter operators access to unparalleled levels of data and the ability to track their fleet and stay connected anywhere in the world. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/march/honeywell-connected-helicopter-takes-off]]&gt;
NEW TECH FOR LANDING AT CHALLENGING AIRPORTS

Landing an airliner or business jet full of passengers is a huge responsibility for pilots, especially when they’re faced with adverse conditions like turbulence, brutal crosswinds, mountainous terrain and busy airspace. The latest in software and connectivity enabled pilot tools is improving flight safety and making landings easier for pilots. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2017/march/landing-at-some-of-the-most-challenging-airports-with-new-software-and-connectivity-pilot-tools]]&gt;
IN CASE YOU MISSED IT: RECENT CONNECTIVITY NEWS FROM HONEYWELL 
Honeywell and EAD Aerospace Boost In-Flight Connectivity for Airbus A319 with European Agency Certification &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/february/honeywell-and-ead-aerospace-boost-in-flight-connectivity-for-airbus-a319]]&gt; 
Japan Airlines Adopts Honeywell GoDirect Fuel Efficiency Software &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/january/japan-airlines-adopts-honeywell-godirect-fuel-efficiency-software]]&gt; 
FaceTime on a Helicopter? No Problem with Aspire® 200! &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/facetime-on-a-helicopter-no-problem-with-aspire-200]]&gt; 
India&apos;s Jet Airways Joins Growing List of Airlines Adopting Honeywell&apos;s Flight Efficiency Services &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/february/india-s-jet-airways-joins-growing-list-of-airlines-adopting-honeywell-s-flight-efficiency-services]]&gt; 
Honeywell Receives Certification to Keep Helicopters Connected and Mission Ready for Operators &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2017/march/honeywell-receives-certification-to-keep-helicopters-connected-and-mission-ready-for-operators]]&gt; 
To keep updated on the latest connectivity and Honeywell news, please watch this alias or visit the Honeywell News page &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/newsroom/pressreleases/?page=1]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
