<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_BK_Webinar_SocialFlight_Privacy_in_Age_of_ADS-B_MC.Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Privacy in the Age of ADS-B</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for attending our recent SocialFlight webinar “Privacy in the Age of ADS-B”. In a few days, we will have this posted online for on-demand viewing and will send you the link.

A special thank you to our guests from the FAA and DOT who presented with us: William Blacker - LADD Program Manager, Syed Tahmid – PIA Program Manager and Francis Coyne – DOT PIA Program Engineer. We appreciate Jeff Simon developing and presenting this critical topic in such a collaborative way, and look forward to partnering with SocialFlight to expand this series.

 As I mentioned in the presentation, our KT-74 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/kt-74]]&gt; Mode S transponder is a slide-in replacement for the KT-76 A/C 
and KT 78, using the form factor, wiring and tray. Add an ADS-B compliant GPS position source, and you’re ADS-B compliant.
 
 The KT 74 supports an easy Flight ID entry through the Function menu in the Pilot’s Guide &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/~/media/bendixking/files/d201308000036_kt-74-pilot-guide.pdf]]&gt;. You are also able to modify the ICAO code through the Config menu.

 Our UAT-based KGX 150/130 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/productitems/kgx-150-130]]&gt; products support ADS-B Out and FIS-B, TIS-B ADS-B In. The KGX 150 includes a WAAS GPS, while the KGX 130 does not. With these products, the pilot can easily select UAT anonymous mode through a discrete switch.

 As a seminar special, we are offering a 10% discount on our transponders through our My Avionics &lt;[[https://apps.apple.com/us/app/my-avionics/id1367559967]]&gt; app found on the App Store for iPhone and iPad products. Easy to use; either upload a photo of your panel or take a photo through the app, complete the information and you’ll receive the discount in your inbox. 

 If you have any feedback or questions, please email &lt;[[mailto:roger.dykmann@honeywell.com?subject=Question%20about%20ADS-B%20and%20Privacy%20Webinar%20Feb%2012]]&gt; me.

 Sincerely,
 Roger Dykmann</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
