<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>RSVP Letter.RSVP Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>RSVP NOW Honeywell Sales Advisory Board Meeting</subject>
    <textOnly>Business Aviation Newsletter: March 2015


The Direct Access App Got an Upgrade 

Direct Access, one of our convenient mobile apps, provides access to vital services at your fingertips. We recently made improvements to the user interface, navigation and contact functions so it is easier to use than ever.
 
Learn more &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/direct-access-app-upgrades&gt;

___________________________________________________________

New Online Technical Support Tool 

Our new support website offers 24/7 answers to your technical questions. Search for technical solutions, view &quot;how-to&quot; videos and access useful tools and information on a wide range of subjects relevant to your equipment.
 
Learn more &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/onlinetechnicalsupport&gt;

___________________________________________________________

The Gold Standard of Avionics Protection 

Avoid downtime and save money with HAPP Gold. This extended warranty program offers the full coverage of our standard HAPP plan as well as coverage for additional charges related to necessary avionics repairs.
 
Learn more &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/maintenance-and-monitoring/aftermarket-services/happ&gt;

___________________________________________________________

Join us at AEA 2015 

We are excited to be a part of the AEA International Convention &amp; Trade Show taking place April 8-11 in Dallas, TX. Stop by Booth 101 for product demos and one-on-one time with Honeywell and BendixKing representatives.
 
Learn more &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/aea-international-convention-trade-show&gt;

___________________________________________________________

ABACE 2015 in Shanghai 

The Asian Business Aviation Conference &amp; Exhibition (ABACE) is the region’s largest event showcasing business aviation products and services. We will join over 150 exhibitors to display the latest in aviation equipment.
 
Learn more &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/abace&gt;

___________________________________________________________

Get the Latest Helicopter News 

What&apos;s your helicopter mission? Whether you&apos;re looking for the latest in efficiency, connectivity or safety, stay up-to-date with the quarterly Honeywell Helicopter Newsletter.
 
Learn more &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/helicopter-newsletter-q1-2015&gt;

___________________________________________________________











Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
