<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Global_BGA_Connectivity_Forge_Network_Monitoring_Email.202010_Global_BGA_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Network Monitoring Available Now Inside Honeywell Forge</subject>
    <textOnly>Cybersecurity is a top priority as connected aircraft have become the norm in business aviation. Flight departments, pilots and passengers need to be confident the onboard network is protected from cyberattacks and other intrusions.

 We are excited to share network monitoring capabilities are now incorporated in Honeywell Forge and have a separate tile where you can see updates and traffic updates. See our list of FAQs below to learn more about this new feature.



 Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)

 What does it do?
 Network monitoring is a 
value-added service that helps keep you informed of network threats and vulnerabilities for their cabin connectivity service. The service is visualized on the Honeywell Forge dashboard via the network monitoring tile. 

 What problem does it solve?
 You want to be informed about the health of your aircraft network. The network monitoring service via Honeywell Forge gives you peace of mind that your network is protected (healthy), your sensitive data is safe and that you will be informed of any suspicious activity occurring on your network.

 How does it work?
 Network monitoring software is installed on the onboard router. The software includes an agent that examines traffic on the onboard network, looking for malicious activity or unauthorized access attempts. Questionable activity is reported to the network administrator and can be used to trigger preventative measures. 

 How is this enabled?
 It is enabled by installing the GoDirect Router software package on your equipped aircraft.

How do I get started?
Please contact your Honeywell sales representative or call 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 or email sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt; to enable this option today. 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2020/08/what-is-network-intrusion-detection]]&gt;






 
Honeywell Forge</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
