<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202009_Portal_Release_Update_September_Email_MC.202009_Portal_Release_Update_Sep</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Expanded Capability on Your Honeywell Portal</subject>
    <textOnly>Online Ordering


	- Aircraft on Ground (AOG) for Spares – Customers can now submit Spares AOG orders through the portal. The AOG order process is fully automated for Repairs, Exchanges and now Spares.
	- Ability to add shipping instructions to orders - Shipping instructions can now be included in the Shipping Information page for repairs and spares orders.
	- Part Number search types are fully exposed and now able to select multiple part number search type criteria.
	- For exchange orders, customers will be able to see accurate order price after entering a warranty exception.


Order Status


	- Ability to see details for orders with waybill lists greater than 256 characters.


Warranty Claims


	- New Warranty FAQ page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services-and-support/warranty-protection-plans/warranty-faqs]]&gt;
	- Multiple Claims Form &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes/2020/warranty-multiple-claims]]&gt;: Deployed functionality for Airline &quot;bulk&quot; warranty claim submittal. This allows a one-time claim entry for multiple events: RNR (remove &amp; replace), freight events and MSP avionics.


Product Reliability Updates - Get the latest information on in-service product improvements addressed by Honeywell, summarizing the issues and including the program schedule. Go to Product Reliability Updates &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes/2020/service-request-updates]]&gt;

 Authorized Sales &amp; Service Partner Lookup Tool – Enhanced the tool for ease of use and search with dynamic filtering. The Sales &amp; Service Partner lookup tool is available here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us/channel-partner-locator]]&gt;.

 Pricing Exception for Spares Orders – A new training topic page was created on How to add a pricing exception to a Spares order. Please click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics/online-ordering-pricing-exceptions]]&gt; to access the page.

 RDR7000 Configure &amp; Buy - The Configure &amp; Buy option allows Honeywell’s authorized sales and service partners to select from the available hardware and 
software for the aircraft type in question and place an online order for all components required, customized to each aircraft tail. This enhanced shopping cart experience virtually eliminates potential order discrepancies around parts or pricing. With near-instantaneous delivery of selectable software features, our partners are ensured maximum responsiveness to deliver against customized operator requests, ensuring the ability to deliver when and where the opportunity arises. Please refer to this product page for RDR7000 for more information: https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/weather-radar/rdr-7000 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/weather-radar/rdr-7000]]&gt; 

 To view the individual release notes for the items listed above and to catch up on latest improvements to 
MyAerospace, please refer to and bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
