<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Amer_HCE_Swift-64-End-of-Life_Emails_Operational.Email 1 - Commercial</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Discontinuation Notice for Swift 64 Services</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 

 If you haven’t already done so, now is the time to upgrade! 

 On December 31, 2020, Inmarsat will be discontinuing &lt;[[https://www.inmarsat.com/closure-of-fleet-77-and-swift-64-services]]&gt; Swift 64 Services and you will need to upgrade your hardware and 
airtime service package prior to the deadline to ensure uninterrupted high speed data connectivity. Don’t worry, our team is here to help. It is our top priority to help make sure you don’t experience any disruption to your service. We have several high-speed data solutions that we can provide depending on your mission requirements. 

 SwiftBroadband offers connectivity that is secure, worldwide and compatible with government-grade encryption standards. Providing global voice and high-speed data from cockpit to cabin, SwiftBroadband connects flight crews to high-speed data providing real-time information to improve flight operations. 

 Ka-Band upgrades provide the industry’s fastest and global wideband coverage options in aviation connectivity utilizing Inmarsat’s Global Xpress satellite network. Connect with our team to talk through Honeywell’s JetWave upgrade options. 

 To discuss service and hardware options talk with your regional sales manager or click the upgrade now link below. 

 Thank you for being a loyal Honeywell customer. We hope you enjoy your new connectivity service.
UPGRADE NOW &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/swift-64-services-to-be-discontinued?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;
Thank you, 

Honeywell Forge Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
