<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_SparesPricingUpdate_LG.201809_SparesPricingUpdate_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Portal Makes it Easy to Order Contract Spares</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
MYAEROSPACE PORTAL MAKES IT EASY TO ORDER CONTRACT SPARES
Dear Customer:
You have received this email because our records indicate that this information is relevant to you. If you no longer need this information, please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Distribution-Update.html]]&gt; to 
update your information.

Honeywell continues to enhance our MyAerospace portal to make it easier for you to place and monitor your orders. You can now use our award-winning &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/june/honeywell-s-myaerospace-portal-wins-top-web-design-award]]&gt; MyAerospace to order your contract spares. Customers that have established contracts for spare parts will now see the specific contract number and associated pricing displayed when 
ordering through the MyAerospace Online Ordering tool.
 
What do I need to know? 


	- When ordering, part numbers listed in a contract will default to the contract price. 
	- The list price and the unit price will still be provided.
	- Orders will be placed with reference to the contract number. 
	- Customers that use an electronic data interface are not impacted by this enhancement.
	- 
This new enhancement does not apply to military contracts for United States Government end-use.





What do I need to do differently?


	- Contract customers should use MyAerospace &lt;http://myaerospace.honeywell.com&gt; to place orders.
	- MyAerospace offers 24/7 access and is available for your order management needs, including parts quoting, ordering, order status, and tracking. 




Thank you for using Honeywell. If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell Customer Support contact or submit a 
question &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/VzI0000G7m0X200QqhrE0Z0]]&gt; through MyAerospace.Honeywell.com. 
 


Honeywell Aerospace
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt;
 


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
