<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201910_Global_Email_Flight-Bag-Pro-Updates_amr.201910_Global_Email_Flight-Bag-Pr</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Updates required for security to your Flight Bag Pro application</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Flight Bag Pro Customers, 

 Honeywell’s commitment to continuous improvement and security has carried us to an update in our security policies when using our Flight Bag Pro application. And as an industry leader, we understand the sensitivity in the information and private flight details found within EFB flight planning by our operators. 

 To prevent any unwanted vulnerabilities within your Flight Bag Pro app, our security team has determined that users will only be permitted to remain logged in for a period of 7 days. Honeywell understands that this change in security policy presents a slight inconvenience, but we believe it’s necessary to protect your information. 

 Here is how you will experience this update: 



	- Users will be required to update to the current version of Flight Bag Pro by December 20, 2019
	- Credentials expire after 7 days of non-use of the application
	- Auto logout occurs when a user is inactive for greater than 7 days 
	- If a user remains active in the application the 7-day period resets
	- Auto logout only occurs when your device is connected to the internet



You can CLICK HERE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/services/flight-services/flight-bag-pro/7-day-login?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_godirect&amp;utm_content=flight-bag-pro]]&gt; for a full list of FAQ. 

 Please let our team know if you have any questions or concerns on the information above. We value your business and are here to support you. 

 Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Flight Services
 flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
