<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ADS-B Out.ADS-B Out for All Aircraft.ADS-B Out Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>RE: Your ADS-B Out Solution is Finally Here</subject>
    <textOnly>HONEYWELL&apos;S ADS-B OUT SOLUTION FOR PRIMUS II OPERATORS

If you&apos;re one of the many aircraft operators who still don&apos;t have a solution to meet the ADS-B Out 2020 mandate, now&apos;s never been a better time to upgrade! Honeywell&apos;s ADS-B Out Primus II® upgrade is finally here, designed to save you money, eliminate downtime, and 
most importantly, protect your future travel plans in 2020. 

When you upgrade your existing Honeywell Primus II Radio today and add a stand-alone GPS receiver, you’ll enjoy a cost-effective solution with a Mode-C transponder. And the best? It was designed to meet your current configuration so that you&apos;re able to meet the ADS-B Out mandate without the costly downtime you&apos;d normally experience with another solution.
                                                   
Protect your future travel plans with any of ours Primus II upgrade programs with any of these FAA approved STCs:

 - Citation 560/560 XL STC #ST01810W
 - Challenger 601, Citation 550/ 560/650/750, Global Express, Hawker 800/800XP and Learjet 40/45 STC #ST00361BO
 - Hawker 800/800XP STC #ST01811WI
 - Learjet 40/45 STC #ST04064CH

Update your avionics and get even more savings! For a limited time when you upgrade your aircraft, you can also save up to $42,000 on your Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP)*.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[#]]&gt;
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
