<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201901_Americas_Email_FlightBagPro_OpenBeta_mih.201901_Americas_Email_FlightBagP</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Insider Access to the New GoDirect Flight Planning Experience – Beta Version</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

You asked for a refresh to GoDirect™ Flight Planning and now it’s here! Start your insider access to our beta website and mobile app GoDirect Flight Bag Pro. 
 
Better planning, weather, briefings, filling, charting, maps, flight tracking and so much more. You won’t want to miss out! 
 
We’re on a mission to give you the smartest, fastest and most accurate flight planning experience possible. Testing with us is easy. Simply click the link below and start planning! 
 




YES, START MY INSIDER ACCESS &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/GoDirectFlight_Beta2.html]]&gt;




 IMPORTANT WHILE TESTING:  



	- Flight plans created on beta.flightservices.honeywell.com will not display on mygdc.com. (Example: if you run and file a flight plan in beta, please access that plan in beta.) This also applies to Flight Bag Pro in test flight. You will not experience this after the production release in March.  

	- While calculating Equal Time Points (ETP):



	- ETPs (without oxygen time) functionality is not available.
	- One engine out scenario always uses FL180 for computation irrespective of aircraft type.


	- Euro control routes may take up to 60 seconds to display due to slowness on Euro control business to business service. 

	- We are working diligently to address other minor bugs. We welcome your feedback.
QUESTIONS &amp; SUPPORT 

 

 
Please contact us with questions or support at any time. Our team is ready to help you.
 

 
Email: FlightServices@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FlightServices@Honeywell.com]]&gt; 

 
US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330 

 
International: +1 (602) 365-7020
Email for Beta Trial Feedback: godirectfeedback@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:godirectfeedback@honeywell.com]]&gt; 

 
If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/v0000ZXA0GqXQ0EvI020000]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
