<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201910_Helo_Customer_Connect_Newsletter_DaRocha.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Here is your October issue of Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>CUSTOMER CONNECT OCTOBER 2019

Dear Honeywell Customer,

This month, I’ll highlight the Operators Conference in Toluca, Mexico, the latest Field Service Engineer Profile, the technical support video of the month and other pertinent customer support updates. As always, if you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.
Did You 
Know?

The Toluca Operators Conference was a SUCCESS! 
On September 24th, over 300 operators, pilots, aircraft owners and technicians gathered to participate in 15 informative sessions and 4 onsite plane demos in Toluca, Mexico. Topics revolved around the latest updates in avionics, mechanics, MSP, as well as in customer and product support. See the pictures and read more about the event here. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2019/10/operators-conference-toluca]]&gt;

Field Service Engineer Helps Airlines Bring New Planes Online 
Making sure new airplanes enter service successfully is a big deal. As a member of the Honeywell Global Entry Into Service (EIS) team, Sr. Field Service Engineer John Chow is on the front lines whenever a new aircraft type is delivered to an airline anywhere in the world. Read about his story here. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/news/2019/10/fse-helps-airlines-bring-new-planes-online]]&gt;

Meet Face-to-Face with Honeywell in Scottsdale, AZ this November 5th
Honeywell is 
delighted to host a regional Operator Conference in Scottsdale, Arizona this November 5th. The products and services covered in this seminar have been carefully selected to improve safety, reduce overall cost of ownership &amp; introduce next generation technologies. Representatives from Aero Tech Support, MSP, Customer &amp; Product Support will be in attendance to assist with any questions or pending issues. Register here. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt; 



NEW WEBSITE, NEW TOOLS AND FEATURES! 
 In mid-October, Honeywell Aerospace launched a brand-new website! Please check out and bookmark the new Aerospace website &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt;. You will be able to search all aspects of your online experience – product, service and platform research, order status, pricing and availability, technical support and training, and recent news and events. We are posting several ‘how-to’ resources to highlight these changes. Rest assured, if you have used our platform before or have pages bookmarked, you can still log in and use the portal applications just like before. View the new website here. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt; 

Technical Support Video of the Month 
In this months’ Technical Video segment, 
we’re featuring the most watched video on the VXP System. This video is an overview of how to perform an engine vibration test using the Honeywell VXP System. Watch the video: 


The VXP System &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/videos/the-vxp-system]]&gt;

Visit Honeywell Aerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ002000Z0L0bX00qFI00jG]]&gt; to access the Technical Knowledge Center&apos;s thousands of articles and videos to help you solve technical issues, parts ordering, your order status and much more.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:

Mark DaRocha
 Customer Support Program Manager
 Office: (602) 794-4204
 Email: Mark.DaRocha@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Mark.DaRocha@honeywell.com]]&gt;

Need immediate support? Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
