<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201706_Global_Email_GIV_GV_JRD.201705_Global_Gulfstream_GIV_GV_Cockpit_Upgrade_J</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Next-Generation Cockpit Upgrade for GIV/GV Has Arrived</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

The Honeywell Next-Generation Cockpit Upgrade for GIV/GV


Dear Customer,
  

Take to the skies with the next-generation of avionics enhancements with an all-in-one cockpit upgrade for GIV/GV by Honeywell. Take advantage of new approach capabilities and cutting-edge technology designed to complement your Gulfstream and heighten your view of the skies ahead for years to come.
Seeing is Believing

Gulfstream&apos;s PlaneDeck™ and PlaneDeck SV significantly improve situational awareness by providing a view so clear, you&apos;ll never have to look outside your window. 

When combined, PlaneDeck and PlaneDeck SV provide additional flight cues, video display capability for on-board cameras and optional XM® graphical weather radar, enhancing flight safety and passenger comfort.
Command the Skies 

Open the door to vertical guidance approaches and enhanced functionality with the FMS 6.1 software upgrade. Designed with WAAS-LPV and RNP emerging technologies, this upgrade provides a foundation for the Future Air Navigation System (FANS) mandate. 

Gulfstream&apos;s exclusive onboard navigation technology, precision GPS sensors and the addition of the CD-830, keep your aircraft within a tightly specified airspace, providing a smarter and safer flying experience for everyone on board.
A New Era of Functionality 

The CD-830 control display unit (CDU) is a direct plug and play plug-and-play replacement for the CD-810 and CD-820. Its high resolution display offers full touch-screen functionality and is designed to meet current mandates. 

The CD-830 offers increased reliability, reduced weight and improved cockpit aesthetics that are proven to reduce pilot workload and make your GIV/GV easier to operate.
UPGRADE TODAY &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/CockpitUpgrade_GIV_GV_2017.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
