<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201910_Americas_Event_HOC_SCO_KFK.201910_Americas_Email1_HOC_SCO_KFK.201910_Amer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You&apos;re Invited to the Scottsdale Operators Conference on November 5th</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NOVEMBER 5TH SCOTTSDALE 
OPERATORS CONFERENCE
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customers and Partners}}, 
 
Honeywell is delighted to host a regional Operator Conference in Scottsdale, Arizona this November 5th. The products and services covered in this seminar have been carefully selected to improve safety, reduce overall cost of ownership &amp; introduce next generation technologies. Representatives from Aero Tech Support, MSP, MSP Avionics, Customer &amp; Product Support will be in attendance to assist you with any questions or pending issues. 
 
  Date: November 5, 2019
  Time: 9:00 am to 1:00 pm
  Event cost:  Free for Honeywell Customers – please feel free to invite your colleagues
  
Venue: Aviation Business Center
 15041 N Airport Dr Scottsdale, AZ 85260 (MAP) &lt;[[https://goo.gl/maps/23e5mW2VHCeuV72v9]]&gt;
 





CLICK HERE TO RSVP &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Learn and Participate in Thought-Provoking Sessions  
 
 A wide range of topics will be covered during the half-day session, providing conference participants with useful information about Honeywell engines, auxiliary power units and other mechanical and avionics systems.
Robust Networking and Connecting with Honeywell Representatives 
 
 The conference gives business aircraft owners, operators, pilots and maintenance chiefs a chance to hear about Honeywell developments and meet face-to-face with members of the Customer &amp; Product Support team.
Introducing the Customer Corner 

Take the opportunity to meet with Honeywell Representatives in a 1:1 setting. The local Customer Support Managers and Field Service Engineers will be onsite to answer any questions.
This event is open to all Honeywell customers. Please feel free to share the invitation with your flight department and customers.


We look forward to meeting you in Scottsdale!


Best regards,
 Your Honeywell Customer &amp; Product Support Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
