<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20184_ROUpdates_LG.20184_ROUpdates_NewsEmail</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Managing Your Repair and Overhaul Order Keeps Getting Easier</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Managing Your Repair &amp; Overhaul Orders Keeps Getting Easier
We are always looking for ways to make it easier for you to do business with us and we value your feedback to improve what matters most to you.    

Based on your feedback, we have made changes over the past year to streamline our repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) capabilities, reduce delays, and enhance the MyAerospace Portal usability.
 



 Visit MyAerospace  &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
Recent Updates


	- Understand your warranty claim decision with clear decision justification messages
	- View exact pricing on scrap/return-as-is options for repair quotations
	- Obtain repair station license numbers from our Repair Capabilities application
	- Access consistent parts pricing regardless of factory source
	- Manage your EDI orders more effectively with new message data
View Both Honeywell and Licensed Partner Repair Capabilities


	- Expand your repair site choices when searching for repair services
	- Manage your repair orders more effectively with additional flexibility 
	- View both Honeywell and licensed partner repair capabilities on the MyAerospace Repair Capabilities &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; application.
Let us Know! 

Keep track of our updates on MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00rI0G002000Q9X2eZ0]]&gt; please continue to provide feedback on your recent service experience -- and what is most important to you. We are even making it easier for you to provide feedback through a new, simple look at our transactional assessments.



 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
If you have questions, please contact your Honeywell business representative.

Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
