<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_TPE331 Channel Partner Network Reset_Email to Operators_kcr.201905_TPE331</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Changes To TPE331 Channel Partner Network</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | TPE331 ENGINES
Honeywell Announces New TPE331 Channel Partner Network
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Customer}},

Honeywell establishes Authorized Channel Partners across the globe to help pilots and operators keep their TPE331 engine performing at its best. In a recent review, Honeywell evaluated the Authorized Channel Partner network, ultimately reducing the number of TPE331 Authorized Channel Partners in our global network.  The new Authorized TPE331 Channel Partner network can be found below:



FIND AUTHORIZED TPE331 CHANNEL PARTNER &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/~/media/aerospace/files/authorized-service-centers/tpe331authorizedservicecentermap.pdf]]&gt;



Honeywell&apos;s Authorized Channel Partners are selected due to their unique market reach and strong track record of performance, integrity, and compliance. Our partners provide customers with a Honeywell-approved source of parts, support, installation, maintenance, repair, service, warranty, and special program applications. By servicing and/or repairing your aircraft’s TPE331 engine with a Honeywell Authorized Channel Partner, operators can:



	- Keep maintenance and event costs low with special pricing programs and discounts only available to Authorized Channel Partners
	- Reduce downtime thanks to Channel Partner stocking requirements
	- Feel confident that parts installed on their aircraft are OEM certified and meet the original design intent
	- Have access to long term OEM support and warranties, including product improvements
	- Trust that their maintenance technician has received the latest training and has access to the latest technical publications from Honeywell


Honeywell encourages pilots and operators to leverage the Authorized Channel Partner network to keep your TPE331 engine performing at its best. 

Thank you for your business and continued support.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
