<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.CX New Hire Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Welcome to Air Transport &amp; Regional!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Our whole team welcomes you!

We’re the Honeywell Customer Experience Team, a 4 person group specifically created to help improve customer satisfaction while we build loyalty and sales.







How will we know we’re all doing a good job?
Measuring the “experience” a customer has when they’re interacting with us is hard to do. Fortunately, several of our biggest customers do the measuring for us.
GE, Airbus, and Boeing go to their airline customers with surveys to ask them directly. They rate Honeywell and several other suppliers in areas including delivery, reliability, communication, customer support, and quality.




Recently, the ratings haven’t been kind. In fact, Honeywell was ranked in the bottom third by Airbus customers, dead last by Boeing, and our GE scores are trending downward.
But working together, your team and ours, we’re going to turn those numbers around.
Here’s how we’ll start to turn the arrows to point in the right direction.
Through their answers to the surveys, Honeywell customers said they want us to do an exceptional job at providing them with three things: customer support, ease of delivery, and quick and effective communication.
In our next email, we’ll go into depth about what these categories entail, and how Honeywell can achieve excellence in each of them. And we’ll follow up with a third email about how you personally can put all these good intentions into action as you deal effectively with a less-than-happy customer.
So, look for the next email. And let us hear from you with problems or ideas to solve them.
The Honeywell Customer Experience Team is on your team.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
