<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Global_PortalOnlyforOrderEntry_mih.201905_Global_PortalOnlyforOrderEntry_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Final Reminder: Place All Your Repair Orders on the Honeywell Portal</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
PLACE ALL YOUR REPAIR ORDERS ON THE HONEYWELL PORTAL
Dear Repair Providers, Distributors and Brokers,

This message serves as a final reminder that effective June 1, 2019, Honeywell Aerospace requires you to create and submit repair orders online via MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login]]&gt; moving forward. This is a follow up to previous communications sent in October, November and December 2018.

After June 1, 2019, any repair orders received at Honeywell without an electronic order confirmation will not proceed into the repair cycle. The unit(s) will automatically be placed ‘On Hold’ and you will be notified via email to create the order online. 

What are the benefits of Online Ordering?



	- Electronic repair orders facilitate a timely, seamless flow into the repair cycle.
	- Order paperwork and documentation is accurate, eliminating holds and delays.
	- Immediate confirmation that the order has been placed. 
	- This enables Honeywell to provide faster repair turn times, as non-value added cycle time is reduced.



What do I need to know about Online Ordering?



	- Honeywell policy requires utilization of the MyAerospace portal to create orders for spares and repairs. 
	- Honeywell reserves the right to reject, and will have no liability for, orders which were not entered in the MyAerospace portal.



How do I create a repair order in MyAerospace?



	- This easy step by step guide walks you through repair order creation - Online Ordering Training &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Online Ordering_Repair Orders_051319.pdf]]&gt;
	- Prior to the shipment of the unit(s), create the repair order in the MyAerospace portal.



What do I need to ship with my unit? 



	- Include your paper Purchase Order and the MyAerospace Order Confirmation sheet.



Honeywell has partnered with Aeroxchange and B2B-Aero to offer our customers Electronic Data Interface (EDI) options for placing repairs orders with Honeywell. Contact Alexa Kasselman &lt;[[mailto:Alexa.Nieves@Honeywell.com]]&gt; to learn more about using one of these solutions with Honeywell. 


Thank you for your business,

Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
