<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201907_Americas_Event_HOC_OH_KFK.201907_Americas_Email2_HOC_OH_AB.Subject Line T</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Honeywell for the Cleveland Operators Conference - August 14</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; 
 
 
 
 
 BUSINESS &amp; GENERAL AVIATION
CLEVELAND 
OPERATORS 
CONFERENCE  
INVITATION
Dear Customers and Partners, 
 
 We are pleased to invite you to the 2019 Honeywell Operators Conference! This is a great chance to meet the Honeywell team and get your questions answered. Sign up now -- don’t miss the chance to attend as spots are limited! 
 
  Date: August 14, 2019
  Time: 9:00 
am to 4:00 pm
  Event cost:  Free for Honeywell Customers – please feel free to invite your colleagues
  Venue: House of Blues Cleveland
 308 Euclid Avenue, Cleveland, OH 44114
 Phone: (216) 523-2583 


 
Training certificates for 8 hrs. of credit will be issued to attendees. 





CLICK HERE TO RSVP &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt;
Learn about Honeywell Solutions  
 
 We will highlight Honeywell’s hardware and services, including the latest upgrades, STCs, and mandates
Honeywell Support Processes  
 
 Overview on Honeywell processes and how to make the system work for you. Honeywell staff will share best practices and are ready to answer your questions.
Unique Venue

House of Blues, each attendee will have access to explore one of the coolest venues in Cleveland.
This event is open to all Honeywell customers. Please feel free to share the invitation with your flight department and customers.


We look forward to meeting you in Cleveland!


Best regards,
 Your Customer Core Team 
Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Subscription_Page.html]]&gt; to sign up for Honeywell Aerospace email communications.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
