<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_TechSupportRedirect_LG.201903_TechSupportRedirect_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Access MyAerospace Technical Resources</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Aerospace Technical Support Customer,
 
After March 15th, 2019, your direct access to the Aerospace Technical Support (ATS) team will change. Instead, please take advantage of our 24/7 technical support resources on Honeywell’s MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt;. If you do call or email us, you will receive a response with instructions on how to access MyAerospace. 
 
MyAerospace provides easy and efficient access to thousands of technical knowledge articles and videos, publications and other valuable product support links. The award-winning interface gives you the information you need when you need it. These tips will help you access MyAerospace technical support:  


	- 
If you don&apos;t have access yet, create an ID and password following this quick reference guide &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Document%20Lists%20Files/MyAerospace%20Updates%20Training%20Materials/MyAerospace%20-%20How%20To%20Register.pdf]]&gt;.

	- 
Log in, then visit the technical support page &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; to simply type your subject into the search field.

	- 
Refine and filter your search results as needed. 

	- 
If you are unable to find what you need, complete the contact-us form &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; at the bottom of the page to reach our technical experts. If you use this form, you must also upload an attachment with proof-of-purchase from a relevant Honeywell product to prove support eligibility.

	- 
For additional MyAerospace information, view training videos and additional resources &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20ascending]]&gt;.



You can also reach out to one of our authorized channel partners for technical support. Find an expert in our extensive network by accessing our contact-us page &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt; and searching through the directory. 
 
Thank you.
  
 
Sincerely, 
Honeywell Aerospace 
 
 


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
