<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201705_EMEAI_Leadership-Update-NJM.201705_EMEAI_Leadership-Update_NJM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Organization and EMEAI Leadership Changes</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | BUSINESS &amp; GENERAL AVIATION
Dear Valued Partner,

Honeywell recently made organization changes to drive faster growth and accelerate the delivery of innovative products, software and services to existing and new customers and business segments around the world. These changes improved our aftermarket business in Europe, Middle East, Africa and India (EMEAI), with much more local authority, decision making and customer/partner relationship ownership.
These changes were designed to help drive aftermarket business growth, concentrate resources on great new products, improve our speed and decision-making and emphasize customer service excellence. One of the biggest expectations of this reorganization is to increase the agility, effectiveness and speed of our aftermarket business teams by becoming more locally empowered while improving customer intimacy and satisfaction.
In addition, you will also have heard from us that we are investing in our sales force. We have added 16 sales managers in our EMEAI BGA Aftermarket organization to reinforce our end market sales strategies for services, retrofits, modifications and upgrades. As we grow, our sales force will be linked even more closely with you, our partners, to ensure the best sales, delivery and effectiveness to market.
Further to the above changes, we have recently announced that the Senior Director for BGA Aftermarket Sales and Channel Management, Anthony Florian, will be assuming a new role as the VP Original Equipment Manufacturers. We will be undergoing a transition process as new leadership is established, which will be announced in the near future. In the meantime, please continue to direct any inquiries or escalations to your dedicated account manager, customer support or sales representative.
Our channel partners are the key to breakthrough growth for Honeywell&apos;s business, helping to drive sales and customer satisfaction. We will continue to re-invigorate our engagement with you and manage a tight transition to the new leadership in region. I shall provide further information on Anthony&apos;s replacement as soon as it becomes available. 

James Bryson 
President
Honeywell Aerospace I EMEAI Aftermarket</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
