<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS Newsletter 2014.September 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>September Direct-TO Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Newsletter Title
September 2014 Issue





Honeywell Pilot Gateway

New Website for Pilots Adds Additional Features
Honeywell’s new website for pilots launched just a few months ago, but new features are already being added.  Users can now access this newsletter, Direct-TO, along with other important updates and events.  Read/unread indicators have also been added, along with flags for new and updated publications. 
Read More. &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/September%202014/Pilot%20Gateway&gt;
 





The Radar Corner
The RDR-4000 3D 
Volumetric Radar–The Beginning:
Part 2
Last month’s article started looking at the early human factors study that helped define the RDR-4000 weather radar modes and functions. Some of the questions that Honeywell asked pilot’s during the study were discussed, and answers to the first four questions, which dealt with tilt management, were explained. This month’s article will look at the answers to the last four questions in the study. Read More. &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/September%202014/RDR-4000Pt2&gt;


 &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jul14_tools&gt;






NBAA 2014 Preview

Flight Technical Services to Share Insights at Operations Session

Honeywell Flight Technical Services discusses important operational issues every year during the National Business Aviation Convention and Exhibition Operations 
Session. Read More. &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/September%202014/NBAA%20Preview&gt;  







Global Data Center Update

Creating a Flight Package on MyGDC.com

Global Data Center subscribers have access to the MyGDC.com &lt;http://www.mygdc.com/&gt; website and app, which have a variety of flight planning tools and features, including the Flight Package feature.  By creating a Flight Package, the pilot or dispatcher can schedule a flight plan and weather package to be automatically sent at a predetermined time in the future. Read More. &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/September%202014/GDC%20Flight%20Package&gt; 
 





Tools of the Trade

Sky Connect Tracker III: Powerful Mission Management Capabilities
 
When a serious problem occurs in flight, a long list of items must be completed in a short amount of time.  Notifying dispatch that there is a problem, and transmitting aircraft position and other 
critical information comes second to handling the emergency. Read More. &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/September%202014/SkyConnect&gt;
 




Events and Training Calendar
2014 Events and Training
Honeywell&apos;s Flight Technical Services team travels extensively to bring pilots the latest information on regulations, new technology, and Honeywell product updates. Through Pilot Breakout Sessions at Honeywell Operators Conferences, one-on-one training, entry into service support, and live webinars, Honeywell pilots are on a mission to keep operators informed. Read More. &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_aug14_event_training&gt;





Questions or comments about Honeywell products or services? Please contact Flight Technical Services. &lt;mailto:FTS@honeywell.com&gt;

Upcoming Events &amp; Training  &lt;https://pilots.honeywell.com/&gt;
Operators Conference, Little Rock, AR - September 16
 
Operators Conference, Houston, TX - September 16

NBAA 2014, Orlando, FL -  October 21-23



Technical Publications, Videos, news, events, and other resources for pilots can now be found on the new Honeywell Pilot Gateway.  Click Here &lt;https://pilots.honeywell.com/&gt; to get started.


Aerospace Technical Support &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/%21ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQzc3UONDTzNQ7zN3AICDA0sjPULsh0VAb6AM7A%21/&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
