<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pro Star Aviation.ProStar ADS-B Out Email.ProStar-ADS-B Out Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The ADS-B Out STC for Your Aircraft is Here</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;                                               &lt;[[http://flightstar.com/]]&gt;
Facebook      &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;                                                              Facebook      &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/Pro-Star-Aviation-LLC-181065918611760/]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/pro-star-aviation]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/prostaraviation]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/ProStarAviation]]&gt;
The ADS-B Out STC for Your Aircraft by Pro Star Aviation and Honeywell

Strengthen your pilot&apos;s situational awareness, streamline communication between your aircraft and Air Traffic Control, and keep your aircraft properly spaced in high-density traffic areas with Pro Star Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out STC.

Stop procrastinating and get a solution that was designed to replace your current configuration and receive these benefits:  




 - Reduced separation and highly accurate departure and arrival times


 - Surveillance in areas that do not currently have radar coverage 


 - A clear view of vehicles and runways in order to avoid collisions or delays 

 - More efficient spacing and optimal routing in non-radar environments, including the busy airspace in the Gulf of Mexico, mountainous regions of Colorado and the lower altitudes of Alaska



Pro Star Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out AML STC covers:



 - Bombardier Global Express
 - Bombardier Challenger 601
 - Bombardier Learjet 40 &amp; 45
 - Cessna Citation 550, 560, 650 &amp; 750
 - Hawker 800 &amp; 1,000




Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio System

When you upgrade your existing Honeywell Primus II Radio and add a stand-alone GPS receiver, you’ll enjoy a cost-effective solution combined with the latest configuration to meet the ADS-B Out mandate. Fly with confidence with Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio equipped with a Mode S Transponder and learn more about how this certified solution can keep you flying for years to come.

Protect Your Avionics Investment

For a limited time when you upgrade your aircraft, you can save up to $42,000 on your new or existing Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan*. 

Learn More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/the-ads-b-out-stc-for-cessna-550]]&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
