<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017_HAT_PHXWarehouse_Irina.PHXWarehouse</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>NEWS: Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) expanded facilities</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | HONEYWELL AEROSPACE TRADING
TO BETTER SERVE THE EXPERTS,
 WE ARE GROWING.
As part of the new Honeywell Distribution Center at 1720 E. Grant Street, Phoenix, AZ 85034, Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) has significantly expanded its ability to continue supporting our customers with access to an increased supply of Used Serviceable Material.  
What does that mean for you, our clients?


	-       INCREASED WAREHOUSE SPACE


HAT continues to expand the range of quality products offered globally to our customers.
HAT now stocks a full range of used, serviceable airframe components from B737, B777 and A320 aircraft (and more)!
To accommodate this rapid growth the HAT-Americas team based in Phoenix, Arizona has recently moved into a new office and warehouse facility of more than 100,000 square feet.


	- IMPROVED DISTRIBUTION INFRASTRUCTURE 


The expanded facility allows us to position more of HAT’s Americas inventory under one roof, eliminating the need for satellite storage.
This consolidation provides for streamlined distribution and expanded capacity, improving  both the cycle times and the quality of the deliveries to HAT’s customers.
Our new location is just minutes away from Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX), near the I-10, I-17 and SR-51 roadways.


	- CO-LOCATION OF INVENTORY AND STAFF


For Used Serviceable Material, knowing our individual products and their history is key in meeting the needs of our customers.
The new, expanded facility allows our team of product experts to have quick and easy access to both our inventory and its corresponding records to quickly respond to any customer inquiries.
HAT’s facility is right next door to the headquarters of Honeywell Aerospace and one of our key Repair and Overhaul sites, providing convenience to visiting customers and suppliers.




CLICK HERE TO READ MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/honeywell-aerospace-trading-hat-expanded-facilities-in-phoenix-az-to-better-serve-the-experts]]&gt;



More information will follow soon.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
