<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Annual Metrics 2017.201701_Global_Annual Metrics_dpg</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aerospace Intellectual Property --  2017 Annual Trends</subject>
    <textOnly>Aero Intellectual Property - June Quarterly Metrics
May 2015

Dear Colleagues:
 
 With the help of Aero IP Law &amp; Aero IP Analytics, we prepared Honeywell Aerospace patent trends documenting the changes in inventive ideas (disclosures, filed applications, issued patents) over the past several years.  We provide the trends at 3 levels of increasing fidelity: Honeywell Aerospace overall, Aerospace Gold Enterprises (IP Steering Committee), and Aerospace patent portfolios, as defined in the IPSC Matrix &lt;https://teamsites2013.honeywell.com/sites/IPTracking/Wiki/Useful%20Documents/IPSC%20Matrix_Final.xlsx&gt;.    

Appended below is an example of the patent portfolio-level trend report for our Safety and Connectivity Radar patent portfolio.  This illustrates how key program activity (e.g. IntuVue Radar Hazard Feature development, Connected Weather) helped drive inventions during peak years.   It also illustrates periods of lower inventive activity which may or may not be expected given program phases or activity level.   Since patents are directly linked to competitive advantage, M&amp;PM and E&amp;T should review the data for their respective Gold Enterprises and take action to address changes as needed to support product strategies.

Honeywell Aerospace Annual Patent Trends &lt;https://teamsites2013.honeywell.com/sites/IPTracking/Wiki/2015%20Actuals/Forms/AllItems.aspx?RootFolder=%2Fsites%2FIPTracking%2FWiki%2F2015%20Actuals%2F2015%20Annual%20Metrics&amp;FolderCTID=0x012000B3B9051D34C497499D37EE648AD7CD3B&amp;View={88B832B5%2D403A%2D40&gt; 

We welcome your thoughts or suggestions on how we can improve this data, improve the formatting, or better share it across our teams.  Also, please consider using this data in future product business plans (e.g. highlighting Honeywell/competitor patent trend gaps in key products or technologies to drive additional strategies or actions).

We appreciate your feedback and will help provide any other information you may need.   We plan to update and share our patent trends annually.    




Thank you for your continued work in driving our IP protection program and feel free to contact me with any questions.

Thank you, 
 Dan 
Dan Gutfreund
IP Process Leader
Technology Strategy, Advanced Technology
21111 N 19th Ave (M/S 2J35A5)
Phoenix, AZ 85027
Phone: +1 602 436-9030
Mobile: +1 480 258-8692
Dan.Gutfreund@Honeywell.com &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/WQ04bZI6q0L2XG600v0Rc00&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2014 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
