<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Americas_BK_BGA_AEA_Event.AEA_Email_Invite_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Connect With BendixKing &amp; Honeywell at AEA!</subject>
    <textOnly>CONNECT WITH BENDIXKING &amp; HONEYWELL AT AEA
{{my.Add to Calendar:default=Add to Calendar}}
   
 
 
WILL YOU BE JOINING US AT AEA?
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Partner}},

 Honeywell and BendixKing are excited to connect with you at AEA 2020 and are delighted to invite you to join our training sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. The products and services featured in these sessions have been carefully selected to cover improved safety, reduce overall cost of ownership, and introduce next generation technologies.

 BendixKing Training Sessions

 Product Focus: AeroCruze 100 &amp; 230 Autopilot
 Date: 
Wednesday, March 25 8:30 AM – 9:30 AM
 Room Location: Cheekwood B
 What We’ll Cover: In this one-hour session, we will provide a detailed walk-through on AeroCruze 100 &amp; 230 autopilots. We&apos;ll also review insights, installation, ordering and tips and tricks for the products.

 Product Focus: AeroVue Touch, AeroWave 100 &amp; AeroCorder
 Date: Thursday, March 26 8:30 AM – 10:30 AM
 Room: Cheekwood B
 What We’ll Cover: This two-hour session will focus on AeroVue Touch for the 
first half of this session, and AeroWave 100 and AeroCorder during the second half. 

 Honeywell Training Sessions

 Product Focus: IntuVue RDR-7000 Weather Radar, Micro Power Unit, JetWave, Honeywell Forge Cockpit &amp; Cabin Services and Honeywell Maintenance Service Plans for Avionics and Mechanical Components.
 Dates: Wednesday, March 25 8:30 AM – 10:30 AM
Encore presentation on Thursday, March 26 8:30 AM -10:30 AM
Room Location: Cheekwood A
 What We’ll Cover: In this two-hour session, we will cover product features, capabilities, certification and applications by aircraft type for our IntuVue RDR-7000, Micro Power Unit, JetWave and Honeywell Forge Cockpit and Cabin offerings. We will also cover MSP Avionics &amp; Mechanical Components (formerly HAPP &amp; MPP) highlighting the rebrand of the service and all the recent changes and additions to the service program. 







CLICK HERE TO RSVP &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/aea-events?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_ch_americas_bga_aea-connect_tradeshow&amp;utm_content=invite]]&gt;
WHY YOU SHOULD ATTEND
INCREASE PRODUCT KNOWLEDGE
A wide range of topics will be covered during our sessions, including product overviews, installation tips, sales strategies, new features and more.





GET ANSWERS TO YOUR QUESTIONS
Learn more about Honeywell and BendixKing products and services and meet face to face.
If you can’t join a training session, meet us at booth #223
These sessions are open to all Honeywell and BendixKing dealers. Please feel free to share this email with anyone in your organization we may have missed. 

 SAVE THE DATE! Join us on Wednesday, March 25th from 8:00 PM – 11:30 PM for “Renegades” Dealer Appreciation Event, co-hosted by BendixKing, Avidyne, L3Harris, Genesys, Blue Avionics. 

 See you in Nashville!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
