<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201811_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_OpenBeta_TM.201811_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_Op</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Beta Test New Flight Planning Technology from GoDirect</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

We are thrilled to invite you to beta test our brand new Honeywell GoDirect™ Flight Planning website and refreshed GoDirect Flight Bag Pro app! Both the website and app are powered by our new flight planning engine software. 

Honeywell GoDirect has created the new flight planning engine from the ground up to give you a smarter, faster and more accurate solution. We have been hard at work implementing improvements to your overall experience to add even more value to your flight planning subscription. 

We value your feedback. Input during this evaluation period is especially key. Please share your thoughts so our team can deliver the best solution for you. If you encounter any issues along the way, submit your feedback and observations to godirectfeedback@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:godirectfeedback@honeywell.com]]&gt; so we can review and investigate.

Click the button below for more info and to beta start testing! 
 





GET STARTED &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/GoDirectFlight_Beta.html]]&gt;




Thanks for participating,  
 
GoDirect Flight
Questions &amp; Support  
 
Please contact us with questions or support at any time. Our team is ready to help you.

 Email: FlightServices@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:FlightServices@Honeywell.com]]&gt; 
 US Toll-Free: (888) 634-3330 
 International: +1 (602) 365-7020
Email for Beta Trial Feedback: godirectfeedback@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:godirectfeedback@honeywell.com]]&gt; 

If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/v0000ZXA0GqXQ0EvI020000]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
