<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_APAC_GoDirect_Becomes_Honeywell_Forge_MC.202003_APAC_Email1_GoDirect_Beco</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Name, Even Better Service</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer, 
Your trust, feedback and support in Honeywell GoDirect has given our team enormous pride in ownership to serve you. We have made it our mission to understand your needs in order to deliver valuable solutions and support for your daily operations. As a loyal customer of Honeywell GoDirect, we appreciate your patience with us allowing us to adjust and adapt to better serve you. 
The Honeywell GoDirect services team is proud to announce the next evolution of our services called Honeywell Forge &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/urZ000rIwq0G0g02iKsQXM0]]&gt;. 
This transition allows us to leverage Honeywell’s robust and secure enterprise performance platform enabling us to provide expanded and enhanced offerings that are truly focused on bringing you best-in-class integration of scheduling, flight planning, airtime, maintenance and datalink services from your current provider, eliminating the burden of change. Our objective is to bring all of your key operating services into a single view with closed loop alerting, pulling together your global team of pilots, operations, scheduling and maintenance. We hope our initial release will drive continued conversations that will rapidly expand our services uniquely tailored for your flight department’s needs. 
The adoption of a new name was a carefully considered process. The Honeywell Forge name and platform is shared amongst Honeywell’s other service businesses in our organization, which include Cybersecurity, Worker, Building and Industrial. By migrating to Honeywell Forge, your operations will be able to leverage the most comprehensive platform not just for aviation, but for other industrial parts of your business. 
This rebranding will not affect or delay any current or future services you have with us. However, this letter is intended to offer notice that all invoicing, packaging and related documents will be rebranded. All our satellite communications hardware such as JetWave and Aspire will retain their product names and are not included in this name change. 
Our commitment to you will always remain our highest priority. Our dedicated and experienced team takes great pride in providing you the upmost experience and support for your operations. If you have any questions or concerns for our team, please do not hesitate to reach out. 
We look forward to continuing to work together during these exciting times! 
Kindly, 
Tim Xu
 Sales Director Honeywell Asia Pacific</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
