<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_BK_AeroVue_Demo_Stevens_Aerospace_MC.201906_BK_AeroVue_Demo_Stevens_Aeros</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reminder to join us at Stevens Aerospace for an AeroVue flight demo July 9 and 10</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

 &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/#reg]]&gt;

Join us next week at Stevens Aerospace and Defense, LLC at Dayton, Ohio or Nashville, Tennessee for a personal ground demo or one-hour flight demo on the Blackhawk Aerospace &lt;[[https://www.blackhawk.aero/]]&gt; King Air B200 with the Phoenix &lt;[[https://www.blackhawk.aero/phoenix-by-blackhawk/]]&gt; modification package – complete with the AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerovue-touch]]&gt;.
See for yourself how easy it is to use these products and how they make your flying experience that much more enjoyable. And with the additional engine upgrade, new props, custom interior and paint along with fresh inspections and logs – this B200 is sure to be a welcome addition to any fleet.


July 9, 2019
Stevens Aerospace and Defense Systems, LLC – Dayton &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/]]&gt;
 Dayton International Airport / KDAY
 3500 Hangar Drive, Vandalia, Ohio 45377


July 10, 2019
Stevens Aerospace and Defense Systems, LLC – Nashville &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/]]&gt;
 Nashville International Airport / KBNA
 707 Hangar Lane, Nashville, Tennessee 37217


BendixKing’s AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck offers these benefits:


	- Lower recurring maintenance costs
	- ADS-B mandate requirements
	- Reduced pilot workload and fatigue, and increases safety
	- Reduced aircraft weight up to 125 LBS
	- Rich feature-set included such as industry-leading SmartView™ synthetic vision system
	- Optional features such as weather radar, XM weather, radar altimeter, traffic alert and ground proximity warning



Time is running out for the Stevens Aerospace and Defense, LLC tour stops; sign up today! 

 
We will contact you with details and times upon your registration. Not able to join on those days? We have other dates and locations available in your area; sign up for one today and receive a response to set up your personal demo.






SIGN UP HERE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AeroVue_BK_201903.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
