<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Legacy 600/650 Mailing.Legacy 600/650 Mailing HTML Mailer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing Primus Elite™ Avionics Upgrades for Legacy 600/650</subject>
    <textOnly>Introducing Primus Elite™ Avionics Upgrades for Legacy 600/650







 &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/&gt;   &lt;#&gt;







 









Secure Your Legacy

Introducing Primus Elite™ Avionics Upgrades for Legacy 600/650

Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},

As you prepare for your upcoming 96 or 144 month inspection, there has never been a better time to secure the value and operational efficiency of your Legacy 600 / 650 aircraft. Not only will the Primus Elite™ avionics upgrade packages enable you to fly more safely and more efficiently, it can also reduce maintenance costs and increase your aircraft’s value. What’s more Honeywell is offering Legacy owners up to US$25,000 trade in value for your existing cockpit displays*.

The Primus Elite upgrades have been specifically designed for the Legacy 600/650 and include the following features and benefits:

DU875 Display Upgrade - Honeywell’s DU-875 display technology upgrades the cockpits primary flight displays to the latest in LCD technology providing improved safety, more efficient operations, and increased aircraft value.

XM™ WX Satellite Weather option – DU875 equipped aircraft operating in North America can take advantage of “always on” display of graphical weather enabling strategic route planning around adverse weather conditions resulting in on-time arrivals and fuel savings.

FMS 6.1 - The latest software upgrade for Honeywell’s FMZ-2000 Flight Management System (FMS), gives Legacy operators access to some of the most precise navigation tools available today. These include RNP, VNAV, WAAS-LPV and FANS-1A.

SmartRunway® / SmartLanding® – Building on the success of Honeywell’s RAAS system, which has been installed on thousands of commercial and business jets, SmartRunway / SmartLanding helps prevent runway incursion and excursion accidents, by providing pilots with oral and visual alerts.

Ovation Select Cabin Management System – With Ovation Select as the standard Cabin Management System (CMS) on all new Legacy 650’s, nearly 60 operators worldwide are already experiencing the benefits of this second-generation all-digital CMS/IFE solution. If you are operating a Legacy 600 with the Ovation C-Series CMS you have the unique opportunity to upgrade your analog installations to the latest in digital CMS/IFE technology with our Ovation Select CS (for C-Series). Alternatively, If you’re ready to experience high definition entertainment then ask your Honeywell representative about upgrading Ovation Select.

ADS-B Out – Ensure your Legacy is DO-260B compliant for current and upcoming ADS-B Out mandates around the world. Upgrade now to reap the operational benefits of ADS-B Out and avoid last minute price surcharges and potential aircraft downtime due to congested service centres.

To find out more about the upgrade packages for the Legacy 600 and Legacy 650, please click on the relevant link below, contact an Embraer Authorized Service Centre &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/HQ002000Z0h0JX00q3I00TG&gt; or your local Honeywell Sales Manager. Alternatively, if you would like a Honeywell representative to contact you directly, please click here. &lt;mailto:tomas.hudec@honeywell.com?cc=ed.borger@honeywell.com&amp;subject=Legacy%20Upgrade%20Offer&gt;

Legacy 600 &lt;http://hwll.co/bqel&gt;

Legacy 650 &lt;http://hwll.co/2ktf&gt;


For more information about the Primus Elite Avionics Upgrade options and packages please contact an Embraer Authorised Service Centre &lt;http://hwll.co/n3dv&gt; or your local Honeywell Sales Manager.





Legacy Upgrade Offer

As a special offer for Legacy Owners and Operators, Honeywell is offering up to US$5,000 trade in for each CRT Display with a total trade in value of US$25,000 towards your Primus Elite Upgrade Package.



For new or existing Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP) customers who purchase select Primus Elite Avionics Upgrade packages, the following additional incentives are available*:


	- New multi-year agreement with fixed 3% escalation
	- First year FREE HAPP coverage
	- $20,000 savings in second and third year ($10,000 off regular contract price per year)
	- Fourth year and beyond, will be calculated using regular contract pricing but the new higher reliability LCD DUs will continue to provide a price incentive over the same contract calculated using the older CRT’s.
















* Terms and Conditions Apply **This upgrade is standard on new production Legacy 650 aircraft.

©2015 Honeywell International Inc. All Rights Reserved.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
