<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Americas_GDT_Buy-more_HAT-Price-Match_Airlines_Email.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We will match any competitors price, or we will pay you!</subject>
    <textOnly>Big news. 

 We are excited to announce Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) is launching a new Airlines Price Match Program for the entire month of August. Under this program, HAT will meet anyone’s USM price on comparable, in-stock Honeywell product. Program guidelines can be found here &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/hat-price-match?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Price_Match]]&gt;. 

 Why you will love this program? If the competitor’s quoted price meets all the program guidelines but we choose not to match the price, you will receive a $500 online credit towards future purchases. This credit expires on 12/30/2020 and must be used on HAT’s GoDirect Trade storefront &lt;https://www.godirecttrade.com/marketplace/seller/profile/shop/HoneywellAerospaceTrading&gt;. 

 How does the program work? 



	- Simply provide a valid, non-expired quote. Upon verification of the competitor quote, you will receive your Price Match Offer from HAT.
	- Applies to Honeywell used equipment only. Non-Honeywell parts are excluded.
	- Parts must be comparable and similar across a variety of aspects. Part number, model, quantity, OEM, condition, wear and tear, quality of repair tag/certification, trace, and delivery). Life limited parts and units must have comparable and similar times and cycles. Comparable / “like” quality tags should be from authorized Honeywell repair shops or Honeywell repair shops.
	- Items must be in-stock and immediately available at competing supplier.
	- Item must be purchased online through www.godirecttrade.com &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/]]&gt; in order to be eligible for the price match.
	- Full list of exclusions, limitations and guidelines on HAT’s Price Match Program can be found here &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/hat-price-match?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Price_Match]]&gt;.


 We want to win your business. Buy from a trusted OEM.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/hat-price-match?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Price_Match]]&gt;
Stay healthy, stay safe, and take care, 

 Lisa Butters
General Manager
GoDirectTrade.com &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=User_Growth]]&gt; (powered by Honeywell)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
