<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201806_TechnicalVideos_LG.201806_TechnicalVideos_email_LG</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Tech Tips - New Videos to Manage your Maintenance Practices</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer,
Our goal is to keep you flying. We’re always adding new resources to share our technical knowledge with you. Recently, we’ve hosted webinars and created new videos to help you troubleshoot, maintain and extend the life of your mechanical and electrical products. 
 
Access the following videos from our technical support experts on our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support&gt; (search for product name) or directly at the links below:


	- 
LTS101 Engines &lt;[[https://youtu.be/w5iZ-PXLLvU]]&gt; – product improvements and references to line maintenance service bulletins to avoid unscheduled engine removals

	- 
Wheels and Brakes for A380, A340 and A330 &lt;https://youtu.be/1GQ1wyiRfMc&gt; – published service information, upgrade options, and service procedures to improve product reliability

	- 
Traffic Collision Avoidance System &lt;https://youtu.be/c7H0MMqZjwQ&gt; - maintenance best practices and published technical service information to optimize TCAS troubleshooting and reduce no-fault-founds

	- 
Satellite Communications I-3 Satellite Decommissioning &lt;https://youtu.be/EHK1IPnmGUo&gt; – configuration recommendations to adapt to the I-3 Inmarsat satellite network changes, supporting Classic Aero and S64; View the Service Information Letter D201711000078 &lt;https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/support/techpubsdeeplink?urlSearchId=F49C7B2C-0163-4000-E000-7DFA0AC5408D&gt;. 

	- 
RDR-4000 &lt;https://youtu.be/V4_s1qina3Q&gt; – IntuVue™ 3-D Weather Radar and RDR-4000 fault guidance to identify corrective actions and reduce no-fault-founds

	- 
HTS900 600 Hour Tips and Tricks Video Series – manage HTS900 inspections including replacing the fuel metering unit, checking pressure and inspecting the fuel pump internal spline:



	- 
HTS900 Fuel Metering Unit Replacement &lt;https://youtu.be/pjVwLMRV7OM&gt;

	- 
HTS 900 Delta Pressure Check &lt;https://youtu.be/4U1XVyRHjAg&gt;

	- 
HTS900 Fuel Pump Inspection &lt;https://youtu.be/puJCU9S7FmY&gt;






Need other technical support? Visit our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical publications, or to submit questions to our technical support engineering team.
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/f004G0q0bw00nI2iQZXCi0i]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
