<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>June 2018 Edition.June 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - June 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
June 2018
KEEP FLYING HIGH, EVEN IF YOUR TEAM DOESN&apos;T
Are you planning to be one of the one million attending the football tournament in Russia? Well, we’ve got some great news, so you aren’t stranded with an Aircraft On Ground. The Honeywell Aerospace team is on hand to ensure your experience of the game runs smoothly...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/june/keep-flying-high--even-if-your-team-doesn-t]]&gt;
Pilatus PC-12 training videos now available 
Honeywell has released a series of maintenance training videos for troubleshooting the Honeywell APEX cockpit system. The training videos include informative system overview and best practices for line maintenance work.


PC-12NG / KSG 7200 ADAHRS Diagnostic Tools-Usage &lt;[[https://youtu.be/5kGkVXp59pw]]&gt;
PC-12 CMC Aircraft Diagnostic and Maintenance Systems 1 of 2 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/IgMeb1i-uRA]]&gt;
PC-12 CMC Aircraft Diagnostic and Maintenance Systems 2 of 2 &lt;[[https://youtu.be/97mXmTgpdWI]]&gt;
Embraer jets certified to fly with JetWave high-speed wi-fi system
Aviation safety regulators certify the installation of Connected Aircraft hardware on Embraer Lineage 1000E jets...

Learn more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2018/may/embraer-jets-certified-to-fly-with-honeywell-s-jetwave-high-speed-wi-fi-system]]&gt;
New Dassault service to reinvent Falcon connectivity
FalconConnect offers a new way of providing inflight cabin and cockpit communications...
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/june/dassault-and-honeywell-offer-a-new-way-to-provide-inflight-cabin-and-cockpit-communications-to-falcon-operators]]&gt;
We&apos;re in the hangar with you!Honeywell has expanded its personalized customer service, a dedicated local field service representative is now available in-person when you need assistance...
Read more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_CPS_Programs_2018_CPS_LandingPage.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
