<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Global_BGA_Forge_GoGo-Termination-Notice_Email.202010_Global_BGA_Forge_Go</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>GoGo Policy Change -- Invoice Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>CUSTOMER UPDATES AND NOTIFICATIONS
Dear Valued Customer, 

 Honeywell was recently informed by GoGo that they are terminating our single bill agreement within the next 60-days. Unfortunately, after November 30, 2020, you will be receiving two separate invoices, one from Honeywell Forge and another one from GoGo.

 We apologize for this inconvenience but please note we are working tirelessly to provide you with a seamless transition with no interruption in your service. We are still committed to providing you with our dedicated customer support for both Honeywell Forge and GoGo Service. Our team is here to help you every step of the way through this transition. 

 HOW DOES THIS IMPACT MY EXPERIENCE?


	- The voice number to the aircraft will not change.
	- GoGo will begin billing directly for their voice service. You should work directly with them for call records and billing disputes.
	- Honeywell Forge will continue to support you with troubleshooting and any other inquiries you have. Connectivity can span multiple components; we remain dedicated to you.


FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS (FAQ)


	- Will my cost for service be the same with both Honeywell Forge and GoGo?
 Cost is under evaluation by GoGo
	- When does this change occur?
 November 30, 2020
	- Do I get to keep my current phone number?
 Yes
	- Do I have my same contact for overall service support? 
 Yes, you will have your same Honeywell Forge support person. We can help you with any connectivity issues for both Honeywell Forge and GoGo service.
	- Will I notice any disruption to my service with Honeywell or GoGo? 
 This is only an administrative change not on-wing. There will be no disruption in your service
	- How will my experience change?
 After November 30, 2020, you will receive an invoice monthly from Honeywell Forge for non-GoGo services if applicable and a separate one from GoGo. GoGo will initiate a new service agreement
	- Will my overall costs be affected? 
 The overall bill from Honeywell Forge will actually be reduced by the amount of the GoGo service charge. Expect a slightly lower bill from Honeywell Forge after November 30, 2020.


Have any other questions? Contact our dedicated support team or call: 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 or email sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;. Our #1 priority is to maintain a best-in-class customer experience for you. 

 Sincerely, 
 Honeywell Forge</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
