<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>August 2018 Edition.August 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - August 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
August 2018
JETWAVE PROVIDESBROADBAND-CLASSDATA CONNECTIVITY
JetWave™ satellite communications terminals enable global consistent connectivity via Inmarsat Aviation’s Global Xpress (GX) Ka-band network. Designed to provide broadband-class data connectivity, the hardware and network are optimized for mobility to provide a consistently outstanding passenger experience all over the world...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/jetwave-high-speed-satellite-communications-hardware]]&gt;
Mark your calendars - NBAA 2018 - Honeywell showcasing its newest services and products 

NBAA 2018 is right around the corner! One of your must-stops is Honeywell Booth 2600. We will be showcasing the Connected Aircraft.
Global Customer Committee to meet again in the fall of 2018Honeywell’s Global Customer Committee regional advisory boards will meet this fall in Vienna, Phoenix and Hong Kong. Each meeting will cover... Read more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_08_CPS_CSM_Emails_RW_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;.
Thank you for recognizing Honeywell&apos;s Customer Support Managers on the AIN Product Support Survey

It&apos;s an honor that you, our customers, recognize the passion and commitment we have in supporting you every day. Link to Above and Beyond: Product Support Survey 2018 &lt;[[https://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/business-aviation/2018-08-01/above-and-beyond-product-support-survey-2018]]&gt;, scroll down to Honeywell.
Honeywell extends maintenance intervals on TFE engines

Honeywell recently announced an extension of TFE731-20/-40/-50/-60 engine intervals to maximize operators’ time on-wing... Learn more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_08_CPS_CSM_Emails_RW_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
