<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global Newsletter.June 5, 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aero Express Global: News from EBACE, HOS Gold, Glendale Silver, commenting debuts, team recognition, IDS and delivery/inventory, X-47B launch, A350 XWB first flight and more...</subject>
    <textOnly> 

 










June 5, 2013
Global Edition















Honeywell makes big impression at European business aviation conference
Honeywell Aerospace’s industry-leading business aviation capabilities were on full display in Geneva May 21-23 at the 2013 European Business Aviation Convention and Exhibition (EBACE), the largest annual gathering for Europe’s business aviation community. Honeywell showcased a wide range of B&amp;GA technologies, products and service offerings at its exhibit on the trade show floor. Customers also could see Honeywell technology on customer aircraft that were on static display in the exhibit hall and on the flight line. EBACE success… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywellmakesitsmarkatEBACE2013,Geneva,Switzerland.aspx&gt;

 





Honeywell looks ahead to Paris Air Show
Le Bourget Airport will be the center of the aviation universe June 17-23 when decision-makers from across the aerospace industry gather for the 50th Paris Air Show &lt;http://www.paris-air-show.com/GB.htm&gt;. Honeywell Aerospace will focus on driving sales of key products, systems and services and elevating awareness of Honeywell’s strong brand, broad product portfolio and technology leadership in the aerospace industry. Honeywell’s theme for the show – “Possibilities. Made Easy.” – underscores the company’s commitment to use human factors principles to improve the end-to-end customer experience. Paris Air Show… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywelllooksaheadtoParisAirShow.aspx&gt;









Going for the Gold: Aero launches HOS Gold pilot
The Honeywell Operating System (HOS) is taking a bold step outside the four walls of the factory as the company launches several pilot programs – including one at Aerospace – to define a new, even higher level of HOS performance. The question: What does it mean to be an HOS Gold-level enterprise? Gold pilot program… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/GoingfortheGoldAerolaunchesHOSGoldpilot.aspx&gt;









Glendale employees gear up to reach HOS Silver milestone
Six years into their Honeywell Operating System (HOS) journey, employees at the Glendale, Ariz., Defense &amp; Space site reached the prestigious HOS Silver milestone on May 6. The site is just the second in the Americas and fifth in all of Aerospace to achieve Silver performance. The Glendale site develops, produces and supports technologies used on a wide range of government and commercial space platforms, including technologies used in human space flight, satellites and unmanned exploratory missions. HOS Silver… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/GlendaleemployeesgearuptoreachHOSSilvermilestone.aspx&gt;









Join in: Aerospace commenting on intranet articles debuts
Ready to make yourself heard? Start with this article. Now employees have another way to join in the dialogue – simply click on the new “Comment” feature included on select stories posted to the Aerospace Intranet. When viewing a news article, employees will see a Comment tab under the headline. By clicking on the tab and writing a comment, employees can share ideas and opinions on the topic or even ask questions. The change comes directly from employee feedback in the Global Communications Survey conducted late last year. Make yourself heard… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/JoininAerospaceCommentingOnIntranetArticlesDebuts.aspx&gt;









2 Aerospace Engineering teams receive Excellence in Innovation Awards
Honeywell’s highest technical honor, the 2013 Excellence in Innovation Award, went to two Aerospace engineering teams during the annual Technology Symposium in Minneapolis last month. James Piascik accepted the award for the Hexavalent Chrome Plating Replacement Team and Thea Feyereisen, pictured, accepted for the SmartView Lower Minimums Team. Excellence in Innovation… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/2013ExcellenceinInnovationAwards.aspx&gt;









ATR Irkut APU Team finds second look pays off
When an opportunity rates a second look, sometimes the payoff can be huge. That’s what the ATR Irkut APU Team discovered on the auxiliary power unit for the Russian United Aircraft Corp. /Irkut MC-21 aircraft, previously awarded to a competitor. Their ability to spot a rare opportunity and diligence to pursue it resulted in a big win for Aerospace and propelled them to finalists for the Honeywell Team Performance Award. Second look… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/ATRIrkutAPUTeamfindssecondlookpaysoff.aspx&gt;









Navigator Award goes to Rocky Mount, N.C. team for new training center
Mike Stahl, Tammy Wolfe, Jeff Stevens and Tim Weeks are recipients of a Navigator Award for their work establishing a training center that’s improving quality and the work culture in Rocky Mount, N.C. As Weeks put it, “well-trained people just perform better in every way.” The Navigator Award honors behavior that helps move Honeywell’s business culture from reactive to proactive. Navigator Award… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/NavigatorAwardgoestoRockyMount,NCteamfornewtrainingcenter.aspx&gt;









Wanda Mayse retiring after 50-year career
On March 11, 1963, Wanda Mayse was hired at Grimes Manufacturing in the small town of Urbana, Ohio. Grimes Manufacturing was the industry leader in aerospace lighting, with products known around the world for their design, quality and reliability. Now part of Honeywell, it proved to be the perfect place for Mayse to enjoy what turned out to be a 50-year career. Five decades on the job… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/WandaMayseretiringafter50-yearcareer.aspx&gt;









Honeywell unit helped Hillary scale Everest
On May 29 the world paused to remember the 60th anniversary of one of the most celebrated accomplishments of the 20th century – the first conquest of Mount Everest by Sir Edmond Hillary and Tenzing Norgay. But did you know that technology developed by past employees at a Honeywell site in England made the historic first ascent of Everest possible? Rarified air… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywellsystemhelpedHillaryscaleEverest.aspx&gt;



 
Three ways to learn how we’re doing on IDS and our delivery/inventory measures
Improving our Integrated Delivery System (IDS) is one of the Aerospace “must-do” priorities because it results in better customer satisfaction and financial performance. Two top measures of our progress are delivery (complete orders delivered on-time-to-request or OTTR) and inventory (days of supply or DOS, which represents the time it takes for inventory to be converted into sales). In a new 15-minute presentation &lt;http://ez.com/OTTRDOSEmployMay2013&gt; you’ll learn more about our delivery/inventory goals and how we measure our progress. Additionally, find out how we’re doing with IDS by listening to a May 28 update hosted by Mark Howes &lt;http://ez.com/IDSUpdate20130528&gt;. Finally, check out the new tracking metric on the Aerospace home page &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Pages/home.aspx&gt; showing our weekly performance. Click on that metric to get more detailed numbers, definitions and the roles each organization can play.


Honeywell Aerospace wins key component on 737 MAX engine
Honeywell&apos;s Air Transport &amp; Regional business was selected as the supplier of a key engine component – ejector valves – for the propulsion engine that will power the new Boeing 737 MAX airplane. The ejector valve optimizes secondary airflow within the engine, thus improving the specific fuel consumption (SFC), that is, the fuel efficiency of the engine. Including aftermarket services for 20 years, the value of the contract is approximately $249 million. Fuel-saving valve… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywellAerospacewinskeycomponenton737MAXengine.aspx&gt;


D&amp;S supports historic unmanned X-47B carrier launch
Defense &amp; Space was a key member of the Northrop Grumman-led X-47B Unmanned Combat Air System (UCAS) team that made naval aviation history on May 14 by successfully catapulting the X-47B demonstrator from the deck of a U.S. Navy aircraft carrier. The story includes a video &lt;http://bcove.me/8tc33vbh&gt; describing Honeywell&apos;s GPS/INS standard navigator (EGI) used on the X-47B. D&amp;S supports first launch… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/DSsupportshistoricunmannedX-47Bcarrierlaunch.aspx&gt;


Preparations for Airbus A350 XWB first flight under way
Airbus has begun preparing for the first flight of the A350 XWB, an all-new long-range wide-body aircraft, which is expected to take to the skies over Toulouse, France, soon. The A350 XWB represents one of the largest development programs in Honeywell Aerospace history. The A350 XWB’s Rolls-Royce Trent XWB engines ran for the first time recently on the MSN1 aircraft following the start-up of Honeywell’s HGT1700 auxiliary power unit (APU), as part of the preparations for the aircraft’s maiden flight. Once the date and time of the first flight have been finalized by Airbus, Honeywell Aerospace employees can watch the A350 XWB first flight online on the Airbus website &lt;http://www.airbus.com/home/&gt; and on the Airbus A350 XWB website &lt;http://www.a350xwb.com/&gt;. Keep watching the Aero intranet home page &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Pages/home.aspx&gt; for more information on this historic event.


Aerospace supports international engineering and science fair
Honeywell recently participated in the Intel International Science and Engineering Fair (ISEF), the world’s largest international precollege science competition, hosted this year in Phoenix. Honeywell Aerospace engineers served as judges for over 1,500 entries from students from all over the world. The students competed for $3 million in scholarships and prizes. To learn more about Honeywell’s involvement, check out this short video &lt;http://bcove.me/8ytzynys&gt;.


More Headlines…


Featured Product and Video: Wheels &amp; Brakes



B&amp;GA May 29 Business Update with Rob Wilson &lt;http://Ez.com/bgaupdate20130529&gt;



Chris Davis wins Chairman’s Award for new accelerometer testing platform that reduces cycle time &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/News/Chairman&gt;



James Minor wins Chairman’s Award by preventing inspection delays for valves used in Army helicopters &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/News/Chairman&gt;










In the News
Aviation Week cover story –

June 3, 2012
Taking synthetic vision to the next level &lt;http://www.aviationweek.com/Article.aspx?id=/article-xml/AW_06_03_2013_p42-582154.xml&gt;


Rotor &amp; Wing cover story –

June 2013
Synthetic vision: Seeing what you should be missing &lt;http://accessintelligence.imirus.com/Mpowered/book/vrw13/i6/p28&gt;


Aviation International News –

June 2, 2013
Synthetic vision with infrared becomes helicopter&apos;s SmartView &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/aviation-international-news/2013-06-02/synthetic-vision-infrared-becomes-helicopters-smartview&gt;




Avionics – June 1, 2013
Touch the future &lt;http://www.aviationtoday.com/av/issue/cover/Touch-the-Future_79253.html#.UaaVUZx9JU6&gt;


Aviation International News – May 28, 2013
Jeppesen app links iPad to Honeywell avionics &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ainalerts/2013-05-28/jeppesen-app-links-ipad-honeywell-avionics&gt;


Arab News –

May 26, 2013
Honeywell technologies drive airport efficiency &lt;http://sg.news.yahoo.com/honeywell-technologies-drive-airport-efficiency-001300626.html&gt;


Avionics Intelligence –

May 22, 2013
Honeywell Aerospace cockpit avionics brings safety features, situational awareness to Pilatus PC-24 &lt;http://www.avionics-intelligence.com/articles/2013/05/Honeywell-cockpit.html&gt;


Aerospace Technology –

May 22, 2013
Honeywell receives EASA and FAA certification for Primus Epic-based EASy II integrated cockpit &lt;http://www.aerospace-technology.com/news/newshoneywell-receives-easa-faa-certification-for-primus-epic-based-easy-ii-integrated-cockpit&gt;


Flightglobal –

May 21, 2013
EBACE: Honeywell predicts return to good times as new programmes come on stream &lt;http://www.flightglobal.com/news/articles/ebace-honeywell-predicts-return-to-good-times-as-new-programmes-come-on-stream-386032/&gt;


Aviation Week –

May 21, 2013
Honeywell eyes next generation midsize jet engines &lt;http://www.aviationweek.com/Article.aspx?id=/article-xml/awx_05_21_2013_p0-580784.xml&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 21, 2013
Honeywell iPad apps optimized for Pilatus PC-12 &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ebace-convention-news/2013-05-21/honeywell-ipad-apps-optimized-pilatus-pc-12&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 20, 2013
Jetex, Honeywell join forces on flight support &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ebace-convention-news/2013-05-20/jetex-honeywell-join-forces-flight-support&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 20, 2013
Amjet Falcon debuts OnAir connectivity services &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ebace-convention-news/2013-05-20/amjet-falcon-debuts-onair-connectivity-services&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 20, 2013
Bombardier launches Challenger 350 &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ebace-convention-news/2013-05-20/bombardier-launches-challenger-350&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 20, 2013
Honeywell exhibiting cabin systems at EBACE &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ebace-convention-news/2013-05-20/honeywell-exhibiting-cabin-systems-ebace&gt;


Aviation International News –

May 20, 2013
Jetex, Honeywell team on bizav flight support services &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/ainalerts/2013-05-20/jetex-honeywell-team-bizav-flight-support-services&gt;








© 2013 Honeywell International Inc.

Aero Express is produced for internal use only and is not for distribution outside the company.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
