<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_03_Americas_JetWaveObjections_BrunswickAviation_KR.201903_Americas_Brunswic</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Big Myth About SATCOM Installation Downtime</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;  &lt;[[https://www.brunswickaviationservices.com/]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Honeywell_Standard_Logo.png]]&gt;

Install Honeywell JetWave™ SATCOM in Half the Time

How long does it take to install the world’s best satellite communications system on your business jet? 

If you guessed 30 days or more, we’ve got some good news for you. In most cases Honeywell channel partners can install the JetWave SATCOM system in about 14 days – reducing your downtime and getting your aircraft back in the air where it belongs.

We know that downtime is a costly proposition for business aircraft operators. You’ve got places to go, passengers to transport and missions to accomplish. That’s why we designed JetWave to make it easier and faster to install. Many customers simply fold in their SATCOM upgrade with a regularly scheduled service interval, to avoid any additional downtime at all. 

That means you’re closer than you thought to the best in-flight Wi-Fi experience in the sky. With JetWave and the Inmarsat Jet ConneX network, your passengers will connect to Wi-Fi that is fast, reliable and available anywhere they fly – even over the ocean. They’ll be able to send emails, surf the web, send and receive large files, and videoconference from the tarmac and at 45,000 feet. 

Ready to upgrade your in-flight wi-fi experience with JetWave. Contact us today to request a quote and see how quickly you can be back in the sky.



LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/JetWave_Brunswick_Aviation.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_brunswick_jw&amp;utm_content=jetwave+objections+emails]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
