<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201908_BK_Webinar_Engine_Monitoring_MC.201909_BK_PostWebinar_Engine_Monitoring_M</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Thank You For Attending Engine Data Webinar on August 27</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt; &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;

 &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;
Thank you for attending our webinar on “Engine Monitoring Tips for Efficiency &amp; Preventative Engine Maintenance” on Aug 27th.
Steve Pearce, Product Marketing Manager for BendixKing, and Jeff Simon, President of SocialFlight, joined forces to introduce our AeroPoint / engine data monitoring product line and provide details on engine monitoring options and tips to maximize your engine’s healthy life all the way to TBO.
In case you missed it, here’s the link to the SocialFlight webinar recording: https://youtu.be/D6gzl9a-4Uc &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D6gzl9a-4Uc&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
As Jeff mentioned during the webinar, there’s an overwhelming combination of settings and variables for these products to fill a multiple-day seminar, and in the time allotted, we were not able to include a Q&amp;A session. As a follow-up, here are the questions that were queued during the presentation:


	- My aircraft has 3 tanks and 6 (fuel) tanks respectively. How is that handled?


	- The AeroPoint units are priced based on tanks and cylinders. When you are looking for quotes please let the dealer know how many tanks your aircraft has, as well as how many cylinders in your engine or engines




	- I have a legacy C182 with BK avionics. My priority is engine analyzer, so what is the difference between BK &amp; JPI?


	- Currently, the BendixKing variants are the same as the JPI units. As we move forward we plan to continue to increase the integration with our AeroVue Touch and other products within the BendixKing line-up




	- Is there a 4, 7 &amp; 9-cylinder version? And do you offer fuel in liters, and pressures in bar for international?


	- We do have 4, 7, and 9 cylinder options in the AeroPoint 200 and 300. These options are TSO’d and STC’d as primary instruments. We can change any of the fuel calculations to liters, but the pressure calculations are displayed in PSI only.




	- Does HP calculation account for altitude? If so, how does this device obtain altitude information?


	- The %HP calculation in done in conjunction with MAP. Your horsepower should be set when the unit is installed, but you can change that value if you make any customizations to your plane. Once the rated horsepower is correct, you calibrate MAP on the ground using field elevation and the current altimeter setting. This will get your %HP value close, but you can fine tune it using your POH.




For more information about our AeroPoint engine data monitoring products, visit these pages:


	- xPoint 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xpoint-100]]&gt;: Designed for experimental aircraft, with a starting cost of $795
	- AeroPoint 200 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-200]]&gt;: TSO’d as primary instrument for single engine aircraft
	- AeroPoint 300 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-200]]&gt;: Designed for twin-engine aircraft, with pre-wired harness


If you have more questions, or need further details, please reach out to Steve Pearce &lt;[[mailto:steven.pearce@bendixking.com]]&gt; or email sales@bendixking.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@bendixking.com]]&gt;. To find your local dealer, visit our Dealer Directory &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/Dealer-Directory/]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
