<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Global_Internal-Comms_Supplier-Survey-Guidelines_Email_Operational.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell is here to help - Act Now</subject>
    <textOnly>March 20, 2020 

 Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Supplier}}, 

 In spite of the challenges we are facing together during the coronavirus (COVID-19) situation, we continue to be inspired and motivated by the resilience of our employees and our supplier partners. The health and safety of our employees, customers, and suppliers are always our top priority. 

 It is our great privilege to be part of an industry that is critical to infrastructure, transportation, security, and defense. As such, we must safeguard our business continuity and maintain support for our customers who need our products now more than ever. As one of our valued suppliers, your partnership is crucial in making this possible. 

 Honeywell is here to help, and we want to understand how your operations are being impacted. This includes, but is not limited to: 

 Business Continuity 



	- Labor resource limitations causing delays in meeting customer demand
	- Challenges with transportation availability that is needed to ship and receive parts
	- Difficulty securing component parts and raw materials
	- Financial stress


Please complete this short assessment &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DQLTP7L]]&gt; within the next 48 hours. This critical information will enable us to jointly identify and develop solutions for any immediate or long-term challenges you may be experiencing. 

 Government Relations
 Our commercial and defense aerospace products and services are critical to overall transportation and safety infrastructure and essential to national security as part of “Critical Infrastructure” outlined in Presidential Directive 21 &lt;[[https://www.cisa.gov/critical-infrastructure-sectors]]&gt;. The official guidance from the Department of Homeland Security’s Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency, entitled, “Guidance on the Essential Critical Infrastructure Workforce: Ensuring Community and National Resilience in 
COVID-19 Response” &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/DHS Letter.pdf]]&gt; explicitly states, “critical infrastructure industries have a special responsibility in these times to continue operations.” 

 This guidance includes details on what the federal government defines as Critical Infrastructure, which includes the defense and commercial aerospace sector. “Essential critical infrastructure workers” are identified as: 



	- Employees supporting or enabling transportation functions
	- Maintenance and repair technicians
	- Equipment and infrastructure that enables operations that encompass movement of cargo and passengers
	- Workers necessary for the manufacturing of materials and products needed for transportation and the defense industrial base
	- Workers who support the essential services required to meet national security commitments to the federal government and the U.S. Military. These individuals include, but are not limited to, aerospace, mechanical and software engineers, manufacturing/production workers
	- Personnel working for companies, and their subcontractors, who perform under contract to the Department of Defense providing materials and services to the Department of Defense


Additionally, for suppliers providing products or services supporting the federal government and the United States military, the Department of Defense issued additional guidance &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Defense Industrial Base Essential Critical Infrastructure Workforce.pdf]]&gt; clearly 
stating, “[i]f your contract or subcontract supports the development, production, testing, fielding, or sustainment of [Department of Defense] weapon systems/software systems, or the infrastructure to support those activities…” the Department of Defense expects that you remain open and maintain normal work schedules. 

Honeywell is successfully working with federal, state, and local governmental authorities to remind them of the critical nature of the work we do. This collaboration helps ensure that our sites and our suppliers’ sites remain operational. You are a part of this critical infrastructure supply chain. Please contact us right away if any governmental authority (federal, state, or local) has told you, or tells you in the future, that you need to suspend operations. We are ready to assist.

 Who Do You Contact?
Honeywell representatives are working relentlessly to contact suppliers, helping to ensure we keep factories open, workers safe, and parts moving to our customers. Please do not wait for a Honeywell representative to call you—call your local Honeywell contact or send an email to AeroSupplierCommunications@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroSupplierCommunications@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. 

 We are all in this together. Again, thank you for all you do. 

 Sincerely, 

 Bob Buddecke
Chief Procurement Officer 
Honeywell Aerospace Integrated Supply Chain</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
