<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>SurveyFeedback_Sept2017.SurveyFeedback_Sept2017</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your technical support case feedback matters</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer, 
Our Honeywell Aerospace technical support team is always looking for faster and better ways to ensure you can stay flying.  
 
To understand how we’re meeting your expectations, after you confirm your case is closed (by selecting “yes” in our case closure email), you will immediately see a survey asking you to answer four questions about your technical support experience.   
 
It’s simple, but there are a few points we like to highlight: 


	- Our goal is to make sure you’re satisfied - a 9 and 10 means we’ve accomplished that goal. 
	- We strive to solve your issue the first time you contact us. We hope you can choose yes, that we did, but if not, please tell us why. 


We review the survey results, contact anyone with a poor experience, and use the feedback to make short and long-term improvements. For example, within the last six months, we have:


	- Improved our knowledge sharing &lt;[[https://honeywellaerocommunities.force.com/SSCommunity/TSSCommunityCases]]&gt; – both within our teams and with you.
	- Made it easier to transfer your calls and inquiries to other teams that can help, reducing your effort.
	- Enhanced MyAerospace Portal technical search &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; functionality to find more relevant information faster.




Again, thank you for giving us feedback so we can drive the right improvements.


Please visit our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical publications, or to submit questions to our technical support engineering team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
