<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_CPS_Eclair-cut-over_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace News About Support of the ALF502/LF507 Turbofan Engines</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 As Honeywell recently advised, we have decided to optimize our operations and sell the ownership of our ALF502/LF507 Turbofan Engine to CFS Aeroproducts Ltd., herein referred as CFS Aero. CFS Aero is committed to servicing the ALF502 / LF507 engine models and has established strong relationships with the Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEM) and operators. CFS Aero is an established part 145 certified repair center for the ALF502/LF507. They are uniquely qualified to address your support needs. 

 Honeywell Inventory Transfer to CFS Aero



	- The transfer of Honeywell inventory to CFS Aero is currently in process.
	- This bulk of this inventory transfer was completed March 31, 2020.
	- This Honeywell inventory, coupled with the existing CFS Aero inventory, makes CFS Aero uniquely equipped to immediately support your spares and repairs needs for the AL502/LF507 Turbofan Engine.


Effective Date to order Spares or Repairs from CFS Aero



	- Effective immediately, all new spares and repair orders should be sent to CFS Aero. 


	- Honeywell will no longer accept orders for new spare orders or repairs for ALF502/LF507 hardware.




Impacted Part Numbers



	- View ALF502/LF507 Part Number List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/ALF502 LF507 list of impacted PNs.xlsx]]&gt;


Establish CFS Aero on your Approved Supplier List



	- Customers are urged to quickly establish CFS Aero on their approved supplier list (ASL) for these part numbers.


	- This will allow you to seamlessly interact with CFS Aero relative to new and repair orders.
Information for Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
                Name:                                                CFS Aeroproducts Ltd. 
                Address:                                            Harris Road
                City, State:                                         Warwick, Warwickshire
                Postal Code:                                      CV34 5FY
                Country:                                             United Kingdom
                Registration Number:                         07899604
Contact List:






Area 



Email Address


Name


Phone




Quotes &amp; Orders:  
 Spare or Repair

sales@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@cfsaero.com]]&gt;

Rob Fitch


+44(0)2476 305 873



Order Status
stores@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:stores@cfsaero.com]]&gt;
Mike Standfield
+44(0)2476 305 873


General
admin@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:admin@cfsaero.com]]&gt;
n/a
+44(0)2476 305 873


Escalations
turbines@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:turbines@cfsaero.com]]&gt;
n/a
+44(0)2476 305 873


AOG
aog@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:aog@cfsaero.com]]&gt;
n/a
+44(0)2476 305 873


Technical Questions 
and Documents
turbines@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:turbines@cfsaero.com]]&gt;
Rob Fitch
+44(0)2476 305 873
Order Processing 
 To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions: 

 REPAIR UNITS 

 Existing Repair Orders 
 

 	- Honeywell will notify customers regarding which parts will be repaired and which will be sent to CFS Aero for repair. 	- If the repair will be sent to CFS Aero, you will be contacted about transferring the repair/order to CFS Aero and a Purchase order/contract change requirements. 	- Your Honeywell Customer Business Manager or the Customer Support Manager will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity. 

 New Repair Orders 
 

 	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that all new repair orders are sent directly to CFS Aero. See contact details listed above. 	- Honeywell will no longer accept or process new repair orders. Any repair hardware shipped to Honeywell will be returned to the customer. 

 SPARE ORDERS 

 Existing Spares Orders:
 

 	- In case of stock unavailability, the Honeywell Customer Business Manager will contact you to cancel the order and ask that you place the order directly with CFS Aero. 

 New Spares Orders: 
 

 	- To minimize delays to your order requirements, ensure that new spares orders are sent to CFS Aero at the address provided above. 

 
 Technical Documents &amp; Questions
 Contact CFS Aero with any technical inquiries. 

 If you have any questions, please contact Rob Fitch at turbines@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:turbines@cfsaero.com]]&gt;. 

 Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace 
 Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
