<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202009_Portal_Release_Update_September_Newly-Upgraded-Technical-Support.202009_P</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Portal Update - Newly Upgraded Technical Support and Technical Solutions</subject>
    <textOnly>Support Navigation Update
 Honeywell has cleaned up the Customer Support navigation on aerospace.honeywell.com - instead of multiple links to various services, we have created a simple and logical menu under Technical Support. One example of this is Technical Publications which is now a sub-menu to Technical Support. Additionally, users can access useful information under Technical Support such as: searchable technical solutions articles giving tips and tricks from our Field Service Engineers and updates to critical reliability programs. 

 Contact Us – Revamp for Request Support
 The Contact Us page has been fully revamped for accessing forms and easily navigating through the different support options. To access our Contact Us page, please click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;.

 Technical Support &amp; Technical Solutions – New Upgraded Experience
 The Technical Support and Technical Solutions (previously known as the Technical Knowledge Center) pages have been fully upgraded 
to provide easier searchability and usability. Below are the changes that have been made. To view the release note for this update, please click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes/2020/technical-support-solutions-upgraded]]&gt;. 

	- All MyAerospace users will automatically have access to Technical Solutions.
	- Browse By – Users will be able to browse Technical Solutions by the following:


	- Aircraft
	- Product
	- ATA Chapter


	- Popular Technical Solutions – Users will be able to see a highlight of the top 8 most popular technical solutions articles.
	- Technical Solutions Search Results – Robust, dynamic filtering capability for easier and exact search. Detailed information on each result card, so users do not need to click through an article to see high-level detail.
	- Helpful Feedback – Users will be able to provide feedback on how helpful the technical solution article was.
	- Download as PDF – There is an option to download a technical solution article as a PDF.


Order Status 


	- View # of days on hold for customer quote approval - In the order details page, customers will be able to see how many days their order has been on hold due to Customer Quote Approval.
	- Repair orders notification number - Customers will be able to view the notification # for their repair orders until the sales order # is created within the order details download.


To view the individual release notes for the items listed above and to catch up on latest improvements to MyAerospace, please refer to and bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
