<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201908_BK_Webinar_Engine_Monitoring_MC.201908_BK_Webinar_Engine_Monitoring_MC.20</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Engine Monitoring Tips and Efficiency and Preventative Maintenance Webinar Aug 27</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

 &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;WEBINAREngine Monitoring Tips for Efficiency and Preventive Maintenance Webinar

 &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;
Date: Tuesday, August 27th, 8 p.m. EDT
Getting the most from your engine monitor requires proper installation, tuning and interpretation of the data. Learn tips and tricks about cylinder temp management, Lean of Peak (LOP) operations, data customization, calibration and fuel management in this informative webinar. Becoming an educated owner of a digital engine monitor can transform the precision and efficiency of your aircraft operation.
Join BendixKing Product Marketing Manager and avid pilot, Steven Pearce, along with SocialFlight President, Jeff Simon, an A&amp;P/IA mechanic, as they discuss how engine monitoring can be a key diagnostic tool to help spot trends and issues before they escalate to safety of flight issues.
Topics Include:


	- Review of the BendixKing line of Engine Monitors
	- Installation considerations
	- Customization and Tips
	- Operational overview
	- Data Analysis


Produced in association with SocialFlight.com &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/search.php]]&gt;, your webinar registration includes FREE access to information on over 10,000 aviation events, destinations, airport restaurants, contests and more listed on SocialFlight.com, the SocialFlight mobile apps and Local Aviation Event Planner.




REGISTER HERE  &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/2019996775141709324]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
