<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201904_TechTips_CPCVideo_lg.201904_TechTips_CPCVideo_Mail</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Easily Troubleshoot your Cabin Pressure Controller</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
TECH TIPS | CABIN PRESSURE CONTROLLER TROUBLESHOOTING
Dear Customer,
Have you experienced a cabin pressure controller (CPC) issue on your Boeing 757 or 767? Boeing and Honeywell have released a helpful video &lt;https://youtu.be/lzxcW5FuQUc&gt; and supporting documentation to help you troubleshoot your CPC system.
Engine indicating and crew alerting system messages do not always contain sufficient information to diagnose a CPC system from the flight deck. As a result, we have observed an abnormally high no-fault-found rate on the CPCs returned to our service centers for repair, causing unnecessary cost to the owner, operator and customer. This trend indicates that additional in-depth on-wing troubleshooting is necessary to keep the CPCs installed on the aircraft while determining the correct root cause.
Our video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/lzxcW5FuQUc]]&gt; helps demonstrate these best practices for on-wing CPC troubleshooting.
Please also refer to the MyBoeingFleet website &lt;[[https://www.myboeingfleet.com/ReverseProxy/Authentication.html]]&gt; for the latest aircraft maintenance manual and the fault isolation manual for the 757 and 767 aircraft. The &quot;757 and 767 Cabin Pressure Controller Troubleshooting&quot; video can be found under the Supplemental Videos section.
Need other technical support? Visit our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical publications, or to submit questions to our technical support engineering team.





 VISIT MYAEROSPACE &lt;http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
