<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_02_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Kirchhofer_2019_02</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Honeywell continues to expand its connection points to make it easier for you to assess and solve technical issues. We are building a library of technical video and webinars, as well as live webinars hosted by our Technical Sales team. If you haven&apos;t downloaded the Direct Access app, please do, we think you&apos;ll find useful. And I am always available, so don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance.  -- Lee
Did You Know?

Avionics mysteries energize long-time field service engineer

Field Service 
Engineer John Braidich has always loved a good mystery. When a Honeywell customer reaches out, Braidich digs in like a seasoned detective to assess the situation, gather evidence, analyze the problem and find the right solution as quickly as possible... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/february/avionics-mysteries-energize-long-time-field-service-engineer]]&gt;.

Technical solutions at your fingertipsMyAerospace hosts thousands of articles to help you solve technical 
issues &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt;.  For example, if you’re troubleshooting an APU compressor seal leak, find out what we recommend.  Log in to the MyAerospace 
Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Ftechnical-knowledge-center]]&gt;, then click here &lt;[[https://honeywellaerocommunities.force.com/SSCommunity/TSSCommunityDetails?id=ka61B000000kAu6]]&gt; or search for article number 6594.  
2019 
Operators Conferences season revving up!
Honeywell held 57 operator’s conferences during 2018 and our staff personally visited nearly 21,000 customers, and we have even more ambitious goals set for 2019. We are planning 86 customer events worldwide, and we are committed to be available 24/7/365 to resolve issues on first contact. Our customer support managers and field service engineers are already out traveling to support you and strengthening our network. Please attend one of the industry events this year and learn about our cutting-edge solutions to make your aircraft the safer, better, and more advanced than the rest. Honeywell&apos;s Operators Conference Spring season schedule is jam-packed with 22 events through May 25. There&apos;s probably one in your area so check out the calendar and register! &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt;
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Lee Kirchhofer Customer Service Manager Phone: 724-253-2059 Mobile: 602-363-7796 Email: Lee.Kirchhofer@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Lee.Kirchhofer@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
