<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Global Newsletter.April 3, 2013</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aero Express Global - Video answers your questions, survey feedback, IDS podcast, Human Factors, Rocky Mount Learning Center, How Aero Works and more...</subject>
    <textOnly> 

 










April 3, 2013












 &lt;http://bcove.me/g1p807nt&gt;



Aerospace Perspectives: Your questions answered
All employees are encouraged to get the facts on Aerospace topics ranging from the economic environment, customer feedback, IDS performance and Human Factors. That information and more answers to employee questions are included in the latest “Aerospace Perspectives” video, featuring Aerospace President and CEO Tim Mahoney and Adrian Paull, Vice President of Customer &amp; Product Support. Watch the 28-minute full video &lt;http://bcove.me/g1p807nt&gt;, or click on individual segments: Merit; Goal planning, Working more efficiently, Organizational effectiveness &lt;http://bcove.me/29nuol5n&gt;; Velocity Product Development &lt;http://bcove.me/psu6nftl&gt;; Integrated Delivery System (IDS) &lt;http://bcove.me/gyrzgxjs&gt;; Economic impacts to our business &lt;http://bcove.me/3agueis8&gt;; Customer feedback, Embraer win, Human Factors &lt;http://bcove.me/8ip00i6i&gt;; and Obsolescence Management, Product Development &lt;http://bcove.me/s0ylz41v&gt;.

 





Employee survey feedback spurs communication enhancements
Based on more than 8,000 responses to a Global Communications Survey, some changes are coming to enhance the way Aerospace employees receive and share information. “We heard from employees around the world about their preferences on how they like to hear information, where they like to receive it, and who they want to get it from,” said Bill Kircos, Aerospace Vice President of Communications. “We’re acting on this very useful feedback to continually develop the most effective ways to keep our employees informed and engaged.” Survey results… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/AerospaceEmployeeCommunicationsSurveyResults.aspx&gt;









Learn how IDS helps C&amp;PS improve order management
A new podcast shares how Customer &amp; Product Support put the Integrated Delivery System (IDS) to work on its order management policies and processes. Sandra Rogers, C&amp;PS Vice President of Customer Support Operations, joins Marks Howes, IDS Vice President, to discuss the improvements. Listen to this podcast &lt;http://Ez.com/IDSPodcast24Apr2013&gt; to learn more.









April 19 Global Town Meeting: Human Factors and Q1 Performance
Chairman and CEO Dave Cote will host a companywide Global Town Meeting on Friday, April 19, at 11 a.m. Eastern Daylight Time. Topics include Q1 financial results and ongoing performance on the Five Initiatives. Bob Smith, Chief Technology Officer for Honeywell Aerospace, will discuss Human Factors (HF) and how it fits within the Honeywell Operating Model. Smith will cover what it takes to extend HF systematically and comprehensively across the company, and how it is shaping the end-to-end customer experience. Read more… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/News/InsideNews/Pages/13_0328_1QTH.aspx&gt;









Learning helps drive Rocky Mount quality improvements
Rocky Mount employees have lots of good reasons to be proud of their training center. It’s a space where new team members learn the critical skills needed to assemble, test and repair fuel controls, actuators and other parts used in aircraft engines and auxiliary power units. It’s also a place where employees can brush up on their skills. Most importantly, it’s a symbol of how the Honeywell Operating System helps the North Carolina site focus on quality, productivity and people to drive organizational success and customer satisfaction. Training center… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/LearninghelpsdriveRockyMount,NC,qualityimprovements.aspx&gt;









‘How Aero Works’ podcast targets product cost
How does product cost impact Aerospace’s financial performance? That’s the focus of the latest “How Aerospace works” podcast &lt;http://ez.com/HAWPodcast04Mar2013&gt; featuring Jim Fusaro, Vice President of Mechanical Subsystems for Marketing &amp; Product Management. Listen to learn about our approaches to cost management and how we’re reducing costs through Product Action Committees (PACs).









Honeywell sees bright future for used aerospace equipment
With aircraft operators in all segments of the market increasing their use of pre-owned equipment to assist in reducing costs, Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) is well-positioned to take advantage of the trend. From its headquarters in Rolle, Switzerland, HAT buys and sells high-quality, pre-owned Honeywell products from customers and aircraft dismantlers around the world. HAT solution… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/Honeywellseesbrightfutureforusedaerospaceequipment.aspx&gt;









Honeywell Leadership Challenge Academy offers ‘out-of-this-world’ experience
When the Honeywell Leadership Challenge Academy got under way recently in Huntsville, Ala., 227 children of employees from around the world attended at the U.S. Space and Rocket Center. The unique program uses science-oriented workshops and team exercises to teach leadership skills in science, technology, engineering and math (STEM). Applications for the 2014 program will be available online in September. Leadership challenge… &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/sites/aero/Aerospace%20News/Pages/HoneywellLeadershipChallengeAcademyoffers%E2%80%98out-of-this-world%E2%80%99experience.aspx&gt;



 
More Headlines…


Featured Product and Video: Miniature Inertial Measurement Unit



Paul DeRego earns Chairman’s Award for designing innovative prototype for U.S. government &lt;http://in.honeywell.com/News/Chairman&gt;



E&amp;T March 28 Town Hall with Bob Smith &lt;http://ez.com/AEROETTH20130328&gt;










In the News
The Star Online –

April 1, 2013
MRO sector ready for driver’s role, expected to spearhead aerospace industry with 10% revenue growth &lt;http://biz.thestar.com.my/news/story.asp?file=/2013/4/1/business/12907612&amp;sec=business&gt;


Aviation International News –

March 29, 2013
Companies demonstrate small UAS for DHS program &lt;http://www.ainonline.com/aviation-news/2013-03-29/companies-demonstrate-small-uas-dhs-program&gt;


Rotor &amp; Wing –

March 28, 2013
Sizeable fleet orders, new engines front and center at Heli-Expo &lt;http://www.aviationtoday.com/rw/topstories/Sizeable-Fleet-Orders-New-Engines-Front-and-Center-at-Heli-Expo_78777.html&gt;


Rotor &amp; Wing –

March 26, 2013
Integrated safety systems keep helicopters out of the evening news &lt;http://www.aviationtoday.com/rw/products/avinst/78793.html#.UVHklr3n_4i&gt;


Air Transport World –

March 26, 2013
Airbus installs Rolls-Royce Trent engines on A350 XWB &lt;http://atwonline.com/engines/airbus-installs-rolls-royce-trent-engines-a350-xwb?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+AtwDailyNews+%28ATW+Daily+News%29&gt;


Aviation Week –

March 25, 2013
Cockpit guidance gets down to the ground &lt;http://www.aviationweek.com/Article.aspx?id=/article-xml/AW_03_25_2013_p37-560969.xml&gt;


Lansing State Journal –

March 22, 2013
Eaton Rapids teen attends space camp &lt;http://www.lansingstatejournal.com/article/20130324/EATONRAPIDS02/303240018/Eaton-Rapids-teen-attends-space-camp&gt;


Avionics –

March 19, 2013
Honeywell completes GX Aviation preliminary design review &lt;http://www.aviationtoday.com/av/topstories/Honeywell-Completes-GX-Aviation-Preliminary-Design-Review_78759.html#.UUni4r3n-Uk&gt;


Aerospace Technology –

March 18, 2013
Pratt &amp; Whitney to provide AeroPower&apos;s APU for Embraer E-Jets &lt;http://www.aerospace-technology.com/news/newspratt-whitney-provide-aeropowers-apu-embraer-e-jets&gt;


Aviation International News –

March 18, 2013
AIN Blog: ‘NextGen now,’ but maybe not forever &lt;http://ainonline.com/aviation-news/blogs/ain-blog-nextgen-now-maybe-not-forever?utm_source=twitterfeed&amp;utm_medium=twitter&gt;








© 2013 Honeywell International Inc.

Aero Express is produced for internal use only and is not for distribution outside the company.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
