<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Portal_Release_Update_October_Email_MC.202010_Portal_Release_Update_Octob</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Portal Updates – October 2020</subject>
    <textOnly>GoDirect Trade Integration Updated Feature – Customers can access Honeywell’s extensive used serviceable material and now be able to see the following within Online Ordering directly before being navigated to GoDirect Trade to complete their purchase:


	- Price
	- Part Number
	- Serial Number
	- Quantity
	- Estimated Ship Date
	- Availability
	- Condition


Warranty Self Service - A new tool for MyAerospace users to check their warranty coverage for parts by entering the Part Number, Serial Number and Malfunction Date. Please click HERE &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/z0002Gq0000IZPMWQ090X00]]&gt; to access our Warranty Self Service tool.

 Online Ordering


	- Customers can update their contract selection after an item is added to the cart.
	- Customers will now be able to add “Aircraft Information” in “Edit Cart” for non-serialized parts.


MSP Quoting Tool Enhancements


	- Customers will be able clear out all quantities in the configuration screen – where all prepopulated quantities will return to &quot;0.&quot;


Direct Access – Direct Access has moved to a new mobile-friendly webpage HERE &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/ZIZ000WPG0000000v20qXQM]]&gt;. Please use this new page moving forward for all your Direct Access needs. The iOS and Android apps will be decommissioned by the end of this year. 
 
To view the individual release notes for the items listed above and to catch up on latest improvements to MyAerospace, please refer to and bookmark our Release Notes page:
RELEASE NOTES &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;
For training topics pages related to the portal, please refer to and bookmark this page:
TRAINING TOPICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;
Please be sure to Opt-IN to receive important portal enhancement update emails.
OPT-IN &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/subscription-page]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
