<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>BAN 2015.April - Channel Partner.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Business Aviation Newsletter: April 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>Business Aviation Newsletter: April 2015
Avionics Mandates Offer Safety, Efficiency and Continued Business for Partners  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/avionics-mandates-offer-safety%2C-efficiency-and-continued-business-for-partners&gt;


Government-mandated avionics upgrades &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/mandates&gt; are a fact of aviation life as pressures to increase efficiency in crowded airspace and lower fuel expenses are called for by operators in all segments of the aviation industry.





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/avionics-mandates-offer-safety%2C-efficiency-and-continued-business-for-partners&gt;























 Honeywell Rotable Services Give Customers Star Treatment  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/honeywell-rotable-services-give-customers-star-treatment&gt;


He advocates living on island time, but when it’s time to hit the road and play those songs you know by heart, Jimmy Buffett needs to stay on schedule. That’s why the music icon and aviation enthusiast turned to Honeywell Aerospace...





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/honeywell-rotable-services-give-customers-star-treatment&gt;























 Satcom Router Offers Higher Speeds and 4G LTE Growth  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/satcom-router-offers-higher-speeds-and-4g-lte-growth&gt;


A new aircraft router from Honeywell offers higher Wi-Fi speed potential and growth to 4G LTE on-ground capability, among other benefits to both passengers and crew. The CNX-250 Cabin Gateway is a multi-port network router...





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/satcom-router-offers-higher-speeds-and-4g-lte-growth&gt;























 Ovation Select to Offer Personal HD Moving Map for Individual Passenger Tablets  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/ovation-select-to-offer-personal-hd-moving-map-for-individual-passenger-tablets&gt;


Honeywell&apos;s Ovation Select® is a state-of-the-art cabin management system giving business jet passengers unprecedented business productivity and connectivity and allowing control of in-flight entertainment and environmental conditions...





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/ovation-select-to-offer-personal-hd-moving-map-for-individual-passenger-tablets&gt;























 The European Business Aviation Convention &amp; Exhibition (EBACE) &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/destination-ebace&gt;


EBACE is the premier event and annual meeting place for the European business aviation community. The exhibition brings together business leaders, government officials, manufacturers, suppliers, operators, owners, handlers...





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/destination-ebace&gt;























 You&apos;re Invited - Honeywell&apos;s Business Aviation Operator Conferences  &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/operator-conferences&gt;


Join Honeywell&apos;s Customer Support Managers as they host business aviation operators conferences in 40 locations around the world this year. These conferences are designed to provide maintenance personnel...





Continue Reading &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/news/operator-conferences&gt;












Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
