<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_Americas_SpiritAero_PrimusElite_MC.201906_Americas_Email2_SpiritAero-DU87</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See Why This NASCAR Champ Chose Primus Elite!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Why NASCAR Champion Brad Keselowski Chose DU-875 LCD Displays
The Honeywell DU-875/885 display upgrade replaces those old cathode ray tubes with modern LCDs, removing obsolescence and updating the cockpit with the latest technology. For two-time NASCAR Champion, Brad Keselowski, having the latest and greatest equipment that is maintained for safety is a top priority.
&quot;I chose to upgrade to new DU-875 displays because of the financial and operational benefits. My plane is essential for helping me manage my racing schedule and my business needs. I have a tight travel window each week and the plane allows me to arrive at the track on time, to travel to sponsor commitments, and most importantly - get quickly home for family time following the race.&quot; 
Brad Keselowski, NASCAR Champion




















&quot;My copilot and I have really clear and well-defined images on the new DU-875 LCDs. And with the PEEF (Primus Elite Enhanced Features) upgrade, we get our charts, georeferenced taxiways, and XM Weather.&quot;
Joey Meier, Pilot for Brad Keselowski




Ready to experience the DU-875/885 display units and Primus Elite for yourself? Contact Spirit Aeronautics today at 614-333-8540 &lt;tel:614-333-8540&gt; or online by clicking below and filling out the form.




CONTACT SPIRIT AERONAUTICS &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/three-options-for-upgrading-to-primus-elite?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_spiritaero_pe&amp;utm_content=customer+form+fill]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
