<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201904_EMEAI_MSP_Helicopters_MC.201904_EMEAI_Email_MSP_Helicopters_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Valued Customer,

We are excited to bring you news of our latest changes and recently added solutions to our family of aftermarket maintenance service plans. Honeywell’s Maintenance Service Plan umbrella of offerings will include the current Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), and Helicopter Support Plan (HSP) Programs. All service programs will now be identified by, and located under, this overarching Maintenance Service Plan umbrella.
As an existing HAPP/HSP customer you can rest assured that everything you know and love about them will remain the same. Same great program, same great features, same great value, just under a new name.
Maintenance Service Plan is a maintenance solution that makes it easy for you to choose from a range of selectable coverage options, tailored to your platform and operations.
Under the new Maintenance Service Plan umbrella, selectable options include:



New Name
Old Name   


Maintenance Service Plan – Avionics
HAPP – Honeywell Avionics Protection Program            


Maintenance Service Plan – Engines
HSP – Helicopter Support Plan           



Our new Maintenance Service Plan structure enables you to easily and quickly add additional services to your coverage, from the options outlined above. We believe our Maintenance Service Plan will continue to add real value to your helicopter resale value and operations – reducing the maintenance burden and ensuring your helicopter is where it belongs – up in the sky.
There are no immediate changes to your existing contract or overall service. Starting on April 3rd, 2019 and extending over the course of the next few months, you will see changes to our websites, sales brochures and other program documentation reflecting the new name and program structure.
To find out more about Maintenance Service Plan and how you can benefit beyond your current coverage, please click the link below or contact your local Honeywell representative.
If only everything in life was as easy as Maintenance Service Plan from Honeywell!



LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/maintenance-service-plan-helicopters]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
