<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201707_Global_Email_Aspire200_Helo_mih.201707_Global_Email_Aspire200_Helo_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>CONNECT NOW! Honeywell Brings Broadband to Helicopters</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Honeywell: Your One-Stop Connectivity Shop

Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},


Honeywell is the trusted name and one-stop shop for your connectivity needs. From hardware to services, airtime to apps, solutions to support, Honeywell is networking the skies, bringing high-speed, reliable, secure connectivity to operators worldwide.

Now, Honeywell and our channel partner network are making your upgrade experience even easier. For a limited time and quantities, Honeywell is offering operators a 25 percent discount on its Aspire 200 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/aspire-200]]&gt; Satellite Communications hardware package when combined with our GoDirect Cabin Connectivity &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/service-listing/cabin-connectivity]]&gt; services*. This combination means no more Wi-Fi dead zones, dropped calls or excessive buffering! You stay connected, you accomplish your missions, and you realize added benefits wherever you fly.

As helicopter operators globally get connected – like the adventurers Bob and Steve Dengler &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/c150go/?ref=br_rs]]&gt; who are completing a &quot;connected&quot; circumnavigation in their Honeywell-equipped Bell 429 – they are experiencing sustained communications, data speeds and throughput previously not available in helicopters.

Contact us &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Aspire200_Helicopters.html]]&gt; now as this deal won’t last! And be on the lookout for information about Connected Helicopter demos in your region!







READY TO GET CONNECTED? &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Aspire200_Helicopters.html]]&gt;







(*Must purchase equipment through an authorized dealer and take delivery in 2017; pricing does not apply to nor include the cost of any Supplement Type Certification, kit, or labor associated with the installation; Must, at the time of equipment purchase, also sign up via subscription direct with Honeywell for its GoDirect Cabin Connectivity Services’ L-Band SwiftBroadband Class 6 or 7 Background IP Plan and High Data Rate Streaming.)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
