<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Americas_GDT_Sell-More_8_Month_Free_Subscription_Email.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Free seller subscription just got a boost.</subject>
    <textOnly>It is time. 

 Over the past three weeks, GoDirect Trade has seen record levels of activity come through our marketplace. From search activity to online ordering, we’ve seen huge spikes of activity. Our customers are #1 and we want to ensure that the right inventory is available on our marketplace. 

 To get more parts listed, for a limited only, we are offering an incredible promotion to our sellers. Using promo code SELLERSUMMER, Sellers will receive a FREE 8-month seller subscription which comes with unlimited listings and unlimited transactions. We have never offered sellers this promotion before!

 GoDirect Trade takes the hassle out of selling and makes it simple and easy to start selling online:


	- Click on Launch A Storefront below, input promo code SELLERSUMMER.
	- Next, you will be guided to complete three easy steps (~5 minutes to complete). Your free 8-month subscription does not require a credit card.
	- Watch your customer base grow and the orders come in.


GoDirect Trade is the aerospace marketplace of the future. It has been featured on Forbes &lt;[[https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2020/01/29/honeywell-demonstrates-that-its-an-iiot-not-just-an-ot-company/#3e7c44d768e9]]&gt;, The Wall Street Journal &lt;[[https://www.wsj.com/articles/honeywell-brings-blockchain-to-used-aircraft-parts-market-11559072819]]&gt; and Harvard Business Review &lt;[[https://www.tcs.com/content/dam/tcs/pdf/Industries/manufacturing/abstract/HBR-TCS-WP-Nov-2019.pdf]]&gt; and is rapidly moving from “small startup” to “major disruptor”.

 Zero upfront costs to start selling online today.
LAUNCH A STOREFRONT &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?param=launch_promotion]]&gt;
Stay healthy, stay safe, and take care, 

 Lisa Butters
General Manager
GoDirectTrade.com &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=User_Growth]]&gt; (powered by Honeywell)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
