<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201908_BK_Email_AeroVueTouch_MC.Whole Emails Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AeroVue Touch integrated flight display now certified and STCd</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
Joe Coraggio &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2019/july/upgraded-flight-panel-gives-race-pilot-an-edge]]&gt;, professional pilot, builder, mentor and air race pilot, has the AeroVue/xVue Touch flight display and entire BendixKing product suite installed in his Lancair Legacy, which won 
1st place in the 2019 AirVenture Cup Race. His winning panel and crew are now on their way to the Reno Air Races!

 Joe may race an experimental aircraft, but now certified aircraft owners/operators have the choice to upgrade to the same lightweight, cutting edge flight deck technology as his, with the FAA certified AeroVue Touch.



	- Critical functions reached in two touches or less
	- Includes synthetic vision, ADS-B In, weather, traffic, terrain, charts, engine data monitoring
	- Wi-Fi and USB-C port
	- One of the three highly anticipated cockpit upgrades announced &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/news-listing/2019/july/bendixking-receives-certification-for-three-highly-anticipated-cockpit-upgrades]]&gt; at Oshkosh 2019


 Since the installation of Coraggio’s new panel centered around AeroVue/xVue Touch, Joe’s aircraft is now 40 pounds lighter, without cooling fans and excess noise/heat.

The AeroVue Touch integrated flight display was recently chosen as part of a new cockpit upgrade program &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/news-listing/2019/july/bendixking-offers-new-cockpit-upgrades-for-over-6-000-cessna-aircraft]]&gt; for 6,000 Cessna single-engine piston aircraft.

Pipistrel &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/news-listing/2019/july/bendixking-and-pipistrel-to-enhance-pilot-training-with-a-touchscreen-integrated-flight-deck?utm_source=social&amp;utm_medium=facebook&amp;utm_campaign=19_bendixking_xvuetouch]]&gt; announced the entire BendixKing Aero/xVue Touch Integrated Flight Deck will be installed in their 
Alpha King training aircraft.

  Click to find your dealer and upgrade to your AeroVue Touch flight display!





I’M INTERESTED &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AeroVue_Touch_A.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
