<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20181_UseMyAerospace_LG.20181_UseMyAerospace_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Are you Benefiting from the MyAerospace Portal Yet?</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Honeywell Customer,



Honeywell has made significant improvements to our MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; - your single site to place and track your parts and repair orders. 
 
Our MyAerospace Online Ordering tool allows you to place your repair order with Honeywell prior to sending us your part. Completing your repair order using Online Ordering gives you many 
advantages:


	- Know exactly which Honeywell location to send your part to for repair to prevent shipment delays
	- Document the correct repair price for your repair purchase order to prevent receipt delays
	- Receive your order with 100% accuracy since your order is created in our system directly from your inputs


Using MyAerospace will result in your part completing the repair cycle with minimal interruptions since your electronic repair order will be created in our system before your part arrives. Once the part arrives, we can start your repair without disruption. And, MyAerospace gives you immediate confirmation that your order has been placed and allows you to track its progress from any computer, tablet or smartphone.
 
As we communicated last month, we are now requiring that you enter your repair orders on the MyAerospace Portal prior to sending your part to Honeywell, in accordance with our &quot;Repair and Overhaul Terms&quot; posted on 
MyAerospace.  
 
Honeywell requires submitting a MyAerospace repair order to support a seamless repair and return of your unit. MyAerospace will open a world of convenience, dependability, and speed for your company. For additional information on how to submit your repair orders online, please watch this training video &lt;[[http://www.kaltura.com/index.php/extwidget/preview/partner_id/2109061/uiconf_id/36386122/entry_id/1_hmsopfaw]]&gt;.
 
In addition, Honeywell has partnered with Aeroxchange &lt;[[https://www.aeroxchange.com/aexportal/home.jsp]]&gt;, an aviation supply 
chain solutions company, to provide additional 
options for placing your repair orders. If you’d like more information about using Aeroxchange, please contact your Honeywell Customer Support Manager.


Learn more about MyAerospace Portal updates here &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/MZ0X0000Qx0eG00sq00I052]]&gt;.


Thank you for your business,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
