<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_BK_Global_Email_KI-825&amp;IVA-81D_Customer_mih.201809_BK_Global_Email_KI-825</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Please Consider Taking Action: Product Notification from ONTIC</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
September 20, 2018
As you may already know, Honeywell/BendixKing licensed certain products to ONTIC back in March of this year. If you’d like to review the original announcement letter, you can find it here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/BK_Follow-up_ONTIC_announcement_090618.pdf]]&gt;. A list of the part numbers affected can be found here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/BK_ONTIC_Permission_Letter_2018-09-06.pdf]]&gt;.

To maintain compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and to be sure that we follow all data privacy laws when processing any personal data under valid agreements, BendixKing would like permission to share your 
contact details with ONTIC. This will make it possible for ONTIC to contact you directly so that you can continue to get important product-related information. 

BendixKing will define the specific purposes for which ONTIC could use personal data and will make sure all of our customers’ personal data is returned to us on expiration or termination of the relevant Agreement with ONTIC. 

Please click on the button below to give BendixKing permission to forward your contact information to ONTIC for product updates, news, surveys, special offers and other forms of electronic communication.

Thank you.






SIGN UP &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/BK_Subscription_Page.html]]&gt;






If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/T3ZQS0h0v000BIG20qjdGX0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
