<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GoDirect CSP - Compliance - Customer Communication Email.201801_Global_Email_GoD</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Communication Service Provider Performance Based Communication and Surveillance Compliance</subject>
    <textOnly>January 25, 2018

Dear GoDirect Customer, 

The Federal Aviation Administration recently published AC No: 90-117 that applies to all pilots, certificate holders, operators, and/or program managers conducting data link communication operations and to those providing data communication services on behalf of operators to meet Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) and International Civil Aviation Organization (ICAO) requirements. 

GoDirect provides datalink services via contractual agreements with satellite communication service providers and VHF Communication Service Providers (CSP) that enable Future Air Navigation System (FANS),   Controller Pilot   Datalink Communication Departure Clearance (CPDLC DCL), Aeronautical Telecommunications Network- B1(CPDLC-ATN B1), also known as Protected Mode CPDLC or Link 2000+. 

The Advisory Circular outlines that operators must ensure the services they have arranged with CSPs include: 
1 – Failure Notification 
2 – Recording data link messages
3 – CSP integrity 
4 – Compliance with CSP allocations for Required Communication Performance (RCP)/Required Surveillance Performance (RSP)
5 – Adequate subnetwork coverage for the route flown

While GoDirect enables its customers  access  to the CSPs networks GoDirect does not own them nor have control over their domains to ensure Performance Based Communication and Surveillance (PBCS). It is the CSP themselves that to the best of their abilities comply with PBCS. As outlined in the Advisory Circular an acceptable alternate means of compliance CSPs need only to become PBCS charter members. 
“Operators who are seeking an Operations Specification (OpSpec)/Management Specification (MSpec)/Letter of Authorization (LOA) A056, Data Link Communications, authorization and are charter members satisfy their responsibility of ensuring their CSP meets the minimum specifications of this chapter provided that their CSP is also a charter member”. Both ARINC and SITA are charter members for PBCS and can be found at the following link http://www.fans-cra.com/ &lt;[[http://www.fans-cra.com/]]&gt;. Furthermore, GoDirect’s internal network does not add any latency, manipulate information, nor impact the CSPs or ATSU integrity. 

GoDirect strives to provide cutting-edge communication, essential communication services  and  customer service. Through the PBCS charter membership, our customers can show compliance for PBCS with CSP that GoDirect enables access. It is our pleasure to serve you. 

Sincerely, 

GoDirect Flight Support Services</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
