<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201904_EMEAI_MSP_MC.201904_EMEAI_MSP_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the New Maintenance Service Plan from Honeywell</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Valued Customer,

We are excited to bring you news of our latest changes and recently added solutions to our family of Aftermarket maintenance service plans.
Introducing Maintenance Service Plan – an umbrella of offerings that incorporates the current Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) and Maintenance Protection Plan (MPP) Programs. All service programs will now be identified by, and located under, this overarching Maintenance Service Plan umbrella.
For more than 40 years Honeywell has built the preeminent Business Aviation services program, with its Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) for Engines and APUs offerings. Going forward, we will utilize the MSP umbrella naming to cover all our Business Aviation Aftermarket service offerings.
As an existing customer, you can rest assured that everything you know and love about these services will remain the same. Same great program, same great features and benefits, same great value, just under a new name. In fact, we are rolling out some additional upgrade features which we think will add even more value for you.
Maintenance Service Plan is a maintenance solution that makes it easy for you to choose from a range of selectable coverage options, tailored to your platform and operations.
Under the new Maintenance Service Plan umbrella, selectable options include:



New Name
Old Name   


Maintenance Service Plan – Avionics
HAPP – Honeywell Avionics Protection Program            


Maintenance Service Plan – Mechanical Components
MPP – Mechanical Protection Program            


Maintenance Service Plan – Propulsion
MSP – Maintenance Service Plan for Engines            


Maintenance Service Plan – Auxiliary Power Units
MSP – Maintenance Service Plan for APUs            


Maintenance Service Plan – Expanded Component Coverage
New feature            



Our new Maintenance Service Plan structure allows you to understand, evaluate and easily add additional service options to your coverage from those outlined above. Our Maintenance Service Plan will continue to provide real value to your operations through enhanced aircraft resale value, and other benefits such as financial predictability and simplified budgeting. These benefits are intended to reduce the maintenance burden and ensure your aircraft is where it belongs – up in the sky.
There are no immediate changes to your existing contract or overall service. Starting on April 3rd, 2019 and extending over the course of the next few months, you will see changes to our websites, sales brochures and other program documentation reflecting the new name and program structure.
To find out more about Maintenance Service Plan and how you can benefit beyond your current coverage, please click the link below or contact your local Honeywell representative.



LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/maintenance-service-plan-business-aviation]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
