<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201711_EGPWSCardTechSupport_LG.201711_EGPWSCardTechSupport_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Tech Tips - Loading the EGPWS Database Using a PCMCIA Card</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer,  
We want to make sure you have a smooth process when you load your Enhanced Ground Proximity Warning System (EGPWS) terrain database using a PCMCIA card.  

 
Unfortunately, we have discovered a few cases where the PCMCIA cards don’t support a complete load, resulting in an illuminated EGPWS “XFER FAIL” LED light. 

 
We are making the necessary changes to the PCMCIA card to correct this. In the meantime, if you experience this transfer issue, we recommend reloading the PCMCIA card with the terrain database per the Omni drive loading process (view the Downloading the Terrain Database &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/o023Z005600k0Q000XIG0q0]]&gt; video). If you experience any Omni drive issue during reloading, we recommend you replace the PCMCIA card with a new one. Some other tips:  

 	- When the EGPWS “XFER FAIL” LED illuminates, the unit must be power-cycled (off/on) to recover.  	- For greater loading reliability, we recommend ensuring the EGPWS is off before installing the PCMCIA card. Current service bulletins do provide instructions to “make sure the power to the EGPWS is on” but they will be updated once the PCMCIA issue is resolved. 

 
Please reference the following support videos below. And, as you watch these videos, don’t worry if the MyAerospace screens appear differently now – we’ve recently updated the user experience. The link names and processes remain the same.  

 
	-   Downloading the Terrain Database &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gigjb1BIOnQ]]&gt;    
	-   Loading the Terrain Database &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O93DoYyDHro]]&gt;    	-   EGPWS Self-Tests &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SVH46KNN9_o]]&gt;   

 

Please refer to the MyAerospace Portal for the latest terrain database information, including the Database Services Bulletin DSB201507002 and software - Aerospace Software and Data Services (ASDS) &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/z0002Gq0000IZ66kQ080X00]]&gt;. 
We will let you know when the final documentation is available. These documents are also helpful (login required):  

 	- EGPWS Troubleshooting Guide, 060-4199-190 &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/support/techpubsdeeplink?urlSearchId=926BCC1C-015F-4000-E000-34320AC5408E]]&gt; 	- Database Services Bulletin, DSB201507002 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/api/aerofsscms.svc/document?itemid=%7b8865EB4A-19BF-4ED2-ABA6-994C1081D49C%7d]]&gt; 

 
Need other technical support? Please visit our MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u7Z0000I0q0G0902600QXk0&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=]]&gt; for troubleshooting articles, technical publications, or to submit questions to our technical support engineering team. 
 
 
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
