<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201808_Americas_AP_ACADC.201808_Americas_Email_AP_ACADC_LL</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Form, Fit and Function ACADC Upgrade with Aero Precision</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; 

 &lt;[[https://www.aeroprecision.com/]]&gt;

Next Generation F-16 Technology with Honeywell and Aero Precision
The F-16 Central Air Data Computer (CADC) is the first-generation Central Air Data Computer for the F-16 and standard on all F-16s produced through the early 1990’s. Honeywell upgraded the CADC with the Upgraded Central Air Data Computer (UCADC) which was used in production until the 2000’s. The CADC and UCADC became obsolete and have been out of production for approximately 25 years and consequently becoming unsupportable.

In order to address this problem, Honeywell has partnered with Honeywell Authorized Distributor, Aero Precision, to offer the F-16 Advanced Central Air Data Computer (ACADC) which is listed in the F-16 IPB TO’s and is currently in production for F-16s. Critical issues with the CADC and UCADC include failing wire wrap mother boards, unsupportable pressure transducer and others. With the ACADC upgrade, you’ll count on:



	- Solving known issues with the CADC/UCADC
	- Significant cost savings
	- 4x better Mean Time Between Failures (MTBF)
	- Much more


Plus, with Aero Precision, you can expect efficiency and effectiveness on your order. As a leading provider for the F-16, Aero Precision prides itself in being flexible, reliable and committed to quality.

Contact Aero Precision below to learn more about this upgrade. 

PN: 62000030-903 NSN: 6610-01-621-9255





UPGRADE WITH AERO PRECISION  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AeroPrecision_ACADC_ACADC.html?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=18_ChannelAmericas_D%26S]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
