<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_09_October_NBAA_Edition.2019_Nov-Dec_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Engines News, &quot;Mr. Fixit&quot; and More</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
November - December
WHEREVER THE PRAETOR 600 FLIES, HONEYWELL MSP-PROPULSION FLIES WITH IT
Embraer’s Praetor 600 has been called a disruptive force on the business aviation scene. Powered by Honeywell’s HTF7500 engines...





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/news/2019/10/honeywell-msp-is-there?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiWkdZeU9HTTNaV0k1TUdReiIsInQiOiJKTHVGRjMrU0Yrd3BXTjhiczZIUUZyZkNxdExmSytjZWZoV0E1OUFNSnd4SW9XRTVxckRWNit4XC9NXC9OUjUraytpSU5GRWNrS2xwTm55Qk9Wbnh2WDJheU1raVZcL2MxOFFlRjFaK21PYXhPU2N5MlZSZ0VyTklDZFloeWRQeitOeSJ9]]&gt;
Honeywell unveils innovative Micro Power Units for business aircraft

Honeywell’s Micro Power Units for business and private airplanes, helicopters, and advanced ground vehicles deliver many of the same benefits of APUs. These include major savings from reduced fuel burn, coupled with mobile power on the ground for critical aircraft systems such as air conditioning and avionics... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2019/10/innovative-micro-power-unit-for-business-jet]]&gt;.
Big changes to your newsletter landing in 2020

We are pleased to announce that there will be some exciting changes coming to the Honeywell Business Aviation and Direct-To Newsletters starting in 2020. Beginning in January, you will see a fresh look, a new experience and access to even more business aviation content... Sneak peek &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/big-changes-newsletter-2020?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiWkdZeU9HTTNaV0k1TUdReiIsInQiOiJKTHVGRjMrU0Yrd3BXTjhiczZIUUZyZkNxdExmSytjZWZoV0E1OUFNSnd4SW9XRTVxckRWNit4XC9NXC9OUjUraytpSU5GRWNrS2xwTm55Qk9Wbnh2WDJheU1raVZcL2MxOFFlRjFaK21PYXhPU2N5MlZSZ0VyTklDZFloeWRQeitOeSJ9]]&gt;.
Efrain Villafane is still “Mr. Fixit” when operators experience engine problems

Honeywell Field Service Engineer Efrain Villafane knows aircraft engines from the inside out. He spent a big part of his 20-year aviation industry career working as a mechanic for legendary aircraft manufacturers... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/september/former-mechanic-still-focused-on-customer-fixes]]&gt;.
Honeywell&apos;s updates your website experience
We have updated our website to focus on solving problems that our customers face daily... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2019/10/solving-the-toughest-challenges-in-aerospace]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
