<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017_EMEAI_COPENHAGEN_GODIRECT_Conf_Irina.Evite_irina</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You are invited to the Honeywell GoDirect Connectivity Conference</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | GoDirect
Join us for the GoDirect Connectivity Conference!
Copenhagen
August 25th, 2017
Dear valued customers, partners and friends,
We are pleased to invite you to our GoDirect Connectivity Conference that will take place in Copenhagen, Denmark on the 25th of August 2017. 
Join us for the third annual GoDirect satellite communications conference for the Northern and Eastern Europe region, it will give you a great overview and understanding of cabin connectivity products &amp; services, latest applications, certifications, support and troubleshooting procedures as well as activation of the service and support. 
Previously hosted in Dubai, Shanghai, Basel, Copenhagen and Nuremberg, our rotating GoDirect events are gaining more popularity from business jet owners and charter operators, as well as MROs. It will be a great opportunity to have all your questions answered (feel free to submit your questions here &lt;[[mailto:jimmy.larsen@honeywell.com]]&gt; beforehand) and to network. 
 Latest inflight connectivity updates | Ka-Band | Ku-Band | Swiftbroadband | SBB-Safety | | Flight Support Services | Hardware and Software updates | New applications and service demonstrations | 
Hotel accommodation: A limited number of rooms are blocked till mid August at the Tivoli Hotel &amp; Congress Center.
Please book at www.tivolihotel.dk &lt;[[http://www.tivolihotel.dk]]&gt; and use the code 1579689 when making your reservation. 
For nearby budget alternative we recommend the WakeUp Copenhagen Hotel https://www.wakeupcopenhagen.dk &lt;[[https://www.wakeupcopenhagen.dk]]&gt; .
Parking: There is a parking house between, operated by and for Tivoli Hotel &amp; Congress Center and WakeUp Copenhagen Hotel’s guests. 


Please confirm your attendance directly to Jimmy Larsen (jimmy.larsen@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:jimmy.larsen@honeywell.com]]&gt;).



Jimmy Larsen
Connectivity Sales Manager, North and Eastern Europe.
Honeywell GoDirect</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
