<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201901_Americas_Mandates_Duncan.kcr.201901_Duncan_Mandates_Owners_Email_1_kcr</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Don’t Wait Another Minute. Schedule Mandate Upgrades Today!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
 
 &lt;[[https://www.duncanaviation.aero/]]&gt;

The deadline for 2020 mandates is fast approaching. But, December 31, 2019 isn’t the most important date. In most scenarios if your upgrades aren’t scheduled by July, you won’t get in before the deadline.

If your aircraft isn’t compliant with the 2020 FAA mandates, there’s no better time than NOW to upgrade with Honeywell’s solutions. Honeywell’s solutions for the ADS-B Out and FANS 1/A mandates offer owners a low risk, high value option for mandate compliance.  

Why install Honeywell’s Upgrades?



	- Minimal impact to the aircraft during the upgrade, unlike the low-cost aftermarket solutions which require external systems and are not guaranteed to be compatible with future evolutions of the airspace requirements.
	- High reliability of Honeywell products.

	- Your aircraft will increase in value with an integrated system.

	- Take advantage of a 100% tax write-off for component upgrades. 
	- Duncan Aviation has the required STCs to upgrade equipment.



If you’re looking for a well-engineered solution that integrates well with other avionics systems on your aircraft and has OEM approval, look no further. Contact Duncan Aviation, a Honeywell Authorized Service Center, to request a quote or to learn more about Honeywell’s integrated solutions.



LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/schedule-your-mandate-upgrades-with-duncan-aviation?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_duncan_adsb&amp;utm_content=paid&amp;utm_term=mandates]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
