<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_Connectivity_Honeywell_Forge_Dispatch_Services.202005_Email_Connec</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How Honeywell Forge Dispatch and the FAA’s CDM Program Saves You Time &amp; Money</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt;

Join Carey Miller, Honeywell’s Technical Sales Manager, and Wayne Hundsdorfer,
Regional Sales Leader, for an exclusive webinar discussing how business aviation operators can gain access to the FAA’s Collaborative Decision Making (CDM) program through Honeywell Forge Dispatch 
Services. 

During the 30-minute session, you will learn how Honeywell Forge Dispatch Services protects against challenges that can adversely affect the productivity and efficiency of your flight department and provides significant time and cost savings.

From start to finish, the Honeywell Forge Dispatch team monitors the aircraft position and progress of your flight while looking ahead for weather hazards, traffic congestion, ATC delays, or any other conditions that may affect your flight. We keep you informed with proactive communications sent to your mobile device, aircraft datalink or other designated destinations.

Benefits Covered in the Webinar



	- Increase efficiency and reduce delays
	- Preferential treatment in U.S. airspace utilizing Honeywell’s partnership with ATC
	- Active flight following, communication, and weather mitigation with re-route suggestions
	- Global coverage and support
	- Tour the New Honeywell Forge Suite of Services











DATE 
May 15th, 2020







TIME 
8:00am Pacific Time







LOCATION 
Online: ZOOM Link &lt;[[https://honeywell.zoom.us/j/95707617791?pwd=ZS8yRVdFVmhhMVMvYVlXeWpEcFc2Zz09]]&gt;







HOSTED BY 
Carey Miller







SPECIAL OFFER 
Try Honeywell Forge Dispatch Services for Free: Tune in to get learn how to receive a 90 day free 
trial
DOWNLOAD CALENDAR INVITE WITH LINK &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Webinar_Honeywell_Forge_Dispatch.ics]]&gt;
© 2020 Honeywell International Inc.
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202   
This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=NA}}. If you don&apos;t want to receive these emails from Honeywell in the future, you can edit your profile &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Email_Confirmation_OptOut.html]]&gt;.
Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;   



 
  &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;     
 &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;        &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;       &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
