<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>June 2017 Edition.June 2017 Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - June 2017 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
June 2017
DON&apos;T SIT ON YOUR FANS TOO LONG
Or you may be parked in 2020. Honeywell has the satellite communications systems, communications management units, VHF Data Link Mode 2 radios, and flight management system software upgrades your aircraft needs to comply with all FANS 1/A requirements....





LEARN MORE       &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/fans-mandates]]&gt;
Honeywell Delivers Next-Gen Avionics for Gulfstream GIV / GV Platforms
Honeywell has upgrades available right now for your aircraft which provide improved pilot situational awareness, mandate compliance and increased aircraft value...

Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/june/honeywell-delivers-next-gen-avionics-for-gulfstream-giv-gv-platforms]]&gt;.
Protect Your Investment with GoDirect Maintenance and Service Plans  We have a wide range of cost-efficient plans to protect your Honeywell avionics and mechanical systems...
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/service-listing/maintenance-and-service-plans]]&gt;
Honeywell Puts GoDirect Cabin Connectivity Services in the Hands of Business Jet Operators to Control the In-Cabin Experience
The updates allow business jet operators to control network services on the aircraft in real time... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/may/honeywell-puts-godirect-cabin-connectivity-services-in-the-hands-of-business-jet-operators]]&gt;
Learjet Owners: Cost-Saving Opportunity to Upgrade Your Cockpit  Learjet 40/45 business jet have a unique opportunity to breathe new life into their cockpits with Primus Elite® displays... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/june/learjet-owners-cost-saving-opportunity-to-upgrade-your-cockpit]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
