<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Global_CPS_Email_Satair-Airbus-Update_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Satair appointed as exclusive distributor for Honeywell Mechanical LRU new spares</subject>
    <textOnly>In order to better serve our customer’s needs, Honeywell is very pleased to announce that we have recently appointed Satair, an Airbus subsidiary, as the Exclusive Worldwide Distributor for Honeywell´s Mechanical and Air Thermal Components products on the A320, A330, A340 and A380 platforms. Additionally, the distribution agreement also covers A350 platforms on a non-exclusive basis. 

 As a trusted Honeywell partner, we want to make sure you are aware of the appointment of SATAIR, so you can connect with them to facilitate any customer requests for mechanical and air thermal components products for the platforms mentioned above. If Satair is not yet in your Authorized Supplier List, we would recommend adding them to your list of suppliers at the earliest opportunity. 

 This partnership also guarantees that you will always have immediate access to parts and components, in case of an unexpected need, once Satair will maintain an inventory to support customers globally. 

 Honeywell will continue to maintain any current contractual obligations on the A320, A330, A340 and A380 platforms, but the remaining network and non-contractual customers should approach Satair directly. All future orders for these product categories will also be placed through Satair

 Honeywell’s appointment of Satair is an expansion of an existing relationship. The company already has two other agreements with Honeywell: A distributor agreement for the ADSB-Out Upgrade Pilot Program, and a non-exclusive worldwide distributor agreement for Honeywell’s JetWave satellite communications products. 

 Should you have any other queries regarding part numbers &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Satair_Distribution_Part-Numbers_202101.xlsx]]&gt; and products eligible in this agreement or the appointment of Satair, please contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager or Satair at https://www.satair.com/about-satair/contact-us/locations &lt;[[https://www.satair.com/about-satair/contact-us/locations]]&gt;.
Satair A/S
 Amager Landevej 147A
 2770 Kastrup
 Denmark 

Tel: +45 3247 0100 
 
info@satair.com &lt;[[mailto:info@satair.com]]&gt;
Satair Pte Ltd
 12 Seletar Aerospace Link
 Singapore 797553


 Tel: +65 6543 0977

 infosin@satair.com &lt;[[mailto:infosin@satair.com]]&gt;
Satair USA, Inc.
 525 Westpark Drive, Suite 400
 Peachtree City, GA 30269
 USA

 Tel: +1 404 675 6333
 
satairinq@satair.com &lt;[[mailto:satairinq@satair.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
