<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018PricingUpdate_Oct2017.2018PricingUpdate_Email_Oct2017</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2018 Catalog Pricing Now Available on MyAerospace Portal</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer, 
Updated 2018 spares catalog pricing is now available on Honeywell’s MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt; portal for our air transport &amp; regional (ATR) customers. Universal flat fate (UFR) pricing for repairs is always available through the MyAerospace &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; Online Ordering application.
 
Important Information: 


	- 
Since Honeywell’s pricing policy applies to when an order is delivered, all orders placed starting Oct. 1 with lead times indicating delivery in 2018 must reflect the 2018 price.

	- 
You must update your internal tracking systems to reflect the 2018 catalog pricing unless you have contractual pricing with Honeywell.

	- 
Failure to update your system may result in 2018 order delivery delays since an updated purchase order will be required.

	- 
You may access the new pricing when searching for parts using MyAerospace’s Online Ordering or downloading the pricing catalog from MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt;.



Thank you for your cooperation in updating your tracking systems to reflect 2018 pricing. If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell Customer Support contact or submit a question &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt; through MyAerospace. 
The MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; is always available for your order management needs, including parts quoting, ordering, and tracking. View MyAerospace updates and tutorials here &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training]]&gt;.


Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
