<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Sales Excellence Playbook.Sales Excellence Memo#2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing the Aerospace Sales Excellence Playbook</subject>
    <textOnly>   

Colleagues, 

By now, you should be familiar with AeroUp, a new, innovative, customer facing digital selling tool rolled out recently by Commercial and Sales Excellence. AeroUp was designed entirely to meet the needs of our sales teams – giving you immediate access to the latest brochures, videos, infographics and other key sales material to support your customer meetings.  

I am very excited about this initial version of the tool and would like to personally ask each of you to download AeroUp if you haven’t already done so. Please refer to iPad &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/iPad%20instructions.pdf]]&gt; or Windows &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Windows%20instructions.pdf]]&gt; installation instructions and download it today so you can become familiar with the material and the functionality of the tool. We want our sales teams to start using it, but to also give us feedback on how we can make it better.   

In the meantime, I wanted to share a few tips and insights we’ve identified since the launch: 

 
	-  
AeroUp runs on Honeywell-issued iPads and PCs with Windows 8.1 or newer. If you do not have an iPad, contact your manager. Contact your local IT tech to upgrade if you are still on Windows 7.  
	-  
The iPad version takes about an hour to sync the content. There is more than a 1GB of brochures, videos and brochures to download. Since the initial launch, we have optimized and removed some large files and have seen download times decrease. PLEASE BE PATIENT. The download pauses when your iPad goes to ‘sleep;’ and it takes a few minutes to restart. So, tap the screen every few minutes to keep the download going.  
	-  
AeroUp is designed to work offline (which is why the initial download takes so long). However, we’ve noticed a bug in the Windows version that will ask you to sign-in when you launch the app if you’re offline. We are working on a fix.  

 

We plan to have an updated version early next week with increased functionality, and additional platforms based off of feedback received from the sales team. We developed AeroUp to get in to your hands quickly, but want to continue to evolve the app based on what you need. See something that isn’t right, or something that should be added? Send suggestions to ed.tribble@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:ed.tribble@honeywell.com]]&gt; 

I am also happy to share that AeroUp will be available in the Apple app store for non-Honeywell iPads and for dealers/channel partners in the next few weeks. 

Thank you for your support and I wish you all the best with bringing in those sales. 

Let’s Get Growing! 

Mark Winston
Commerical &amp; Sales Excellence Vice President
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2017 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
