<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20191009_Global_Email_CoonRapids_KFK.20191009_Global_Email_CoonRapids_KFK</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Coon Rapids, MN Move Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer, 

As Honeywell advised earlier this year, we have decided to optimize our operations and close our Coon Rapids, Minnesota facility by Q1 2021. The transition teams are engaged and details for all move phases are being incorporated into the overall project plan. As a reminder, the product lines affected by this transition include: 



	- Commercial Inertial Reference Units, Data Acquisition Units (DAU), Yaw Damper and Flame Sensors are moving to the Honeywell Clearwater, Florida site.
	- Digital Analog Adaptor (DAA), Air Data Computer (ADC), Air Data Management and Fuel Probe repairs are moving to the Honeywell Deer Valley, Arizona site.
	- We are also taking this opportunity to better align Control Sensor Products (CSP). This will move from our Golden Valley site to the Honeywell Clearwater, Florida site.


This notification is for the first transition for the following product lines. 
This move includes: 



	- Complete product line move for the DAU and Yaw Damper.
	- A partial move of the 10 MCU Inertial Reference Unit (IRU) product line.


Repair Unit Shipments 



	- View the Part Number and Move Schedule &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Coon Rapids-Move 2- PN and Move Schedule.xlsx]]&gt; file to determine the date that each part number will move. Locate the move sequence number and match to the ‘Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date’ identified in the chart below.


-- OR --


	- Access MyAerospace Repair Site Capability &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/TyZQd0n0G000YId21qicGX0]]&gt; list available 24x7.





Product
Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date – 
For Repairs and New OE/Spares (if available) 


DAU Line
Nov. 25, 2019


Yaw Damper Line
Nov. 25, 2019


Inertial Reference Units – 10 MCU
Dec. 9, 2019 




Repair Order Processing 
To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions: 

Existing Repair Orders 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Coon Rapids.
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification.
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity.


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.




New Repair Orders 



	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the new location.
	- Part numbers received on or before the ‘Coon Rapids Repairs Last Receipt Date’ will be accepted at Coon Rapids.
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date’ to Clearwater for repair.


	- A PO/contract modification may be required.
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity.


	- The Repair Site Capability list will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs.


Existing Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders 



	- Honeywell is working to fulfill existing orders.
	- Depending upon inventory, due dates and lead-times associated with the order, some orders may require a purchase order or contract modification to revise the place of performance.
	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact you with the next few weeks to advise and coordinate that activity.


New Original Equipment &amp; Spares Orders



	- Please view the chart to determine the last date that Coon Rapids will accept new OE/Spares orders.
	- After these dates, all new hardware orders are to be addressed to Honeywell International, Inc. at the OE/Spares address provided below.
	- Depending upon inventory, due dates and lead-times associated with the hardware, some orders may require a purchase order or contract modification to revise the place of performance.
	- If a purchase order or contract modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact you with the next few weeks to advise and coordinate that activity.


AOG Support 
There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware. 

Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts. 





Honeywell Name for Repairs:


 Honeywell International Inc. Clearwater Commercial Service Center


Honeywell Name for OE/Spares:


Honeywell International Inc. Clearwater Commercial Operations


Address:    
13051 66th Street Plant 4


City, State:
Largo, Florida


Postal Code:  
33773


Country:
U.S.A.


Cage Code: 
65507







As we move closer to the next transition phase, we will be sending out additional communications specific to those product lines and part numbers. If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 

Sincerely, 
Honeywell Aerospace 
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
