<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201705_APAC_Email_APACHQ60Days_ENG_mih.201705_APAC_Email_APACHQ60Days_Eng_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell International Sdn Bhd: Asia Regional Distribution Center</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

May 5, 2017




Dear Honeywell Customer, 



In reference to the letter sent on 5 April 2017, we would like to assure you that we are effectively progressing with the transition. As mentioned earlier, Honeywell Aerospace has decided to set up a new aftermarket headquarters and a new distribution center under Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The new distribution center will be called the Asia Regional Distribution Center (ARDC). ARDC will streamline Honeywell’s Asia Pacific Aero aftermarket distribution operations to better support our customers in the Asia Pacific Region.

The establishment of the new regional distribution center will see APAC business content that is currently managed by Honeywell International Sarl (HIS) in Switzerland transitioned to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd in Malaysia. The optimized local distribution center will be able to serve our customers in the Asia Pacific Region with quicker delivery turnaround times, and will provide exemplary aftermarket support and services.

To follow up on the action, we appreciate your kind validation on whether the following activities we requested previously have been completed. If not, we would appreciate your immediate attention to ensure that the following actions and changes be made as soon as possible: 



	- Update your Authorized Vendor List and internal systems to reflect the new Honeywell International Sdn Bhd legal entity name and address:




Company Name: Honeywell International Sdn Bhd 
 Address: Lobby A, Avenue 10, The Vertical, Bangsar South City, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi 
 City: Kuala Lumpur 
 Postal Code: 59200 
 Country: Malaysia



	- Appoint a new freight forwarding agent that will handle all the shipments from Kuala Lumpur Malaysia to your country of destination that is registered under the Royal Malaysian Custom. Please send your freight forwarding agent’s name to your business manager or to joel.miranda@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:joel.miranda@honeywell.com]]&gt; so we can update our system.




	- The invoice “Pay To” account changes to the Honeywell International Sdn Bhd:








The United States Dollar Account: 
CITIBANK BERHAD
MENARA CITIBANK
165 JALAN AMPANG
50450 KUALA LUMPUR
MALAYSIA
SWIFT CODE: CITIMYKL
ACCOUNT: 0117470059



Malaysia Ringgit Account (for Malaysia based customer only)

CITIBANK BERHAD
MENARA CITIBANK
165 JALAN AMPANG
50450 KUALA LUMPUR
MALAYSIA
SWIFT CODE: CITIMYKL
ACCOUNT: 0117470105




Note: In accordance with the new FX policy introduced by Bank Negara Malaysia, the Malaysia based customers can only settle their invoices due to HISB in Malaysia Ringgit, unless they receive an exemption from Bank Negara Malaysia. If the current agreement has stated USD as the invoice billing currency, we can maintain status quo but the settlement currency will be in Malaysia Ringgit.


For Contract Customers Only: Execute an Amendment Agreement to assign Contracts, to include Honeywell International Sdn Bhd legal entity name and address, to amend bank details, delivery/export clauses, where required. Our contracts managers will contact and work with you closely.

As we go through this transition, we want to assure you that we have your best interests in mind. For frequently asked questions, please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/English -Asia Regional Distribution Center %28ARDC%29 - FAQ.pdf]]&gt;. If you have any further questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us via your account leader or customer manager.

Thank you for your support as we work to enhance the way Honeywell Aerospace does business with you.

Sincerely,</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
