<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201902_Global_Event_AEA_Dealers_MC.201902_Global_Invite1_AEA_Dealers_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Connect with BendixKing and Honeywell at AEA 2019</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt;   &lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/home]]&gt;
AEA INTERNATIONAL CONVENTION &amp; TRADE SHOW
March 25-28
The 2019 AEA International Convention and Trade Show is right around the corner and we&apos;re excited to see all of our BendixKing and Honeywell dealers there. Please join us as we introduce new products, host training sessions and celebrate with you. See you in sunny Palm Springs!
New Product Introduction Sessions

BendixKing is very excited to be participating in the new product introduction ceremony this year. Join us as we introduce:



	- AeroCruze 100 Autopilot, an affordable and flexible digital autopilot system for Cessna 172, 175 177 and Piper PA 28 aircraft. 




	- AeroPoint, an advanced and accurate high-resolution display for engine monitoring.
Honeywell Training Sessions
 
Honeywell is hosting ten training sessions to educate our dealers on the features and benefits of our connectivity and cockpit upgrades, to help dealers sell, configure and install JetWave and to learn about our Honeywell Avionics and Mechanical Protection Plans (HAPP &amp; MPP), including recent program enhancements.

If you are a Honeywell dealer, you won&apos;t want to miss this. Click here &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/AEA-2019]]&gt; to view our training schedule and reserve your spot today.
BendixKing Training Sessions 

Attention all BendixKing dealers! We&apos;re hosting two installation training sessions covering AeroVue, xVue Touch, KI 300 / KA 310 electronic attitude indicator, KFC 230 autopilot and AeroWave. 

These 2 hour training sessions will cover product features and installation tips you won&apos;t want to miss.  

View our full schedule and reserve your spot &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/AEA-2019]]&gt; today.
Dealer Appreciation Reception

Wednesday, March 27 2:00 PM - 5:00 PM
Honeywell and BendixKing dealers are invited to join us for cocktails and hors d&apos;oeuvres for an in-booth reception as we celebrate our accomplishments. RSVP today &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/dealer-appreciation-event]]&gt; to let us know you&apos;re coming.
For more information about our AEA 2019 plans, please contact Lisa Watmore (BendixKing) &lt;[[mailto:Lisa.Watmore@Honeywell.com]]&gt; or Krysti Roush (Honeywell) &lt;[[mailto:krysti.roush@honeywell.com]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
