<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202009_Global_CPS_Pricing-Update_Email_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2021 Catalog Pricing Coming October 1, 2020</subject>
    <textOnly>2021 Pricing Catalog Now Available
Dear Honeywell Customer, 

The 2021 published Commercial Spares and BGA Universal Flat Rate pricing catalogs are now available on Honeywell&apos;s MyAerospace &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt; Portal. 

 Key Information: 



	- 2021 downloadable Pricing Catalogs &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/secure/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt; are available on the MyAerospace portal.
	- The pricing in the 2021 catalogs is effective January 1, 2021.
	- 2021 pricing will be reflected when searching for parts or placing orders on MyAerospace Online Ordering &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/redirects/sso/online-ordering]]&gt; beginning on January 1, 2021.
	- Download the 2021 catalogs and update any internal systems to reflect the 2021 catalog pricing.
	- Please ensure to update Honeywell prices in your system such that all purchase orders placed January 1, 2021 and after use the correct 2021 pricing so they can be processed without interruption to your order.
	- Note that this does not apply to contractual pricing.


Why Use MyAerospace: 



	- Easy access with 24/7 availability.
	- Use MyAerospace for your order management needs, including: Quoting, Ordering and Order Status.
	- Periodically monitor the order status dashboard to view orders ‘on hold’ for price discrepancy or missing data.
	- At the same location, you can also sign up for catalog change notifications. This sends an email when any of your pricing catalogs are modified.
	- To catch up on the latest improvements to MyAerospace portal, Click Here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace/release-notes]]&gt;.
	- For training topics pages related to the portal, Click Here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/training/topics]]&gt;.


Thank you for your cooperation in updating your systems to reflect 2021 pricing. If you have any questions, please visit this page to Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;.

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace 
Customer &amp; Product Support
PRICING CATALOG &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/secure/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
