<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201707_Global_Email_Honeywell Channel Newsletter_LL.201707_Global_Email_Honeywel</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2017 Q2 Honeywell Channel Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
CHANNEL NEWSLETTER
July 2017
Get the latest news from Honeywell’s Q2 2017 Channel Newsletter.
FMS 6.1 Update 
 
Do your customers know that starting December 31, 2018, navigational database customers who do not have FMS 6.1 will be subject to additional costs? Educate your customers today about the benefits of upgrading their FMS subscription before their next renewal cycle. 





GET DETAILS  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/business-jets-get-key-flight-management-upgrades]]&gt;
Mechanical Service Center Agreements 

 

Are you aware of the latest changes we’ve made to our mechanical service center agreements (MSCA’s)?




READ MORE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Honeywell_MechanicalServiceCenterAgreements_063017.pdf]]&gt;
Honeywell Aerospace StandardAero’s JetWave STC for GIV 

 

Help your customers stay connected in the skies with StandardAero’s new JetWave™ STC for the Gulfstream GIV. Read more about how this STC now gives passengers endless streaming possibilities.
  





GET CONNECTED  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/june/fast-reliable-wi-fi-here-today-for-g-iv-operators]]&gt;
Limited Time Offer for RM-850 Replacement and ADS-B Out Upgrade 

 For a limited time, Honeywell is making it easier for several business aircraft operators by providing a low-cost, integrated ADS-Out upgrade for aircraft that have the Honeywell RM-850 forward-fit solution. Learn more about this limited time offer. 
  




SEE THE OFFER &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/ADS-B_Out_RM850.pdf]]&gt;
Channel Partner Advisory Board 



The Channel Partner Advisory Board met on May 2 and 4 to discuss a variety of topics including channel partner strategy and more.






READ MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-s-channel-partner-advisory-board-discusses-strategy-development]]&gt;
Simplified Rental Process  
 
 We’re making it easier for you to rent engines and APUs from us. This new streamlined process will significantly shorten the time for an operator to start flying again and minimize confusion.
 





SEE DETAILS &lt;[[http://bit.ly/2tKvnmQ]]&gt;
Excess Inventory


Do you need an engine or an APU for an upcoming operator visit? Click out our latest engine and APU inventory.



SEE INVENTORY &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2017_ERBexcesslist.html]]&gt;
LinkedIn Group


Get STC updates, network with other Honeywell channel partners and stay up to date with the Honeywell Aerospace Dealer LinkedIn Group.






JOIN THE CONVERSATION &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/groups/12014354]]&gt;
Q2 STCs  
 
 For more information, or to see a full list of FAA and EASA STCs approved in Q2, please visit the Honeywell Aerospace Dealer LinkedIn group.
 





SEE STCs &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/groups/12014354]]&gt;
Do you know someone who should be added to the Honeywell Channel Newsletter distribution list? Sign them up here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Honeywell-Channel-Newsletter-Subscription.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
