<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>June 2015.June 2015.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Customer Support Communication</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Newsletter Title
Making It Easier to Do Business with Honeywell
 

Ryan Lees, Vice President
BGA Customer and Product Support 





Honeywell is listening to your feedback and we are continually improving and introducing new tools and processes to make it easier for you to do business with us.

This newsletter was developed to share some of the initiatives we’re undertaking to respond more quickly to your needs. For example, we have introduced a number of new tools to accelerate response times and decrease complexity. These tools include the Support Locator mobile app, Pilot Gateway website/mobile app, new Aerospace Technical Support channels, and an upgrade to the MyAerospace portal.

But customer service is more than enhancing or introducing new tools. It’s providing you with access to knowledgeable professionals – our worldwide network of Field Service Engineers, Product Support Engineers and Technical Support Engineers – striving to meet and exceed your support needs at all times.

This newsletter includes a message from Heath Patrick, vice president, Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support, and provides updates on our new and evolving support tools and updates on GCC subcommittee 
activities.

We also encourage you to complete the upcoming industry surveys in Aviation International News and Professional Pilot, and reach out directly to the GCC.

We&apos;re all about making it easier for you to do business with Honeywell.

 We are listening.
Continue reading&gt;



 &lt;http://www.facebook.com/sharer.php?u=http://aerospace.honeywell.com/&amp;t=Article%20Title&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;    &lt;http://twitter.com/share?text=Article%20Title&amp;url=http://aerospace.honeywell.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;    &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/shareArticle?mini=true&amp;url=http://aerospace.honeywell.com&amp;title=Article%20Title&amp;summary=Article%20Summary&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;   &lt;https://plus.google.com/share?url=http://aerospace.honeywell.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&gt;
CTA Title

Body paragraph habitant

Morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
