<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201803_Americas_Nurture_ADS-B_NUG_mih.201803_Americas_Email2_ADS-B_NUG_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Be Ready for the ADS-B Mandate with New United Goderich</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;      &lt;[[http://newunitedgoderich.com/]]&gt; 

Embraer 135/145 ADS-B Out STC by New United Goderich

Fly today with a complete solution and prepare for the future with New United Goderich´s Embraer 135/145 ADS-B Out STC. 

By January 1st, 2020*, all operators must have Automatic Dependent Surveillance-Broadcast capability in order to fly in North America airspace. 

ADS-B Out increases efficiency, strengthens situational awareness and allows aircraft to transmit information to Air Traffic Control ground stations by using satellite signals instead of ground radar and navigational aids. As a result, ATC is able to keep your aircraft properly spaced in high-density traffic areas.

New United Goderich&apos;s Embraer 135/145 ADS-B Out STC# ST03177NY incorporates Honeywell’s RCZ-8XXM Mode S Extended Squitter transponders and FreeFlight Systems’ 1203C SBAS/GNSS sensor for a complete ADS-B (Out) solution.

This solution utilizes a streamlined, simple 
design to minimize installation aircraft down time - the amendment requires no additional flight testing.

And you can also choose between performing full installation at New United Goderich facility or the acquisition of partial Installation Kits for the ADS-B (OUT) STC.
Contact New United Goderich to upgrade your Embraer 135/145 today!







UPGRADE TODAY  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/ADS-B_New_United_Goderich_Email.html]]&gt;





 
 *Other regions and countries have their own calendar schedule for the DO-260B Mandate.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
