<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_BK_Dealer_Email_Sun_and_Fun_MC.201903_BK_Dealer_Email_Sun_and_Fun_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Visit us at Sun ‘n Fun in Lakeland, FL</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

Sun &apos;n Fun International Expo, booth A-034, A-035, April 2-7, 2019 
 
 Stop by and visit us at Sun &apos;n Fun, where this year we are excited to present products specifically for our experimental, kit and homebuilder audience. Whether your panel is compact or expansive, we have products that are award-winning, innovative and modular. Single component to complete upgrades. We have a solution for every style of flying, aircraft and budget.

xVue Touch &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xvue-touch]]&gt;: Primary flight display or split-screen primary flight display and multifunction display. Streamlined and simplified menu structure results in critical functions can be reached in two touches or less. Feature-rich and seamless integration with popular GPS navigators. 
 
xCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xcruze-100]]&gt;: Low-cost autopilot for experimental aircraft available in three form factors. It features all the same features as the certified AeroCruze 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-100]]&gt;, but priced for experimental, light sport and other non-certified aircraft. 
 
xPoint 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xpoint-100]]&gt;: An engine monitoring system designed for experimental, light sport and other non-certified aircraft, it is extremely compact, weighing only 13 ounces. It includes advanced capabilities such as its high-resolution display, providing nearly perfect legibility. It offers a wide variety of engine parameter displays from Turbine Inlet Temperature (TIT) to fuel flow. Also available for certified aircraft as the AeroPoint 200 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-200]]&gt; for single engine and AeroPoint 300 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropoint-300]]&gt; for twin engines. 
 
 We 
have more products to show you on display, so please stop by to visit and check out our demos!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
