<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Global_ATR_Hygiene_UV-Cabin-Systems_Bill-Good-Morning-America_email.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>“A Clean Sweep” - Watch Our UV Cabin System On ABC’s Good Morning America</subject>
    <textOnly>“A Clean Sweep”—Watch Our UV Cabin System On ABC’s Good Morning America
On behalf of the entire Honeywell “crew”—we hope you, your family, co-workers and customers are safe and well. 

 This pandemic has significantly changed our personal and work lives, with and air travel being no exception. We have worked tirelessly to quickly develop a family of cleaner air travel products and services, spanning the airport, airplane, office and hotels to help our industry get back in the air and office in a more confident, sustaining and profitable way. 

 Enter the Honeywell UV Cabin System &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-cabin-system?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_americas_atr_hygiene&amp;utm_content=gma]]&gt;—recently featured in this video &lt;[[https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/travel/story/jetblue-test-uv-cleaning-inside-planes-72028631]]&gt; by ABC’s Good Morning America, now under trial by JetBlue &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2020/07/jetblue-deploys-honeywell-ultraviolet-system?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_americas_atr_hygiene&amp;utm_content=gma]]&gt; and purchased by other well-known carriers. 

 In addition, we are hosting a webcast on this breakthrough product, and you can register here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/events/2020/08/uv-cabin-system-webinar?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_americas_atr_hygiene&amp;utm_content=gma]]&gt;. 

 The cabin system is a portable, ultraviolet-c light (UVC) system that brings a consistent “dose” and coverage to an airline’s cleaning process, eliminating the variability and length of time to clean by hand. This efficient and cost-effective system similar in size to a beverage cart can navigate an entire mid-sized airline cabin in less than 10 minutes, fast enough to run in between flights or overnight. 

 In clinical studies, UVC light has been shown to be capable of inactivating tested pathogens on multiple surfaces at specified doses. We are leveraging technology developed for hospital use, and while limited testing has been done regarding effectivity against SAR-CoV-2 (the virus that causes COVID-19), multiple clinical studies have found UVC lights to be capable of inactivating various pathogens—including SARS CoV and MERS 
CoV. 

 Our cabin system is just one of several air-travel related product and services we offer, spanning passenger and crew safety packs, fresh air checks, thermal fever screening, building management systems—and with more on the way.
Click here to clean! &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/products/cabin/uv-cabin-system?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_americas_atr_hygiene&amp;utm_content=gma]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
