<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_05_May.2019_May_Edition_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Biz Av News - Primus Elite Advanced Features Certified for Global Express</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
May 2019
PRIMUS ELITE ADVANCED FEATURES CERTIFIED FOR GLOBAL EXPRESS
Primus Elite Advanced Features adds Synthetic Vision System (SVS) and TCAS to the Primus Elite Advanced Map display, and two additional XM weather features: Terminal Area Forecasts (TAFs) and Meteorological Terminal Aviation Reports (METARS)...  
 

 
   LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_PEAF.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_americas_bga_primuselite&amp;utm_content=may-bganewsletter]]&gt;
Helicopter technical support leader is a breed apart  Helicopter people are a different breed. Just ask John Sanner, Honeywell’s Field Service Engineer and Technical Core Team Leader for helicopter engines and military mechanical systems...  Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/helicopter-technical-support-leader-is-a-breed-apart]]&gt;.
The Aviation International News (AIN) Survey was released on May 1
Our goal is to achieve top marks in this survey and we need your feedback to make this happen. Honeywell takes AIN and other industry surveys seriously, therefore we have worked on several improvements... Learn more &lt;[[http://www.aerospace.honeywell.com/customersupport]]&gt;.
How do you make the &quot;best wi-fi in the sky&quot; even better? Cut the price! 
 
 
Honeywell is offering special pricing on the JetWave™ satellite communications system for business aircraft... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/may/how-do-you-make-the-best-wi-fi-in-the-sky-even-better?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=may-bganewsletter]]&gt;.
5 myths about using the gray market for aircraft maintenance
 
 
Many operators believe that gray shops, or unauthorized service centers, offer faster service and lower pricing than a Honeywell Authorized Channel Partner. It’s time to set the record straight!  
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/may/top-5-myths-about-using-the-gray-market-for-aircraft-maintenance?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=may-bganewsletter]]&gt;.
Mandates compliance time is running short! 
Time is ticking away ahead of the deadline for 2020 ADS-B Out mandate compliance. But Dec. 31, 2019 isn’t the most important date, it’s actually now! If you don’t have your plane scheduled for upgrades, you may not beat the deadline... Read more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_ADS-B.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_americas_bga_primuselite&amp;utm_content=may-bganewsletter]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
