<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202103_DSS_Application_Email.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Advanced Notice - New Mobile Applications Versions Coming March 30</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customers, 

We’re committed to helping our customers/partners maintain the security of our products and their aircraft and frequently provide software updates for existing, fielded products to keep pace with current technological advances. We will be rolling out a new version of our mobile applications starting on Monday, March 29 at 11:59 p.m. PDT / Tuesday, March 30 at 7:59 a.m. UTC. 

 After this date, the following versions of the mobile applications will be taken offline. 






Mobile Application


Discontinued Version




IDM


iOS v4.0.6 – v4.0.5




IDM


Windows v4.0.7 – v4.0.0




Data Manager


Windows v4.7.0 or earlier




OneNav+


Windows v2.9.0 or earlier




MxAdvisor


iOS v1.1.0 or earlier






After Monday, March 29, if you are using any of the applications referenced above, you will be required to update to a version listed in the table below.






Mobile Application


Versions
 Supported


Release Date


Location of Software




IDM


iOS v1.7


Current


Apple Store




IDM / JDM


Windows v3.4.5.4


Current


https://inds.epicinds.com/epic/login &lt;[[https://inds.epicinds.com/epic/login]]&gt;




IDM


iOS v4.0.8


March 30, 2021


Apple Store




IDM


Windows v4.0.8


April 2, 2021


https://inds.epicinds.com/epic/login &lt;[[https://inds.epicinds.com/epic/login]]&gt;




Data Manager


Windows v4.8.0


April 8, 2021


https://ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com]]&gt;




OneNav+


Windows v2.10.0


April 9, 2021


https://ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com]]&gt;




MxAdvisor


iOS v1.2.0


April 9 2021


Apple Store





Note: These applications may be released sooner than the dates above however they will not have full functionality until Tuesday, March 30. 

While this should be a straightforward update, it may cause temporary disruptions for some customers. We’re committed to limiting and mitigating any issues. We’re letting you know now so you have time to prepare and we’ll also provide you with a standard email notification that you can use to let your people and network know about the change. 

If you have any questions, please let a INDS/Honeywell contact know. As always, thank you for your business. FAQs will be provided at the following link: https://ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com]]&gt;.

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Team 

fsstechsupport@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:fsstechsupport@honeywell.com]]&gt;
1-800-601-3099 
602-365-3099 Option 2 then option 1</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
