<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Anniston3_Aug25_2017.Anniston3_Aug25_2017</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New Update on our Anniston, Alabama Site Recovery</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer,
 
Again, thank you for your patience as we continue our efforts to ensure our Anniston, Alabama facility is operating soon after sustaining storm damage on August 14th. 
 
We received formal FAA approval to repair &amp; overhaul Anniston products at our Tempe, Arizona facility on a temporary basis. These repairs will be covered by Anniston&apos;s FAA repair certificate (Anniston 8130 RTS tags).
 
Our Tempe facility will repair units under the Anniston FAA repair certificate until Anniston is fully operational.  
 
What this means for you:



	- If the MyAerospace Repair Capabilities application &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; indicates that Anniston has repair capability, please send your units to Anniston for repair. The Anniston team will determine whether your unit will be re-directed to Tempe and repaired under the Anniston quality system in order to meet customer turn-around-time needs.  
	- If you have already sent a unit to the Tempe facility for repair and your PO is addressed to Tempe, we will process your unit under the Tempe quality system.







Our plan to resume work on customer units that were already in process before the storm is still on track for August 30th through September 5th. And, we still plan to receive new customer units for repair at Anniston starting September 5th. Estimated ship dates will be available by September 8th for units that are already in the repair process. 
 
We will provide another update on or before September 5th. If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell account leader. If you do not know who that is, please visit the MyAerospace contact-us page &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;.
 
Again, thank you for your patience and working through this with us.
Thank you for your business,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
