<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>JetCity Engineering.HAPP/MPP Mailer - ENG.HAPP/MPP Mailer - English-JETCITY</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Protection Plan for Your Aircraft</subject>
    <textOnly>      &lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;                                                     
Protect Your Investment with Honeywell&apos;s HAPP and MPP from JetCity Engineering


Honeywell Avionics Protection Program

Minimize unexpected travel delays and streamline your aircraft maintenance with Honeywell’s Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP). Over the years, HAPP facilities have serviced over 3,800 aircraft to help operators avoid the costly downtime that comes with unexpected maintenance and lengthy repairs. Protect your investment and get full coverage of your Honeywell avionics.



Take advantage of a fixed-cost plan customized to meet your fleet’s needs and receive:




	- Free exchange units for customers if the part has failed 


	- Free loaners for customer’s that need to fly while their aircraft is down


	- Access to Honeywell’s global dealer network


	- Reduced overall maintenance costs 

	- 24/7 emergency support from Honeywell’s Aircraft on Ground (AOG) service



Mechanical Protection Program 
Protect your aircraft and future travel plans with Honeywell’s Mechanical Protection Plan (MPP). Save time and money knowing your aircraft’s environmental and cabin control systems are serviced correctly by professionals with your best interest in mind. Get a comprehensive plan customized to fit your fleet’s needs and save a great deal of money every year with Honeywell’s Mechanical Protection Plan.

Honeywell&apos;s Mechanical Protection Plan covers:



	- Gulfstream GIV, GIV-SP, GV, G200, 350, 450 and 550
	- Pilatus PC-12 and PC-12 NG
	- Bombardier Challenger 600, 601, 604 and Challenger 605


Choose the coverage that is best for your fleet and receive:




	- Free exchange units for customers if the part has failed 


	- Access to Honeywell’s global dealer network


	- Flexible payment options and fixed-cost plans

	- 24/7 emergency support from Honeywell’s Aircraft on Ground (AOG) service



JetCity Engineering
As a trusted Honeywell Aviation Protection Plan and Mechanical Protection Plan authorized dealer, JetCity Engineering provides their operators with first-class customer service because their team is made up of aircraft owners and pilots. See the difference of working with a partner that knows your aircraft configuration and learn more about how JetCity Engineering can help protect your investment with HAPP and MPP.

Learn More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/protect-your-investment-with-honeywell-happ-and-mpp-from-jetcity-engineering]]&gt;
This message was sent to name@website.com. If you don&apos;t want to recieve these emails from Honeywell in the future you can edit your profile &lt;[[#]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Unsubscribelandingpage.html]]&gt;
Terms of Use &lt;[[#]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[#]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
