<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017 Helicopter Newsletter Q3.201707_Global_Email_HeliNewsletterQ3_SES</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Helicopter Newsletter for Q3 has landed!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
QUARTERLY HELICOPTER NEWSLETTER
Q3 2017
THE Q3 EDITION
The first half of 2017 appears to be strengthening at the core. Most of our leading indicators are showing tangible signs of stabilization- potentially anchoring a healthy recovery in 2018. We anticipate industry momentum to gradually gain steam in the second half of 2017 which will solidify stabilization and return this sensational market back to growth.

In this newsletter, we will update you on:



	- How we have enabled a prominent 429 operator to ‘stay connected’ using our Aspire 200 HDR and Go-Direct services which allow for connectivity from the air everywhere in the world, including over cities, mountains and oceans. 

	- Why the Eagle 407HP is ideal for Law Enforcement missions.

	- Our EASA AW139 STC certification for our Aspire 200 Satellite Communications system.

	- Our enhanced customer portal, MyAerospace, which was anchored around direct input from you, our customers. These enhancements include improved site navigation, the ability to book repairs online and allows customers to track their orders online.

	- Our new multi-phase program to introduce new LED searchlight technology which will be more reliable, use less power and last longer.




As this year progresses, we will be sharing new and exciting product and service enhancements anchored around safety and market differentiation.

Sincerely,
Rick Angelo
Director of Strategic Marketing: Global Commercial Helicopters
&lt;[[1. https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-powers-first-connected-helicopter-circumnavigation]]&gt;Honeywell Powers First Connected Helicopter Circumnavigation 

Honeywell&apos;s Connected Aircraft satellite communications are connecting a Bell 429 helicopter during Canada’s first flight around the world. The father-son team are using Honeywell’s Aspire 200 Wi-Fi system and GoDirect™ Cabin Connectivity services to share their journey and stay connected from the air. Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-powers-first-connected-helicopter-circumnavigation]]&gt; &lt;[[1. https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-powers-first-connected-helicopter-circumnavigation]]&gt;
Honeywell Power Makes Eagle 407HP Ideal for Law Enforcement  
Law enforcement helicopters do much more than patrol the highways these days. They operate in diverse terrains and challenging environmental conditions, performing airborne law enforcement and search and rescue missions that are critical to public safety and homeland security.
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-power-makes-eagle-407hp-ideal-for-law-enforcement]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/aspire-200-receives-first-easa-certification]]&gt;Aspire 200 Receives First EASA Certification 


Honeywell’s Aspire 200 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/aspire-200]]&gt; Satellite Communications system received supplemental type certification (STC) from EASA for installation on the AW139 helicopter from Leonardo, marking the first STC for the system in Europe, covering both the short-nose and long-nose configurations of the airframe.
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/aspire-200-receives-first-easa-certification]]&gt;
MyAerospace Makes it Easy to Connect with Honeywell 
Honeywell’s unique MyAerospace &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.com/]]&gt; web portal keeps getting better. We’ve rebuilt the site from the inside-out using input from Honeywell customers, including helicopter operators, pilots and maintenance chiefs. 
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/myaerospace-makes-it-easy-to-connect-with-honeywell]]&gt;
Honeywell Shines with New Searchlight Technology 


Dramatic improvements in searchlight technology promise to deliver better performance, enhanced safety and lower cost of ownership for commercial helicopter operators. Honeywell Aerospace is on the leading edge of this evolution. 
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/honeywell-shines-with-new-searchlight-technology]]&gt;
The Dawn of the Connected Helicopter Brought to You by Honeywell


Connectivity is everywhere – in our offices, in our homes, and now in the air. Being airborne is no longer an excuse for being out of touch. Connectivity is no longer a luxury; it’s a mission-critical capability for helicopter operators. 
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/july/the-dawn-of-the-connected-helicopter-brought-to-you-by-honeywell]]&gt;
Check out our Health and Usage Monitoring System (HUMS) Infographic



Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/~/media/aerospace/files/infographics/hums-ig.pdf]]&gt;
Upcoming Helicopter Shows and Events 


NBAA  &lt;[[https://www.nbaa.org/events/bace/2017/]]&gt;

Air Medical Transport Conference &lt;[[http://aams.org/events/amtc/]]&gt;

Helicopter Association of Canada &lt;[[http://www.h-a-c.ca/convention.html]]&gt;

HAI Heli-Expo &lt;[[http://heliexpo.rotor.org/?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTURneFpXSTNPRGMyTjJFeiIsInQiOiJHZmZOSFNlS0JxYWY3Y0JFQTU5MHpZUCtQTzdtbU13a1kwenVyZXIwU2JKXC9PeHVCU1VyYXNQcVBPNkpET1FyMlpEc2ZtaHRkc1N5aEFOWDVIQVpxQ0E9PSJ9]]&gt;
Subscribe to the Honeywell Aerospace Newsletter
 
Subscribe now and we will keep you updated on latest helicopter news and information.



CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
