<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>210708_EMEAI_ExecuJet(SA)_Aspire200/KingAir_NJM.201708_EMEAI_ExecuJet(SA)_Aspire</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Fly like you Live – Connected. Aspire 200 for the King Air</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear {{lead.Salutation:default=edit me}} {{lead.Last Name:default=Valued customer}},

INTRODUCING ASPIRE™ 200 for the KING AIR
The Aspire 200 SwiftBroadband Satcom is Honeywell’s most economical connectivity solution offering high speed data capability. Designed as a compact, lightweight Satcom solution for smaller business and general aviation aircraft, the Aspire 200’s high level of performance and two antenna options make it the ideal choice for the King Air aircraft. With Aspire 200 your cabin voice and data connectivity needs are delivered with a single-channel of SwiftBroadband service.
Aspire 200 will soon be available for the King Air fleet through Honeywell authorized dealers including ExecuJet South Africa. Upgrading your aircraft with an Aspire 200 solution provides your passengers with a means to remain connected, vital in today’s ever-connected world. Passengers can use the system from the moment they board the aircraft until they disembark and therefore they are never out of touch from the office, family or friends. We expect demand for the Aspire 200 to be high, we therefore recommend you contact us immediately to confirm your interest and avoid disappointment.
KEY FEATURES &amp; BENEFITS:


	- Most economical connectivity solution with high speed data. Crystal clear communications from multiple sources. 
	- Lease options available providing hardware at nominal cost on a monthly GoDirect service
	- 2 Antenna options as well as an optional HDR upgrade allows Aspire 200 to meet data requirement needs for all markets
	- Honeywell provides worldwide support through HAPP and SPEX plans to minimize downtime
	- The satellite-based Aspire 200 works on the ground, below and above 10,000 feet, meaning pilots, crew and passengers stay connected at all times


Through ExecuJet South Africa, operators across the continent now have access to Honeywell’s GoDirect Airtime &amp; Connectivity Solutions – the only complete satellite communications offering for both the cabin and cockpit. 

Warwick Stone
MRO Business Development Manager
 ExecuJet Aviation Group (South Africa) 






CLICK HERE TO FIND OUT MORE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/ExecuJetSA_Aspire200.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
