<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Amer_HCE_Forge_Email_Jet-ConneX-Overage.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>JX Overage Implementation - Effective February 1, 2021</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 During the past several months, we have made it our mission to keep you informed about a new monthly overage charge that Inmarsat will be implementing to all service accounts that exceed their allocated data limits. Overages will appear on your April 2021 invoice. 

 In preparation for this policy change, the Honeywell Forge team has developed advanced data management tools to help you manage your data allotment each month. In addition to these tools, we will have incorporated to all service accounts your total data used for the previous month and will appear inside your monthly invoice.

To learn about these advanced data management tools and how to enable them click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/overage-honeywell-forge?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;. 

 HOW HONEYWELL IS HELPING YOU AVOID OVERAGES:  



	- Starting on February’s invoice, customers will see a line item for overage and data carryover considerations for January usage (if applicable). Until the April invoice, we are just showing you what your carryover and overage amount would have been, you will not be charged.
	- On the March invoice, you will see carry over from January and February usage to help you determine if overages would have applied. Overages will not be billed for this invoice.
	- Starting on April’s invoice, overages will be billed if applicable.
	- You can set up alerts in the Honeywell Forge dashboard once a threshold of data is used. Our support team, Inside Sales, or your Field Service Engineer are available anytime to help and explain how this works. If you previously had notifications set up, your custom configurations will not change.


To understand more about the impact of this change, the available data management tools and how the monthly overages/carryover would look like on your invoices, please click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/overage-honeywell-forge?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=21_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; to see our frequently asked questions. 

Our team is here to help. If you would like to discuss overage changes or solutions for your flight department, please contact your Honeywell Forge representative or the number below. We thank you for your business and look forward to continuing to serve you. 

 Thank you, 
The Honeywell Forge Team 

Honeywell Customer Support
+1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 
sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
