<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Americas_Duncan_Primus_Elite_MC.201903_Americas_Duncan_PrimusElite_Email3</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Stop Replacing DU-870 Displays with Spares!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; &lt;[[https://www.duncanaviation.aero/]]&gt;

Frustrated by failures and exchange costs on your DU-870 displays? Stop supporting 
your aircraft with spares that have a limited life span. Instead, improve your vision and add instant value to your aircraft by upgrading to Honeywell Primus Elite DU-875 LCD displays with Duncan Aviation. Certified for Falcon 900EX, Legacy 600, Global Express  and Learjet 45 aircraft, the benefits of upgrading include:



	- Updates cockpit to latest technology with a quick &quot;plug and play&quot; display
	- Removes obsolescence issue facing DU-870 CRTs 
	- Lowers your cost of operation - increases reliability by 2X and lowers weight by seven pounds per display unit
	- Brings a brighter, clearer, high resolution picture to the pilots that runs cooler and creates less heat in the cockpit
	- Operators can replace display units one at a time upon failure or all displays at once
	- Positions aircraft to later add operational features as part of the Primus Elite upgrade such as electronic charts, advanced maps, maintenance pages, optional Weather XM® information, and even 
Synthetic Vision (SVS). 


Plus, when you upgrade one or all of your displays you can take advantage of a limited-time $35,000 trade-in credit per DU-870 display unit (no limit). This trade-in offer is 
only good through 6/30/19, so don’t delay. 





UPGRADE NOW! &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Duncan_Primus_Elite_201903.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_duncan_primuselite&amp;utm_content=marketo&amp;utm_term=primus+elite]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
