<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_2019PricingUpdate_LG.201809_2019PricingUpdate_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Access 2019 Pricing on MyAerospace</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
ACCESS 2019 PRICING ON MYAEROSPACE
Dear Customer, 

You have received this email because our records indicate that this pricing information is relevant to your job function. If your job function has changed and you no longer need this information, please help us update your information in our database. Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Distribution-Update.html]]&gt; to update your information.


The 2019 published commercial spares and universal flat rate pricing catalogs will be available October 1, 2019 on Honeywell’s MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/MZ0X0r0zQ6hmG00Xq0EI0Y2]]&gt; portal. In addition, to help simplify pricing on orders where deliveries extend into the next calendar year, there will be some changes to our standard terms and conditions starting January 1, 2019. You can also now sign up for catalog change notifications on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending]]&gt;.
 
Important Points:



	- 2019 downloadable catalogs &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTldNM09XRXpOREUxWlRCbSIsInQiOiJFRWhcL090YklWb3Q2MEJrczVDNkxPcHV0c0JXZlhmVG45akpVUFdtaVBZQmtrR3M3Uml2ckZlMFRma3lpZVdJOU9lVXFONHQ1SmpjaDVOQmdTQzlMcSt4S0NuVXMwXC9NaThhYmZPUkZoeTdDNXZldUQxTTM2WEpZUlhBaXN4U3JUIn0%3D]]&gt; are available on MyAerospace &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;.
	- 2019 pricing will be reflected when searching for parts or ordering through MyAerospace Online Ordering &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/ordering/OOPriceAvail]]&gt;.
	- The effective date is January 1, 2019 for pricing and updated terms and conditions.
	- New orders placed with a 2018 delivery date should reflect the 2018 price.
	- New orders placed with a 2019 delivery date should reflect the 2019 price.




What are the key changes to the standard terms &amp; conditions starting 1 January? 



	- Spares orders (non-contract) will be priced based on the date the order is accepted.
	- Spares orders (non-contract) may be shipped as soon as material is available, potentially ahead of customer request date.



Your actions:



	- Download the 2019 catalogs.
	- Existing orders with 2019 delivery dates need amended purchase orders (POs) to reflect the 2019 pricing. 
	- Update your internal systems to reflect the 2019 catalog pricing.



	- This does not apply to contractual pricing.
	- Failure to update your system/POs could result in shipment delays.



	- Sign up for catalog change notifications on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending]]&gt;.
	- Periodically monitor the order status dashboard on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTldNM09XRXpOREUxWlRCbSIsInQiOiJFRWhcL090YklWb3Q2MEJrczVDNkxPcHV0c0JXZlhmVG45akpVUFdtaVBZQmtrR3M3Uml2ckZlMFRma3lpZVdJOU9lVXFONHQ1SmpjaDVOQmdTQzlMcSt4S0NuVXMwXC9NaThhYmZPUkZoeTdDNXZldUQxTTM2WEpZUlhBaXN4U3JUIn0%3D]]&gt; to view orders that are held for price discrepancy or missing 
data.
	- If you want to establish a contract with negotiated terms and conditions, please contact your Business Manager.
	- Use the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/qmXQ0G0zq10Zh702I0E100r]]&gt; to review order status. It provides you with 24/7 availability for your order management needs, including parts quoting, ordering, and tracking. View MyAerospace updates and tutorials here &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/CIE00202q07Q0ZGz2r0mX0h]]&gt;.



Thank you for your cooperation in updating your systems to reflect 2019 pricing. If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell Customer Support contact or submit a question &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/VzI0000G7m0X200QqhrE0Z0]]&gt; through MyAerospace. Please also sign up for catalog change notifications on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs#sort=%40fdisplayname2077%20descending]]&gt;.




Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support 
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt;   
 


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/AB0000QI20ZGs0000q0l00X]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
