<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS Newsletter 2014.July 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>July Direct-TO Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Newsletter Title
December  2013 Issue






Honeywell Pilots App

Website Launches Next Month
Honeywell’s new website for pilots is in the final stages of development and testing. Arriving next month, it is designed to work on desktop computers, laptops, tablets, and smartphones. An iPhone® and iPad® app will follow in September.......Read 
More&gt;&gt;








Honeywell Flight Technical Services Q&amp;A
Gulfstream 650 &quot;Block Point&quot; Release Update  
Gulfstream has released ASCs 901 and 018 - which together are reffered to as “Block Point” - for the G650 fleet for in-service evaluation aircraft. This update brings about full functionality and highly anticipated new capabilities for the G650 platform, and addresses various problem reports and nuisance messages... ... &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun_2014_qa&gt;Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun_2014_qa&gt;  







Engine Insights
TPE331 Hot Weather Engine 
Care
Now that summer is less than a month away and indicated outside air temperatures (IOAT) approach the +350 C (+950 F) range, a number of operational factors should be considered when operating any Honeywell TPE331 engine.  ... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun14_engine_insights&gt;  
 





High Speed In-Flight Internet
Inmarsat Launches Jet ConneX at EBACE, Honeywell Master Distributor  
Passengers aboard business aircraft can soon access internet, boasting the same speeds they’re used to at home and in the office. Jet ConneX (JX), the business aviation service powered by Inmarsat’s Global Xpress network, is set to debut in the first half of 2015. It will deliver passengers and operators fast, global in-flight Wi-Fi across land and sea.... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun14_inflight_internet&gt;   
 





Go Direct TM Briefing
RNP-AR 
RNAV approaches have spread rapidly through the United States and are expanding 
internationally as well. There are a few different types of RNAV approaches available, and some have special rules around the design of the approach and which aircraft can fly them. Identified as Required Navigation Performance - Authorization Required (RNP-AR) approaches, rules for these procedures are spelled out by the FAA and EASA, and also by an ICAO blueprint that defines when these approaches can be flown...Read More&gt;&gt;






Mandates Corner
Understanding the Mandates Landscape
With commercial airspace becoming increasingly crowded, safety and efficiency upgrades mandated by international regulatory agencies are a fact of aviation life...Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun14_mandates&gt;
 



Operator Conference Update
Business and General Aviation Operators Meet with Honeywell Pilots
Honeywell’s 2014 Business and General Aviation Operator Conferences have been a great success so far. Operators have been attending their local conferences in large numbers to learn about upcoming mandates, operational topics, and future avionics concepts directly from Honeywell. Program Pilots from Honeywell Flight Technical Services have also been discussing items working their way through the Global Customer Committee (GCC) and soliciting feedback and requested enhancements...Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jun14_op_conf&gt; 
 



Events and Training Calendar
2014 Events and Training
Honeywell&apos;s Flight Technical Services team travels all over the world to bring pilots the latest information on regulations, technology, and Honeywell product updates. Through pilot breakout sessions at Honeywell operator conferences, one-on-one training, entry into service support and live webinars, Honeywell pilots are on a mission to keep operators informed...Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_june14_event_training&gt; 





Questions or comments about Honeywell products or services? Please contact Flight Technical Support. &lt;mailto:FTS@honeywell.com&gt;

Upcoming Events &amp; Training &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_june14_event_training&gt; 
Hillsboro, OR - July 
24
G650 Block Point Webinar - July 28
Singapore - July 29
Guadalajara, Mexico - July 29

More.. &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=gdc_jul14_event_training&amp;mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRomrfCcI63Em2iQPJWpsrB0B%2FDC18kX3RUqILibfkz6htBZF5s8TM3DV1ZBXqFI%2BEEBS7I%3D&gt;. 
 
Pilot Training 
Webinar
Aerospace Technical Support &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/%21ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQzc3UONDTzNQ7zN3AICDA0sjPULsh0VAb6AM7A%21/&gt;   

Direct-TO Archives &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_newsletters.php?flag=all&amp;mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRow5%2FmYJoDpwmWGd5mht7VzDtPj1OY6hBoqILyJK1TtuMFUGpsqOOGRDwcJBJVtzF8%3D&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
