<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017 Helicopter Newsletter.Q1 2017 Helicopter Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Helicopter Newsletter for Q1 has landed!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | Quarterly Helicopter Newsletter - Q1 2017 Issue
2016 proved to be one of the most economically challenging years in this millennium. Fortunately, the year is now behind us and we’re seeing some positive signs of industry stabilization. Specific to new OEM aircraft demand, it’s been communicated that some OEM’s have experienced higher order velocity in the second half of 2016 - which is excellent news. On the aftermarket side, we’ve seen deferments of some differentiating retrofits, modifications and upgrades continue, however, many operators have pushed forward and have configured their aircraft with enhanced safety equipment to comply with mandates and to increase operational capabilities.

Prior to HAI&apos;s HELI-EXPO, Honeywell will be releasing their Annual Buyer X survey, which is a great customer driven barometer of the industry’s near-term outlook. We look forward to sharing the results and are optimistic that 2017 indeed will be the year of industry stabilization.

We wish you a successful 2017 and look forward to seeing you in Dallas for HELI-EXPO.

Sincerely,
Rick Angelo
Director of Strategic Marketing: Global Commercial Helicopters







Join Honeywell Deep in the Heart of Texas for HELI-EXPO 2017

Connectivity, operational efficiency and safety will be the focus of the Honeywell presence at HELI-EXPO, the world’s largest commercial helicopter trade show and conference.
Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/join-honeywell-deep-in-the-heart-of-texas-for-heli-expo-2017]]&gt;




Honeywell Turboshaft Engines to be Featured at HELI-EXPO

Light helicopter operators and aircraft and powerplant technicians working on Honeywell’s proven T53 and LTS101 turboshaft engines will want to spend some time with us at this year’s HELI-EXPO in Dallas.

Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/honeywell-turboshaft-engines-to-be-featured-at-heli-expo]]&gt;




Honeywell Drives Down LTS101 Engine Operator Costs

More than 40 years after its introduction, the Honeywell LTS101 turboshaft engine is still the reliable workhorse of many helicopter fleets – and in demand with good reason.

Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/honeywell-drives-down-lts101-engine-operator-costs]]&gt; 




FAA Approves Mandarin for Honeywell Helicopter EGPWS
Mandarin-speaking helicopter pilots will be able to hear cockpit warnings in their own language thanks to a modification approved by the FAA.
Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/february/faa-approves-mandarin-for-honeywell-helicopter-egpws]]&gt; 





Air Methods Picks Honeywell Sky Connect Tracker
The largest emergency air medical service provider in the U.S. is upgrading its fleet with the Honeywell Sky Connect Tracker III &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/safety-and-connectivity/sky-connect-tracker-systems]]&gt; satellite communications and helicopter tracking system.
Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/december/air-methods-picks-honeywell-sky-connect-tracker]]&gt;






Find Out How HUMS Keeps You Flying Longer
Honeywell’s Health and Usage Monitoring Systems (HUMS) sensors and embedded diagnostic software monitor and communicate the health and maintenance needs of critical components. Listen to our customer Abu Dhabi Aviation’s review of the product.
Watch Video &lt;[[https://youtu.be/sW3QxclOgWc?list=PLH21RF-YmEQSYAlylPw5hpVHfZdZ24rR5]]&gt;








Honeywell and Truth Data Team Up for Better Monitoring
Honeywell and Truth Data are working together to help operators use data from their helicopters to improve safety, performance and efficiency.
Continue Reading &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2016/december/honeywell-truth-data-team-up-for-better-monitoring]]&gt;





Upcoming Helicopter Shows and Events
 &lt;[[worldhelicopterday.com]]&gt;Helicopter Association International (HAI) HELI-EXPO 2017 &lt;[[http://heliexpo.rotor.org/]]&gt; - March 6-9, 2017
Rotorcraft Asia 2017 &lt;[[http://www.rotorcraft-asia.com/]]&gt; - April 18-20, 2017








Would you like to subscribe to the newsletter? You can sign up here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/newsletter]]&gt;.
© 2017 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[ttps://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://m.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 
This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=edit me}}. 
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
