<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201709_APAC_Email_APACHQ_Final_ENG_mih.201709_APAC_Email_APACHQ_Final_ENG_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>FINAL NOTICE - Honeywell International Sarl (Avionics R&amp;O and Mechanical/APU in Singapore) Transition to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd (HISB)</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

HONEYWELL INTERNATIONAL SDN BHD
(1164217-X)
Level 25, The Vertical, Avenue 10, 
Bangsar South City, 
UOA Corporate Tower, Lobby B, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi, 
59200 Kuala Lumpur, 
Malaysia


October 3, 2017


Dear Honeywell Customer, 



Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd. Avionics R&amp;O Site at Loyang and Honeywell Aerospace Mechanical/APU R&amp;O Site at Gul Circle (currently under Honeywell International SARL) transition to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd (HISB) is progressing successfully.

In order to make this transition process as seamless as possible for your organization, we kindly ask you to update the following in your procurement systems latest by October 20, 2017.


	- Update your Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to reflect supplier as Honeywell International Sdn Bhd as an Approved Repair Supplier.




	- The new supplier address for Honeywell Avionics Singapore at Loyang and Mechanical/ APU Gul Circle procurement and accounting transactions is:





Company Name:

Honeywell International Sdn Bhd 
(1164217-X)



Address:
Level 25, The Vertical, Avenue 10, Bangsar
South City, UOA Corporate Tower, Lobby B, No. 8 Jalan Kerinchi


City:
Kuala Lumpur


Postal Code:
59200


Country:
Malaysia







	- The amended “Ship To” addresses for the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Avionics R&amp;O and Honeywell Aerospace Singapore APU and Mechanical R&amp;O sites remain unchanged:









For Honeywell Avionics Singapore Loyang Site:  
 Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
2 Loyang Crescent, Singapore 508976
Plant Code 5253/ Cage Code QB623










For Honeywell Mechanical/APU Singapore Gul Circle Site:  
 Honeywell International Sdn Bhd
C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
161 Gul Circle, Singapore 629619
Plant Code 5252/ Cage Code QC287









	- Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Consignment_Goods_Manufacturing_Final_ENG_092917.pdf]]&gt; for more information.




	- Honeywell International Sdn Bhd default currency is set up to US Dollars for quotations and invoices.




	- If you are based in Malaysia, In accordance with the new Foreign Exchange policy introduced by Bank Negara Malaysia, the Malaysia based customers can only settle their invoices payable to Honeywell International Bhd Sdn in Malaysia Ringgit, unless they receive an exemption from Bank Negara Malaysia. If the current agreement has stated USD as the invoice billing currency, Honeywell International Sdn Bhd can maintain status quo, but the settlement currency will be Malaysia Ringgit.




	- All other Customers out of Malaysia will be invoiced in USD unless the contract states otherwise.




	- The invoice “Pay To” account changes to the Honeywell International Sdn Bhd. 



For Contract Customers Only – All novation agreements or amendments assigning existing contractual rights and obligations from Honeywell International Sarl to Honeywell International Sdn Bhd had been sent to you. We request your attention to execute such novation agreement or amendment as soon as possible.

As we go through this transition, our Customer Support Manager and Customer Business Teams will be working closely with your procurement organization and program teams to ensure that each step of the process is well communicated and effectively implemented.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us through your regular Honeywell Aerospace representative.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
