<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Conducting an A/B test of emails in November of 2015. This is version A.</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Performance Accelerator Email A 11-2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Stop Playing Hide and Seek with Honeywell Service Bulletins</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Flight enhancing SB information. At the Speed of Light… 
Only from Honeywell.

Now, instantly pull up every service bulletin you need to see. And none you don’t. Click Here. &lt;http://performanceaccel.honeywell.com/&gt;
You want to boost your fleet’s performance, dependability, even safety. The problem is, you have to hunt for just the right service bulletins. Honeywell is about to change all that, with the Performance Accelerator – a user-friendly website that finds the service bulletins specifically designed for your fleet.


 


 







Yes. That is your aircraft on the screen.
You’ll access this powerful tool with your existing Honeywell portal login – no need to remember another password. Click on this service bulletins link  &lt;http://performanceaccel.honeywell.com/&gt;and immediately, there they are - categorized by ATA chapter, efficiencies/benefits, part #, downtime – whichever format you prefer.
Or, click and pull back the skin of your airframe to reveal service bulletins by system and/or location. Electronics. Brakes. Landing gear. Avionics. Everything!






The business of aviation transcends borders, cultures, and language. So does the worldwide functionality of Honeywell’s Performance Accelerator. Choose one of seven languages to navigate the site.
Step up your game.
Step up to the quick, customized service of Honeywell’s Performance Accelerator.
Try it now, here &lt;http://performanceaccel.honeywell.com/&gt;. And expand your fleet’s knowledge-base at light speed.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
