<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>New updates for MyAerospace.com website.</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2014 March Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace News  - March 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>Updated Repair Quotes


Honeywell Aerospace is introducing a new, comprehensive Repair &amp; Overhaul (R&amp;O) quote form that provides richer information about your Honeywell repair unit.


The added information will simplify and improve your R&amp;O quote experience by ensuring all the essential unit repair information is available in one document. The changes to the R&amp;O quote form include:



 - Clearer definitions on the “Reason for returns, condition received, customer instructions” section
 - Specific pricing breakdown on the “Detailed estimate on repair unit” section
 - New “CAFE/Findings” report
 - New “Service Bulletin” section that references ATA chapter, if applicable
 - Richer context on “Warranty information”, if applicable
 - Photos and graphical images embedded



Repair &amp; Overhaul customers can now see the new standard, comprehensive quote form from Honeywell Service Centers.
 
Avionics Repair Findings
 
Order Status now has the avionics repair findings report to view/download online. You can now download and view the repair findings form when you click on the Configuration Findings Evaluation (CAFE) link.

 
Label Change Estimated Ship Date
 
In Order Status we’ve made a slight word modification to the label “Estimated Delivery Date” to reduce any confusion our customers may have on the shipping timeline. The new label that will be displayed to customers is “Estimated Ship Date” which indicates the date the product will be shipped. 



 
Technical Publications access for your iPad just got easier.
 
It is now even easier to download a Technical Publication to your iPad from the MyAerospace.com website. Just click &quot;View Publication&quot; and it will download directly to your device. Try it out today!



 
Coming in April Repair Site Locator (ROCAPS) Updates


Honeywell will be updating our Repair Site locator application ROCAPS with a totally new look and feel. ROCAPS can be found under the Repairs Tab &gt; Repair site locator (ROCAPS).  Scheduled to be available April 8.

 
You can search and find by the following information:  



 - Find repair locations by part number

 - Find information about our repair sites such as 
 


 - Contact details

 - Address information





 - License &amp; CAAC certification by part/site 



 - View ATA Chapter
 - Manufacturer
 - AC Application by part number. 
 - Product Information/Third Party Ship details





 
Strongsville Ohio Repair Facility Closure
 
Honeywell’s Strongsville, OH facility is closed and is no longer able to receive or accept product. To find out where your part can be repaired please use our repair capabilities (ROCAPS) tool.  ROCAPS can be found under the Repairs Tab &gt; Repair site locator (ROCAPS &lt;https://www-a.honeywell.com/esource/servlet/com.honeywell.asesrc.rocaps.search.capability.AdvancedCapabilitySearchHomeServlet&gt;).  
 
SPEX customers if you need assistance with locating an alternate core return location, please contact Honeywell’s Customer Support Operations team at 1-800-601-3099, Option 1 or send an email to the corerecoveryinteam@honeywell.com for support.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
