<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_BK_Customer_Newsletter_Apr_MC.202004_BK_Customer_Newsletter_Apr_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AeroCruze 230 EASA Cert, New Product Video Series and More</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Newsletter Vol IV - April 2020

Honeywell will continue to do what we can to ensure you have the product, support and information you need during this difficult time.

For information on how we are responding to COVID-19, please visit the 
Aerospace FAQ page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/aero-covid-19]]&gt;.





NEWS &amp; ANNOUNCEMENTS

 

AEROCRUZE 230 AWARDED EASA CERTIFICATION
This approval opens the doors for over 35 airframes to upgrade their KFC 150 autopilots to increase efficiency and safety within the European general aviation markets. Read Announcement&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/blogs/2020/april/aerocruze-230-receives-stc-from-easa]]&gt;

Please contact your BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; with any questions.




INTRODUCING AEROPANEL 
The technologically advanced, cost-effective, AeroPanel 100 is a feature-rich audio panel system that is perfect for the pilot, the crew and the passengers – each getting their own audio streams when and where needed!

AeroPanel 100 includes the ability to 
pair more than one Bluetooth device at a time, such as a smart phones or video cameras through three types of music distribution modes. Additionally, the AeroPanel 100 can record up to 40 seconds from a selected input, making it easy to play back radio calls and important messages. Find Out More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropanel]]&gt;




AERONAV GPS 
NAVIGATORS
The AeroNav &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigators]]&gt; series offers a full-featured touchscreen GPS/FMS/NAV/COM suite that is designed as a slide-in replacement for the GNS 430 and GNS 530 legacy navigators. AeroNav features a predictive next-waypoint entry based upon its proximity to your current location or the previous waypoint in your flight plan, reducing data entry by as much as 75%. And with the AeroNav tablet app, you can extend the navigation screens on your personal device. AeroNav also includes a unique wireless keyboard to make data entry simple, flexible and within easy reach, and features built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi. Product Details Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeronav-gps-navigation]]&gt;


 

AEROCRUZE 100 AND XCRUZE 100/110 
AUTOPILOTS
If you’re looking for an affordable autopilot for your aircraft, we have the perfect option for you. The AeroCruze 100 is STC’d for Cessna 172, 175, 177, 180, 182, 185 and Piper PA 28 and PA 32, with the choice of three standard-size form factors to fit your panel with minimal panel-revision and expense.

For experimental aircraft, the xCruze 100 and 110 offer the same form factor choices and feature set, and interfaces with the most popular experimental EFIS displays. The compact xCruze 110 autopilot contains a PFD and displays attitude, airspeed, altitude, vertical speed, slip/skid, bank angle, turn rate and track-slaved directional gyro. Find Out More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/xcruze-100]]&gt;

 
   
WEBINARS &amp; TRAINING 
Upcoming: 
April 30, 2020 8pm EST 
“AeroVue Touch Integrated Panels” Join Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and Simon Williams from BendixKing discuss the award-winning AeroVue Touch, including the panel planning process, installation tips and whether the AeroVue Touch might be the right choice for your next panel upgrade. 
Register Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/1272090279735663875]]&gt; 

On-demand webinars: “Automation and the Flight Envelope.” SocialFlight’s Jeff Simon and BendixKing’s Andrew 
Barker and Mariellen Couppee explore the levels automation, autopilots and aligning with the phases of flight. 
View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/eYb46FKXAzoM4dQwP2Up4w]]&gt;
Access code: 850409

Who’s tracking your flights and how to protect your privacy? Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and Roger Dykmann from BendixKing discussed this and more in “Privacy in the Age of ADS-B”. 
View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/xsDShFJY2Z3WQnUTwE9qZU]]&gt;
Access code: 902384

“Five Hours from the U.S. to France in a Bonanza” What? How did Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and his sons accomplish this? Find out the details and how the AeroNav GPS navigator kept them on course.
View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/4XAGurqui4LZPWY8RBScb4?]]&gt;
Access code: 253747

SHOWS &amp; EVENTS

Due to state and local governments current restrictions on public gatherings, in-person 
events and shows for April and May have been postponed or cancelled. 

We’re coming up with ways to keep in touch with you in some non-traditional ways, such as the product and support videos (mentioned above) created by our sales managers and participating in virtual shows and events.

CONTACTS
Find Your Sales Rep &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;
Find A Dealer or Repair Partner &lt;[[https://bkx.bendixking.com/Dealer-Directory/]]&gt;
More Contact Info &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;





NEW PRODUCT 
VIDEOS AVAILABLE! 
Our sales team has personally created several short-form product overview videos (about 4 minutes each) which will be continually updated and included with our monthly newsletter. These videos are being sent to dealers and customers, are saved in the dealer portal and you may also see snippets in upcoming social postings.  If you have any feedback or need further information, reach out to Lisa Watmore &lt;[[mailto:lisa.watmore@honeywell.com?subject=Feedback about sales and support videos]]&gt; or to your regional Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;. 

AeroCruze 100 affordable autopilot: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS]]&gt;

AeroFlight / KI 
300 attitude indicator and KA 310 autopilot adapter: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8 &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8]]&gt;

AeroNav 900 GPS navigator: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM]]&gt;

AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck:
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W]]&gt;

HeliVue Touch touchscreen PFD/MFD display 
specific for helicopters: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA]]&gt;

AeroCruze 230 touchscreen autopilot: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Wotxp12uYggtjrDqR2AN2C? &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Wotxp12uYggtjrDqR2AN2C?]]&gt;

AeroPanel: 
https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/ZuhUyoDWgDVAQRiiNRnvFr &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/ZuhUyoDWgDVAQRiiNRnvFr]]&gt;






CUSTOMER SUCCESS STORY: AVIONICS SALES CORPORATION AND WINGS 
INTERNATIONAL 
When United Wings International first signed on with a charter operator, it had to guarantee the availability of a reliable Wi-Fi system on board. After looking at different options, the aircraft management company, with Avionics Sales Corporation’s expertise, determined that BendixKing’s AeroWave 100 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerowave-100]]&gt; was the best fit because of its small antenna, only-pay-for-what-you-use business model and reliable connectivity on 
the ground and in the air. 

“It&apos;s extremely important to have a reliable Wi-Fi system in a charter jet. In fact, most businesspeople will not even get on an aircraft that doesn’t have a reliable Wi-Fi system.” Watch the Video&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://youtu.be/oWQxKihk_5Q]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
