<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201906_BK_AeroVue_Demo_Stevens_Aerospace_MC.201906_BK_AeroVue_Demo_Stevens_Aeros</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join us at Stevens Aerospace for an AeroVue flight demo July 9 and 10</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

 &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/#reg]]&gt;

Experience BendixKing’s powerful AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerovue-touch]]&gt; in the newly updated Blackhawk Aerospace’s Phoenix King Air B200! Join us for a ground demo or one-hour flight demos with Stevens Aerospace and Defense, LLC Open House events this summer. See for yourself how easy it is to use these products and how they make your flying experience that much more enjoyable.
July 9, 2019
Stevens Aerospace and Defense Systems, LLC – Dayton &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/]]&gt;
 Dayton International Airport / KDAY
 3500 Hangar Drive, Vandalia, Ohio 45377


July 10, 2019
Stevens Aerospace and Defense Systems, LLC – Nashville &lt;[[http://www.stevensaerospace.com/]]&gt;
 Nashville International Airport / KBNA
 707 Hangar Lane, Nashville, Tennessee 37217


BendixKing’s AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck offers these benefits:


	- Lower recurring maintenance costs
	- ADS-B mandate requirements
	- Reduced pilot workload and fatigue, and increases safety
	- Reduced aircraft weight up to 125 LBS
	- Rich feature-set included such as industry-leading SmartView™ synthetic vision system
	- Optional features such as weather radar, XM weather, radar altimeter, traffic alert and ground proximity warning



The Blackhawk Aerospace &lt;[[https://www.blackhawk.aero/]]&gt; King Air B200 boasts the comprehensive Phoenix &lt;[[https://www.blackhawk.aero/phoenix-by-blackhawk/]]&gt; nose-to-tail modification package:br/&gt;


	- AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck
	- XP52 Engine+ Upgrade


	- 31% Increase in Available Horsepower
	- 25% Increase in Climb Rate
	- 311+ KTAS
	- Full Torque to Altitude


	- Fresh Prop Overhaul
	- Fresh Custom Paint and Interior
	- Fresh Inspections &amp; Logs
	- This Aircraft is Currently For Sale



Limited seats are available, so sign up today!

 
We will contact you with details and times upon your registration. Not able to join on those days? We have other dates and locations available in your area; sign up for one today and receive a response to set up your personal demo.






SIGN UP HERE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AeroVue_BK_201903.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
