<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201810_Global_Email_UMB_Transition_mih.201810_Global_Email_UMB_Transition_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Consolidation of Urbana, Ohio Area Sites</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt; Dear Customer:  
 
 As part of our normal business process, Honeywell 
continually looks for ways to better serve customers more efficiently and cost-effectively. After an extensive evaluation, we have decided to consolidate our Urbana, Ohio area sites, moving machining operations from our Russell Street site to our main Rt. 55 Urbana facility and transitioning Russell Street plating operations to a third-party supplier, Hohman Plating, based in Dayton, Ohio. We expect to complete all phases of this transition by the end of 2019.  
 
 Hohman Plating is currently listed on Honeywell’s APSL (Approved Process Supplier List) and maintains their own independent NADCAP accreditation for chemical processing. Hohman Plating will not require any other certifications, qualifications, or regulatory approvals to perform the work. 
 
 In general, this transition should be seamless for you and we do not anticipate any disruptions to your orders. We have established a dedicated transition team to manage the transition process and ensure there is no break in service or shipments during this period. Our commitment to customer service does not wane during a transition.  
 
 We will continue to provide you with updates over the next several months. In the meantime, if you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Honeywell contact.  
 
 We’re working to always give you the quality and the service you deserve. 
 
 Sincerely, 
 
 Honeywell Aerospace 
 
  

If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
