<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Americas_StandardAero_JetwaveObjections_KCR.201903_Americas_StandardAero_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Make the Best Connected Cabin Choice</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.standardaero.com/]]&gt;

Wi-Fi So Good You’ll Forget You’re Flying

Honeywell and Inmarsat have teamed up to create the best connected aircraft experience in the sky. With our JetWave™ satellite communications system and the Inmarsat Jet ConneX Ka-band network, your passengers will experience connectivity comparable to what they’re used to in their office or home. It’s fast, reliable and available anywhere – even over the ocean. 

We’ve raised the bar for in-flight Wi-Fi by giving passengers the ability send emails, surf the web, send and receive large files, video conference and stream live video, whether your aircraft is on the tarmac or cruising at 30,000 feet. 

JetWave and Jet ConneX create an unparalleled cabin experience that keeps passengers connected, productive and entertained. We offer a variety of flexible affordable service plans and the industry’s best minimum performance guarantee to ensure that your bandwidth requirements are always met. And, with Honeywell GoDirect services and applications you can manage data use to control your connectivity costs and still meet the needs of everyone onboard. 

We know you consider lots of factors before choosing the connected aircraft solution to meet your needs today and in the future. With the Honeywell/Inmarsat approach you’re making the value-driven choice that you won’t outgrow anytime soon. 




LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/StandardAero_JetWave.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_stda_jw]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
