<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201907_Americas_CorporateJetSupport_MSP_KR.201907_Americas_CJS_MSP_Email3_AB_Tes</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>3 Reasons to Say Yes to MSP Coverage from Honeywell!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Honeywell&apos;s signature Maintenance Service Plan is like an extended warranty available on a home, car or major appliance. Business aircraft operators simply choose the coverage that best meets their needs, pay an annual usage-based fee, and stop worrying about the devastating impact of an unplanned equipment failure on their operations and maintenance budget. 

Don&apos;t believe in extended warranties?  While it&apos;s true that some operators prefer a &quot;pay as you go&quot; approach to 
aircraft maintenance, this is unreliable and can quickly become unmanageable. Unexpected failures happen and when they do the cost of parts and labor can mount up quickly. Many times, we&apos;ve seen customers spend as much as six figures replacing a component when they could have covered the cost of the cockpit or whole system at a fraction of the cost of the repair. 

Don&apos;t think you can afford a maintenance service plan? Unplanned failures and expenses can blow your entire budget.  With fixed 
pricing plans based on important facts such as flying hours and engine use, you can select the right coverage option for your unique needs.  The Honeywell Maintenance Service Plan also helps take the guesswork out of determining your annual maintenance budget. 

Control your costs and 
keep your aircraft flying. Contact Corporate Jet Support to learn more about Honeywell MSP or request a quote today. 





LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/CorporateJetSupport_MSP.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_cjs_msp&amp;utm_term=email]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
