<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Global_Transition_GR_mih.201905_Global_Email_Transition_GR_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Update Your System to Order Engine Component Repairs by June 14</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
UPDATE YOUR SYSTEMS TO ORDER ENGINE COMPONENT REPAIRS
Dear Customer,
As part of our normal business process, Honeywell continually looks for ways to better serve customers more efficiently and cost-effectively. In November 2018, Honeywell announced the decision to relocate all engine repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) operations at our facility in Greer, South Carolina, to our facility in Phoenix, Arizona. 
 
 Honeywell remains committed to our engine product lines. We plan to continue to support repair and overhaul of the T55-GA-714, 55-L-714, LTS101, and ALF502/LF507 engine product lines for many years to come. 
 
 A review of past orders indicates that you have previously placed production or repair orders for some of these impacted part numbers. 
 
 Which repairs are impacted by this move?


	- This list represents R&amp;O services for rotating components and parts that require outside processing.
	- Impacted parts list &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/BD00SQ2XZ000j0mI0BTqhdG]]&gt;
	- Engine Component Repair Orders


What is the effective date?


	- Effective June 14, 2019 engine component repair orders should be placed with our Honeywell site in Phoenix. See site details below.


How does this impact existing orders?


	- Honeywell will make every effort to fulfill orders that are already in process.
	- We will work closely with all parties to coordinate the repair completion if an issue arises that prevents the completion.
	- For real-time queries about where to send your repairs, see the Repair Site Capability 
List &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/VBIT000GmD0X200QqjdhUZ0]]&gt; on MyAerospace.honeywell.com.


What is not impacted right now?


	- Static components (ie: housings, nozzles, etc.) will move during the fourth quarter 2019.
	- There is no impact to Honeywell’s Original Equipment (OE) production operations.


What has already moved?


	- Engine Repair Orders: Instructions on submitting engine level repairs have been previously communicated. This data is now available on the Repair Site Capability List on MyAerospace.Honeywell.com.
	- LTS101 engine repairs will be serviced by our channel partners Intermountain Turbine and Airwork.
	- T55-GA-714, 55-L-714 will be serviced by our Honeywell Sky Harbor site at the address listed below.


Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems

 Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these 
parts.





Company Name
Honeywell Aerospace


Address
1944 E Sky Harbor Circle


City, State
Phoenix, Arizona


Postal Code
85034


Country
United States





AOG Support 
 
 There are no changes to Aircraft of the Ground (AOG) support. Our dedicated support service teams are poised to assist you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week worldwide. Please make sure you have the required AOG information ready to be provided: aircraft make, model &amp; serial number, aircraft tail/registration number, operator/end-user name &amp; address, location of ground aircraft, next scheduled Flight/Minimum Equipment List (MEL) expiration, any additional details regarding the aircraft&apos;s current situation. 


	- United States or Canada, call 1-800-601-3099
	- International customers, call 1-602-365-3099


If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell representative. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 


Sincerely,
 
Honeywell Aerospace
Visit MyAerospace


 &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Umr805X0qI0QGo02tZ000Zq]]&gt;
If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
