<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_06_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Azevedo_2019_06</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Customer Connect - Ops Conference Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
The Honeywell team would like to Thank You for Participating in the AIN industry Product Support Survey. The feedback given in these surveys is vital for Honeywell to improve the way we serve you and to highlight the most effective ways we can engage with you. Your experience is important to us and appreciate your contribution. -- Rafael
Did You Know?

Honeywell&apos;s ‘Tool Man’ focused on customer service

Field Service Engineer Clark Rodgers grew up with a wrench in his hand. He was one of those kids who loved to tinker with mechanical things, he remembers, comparing himself to “Tim the Tool Man” on the “Home Improvement” TV sitcom... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/june/honeywell-tool-man-focuses-on-customer-service]]&gt;.

The operators conference in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil was a success

Led by Rafael Azevedo, our Customer Support Manager for the Central and South America, OEMs, operators, dealers, channel partners, pilots, and technicians from all over Brazil had the opportunity to meet with Honeywell 
support representatives and learn about the latest product updates and services. Topics engaged throughout the event included:



	- Engine and Avionics updates
	- How to get support from Honeywell
	- Products (RMU upgrades) and Services (GoDirect, MSP, HAPP and MPP)
	- Cabin Connectivity JetWave and Ka Band
	- Connectivity Services (GoDirect, Datalink and Flight Data Services)


If you couldn’t attend this Operators Conference, Honeywell will 
be hosting nine more regional conferences this year. 



	- July 18, Orange County, CA
	- July 18, Minneapolis, MN
	- July 30, Bogota, Colombia
	- Aug 1, Houston, TX
	- Aug 12, São Paulo, Brazil
	- Aug 14, Cleveland, OH
	- Sep 25, Santiago, Chile
	- Sep 25, Toluca, Mexico
	- Nov 5, Scottsdale, AZ


We hope you&apos;ll join us to learn more about the products, services and technical information that are critical to your flight department. Register. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt;

Technical 
solutions for Cabin Management Systems at your fingertips

Cabin Management Systems tech support can be found in MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center: Click here &lt;[[https://honeywellaerocommunities.force.com/SSCommunity/TSSCommunityDetails?id=ka61B000000kB9V]]&gt; or search for article number 13260. Just click on MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; to access the Technical Knowledge Center&apos;s thousands of articles to help you solve technical issues, parts ordering, your order status, and much more.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Rafael Azevedo 
Manager, Customer Support - South and Central America &amp; Caribbean
Mobile: + 55 12 99122-1600 
Email:  Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
