<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202101_Americas_CH_Email_CPDLC_Textron.202012_Americas_CH_Email_CPDLC_DT</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Commit Now to the FANS PM-CPDLC Program</subject>
    <textOnly>Let Textron Aviation and Honeywell Future-Proof Your Hawker 4000 or Citation Sovereign
Textron Aviation and Honeywell are exploring your interest in upgrading the capabilities of your Hawker 4000 and Citation Sovereign aircraft equipped with Honeywell’s Primus Epic flight management system. This solution would enable you to reach standards required for FANS 1/A+ and Protected Mode Controller Pilot Data Link Communication (PM-CPDLC) operation. 
Over twenty $100,000 deposits are still required from operators to move forward with this project to develop a fully integrated FANS 1/A+ and PM-CPDLC solution. If we don’t receive sufficient interest, the program will be terminated and the viability, cost and timing of upgrade solutions for these aircraft will be uncertain. 
Total flyaway cost of the system will be no more than $350,000, depending on aircraft configuration. Your deposit will be applied against this amount and will assure you priority installation scheduling after STC certification. If the program does not go forward, we will refund your deposit. As you probably know, compliance to FANS 1/A+ is already required on the North Atlantic Track Minimum Navigation Performance Specification (NAT MNPS) tracks when using flight levels of 290 to 410. In addition, the European Commission has mandated installation of PM-CPDLC technology as one of the first of several anticipated compulsory upgrades to the datalink systems on some aircraft.  
With this upgrade, you will experience improve departure times, dispatch speed and arrival times, among other benefits. Flight time will be reduced and you will experience fewer delays and improved communications between flight crews and ATC.

Still not convinced? Click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/blogs/2020/12/upgrade-aircraft-communication-capabilities?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_ch_americas_cpdlc_textron]]&gt; and learn three reason why you should consider this upgrade! 

For more information, contact Tom Heck, Service Sales Manager, at 316-761-0161 or tlheck@txtav.com &lt;[[mailto:tlheck@txtav.com]]&gt; as soon as possible. All deposits must be received by January 31st, 2021.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
