<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201703_Americas_Email_AEA2017-E-vite_Reminder_EMPLOYEES_JRD.201702_Americas_Emai</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reminder: RSVP and Connect with Honeywell and BendixKing at AEA 2017</subject>
    <textOnly>Connect with Honeywell and BendixKing from March 13-16 for AEA in New Orleans! 

At AEA, we’ll be showcasing some of our latest solutions in connectivity, maintenance, mandates and cockpit upgrades. Stop by booth #211 to learn more about them and talk to one of our product experts.
 

This year, Honeywell and BendixKing will be sponsoring several training sessions for our dealers, along with a dealer appreciation event on Wednesday evening. RSVP now &lt;[[google.com]]&gt;, or read more about the events we have planned below.







New Product Introduction

 
Join Honeywell and BendixKing on Monday, March 13 as we discuss our latest news related to routers and how it enhances our connectivity offerings. You won&apos;t want to miss it! Event begins at 8:30.




  

Dealer Appreciation Event



Take a load off and have a drink with us with us on March 15 as we close celebrate our dealer network and their success in 2016. RSVP today to reserve your spot. &lt;[[google.com]]&gt;




BendixKing Training Sessions



BK&apos;s Sr. Product Manager, Jeff Kauffman, will be hosting (3) two-hour training sessions on AeroWave 100, KSN 770 and ADS-B solutions. RSVP today to reserve your seat &lt;[[google.com]]&gt;. 






Honeywell Training Sessions



On Thursday, May 16, Honeywell will be sponsoring a 8-hour Satcom training sessions for all Honeywell dealers. RSVP today to reserve your seat &lt;[[google.com]]&gt;.




Learn more &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/tGX0200bQ00qF00ZI0000eE]]&gt; and view a video on these latest enhancements.











© 2017 Honeywell International Inc.
 &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 



Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
