<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>April 2018 Edition.April 2018 Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - April 2018 Edition</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
April 2018
GODIRECT TO YOUR CABIN
GoDirect™ Cabin delivers unparalleled connectivity and functionality, including access to real-time TV, TV on demand, high-speed broadband internet, video conferencing, email, and voice over IP... 





  LEARN MORE       &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/service-listing/godirect-cabin]]&gt;
Honeywell Engineer goes the distance to connect with customers
Connecting aircraft passengers to the internet at 40,000 feet is all in a day’s work for James Lee. A senior product support engineer, Lee is Honeywell’s go-to guy on satellite communications systems for just about anything that flies...

Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/april/honeywell-engineer-goes-the-distance-to-connect-with-customers]]&gt;
Honeywell is keeping your ADS-B upgrade affordable, but you must act now!
Experts predict 50%+ price increases on components and installation! Honeywell has affordable &quot;fly-away&quot; pricing...

Learn more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/NewPricing.html]]&gt;
Operator saves nearly $1 million in maintenance costs with Honeywell protection plans
Deer Jet is enrolling 12 aircraft from its Gulfstream fleet into the Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan and another nine aircraft into the Honeywell Mechanical Protection Plan. Existing protection plans on Deer Jet aircraft have already saved the company nearly $1 million...
Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2018/april/deer-jet-saves-nearly-$1-million-in-maintenance-costs-with-honeywell-protection-plans]]&gt;
Honeywell is more than an 800#. We&apos;re in the hangar with you! Honeywell is making a dedicated local field service representative available in person when you need assistance...

Learn more &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_CPS_Programs_2018_CPS_LandingPage.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
