<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201705_Global_Email_TechPub_mih.201705_Global_Email_TechPub_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important News Regarding Your Honeywell Aerospace Technical Publications</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
FIND MORE ONLINE.
Hello,
Honeywell Aerospace has important news for you. In a continued effort to improve our online experiences, we’ve made changes to the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; portal to make it faster and easier to use. As part of this, we are updating and improving our online technical publication database. This is good news for you and every Honeywell customer. With it, we can keep important information accurate and up-to-date and more efficiently answer your questions.

We are verifying the accuracy of all customer information to make sure we are providing the best possible service. To ensure there is not an interruption in your access to technical publications, please reply directly to this email with the requested customer information below.

We will need your response no later than May 31, 2017, in order to update and verify your customer information.





Your Name




Company Name




Company Address




Phone Number




Aircraft(s) or Honeywell Products Currently Owned/Operated  






Description of Business  
Choose the one that applies: (Owner/Operator, Service Provider, Dealer, Channel Partner, OEM, Part 145 Repair Station, Management Company, FBO, Fractional, Charter, Other)




We appreciate your help in updating this new, more efficient system. Once you’ve had the chance to use it yourself we think you’ll agree this is good news for all of us.

Thank you,
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Email: Pubs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Pubs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;
Web: http://www.myaerospace.com &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.com]]&gt;
Phone: 1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099


P.S. Don’t forget to respond by May 31, 2017. After that date we will be restricting access to only those contacts we’ve been able to verify.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
