<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20190926_Global_Email_Price-Change_AMR.20190926_Global_Email_Price-Change_AMR</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell 2020 Pricing Catalogs Available This Tuesday, October 1</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer, 

 The 2020 published Commercial Spares and BGA &amp; D&amp;S Universal Flat Rate pricing catalogs will be available October 1, 2019 on Honeywell’s  MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt; portal. 

Key Information:  



	- 2020 downloadable catalogs &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/parts-and-repairs/downloads/pricing-catalogs]]&gt; will be available on MyAerospace.com October 1, 2019.
	- The pricing in the 2020 catalogs is effective January 1, 2020.
	- 2020 pricing will be reflected when searching for parts or placing orders on MyAerospace Online Ordering &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Fonline-ordering]]&gt; beginning on January 1, 2020.
	- Download the 2020 catalogs and update any internal systems to reflect the 2020 catalog pricing.
	- Failure to update your system/POs with updated pricing could result in shipment delays.
	- Note that this does not apply to contractual pricing.


Why Use MyAerospace: 


	- Easy access with 24/7 availability.
	- Use the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Fonline-ordering]]&gt; portal for your order management needs. Including: Quoting, Ordering and Order Status.
	- Periodically monitor the order status dashboard to view orders ‘on hold’ for price discrepancy or missing data.
	- At the same location, you can also sign up for catalog change notifications. This sends an email when any of your pricing catalogs are modified.
	- Need help? View MyAerospace updates and tutorials. &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/myaerospace-training]]&gt;



Thank you for your cooperation in updating your systems to reflect 2020 pricing. Please submit any questions &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt; through MyAerospace or contact your Honeywell Customer Support Representative. 


Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support
 Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
