<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Global_CPS_Truffle -Transition_Email_Operational.Email 1 777-Cargo Smoke</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace News About Support of the 777-Cargo Smoke Detectors</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 

As communicated initially in July 2019, Honeywell entered into a licensing agreement with AbelConn to service our cargo smoke detector product line used on the passenger Boeing 777 aircraft. AbelConn, a Celestica company, is committed to servicing these products and is uniquely qualified to address your support needs as the primary source of manufacturing and repair for these smoke detector products for Honeywell since 2016. This email serves as a transition notification for the 777-cargo smoke detector part numbers identified as: 2119835-6, 2119835-7, 2118860-4, and 2119042-1. 

Action required: Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to reflect the new supplier information for these impacted part numbers 2119835-6, 2119835-7, 2118860-4, and 2119042-1. 





Company Name 

AbelConn, LLC 



Street Address 

9210 Science Center Drive



City, State 

New Hope, MN



Postal Code 

55428



Country 

USA



Cage Code 

66886



DUNS Number

17-592-3853



Contact Name

Brad Johnson



Email Address

bjohnson@abelconn.com &lt;[[mailto:bjohnson@abelconn.com]]&gt;


Phone Number (office)

+1 (763)-533-3533



Phone Number (mobile)

+1 (612)-391-0144
TRANSITION SCHEDULE




Request Type
Honeywell Last Receipt Date
AbelConn Start Date
Abelconn Contact Information


Repairs &amp; Overhaul: quotes, orders, order status updates, and AOG support for repair orders
August 31, 2020
September 1, 2020
Mai Vang- Customer Support 
Email: mvang@abelconn.com &lt;[[mailto:mvang@abelconn.com]]&gt; 
Office: +1 (763)-536-3668 AOG: +1 (612)-391-0149


Spare Orders: request for quotes, orders, order status updates, and all AOG requests
October 31, 2020
November 1, 2020
Mai Vang- Customer Support 
Email: mvang@abelconn.com  &lt;[[mailto:mvang@abelconn.com]]&gt;
Office: +1 (763)-536-3668 AOG: +1 (612)-391-0149


Technical Requests: Technical Publications, documentation and other technical inquiries
August 31, 2020
September 1, 2020
Brian Woltman 
Email: bwoltman@celestica.com &lt;[[mailto:bwoltman@celestica.com]]&gt; 
Office: +1 (612) 391-0144




Escalation Contact Information





Brad Johnson
Program Manager
bjohnson@abelconn.com &lt;[[mailto:bjohnson@abelconn.com]]&gt;
+1 (612)-391-0144
Seven Kunkel
Director, PMO
skunkel@abelconn.com &lt;[[mailto:skunkel@abelconn.com]]&gt;
+1 (763)-453-0195
Chris Milano
Site President
cmilano@abelconn.com &lt;[[mailto:cmilano@abelconn.com]]&gt;






To minimize issues or delays with the repair of hardware, customers should follow these guidelines and actions: 

REPAIR &amp; OVERHAUL ORDER PROCESSING 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders received before August 31, 2020.
	- Effective September 1, 2020, Honeywell will work with AbelConn to transfer both the administration and repair of orders received on site after this date.
	- If we are unable to complete your order prior to the cutoff date, your Honeywell Representative will contact you to cancel the order and ask that the order be placed directly with AbelConn.
	- MyAerospace Repair Site Capability (ROCAPS) &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send repairs.
	- Please note: AbelConn has submitted for a Part 145 Repair Station certification and is anticipating to complete the certification process in early August.


Please note: AbelConn has submitted for a Part 145 Repair Station certification 

SPARES ORDER PROCESSING 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill any open orders received prior to October 31, 2020, based on stock availability.
	- If we are unable to complete your order prior to the transition cutoff, your Honeywell Representative will contact you to cancel the order and ask that the order be placed directly with AbelConn.
	- Effective November 1, 2020, all spares orders must be placed directly with AbelConn as Honeywell will no longer accept new orders.


TECHNICAL OPERATIONS &amp; PUBLICATIONS 



	- Effective September 1, 2020, inquiries related to technical documentation should be submitted directly to the AbelConn using the contact information provided above.


Aircraft-On-Ground (AOG) SUPPORT 



	- Repair &amp; overhaul orders: Effective September 1, 2020, AOG support questions shall be submitted to AbelConn using the contact information provided above.
	- Spares orders: Effective November 1, 2020, AOG support questions for new spares orders shall be submitted to AbelConn using the contact information provided above.



If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell Representative. 

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace 
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
