<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018_12_C&amp;PS_CSM_Email_RW.Azevedo_December_2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Hello, it’s Rafael again -- wishing you Happy Holidays and a Wonderful New Year. It&apos;s hard to believe that 2019 is upon us and I want to assure you that I’m here to assist you with whatever you need, so please don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance. Let me also take a moment to say on behalf of all of us at Honeywell -- we appreciate your business and we are privileged to have you as a customer.
Did You 
Know?

Direct Access App is updated to provide 
access to the help you need easier and faster

Use the Direct Access app to reach Honeywell support, including getting status on your open orders, contacting the AOG desk, talking to a technical expert, reaching out to your Customer Support Manager, finding your nearest authorized Service Center, and registering for Operators Conferences. The app can be downloaded for free at the Apple App Store &lt;[[https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/direct-access/id719039616?mt=8]]&gt; and Google Play &lt;[[https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.honeywell.directaccess]]&gt; or from the Honeywell Aerospace App Store &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/apps-by-honeywell]]&gt;. BlackBerry, Windows phone and desktop users can access the same information by logging into 
the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login]]&gt;.

Field Service Engineer Larry Lindsey has customer support in his blood

&quot;If you take care of the customer, everything else will take care of itself&quot;... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/november/field-engineer-takes-proactive-approach-to-customer-support]]&gt;.

Honeywell offers rebates for Preferred Engine 
Operation


Honeywell will pay you for taking it easy on your engine. We are changing our signature Maintenance Service Plan (MSP) to what is believed to be the business aviation industry’s first usage-based protection program... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2018/november/msp-offers-rebates-for-preferred-engine-operation]]&gt;.

Honeywell’s Global Customer Committee Asia Pacific met recently in Hong Kong

The members of the Global Customer Committee (GCC) in Asia Pacific covered numerous topics including “in-region” parts availability, technical 
solutions to support aging aircraft, and duties and customs across regions. The GCC will be wrapping up 2018 with teleconferences in December, and is working on the 2019 dates.

2019 Honeywell Operator Conferences and events schedule – coming soon

Honeywell hosted 2000 customers this year at 60 events worldwide: 44 in the Americas, 12 in Europe / 
Middle East and four in the Asia Pacific region. During these events, customers met with our technical and business teams to discuss the latest information regarding their Honeywell products. We will have new types of events at different locations in 2019 to make it more convenient for our customers. Thank you for your support in 2018, and be on the lookout for our upcoming 2019 schedule.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Rafael Azevedo 
Gerente de Suporte ao Cliente, América do Sul 
Celular: + 55 12 99122-1600 
Email:  Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Rafael.Azevedo@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
