<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS Newsletter.August FMS Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>FMS Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;

Newsletter Title
Issue Number





NavDB Update
Approaches with Flight Path Angles in Excess of 6.0 degrees included in Cycle 1308 Database
Procedures with flight path angles in excess of 6.0 degrees have been restored to applicable Honeywell navigation databases. Inclusion of these procedures is effective with Cycle 1308.... Read &lt;http://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=navdb_update&gt; More&gt;&gt;








Flight Management System Version 6.1 Upgrade Corner
FMS Software Version 
NZ 6.1 WAAS/LPV
The Honeywell FMZ-2000 Flight Management System (FMS) version 6.1 provides better access to more airports, increased safety, reduced crew workload and significant operational 
efficiency improvements... Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;http://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_news_desc.php?art=fms_upgrade&gt; 

FMS Software Version NZ 6.1 Active Leg Preview Function
One of the many new features operators will enjoy with NZ 6.1 software is the &quot;Preview an Active Leg Change 
in Flight&quot; function. Honeywell has received several reports from newly upgraded operators that the functionality... Read More&gt;&gt; 








Global Customer Committee News
Honeywell Goes Right to the Source to find out what Business Aviation Customers are Thinking  
The Global Customer Committee, an 85-member group that includes pilots and chiefs of maintenance from corporate flight departments, as well as representatives of 
large aviation service centers that maintain... Read More&gt;&gt;








Training News
Free Pilot Training 
Honeywell offers several types of free training opportunities to customers. In addition to the free training provided during Entry into Service and operators conferences throughout the year, Honeywell provides online training... Read More&gt;&gt;





Honeywell Flight Technical Services
Operator Conference Pilot Breakout Sessions
The Honeywell Flight Technical Services team hosts breakout sessions for pilots at approximately 15 operator conferences every year, connecting with the operators who use Honeywell products and services every day... Read More&gt;&gt;





GDC Update
myGDC iPad App Version 2.0
The Honeywell Global Data Center has just released version 2.0 of the myGDC iPad app. The app received several upgrades and new features... Read 
More&gt;&gt;





Events and Training
2013 Calendar of Events and Training 
Opportunities  
Honeywell Customer and Product Support pilots will be available at many events this year, including Honeywell Operators Conferences, online Webinars, and 
customer/industry events. Read 
More&gt;&gt;
Upcoming Events &amp; 
Training 
 
8/22 - RDR-4000 Radar for Boeing
9/4 - KSN-770 Functions &amp; Features
9/5- Frankfurt, Germany
9/11 - Dallas, 
Texas   
Online Pilot Training Webinar &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/cpsfltops_training.php?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRow5%2FmYJoDpwmWGd5mht7VzDtPj1OY6hBoqILyJK1TtuMFUGpsqOOGRDwcJBJVtzF8%3D&gt;
Tech Ops Center &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/%21ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJDfU19LNxMTQzc3UONDTzNQ7zN3AICDA0sjPULsh0VAb6AM7A%21/&gt;   

Direct-TO Archives &lt;https://www.mygdc.com/new/static/fms_newsletters.php?flag=all&amp;mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRow5%2FmYJoDpwmWGd5mht7VzDtPj1OY6hBoqILyJK1TtuMFUGpsqOOGRDwcJBJVtzF8%3D&gt; 
 
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
