<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_Americas_Email_BGA_WSJarticle_mih.201809_Americas_Email_BGA_WSJarticle_mi</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Take Advantage of U.S. Tax Incentive for Aircraft Upgrades</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

We Agree with the WSJ – There is a Major Government Incentive to Buy and Upgrade Your Corporate Jet

Have you read the Wall Street Journal’s 
article &lt;[[https://www.wsj.com/articles/tax-change-helps-executives-afford-pricier-planes-1536763868]]&gt; on how you can now write off 100% of new and used business jet purchases and upgrades? 

If not, or you can’t access the article, read on.

Last year the U.S. Government approved a tax code change that allows for as much as a 100% tax write-off for the price of new and used airplanes and upgrades with few exceptions. No need to check your eyesight – that’s right, you read this correctly.

Previously, newly purchased aircraft could only receive up to a 50% deduction, and upgrading or buying used aircraft had fewer immediate benefits.

In the market for a new plane? Want high-speed Wi-Fi in your 
aircraft like you experience in your home or office? Ask for Honeywell and JetWave™.  We’ve got it for virtually every business jet model you can think of.

In addition, Honeywell’s vast portfolio offers a multitude of products and services for your cockpit, cabin, engine, auxiliary power unit and a whole lot more. And again, these upgrades for your airplane can be 100% deductible. Even better, many of our products can significantly reduce your operating expenses by countering rapidly rising fuel costs and reducing delays due to bad weather. They enable safer and faster flying and flight planning, maintenance, repairs and more. 

So give your tax professional a call, then visit aerospace.honeywell.com &lt;[[aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt; and check out all the products we offer. 






CONTACT US &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/BGA_WSJ_Inquiry.html&gt;




Thanks, and happy flying!

Mike Beazley
Vice President, Sales - Americas</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
