<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202011_Global_BGA_Connectivity_Forge_Test-Performance-Based-Communication-and-Su</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Beta Test our new Performance-based Communication and Surveillance Monitoring tool Inside Honeywell Forge</subject>
    <textOnly>We are excited to share a new feature called Performance-based Communication and Surveillance or PBCS monitoring is available inside Honeywell Forge. We would love for you to try this out and tell us what you think. See our list of FAQs below to learn more about this new feature.

 Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)

What is Performance-based Communication and Surveillance (PBCS) Monitoring?
A new monitoring feature inside Honeywell Forge that helps operators almost immediately recognize when they’ve exceeded maximum allowed timing while using 
FANS data link. It provides Performance-Based Communication and Surveillance (PBCS) monitoring data after each flight so the operator can deal proactively with any issues which will help retain the ability to fly the FANS reduced separated tracks in the North Atlantic. 

 What is the value to you?
It provides Performance-Based Communication and Surveillance (PBCS) 
monitoring data after each flight so the operator can deal proactively with any issues which will help retain the ability to fly the FANS reduced separated tracks. 

 When is it available?
We are currently testing the new service inside Honeywell Forge. Subscribers to the Honeywell Forge Datalink Services &lt;[[https://aerospace6.honeywell.com/en/services/aerospace-services/godirect-datalink]]&gt; will be able to access the new PBCS monitoring feature through the Honeywell Forge dashboard beginning in the first quarter of 2021.

 Does this cover all my aircraft?
PBCS is enabled in beta for all of your aircraft that are FANS equipped and subscribe to Honeywell Forge Datalink services. 

 How is this enabled and how do I access this new feature?
If you are receiving this email it means you are FANs equipped and can access this test PBCS feature. To get to PBCS go to your analytics dashboard inside your aircraft view where the new PBCS tile will appear. Data will start to populate as you fly in remote/oceanic airspace and indicate when you might not have met the performance requirements during your flight.

 How do I provide feedback?
Click the CONTACT US question mark in the top right corner of your Honeywell Forge dashboard, then fill out of short form with the subject line: PBCS to provide feedback.

If you have questions, our team is standing by to help. Contact one of our support staff here: (602) 365-6502

 Honeywell Forge
LOGIN TO HONEYWELL FORGE &lt;[[https://bga.honeywellforge.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
