<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201709_Email_Global_MSP_Early Scheduled Maintenance_Customer Email_JRD.201709_Em</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Extends Maintenance Intervals for Engines Covered Under MSP</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
NEWS | Business and General Aviation
HONEYWELL EXTENDS MAINTENANCE INTERVALS FOR ENGINES COVERED UNDER MSP
Dear Valued Customer,

Honeywell will release two updates to extend engine intervals in order to maximize operators’ time on-wing performance. The first update is to Honeywell’s TFE731-5BR-1H series engine intervals and the second update is designed for all other propulsion engines enrolled in Honeywell’s maintenance service plan (MSP).
 
Keeping engines on wing for the full major periodic interval or compressor zone inspection maintenance interval provides operators full protection and the best return on their investment. To reach this objective, MSP requires engines to meet the full inspection interval prior to approval of the scheduled inspection, which is up to 100 hours over your interval, allowable per engine manual.

Honeywell is extending maintenance intervals for the TFE731-5BR-1H engine from 2100/4200 hour to 2500/5000 hours. This change is a direct result from feedback Honeywell received from operators and service centers to extend maintenance intervals.

We continue to refine MSP so that operators can schedule maintenance with our industry-leading service center network while minimizing unplanned maintenance costs. Customers enrolled in MSP can take advantage of new features including foreign object damage (FOD) protection, the ability to sign bailment agreements electronically and the option to use rental assets in regions where they operate. 

Your authorized service center will work with you to reach the maximum designated interval. As a result, this helps Honeywell continue to extend other engine maintenance intervals, balance work scopes, and reliability and keeps your investment economically viable.

We look forward to working with you as we continue to increase the benefits of MSP and other programs alike. We appreciate your business and thank you for your continued support.

Sincerely,

Bill Hurst 
VP, Business Aviation</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
