<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_APAC_AIN_Survey_MC.202006_APAC_AIN_Survey_Email4_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Message from Honeywell’s Regional Lead of Customer and Product Support</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Customer,

 This is to echo my previous email inviting you to participate in the 2020 AIN Survey &lt;[[https://www.ainonline.com/product-support-survey]]&gt; before June 12, 2020. The results and feedback gained through the survey will help us monitor our strengths and successes and, more importantly, identify areas for continued improvement and investment. 

 When completing the survey, please consider some of steps we’ve taken, based on your feedback to make it easier to work with Honeywell in the last 12 months. 




*If you are not able to download the infographic above, please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/CPS-improvements_AIN-survey-APAC.pdf]]&gt;.

 Lately, we have refreshed our solutions to keep passengers and crew safer in the skies &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/cleaner-air-travel]]&gt; during this challenging time, and a regional Virtual Operator Conference is on the horizon to go live in June. To provide some relief to your operations, Honeywell is also taking the following actions effective now through June 30, 2020 for our MSP (Maintenance Service Plan) customers:


	- Minimum flight hours for Engines and APUs reduced by 50%
	- Extended time for returns: Rental Engines/APUs (+7 days), SPEX cores (+14 days)


Once again, I would like to take the opportunity to thank you for your business. Your feedback to the AIN Survey will be taken seriously and our team will use the feedback and comments to identify key challenges that we need to address. Our aim is to get wider local feedback from our region to implement solutions needed to serve you better locally.

 Sincerely,


 Matt Spence
Senior Manager, Customer and Product Support 
Business and General 
Aviation (APAC)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
