<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_04_April.2019_April_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - April 2019 Edition... Vote For Us</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
April 2019
VOTE FOR US IN THE 2019 AIN SURVEY
Every year, Aviation International News (AIN) conducts a Product Support Survey where they ask their readers to evaluate aircraft, engines and avionics products with which they have had experience during the prior twelve months. The survey is released during the month of May. 

As an engines and avionics manufacturer, Honeywell takes this and other industry surveys seriously. All the results are reviewed by our leadership and we use the information to improve our products, services and support. Our goal is to achieve top marks in the surveys and we need your feedback to make this happen. If you’re subscribed to AIN, please watch for and complete the 2019 survey. 

Thank you in advance for your feedback on Honeywell!
Field service engineer gives customers &quot;best of both worlds&quot; 

 

Honeywell’s approach to accessing technical support expertise offers business aviation customers the best of both worlds, according to field service engineer Don Neyhard... 
Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/field-service-engineer-gives-customers-best-of-both-worlds]]&gt;.
Interested in flying Required Navigation Performance – Authorization Required approaches? 
Honeywell&apos;s GoDirect RNP Consultancy meets with business jet operators looking to add RNP AR to their capabilities... Learn More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/march/rnp-ar-operational-approval]]&gt;.
BendixKing AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck offers Beech King Air B200 operators a sophisticated avionics platform

Two crystal-clear primary flight displays with optional SmartView Synthetic Vision and one multifunction display with Interactive Navigation help you safely conquer even the most challenging approach conditions and terrain avoidance maneuvering... Read more &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerovue?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=newsletters&amp;utm_campaign=19_bendixking_aerovue&amp;utm_content=april_bga_newsletter]]&gt;.
How to avoid the dreaded call from the cabin 
 The in-flight Wi-Fi suddenly goes down just when the C-suite passengers want to videoconference with a major client... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/april/how-to-avoid-the-dreaded-call-from-the-cabin]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
