<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Website Form.January Follow Up</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Aerospace.Honeywell.com Follow Up</subject>
    <textOnly>Aerospace.Honeywell.com
Thank you for visiting Aerospace.Honeywell.com. 

Your contact form has been successfully submitted. A sales support specialist will be in touch with you shortly regarding your online request. 

We are continuously looking to improve your online experience. Your feedback is critical to our success. This two-minute survey &lt;https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/B9QJ6L5&gt; will help us expand our digital content.  

All survey participants will be entered in a drawing for one of five  $25 Amazon.com gift cards. 

Begin Survey &lt;https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/B9QJ6L5&gt;

Thank you for your feedback,

Honeywell Aerospace

 Note that your participation in the Contact Sales survey is voluntary.  By completing the survey, you agree to be entered into a drawing for a $25 Amazon gift card and agree to be bound by the Official Rules &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Survey - Official Rules_Contact Sales .pdf&gt; for the drawing.  If you do not agree to these Official Rules, please do not take the survey.  

NO PURCHASE NECESSARY.  Offer ends on October 1, 2015 at 12:00 p.m. PT.  Open to residents of the 50 United States (including DC) who are 18+.  5 winners will each receive a $25 Amazon gift card.  Winners notified by email on or about October 12, 2015.   Sponsor: Honeywell Aerospace Communications, 1944 East Sky Harbor Circle North, Phoenix, Arizona 85034.  See [https://pages3.honeywell.com/Website-Form_Drawing-Rules.html] for details and odds.
This email was sent by: Honeywell Aerospace

1944 E. Sky Harbor Circle Phoenix, AZ 85034 USA
We respect your right to privacy - view our policy &lt;http://click.e-honeywell.com/?ju=fe23177376600379721277&amp;ls=fdf41271726200787517727c&amp;m=fefc1575766002&amp;l=fe5d15747367077b7113&amp;s=fde815787361007471137472&amp;jb=ffcf14&amp;t=&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
