<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>BGA Messages.BGA UFR TAT Customer Letter 03.27.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Repair Turnaround Time Policy</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Aerospace Repair Turnaround Time Policy
Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
 
MicrosoftInternetExplorer4          
 

Dear Honeywell Service Center and Authorized Dealer Network, 

Honeywell Aerospace is dedicated to providing you with the best possible repair services, and to making every interaction with our organization as easy for you as possible. 


With that in mind we have made a modification to the Repair &amp; Overhaul ordering screen displayed on the Honeywell portal &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt;. Now when you place a Repair &amp; Overhaul order, you have clear visibility to standard turnaround times* (TAT) for flat rate repairs during your price and availability search.

Improving the TAT visibility allows you to quickly see the estimated time frame needed for Honeywell to perform your repair and to help you plan the return of your part to service. 

If the repair time doesn&apos;t meet your schedule, check out the price and availability in the Honeywell exchange and/or rental program. Exchange and rental information is available by checking the inquiry box in &quot;Request for Price and Availability.&quot; If required, additional information is available at:

 Email:   SPEX-BGAorders@Honeywell.com
 Phone: 1.800.601.3099 (US) or 1.602.365.3099 (International)
 Select #1 (Spares) and #1 (SPEX)

Best regards,

Honeywell Aerospace   

* Exclusions to the standard turnaround times for flat rate repairs include:



 - Any applicable contractual TAT requirements current in place do take precedence. Utilization of flat rate repair prices on your purchase order indicates your acceptance of Honeywell&apos;s Repair and Overhaul Terms and Conditions. 
 

 - Maintenance Periodic Inspection/Core Zone Inspection parts. Please download the 2015 B&amp;GA Repair Catalog on the MyAerospace customer portal &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt;.
 

 - Fast Shop parts. Please download the 2015 B&amp;GA Repair Catalog on the MyAerospace customer portal &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt;.



Watch a short tutorial on how to locate Repair pricing and Turnaround Time information.  &lt;customers how to locate repair pricing and TAT info.&gt;

 


Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
