<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Customer Experience (CX).CX New Hire Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The Power of Customer Feedback</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Here’s how.

It’s the simplest, most powerful rule of business – if you’re selling to a customer, you give ‘em what they want.
In the last Honeywell Customer Experience Team email, we shared the top-three things customers expect from our company. Now, let’s take an in-depth view of what they’re looking for.
Customer Support: OEM surveys said they wanted immediate attention from someone qualified to answer their question when they called. So Honeywell completely rebuilt our technical service call center to eliminate hand-offs and immediately connect customers with Honeywell experts. We increased the average tenure of the tech staff from 8-20 years, and provide true 24X7 service.
Delivery: To help guide customers through the time and cost intensive period after taking possession of a new platform, Honeywell created the Entry Into Service (EIS) Team. A unique offering in the industry, EIS supports new platform owners with training, operational guidance, and trouble shooting.
Communication: Finding information on Service Bulletins is a painstaking experience, customers told us. So we’re changing that. Instead of sifting through every SB or RMU currently available for every platform, AT&amp;Rs Performance Accelerator &lt;http://performanceaccel.honeywell.com&gt; automatically searches for and displays information that pertains to the client’s fleet.








These are just some of the things we’re doing as a company to meet the expectations of our best customers. In our next emailing, the Honeywell Customer Experience team will offer a few suggestions on working with customers who may not be in the best of moods.
Let us know your needs.
The Honeywell Customer Experience Team is on your team.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
