<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_Production_TM.201903_Global_Email_FlightBagPro_</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>New GoDirect Website Launches Today</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yJOzBIINlH0&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
We’ve launched our new GoDirect™ Flight Planning website and we’re excited to introduce you to our new look! We are thrilled to bring a new user experience that makes creating, computing and filing flight plans faster, easier and more accurate than ever before.  


Here’s what you can expect next time you login: 

• New look and flow for flight planning pages.
• Release version 1.8 for GoDirect Flight Bag Pro. (Available now in the Apple App Store)
• Flight 
plans that sync across both our GoDirect™ Flight Planning website and GoDirect Flight Bag Pro app.
• Provide navigation for easy access to the GoDirect Cabin website.

Here are some of the benefits you will see:

• The use of flight management system (FMS) algorithm’s in conjunction with original equipment manufacturer (OEM) performance data for more accurate flight planning performance calculations.
• 4D flight planning optimization which considers time when creating a route.
• More Eurocontrol flight plans cleared as filed using our new B2B connection.
• Improved 
efficiency with route overlays, mapping and tracking to plan routes that match your goals. 
• Added benefit for GoDirect Cabin customers, new navigation has quick links to cabin connectivity website without the need to log in again.

To try the new user experience powered by our Honeywell Flight 
Planning Engine – login using your same credentials and start planning!  

*For your convenience, access to classic MyGDC will still be available, just look for the link in the new website footer. Over the next several months, we will start phasing out the old website and MyGDC app. 

Have questions? We are here to help! Just hit reply. 
More information and release notes can be accessed HERE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/GoDirectFlightPlanning_ReleaseNotes.html]]&gt;. 





START PLANNING &lt;[[flightservices.honeywell.com]]&gt;




Thanks from your GoDirect Flight Services Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
