<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GAM SAP Projects.CGM Singapore 90 Day Contract Customers</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Singapore-Loyang Site Transition</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte.Ltd.
2 Loyang Crescent
508976 Singapore 


June 29, 2015
 

Dear Honeywell Customer, 

As a follow up to our letter dated April 14th, we would like to assure you that Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd. (Avionics R&amp;O Site at Loyang site), is progressing with the transition to the Honeywell International Sàrl (HIS) organization. This change will simplify the way in which you conduct business with Honeywell and deliver a more efficient and effective procurement experience.

As an extension of the existing business environment and structure, the business activity currently linked with the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd facility (Avionics R&amp;O Site at Loyang site), will transition to Honeywell International Sàrl, currently targeted for October 2015. 

We appreciate your understanding and cooperation for a seamless transition for you and your organization. As a reminder, here are the steps you will need to take:



 - Update your Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to reflect the new Honeywell International Sàrl (HIS) legal entity. 

 



 - The new supplier address for the Singapore Loyang procurement and accounting transactions is:
 
 Honeywell International Sàrl
 Aerospace R&amp;O
 Z.A. La Pièce 16,
 1180 Rolle, Switzerland
 
 

 - The amended “Ship To” address for the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Avionics R&amp;O site is:
 
 Honeywell International Sàrl
 C/O Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd.,
 2 Loyang Crescent
 508976 Singapore





 - Execute an Amendment Agreement to assign Contracts, to include HIS and delete HASPL/HAPL from Contract, to amend Bank details, delivery/export clauses, where required. Our Contracts team has been in contact with your company to provide additional information to complete this action. 



As we go through this transition, we want to assure you that we have your best interests in mind and we will provide additional details 60, 30 and 5 days prior to October 2015. We have also attached a frequently asked questions &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Singapore FAQs 06.27.2015.pdf&gt; document on this transition.

For your information, concurrently as a separate project, we are enhancing the SAP software at other R&amp;O sites in August and October 2015. The August transition will include sites in Tempe, Arizona; Wichita, Kansas; Basingstoke, UK, and Shanghai, China. The October transition will include sites in Renton, Washington; Rocky Mount, North Carolina; Toulouse, France, and Tucson, Arizona. We are providing updates to our customers who conduct business at these sites.

If you have any further questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager. 

Yours Sincerely,



Heath Patrick
Vice President 
Customer &amp; Product Support
Honeywell Aerospace

Chinese translation letter &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/HON Aerospace CGM Singapore - 90 day Letter translation Contract.pdf&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
