<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>EBACE14.EBACE 14 Customer Mailing - Possibilities</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Discover the Possibilities of Flight with Honeywell at EBACE 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Discover the Possibilities of Flight @ EBACE 2014

 
 Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Customer}},
  Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
          
MicrosoftInternetExplorer4          
         
For 100 years, Honeywell has been a pioneer in aerospace. As we celebrate our centenary, we continue to innovate and integrate thousands of products and services to advance and deliver safe, efficient, productive and comfortable aviation experiences worldwide.
We invite you to join us during EBACE 2014, taking place from May 20th - 22nd at the Palexpo Convention Centre in Geneva, and meet with our leadership and regional team to discover how our technologies enable the business aviation industry to realise the Possibilities of Flight.
Our booth, which is located on stand number 6622, Hall 6 will showcase a number of our innovative products including:



	- 

Ovation SelectTM – our high definition cabin management system which delivers high flying productivity and entertainment






	- 

Primus Epic – the only business aviation flight deck certified with Honeywell’s award winning SmartViewTM synthetic vision system






	- 

Primus Elite  - the ultimate ‘glass’ cockpit delivers LCD resolution screens for enhanced situational awareness and safety






	- 

Satcom – Honeywell has a suite of satcom solutions including our new JetWave (ka band) hardware to ensure that business doesn’t stop after take off



In addition, our team will be on hand to answer any questions you might have regarding our aftermarket solutions include Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP), Maintenance Services Plans (MSP) for engines and APU’s. 
To ensure that the relevant Honeywell representative is available to answer your queries, please use the EBACE Meeting Request Form.
We look forward to welcoming you to EBACE 2014.
  Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
                      
          
    
            
                  
                                                                        
                   
              
                        
     
          
                                                                                         
      
Book a meeting &gt; &lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/landing-pages/bga/ebace-14&gt;
  Normal 0    
 false false false  EN-US X-NONE 
X-NONE          
    MicrosoftInternetExplorer4
&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/landing-pages/bga/ebace-14&gt;
Book a meeting

Please use the EBACE Meeting Request Form by clicking the button above.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2014 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
