<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>GAM SAP Projects.CGM Singapore 30 day SBU Customers</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Singapore-Loyang Site Transition</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte.Ltd.
2 Loyang Crescent
508976 Singapore


August 27, 2015
                                         

Dear Honeywell Customer, 
As we shared last month, we are entering the final phase of our transition at the Singapore Loyang R&amp;O site. On 27th September 2015, the business activities will transition to the Honeywell International Sàrl (HIS) legal entity. 

Here’s some important information you’ll need to know before the changeover: 




 - Your authorized supplier list should reflect the legal entity/name change – Honeywell International Sàrl. Singapore Loyang repair orders need to reference the HIS legal entity starting on 27th September 2015.




 - Your internal financial systems should reflect the legal entity name change – Honeywell International Sàrl. A transition checklist &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Singapore CGM 30 Day Checklist.pdf&gt; is available and includes the new supplier address, amended “Ship To” address, and invoicing and payment bank details. 




 - Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd. (“HASPL”) will automatically transfer obligations for all open orders in backlog as of 27th September 2015 from HASPL to Honeywell International Sàrl (“HIS”) and assign all rights and benefits from HASPL to HIS. 




 - With the exception of Contract customers, the HIS default currency is U.S. Dollars for all quotes and invoices.




 - For Contract Customers only: To avoid any delays in service, please verify your amendment agreements are executed. Our Contract Managers are available to help you to finalize the agreements. 


We have learned from past experience that the best way to minimize order disruptions during the system changeover is for us to designate one week without R&amp;O shipment or R&amp;O incoming order activity. 

Therefore, we would like to share the dates and details on how this could affect your orders: 

Saturday, September 26 (5pm SGT) 



 - The Singapore Loyang Avionics R&amp;O site will begin transitioning to the enhanced version of SAP. 


Saturday, September 26 (5pm SGT) – Wednesday, September 30 (5pm SGT) 



 - Honeywell will be unable to process new or existing R&amp;O orders or product shipments between these dates. Orders received during this time period will be placed in a queue for processing on October 1.





 - Orders received before and after this changeover may experience up to one week turnaround delay. 


 - The estimated ship date field in the MyAerospace.com &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt; customer portal will not operate during this time frame, and will not reflect updated shipping data until the changeover is completed on September 30.




 - Any outbound product shipments will be suspended until after the changeover is completed. We may contact you to arrange an early shipment if your requested delivery date falls within the one week changeover period. 




 - For any Aircraft on Ground (AOG) issues during this week, please contact the Honeywell AOG Team at +1-800-601-3099 (US/Canada) or +1-602-365-3099 (International), select phone option #4.


October 1 (8am SGT)



 - Product shipments and new orders will resume at the Singapore Loyang Avionics R&amp;O site using Honeywell International Sàrl (HIS) as the supplier.




 - The system upgrade will convert all existing Honeywell sales orders over to new Honeywell numbers. You will need to use your original purchase order number(s) to locate the new sales order number(s) in the MyAerospace.com  &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt;customer portal. 


If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us via your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, your regular Honeywell representative at the Honeywell Aerospace Singapore Pte. Ltd. (Avionics Loyang) site or send us an email to AeroCPSCommunications@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:aerocpscommunications@honeywell.com&gt;.

Chinese translated letter &lt; https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/CGM Singapore_30 day letter translated.pdf&gt;
Chinese translated transition checklist

Yours sincerely, 

Aileen McDowall 
Region Vice President AT&amp;R Airlines, EMEAI 
Honeywell International Sàrl 

Brian Davis 
Region Vice President AT&amp;R Airlines, APAC 
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
