<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>April 2019.201904_Email_Direct-To_Newsletter_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>April Direct-TO Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
 

Direct-TO |  April 2019
&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/march/pdc-it-s-easy-as-1-2-3]]&gt;
Racetrack Procedures &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/racetrack-procedures]]&gt; &lt;[[https://performanceaccel.honeywell.com/Pilots/Newsletters/2017/Aug2017/IRS1Aug17]]&gt;

A Challenge in Coding

Until now, pilots could expect to find charted racetrack patterns in the FMS database... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/racetrack-procedures]]&gt;

PIREP &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/pirep]]&gt;
When Good Departures Go Bad

This month&apos;s PIREP looks at a rare condition that occurs flying certain Standard Instrument Departure Procedures (SIDs) with the EPIC platform... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/pirep]]&gt;
GoDirect Flight Services Update &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/godirect-flight-services-update]]&gt;
Revamping the Flight Services Website



Through the launch of a revamped website, which includes a brand-new flight planning engine based on FMS algorithms, many improvements have been made over the old “My GDC” site.... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/godirect-flight-services-update]]&gt;
 

Engine Insights &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/engine-insights]]&gt;
TFE731 Ignition Use




To avoid excessive plug erosion, Continuous Ignition should only be used as dictated by the appropriate Flight or Crew Manual.... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/engine-insights]]&gt;



Speak Up in the 2019 AIN Survey

Every year, Aviation International News (AIN) conducts a Product Support Survey where they ask their readers to evaluate aircraft, engines and avionics products with which they have had experience during the prior twelve months. The survey is released during the month of May. As an engines and avionics manufacturer, Honeywell takes this and other industry surveys seriously. All the results are reviewed by our leadership and we use the information to improve our products, services and support. If you’re subscribed to AIN, please watch for and complete the 2019 survey. Thank you in advance for your feedback on Honeywell!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
