<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018_09_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails_RW.Contreras_September_2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Hello, it’s Monica again with some information that will help you get the most out of our products and services. But first, I want to thank you for the positive results we received on the 2018 AIN Avionics Products Survey. My goal is to do even better this year!  I’m here to assist you with whatever you need, so please don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance.
Did You Know?

You are eligible for 100 percent tax write-off for component upgrades

One of the more than 100 changes to the U.S. tax code signed into law in 2017 is that the purchase price of a new and used airplane or cost of all component retrofit / upgrades by a company can be written off 100 percent against its earnings. Install now and save on your 2018 taxes.

Just call Jack

Field Service Engineer Jack Wolf&apos;s job is all about getting customers the right answer as quickly as possible... Read More. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/august/veteran-fse-sees-almost-everything-change]]&gt;


Honeywell showed the most positive movement 
on AIN Survey


Honeywell experienced the most positive gains of all 
OEMs in the 2018 Aviation International News Avionics Product Support Survey. These results, coupled with the recognition of Honeywell Customer Support Managers on the same survey, show that we are making a positive difference for you every day. It&apos;s an honor that you, our customers, recognized the passion and commitment we have in supporting you. 

Stop and visit with us at NBAA 2018 - Booth #2600

The Customer &amp; Product Support team will be on hand in Orlando to 
assist you with issues you may be having. You&apos;ll also see how Honeywell is pioneering the collection and use of data from all aircraft systems to control costs on the ground and in the air, prolong systems viability and performance, and improve safety. We look forward to talking with you there... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/october/HONEYWELL-AEROSPACE-AT-NBAA-2018-PIONEERING-THE-FUTURE-OF-DATA-DRIVEN-AND-CONNECTED-INSIGHTS]]&gt;

Honeywell support ... &quot;simple as ordering a pizza&quot;

Learn why Brad Keselowski, two-time NASCAR driving champion, and Joey Meier, his pilot, are very satisfied with Honeywell... Watch video. &lt;[[https://youtu.be/Q60ijIkuXGo]]&gt;

Upcoming Operators Conferences
Operators Conferences are being scheduled in all 
regions - join us to learn more about Honeywell products and services that are critical to your flight department. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/january/2018-operator-conferences]]&gt;
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Monica Contreras
Customer Support Manager
Office: 1-844-288-7605 ext 0076Mobile: +521-686-216-4453Email: Monica.Contreras2@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Monica.Contreras2@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
