<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ABS Jets.HAPP/MPP Mailer - Russian.HAPP/MPP Mailer - Russian</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>План защиты Honeywell для вашего самолета</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;                                                                       &lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
Facebook      &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;                                                                     Facebook      &lt;[[http://www.Facebook.com/DuncanAviation]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/duncan-aviation]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/DuncanAviation?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/DuncanAviation56]]&gt;
The Citation 560 ADS-B Out STC by Duncan Aviation Features the Honeywell Primus II Radio System




ADS-B Out
 
Fly today with a complete solution and prepare for the future with the ADS-B Out STC for Cessna Citation 560/560XL by Duncan Aviation. By Jan.1, 2020, all operators must have Automatic Dependent Surveillance-Broadcast capability. As a staple in NextGen technology, ADS-B Out increases efficiency, strengthens situational awareness and allows aircraft  to transmit information to Air Traffic Control ground stations by using satellite signals instead of ground radar and navigational aids. As a result, these signals improve tracking and give the pilot a clear view of their surroundings – allowing them to see what Air Traffic Control sees.

Under Duncan Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out STC# ST01810W, operators can take advantage of:




 - Reduced separation and highly accurate departure and arrival times


 - Surveillance in areas that do not currently have radar coverage 


 - A clear view of vehicles and runways in order to avoid collisions or delays 

 - More efficient spacing and optimal routing in non-radar environments, including the busy airspace in the Gulf of Mexico, mountainous regions of Colorado and the lower altitudes of Alaska.


Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio System
When you upgrade your existing Honeywell Primus® II Radio and add a stand-alone GPS receiver, you’ll enjoy a cost-effective solution combined with the latest configuration to meet the ADS-B Out mandate. Fly with confidence with Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio equipped with a Mode C or Mode S Transponder to fulfill ADS-B Out requirements and ensure your future travel plans.


Duncan Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out Program

Upgrade your Citation 560/560XL with an integrated solution at any Duncan Aviation maintenance facility: Lincoln, Nebraska; Battle Creek, Michigan; Provo, Utah; or at any of their satellite shop locations throughout the United States*.
Learn More &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/ADS-BOutCampaign_6.1SoftwareUpgrade.html]]&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
