<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_GreerLTS101_lg.201903_GreerLTS101_email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Update Your Systems to Order LTS101 Engine Repairs</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer, 
As part of our normal business process, Honeywell continually looks for ways to better serve customers more efficiently and cost-effectively. After an extensive evaluation, we have decided to move all repair and overhaul operations from our Greer, South Carolina facility. The transition which includes the LTS101 engine product line is expected to be complete later this summer. 
Moving forward, repair and overhaul services for the LTS101 engine product line will be provided by our authorized channel partners listed here &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/HoneywellAuthorizedServiceCenters_LTS101EngineRepair.pdf&gt;. Honeywell remains committed to the LTS101 engine product line and we plan to continue to support repair and overhaul on LTS101 engines through our channel partner network for many years. This information only affects aftermarket repair and overhaul services. There are no planned changes to the production line.
A review of past orders indicates that you have placed production or repair orders for impacted 
 &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/LTS10_PartNumbers_Feb2019.pdf]]&gt;LTS101 engine  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/LTS10_PartNumbers_Feb2019.pdf]]&gt;part numbers &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/LTS10_PartNumbers_Feb2019.pdf]]&gt;. To minimize issues or delays, please follow these guidelines and actions: 

Original Equipment Orders: There is no change to placing 
original equipment orders. 
 
Engine Component Repair Orders: 



	- At this time, there is no change to engine component repair orders. 
	- Later in the transition, we will provide specific direction about the component repair location. 



New Engine Repair Orders: 


	- Effective immediately, all LTS101 engine repair orders should be placed with 
one of our Honeywell 
Authorized Service Centers &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/HoneywellAuthorizedServiceCenters_LTS101EngineRepair.pdf&gt;.  
	- This notice is for engine repairs only.
	- For real-time questions about where to send your repairs, please access the MyAerospace &lt;http://www.myaerospace.honeywell.com&gt; Repair Site Capability list.


Existing Engine Repair Orders:  Honeywell will make every effort to fulfill orders that are already in process with no impact to you. If an issue arises that prevents this, we will work closely with all parties to coordinate the repair completion.  
 
Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems
Please update your authorized supplier list and internal systems to include the supplier information &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/HoneywellAuthorizedServiceCenters_LTS101EngineRepair.pdf&gt; for this equipment. 
 
AOG Support:  Please contact one of the Honeywell Authorized Service Centers listed above if you need AOG repair assistance.
If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell representative. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve.
To stay in the loop with us, please click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Subscription_Page.html]]&gt; to confirm that you agree to receive all forms of e-communications such as e-mail, social media and digital advertising.





Sincerely,
 
Honeywell Aerospace
Visit 
MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Umr805X0qI0QGo02tZ000Zq]]&gt;




If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
