<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201703_Global_Email_Honeywell Channel Newsletter_JRD.201703_Global_Email_Channel</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2017 Q1 Honeywell Channel Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HONEYWELL CHANNEL NEWSLETTER
Q1 2017
Get the latest news from Honeywell’s Q1 2017 Channel Newsletter.
Honeywell Aerospace Dealer LinkedIn Group 
 
Get STC updates, network with other Honeywell channel partners and stay up to date with the Honeywell Aerospace Dealer LinkedIn Group. Click here &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/groups/12014354]]&gt; to join today.
Excess APU/Engine Inventory 
 
Do you need an engine or an APU for an upcoming operator visit? Click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2017_ERBexcesslist.html]]&gt; to view our latest engine and APU inventory.
Tackling the Top 10 Most Challenging U.S. Airports  
 
Every region has airports which provide pilots with a real challenge. Fortunately, Honeywell products and services are here to help pilots navigate through these challenging conditions to ensure a safe landing every time. The following article looks at our portfolio of solutions that are designed to help pilots fly into 10 of the most challenging U.S. airports. Read the full article here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/march/tackling-the-top-10-most-challenging-us-airports]]&gt;.
Take a Flight with Honeywell: Business Aviation 
 
Are your operators visual learners? If so, Honeywell’s latest video gives customers an in-depth view of its solutions and how they work across different sizes of business aviation platforms. Watch the video here &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DRB-1-Zxab4]]&gt;.
Q2 HAPP and DU-875 Promotion for Channel Partners 
 
Honeywell’s HAPP team has created an exclusive offer for Learjet 40 and 45 operators. For a limited, you can help your operators save money on a new HAPP program and receive a 20% margin while doing it. For more information on this exclusive offer, click here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2017_HAPP_Dealer.html]]&gt;.
EMEAI Operator Conference Summary 
 
Honeywell held a business aviation operator conference on March 9 and 10 in Prague, Czech Republic. 
Read more about the conference and what was discussed here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/2017 EMEAI Channel Conference.pdf]]&gt;.
Honeywell Channel Marketing Team 
 
In 2017, Honeywell has added additional marketing resources to help its channel partners sell Honeywell products and services more efficiently. Meet the team &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/service-listing/channel-partner-services]]&gt; and contact your local representative to start your next marketing campaign today.
Q1 STCs 
 
For more information, or to see a full list of FAA and EASA STCs approved in Q1, please visit the Honeywell Aerospace Dealer LinkedIn group &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/groups/12014354]]&gt;.
Do you know someone who should be added to the Honeywell Channel Newsletter distribution list? Sign them up here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Honeywell-Channel-Newsletter-Subscription.html]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
