<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201902_Americas_Email_DU-875_Upgrade_MC.201902_Americas_Pentastar_DU875_Email2_k</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Display Failures and Exchange Costs Got You Down?</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Frustrated by failures and exchange costs? Stop supporting your aircraft with DU-870 spares that have a limited life span and are not supported under the Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP). Instead, improve your vision and add instant value to your aircraft by upgrading to Honeywell DU-875 LCD displays with Pentastar Aviation, an authorized Honeywell Avionics Dealer.    Replace one or all of your old CRT DU-870 displays and receive the 
many benefits that come with this easy upgrade, including:



	- Reduced cost of ownership with lighter LCD displays that provide a weight reduction of up to 7lbs per unit, that translates to significant fuel savings

	- Increased display reliability

	- 12-month warranty

	- Growth plan that takes advantage of future technologies and applications




Plus, when you upgrade one or all of your displays you can take advantage of a limited-time $35,000 trade-in credit per DU-870 display unit (no limit), plus additional Honeywell Avionics Protection Plan (HAPP) incentives. This trade in offer is only good through 6/30/19 so don’t delay.    Avoid obsolescence and  save up to $210,000* by taking advantage of this limited-time screen upgrade promotion. 






LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/DU-875_Upgrade_Pentastar.html?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=19_ch_amer_bga_pentastar_du875]]&gt;






*Savings are based on the upgrade of up to six (6) DU-875 LCD screens on Global Express aircraft. Ask us about the savings for your aircraft model.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
