<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201907_BK_Webinar_Products_Solutions_Oshkosh_MC.201907_BK_Webinar_Products_Solut</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join us for a BendixKing product overview for Oshkosh July 16 at 8 p.m. EDT</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;

 &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;WEBINARBendixKing Products &amp; Solutions at the Upcoming EAA show in Oshkosh, WI, 22-28, July 2019

 &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/#reg]]&gt;

Attend the webinar, and get 10% off any BendixKing avionics that you may purchase at the show.
Date: Tuesday, July 16th
Time: 8 p.m. EDT


Just like you, BendixKing is very excited to participate in this year’s upcoming EAA AirVenture Oshkosh experience. There are a lot of events at this show and we are expecting to receive many guests at our Pavilion; don&apos;t forget to register to join us for dinner at our popular Customer Appreciation Event &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_BK_Oshkosh.html]]&gt;!

 In this webinar, we want to share with you as to what we are 
going to showcase in our booths and give you the inside scoop before you attend the show. We will discuss our integrated flight displays, navigational systems and a host of other products and solutions, for both certified and experimental aircraft. We will also discuss our advanced technology products, in development, and other activities we have planned for you at the show, including, theatre sessions, guest speakers (including a Reno Air Racer) and the aircraft on display with full BendixKing panels.

 The webinar will be given by BendixKing’s Head of Product Marketing, Robert 
Haim.

 This webinar is produced in association with SocialFlight.com &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/search.php]]&gt;. SocialFlight is a popular mobile app and website that provides pilots with an interactive map of over 20,000 searchable aviation events and seminars. Jeff Simon, President of SocialFlight, is an A&amp;P/IA mechanic, avionics industry expert, pilot and aircraft owner. He has spent the last 20 years promoting owner-assisted aircraft maintenance.

 Your webinar registration includes free access to information on over 10,000 aviation events, destinations, airport restaurants, contests and more listed on SocialFlight.com and the SocialFlight mobile app. 






REGISTER HERE &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/307629459549498381]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
