<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_06_C&amp;PS_Helo_CSM_Emails.Adams_Helo_2019_06</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
I want to connect and send monthly updates to keep you in touch and informed about Honeywell-related news and developments, such as introducing you to our Technical Core Team Leader for helicopter engines, John Sanner.

I am always available, so don’t hesitate to contact me for assistance. -- Deta
Did You Know?


Supporting Customers is Job One for 
Honeywell Field Service Engineer

Helicopter people are a different breed. Just ask John Sanner, Honeywell’s Field Service Engineer (FSE) and Technical Core Team Leader for helicopter engines and military mechanical systems. Sanner’s familiarity with the helicopter industry is exceeded only by his knowledge of rotorcraft and the engines that power them... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/april/helicopter-technical-support-leader-is-a-breed-apart]]&gt;. 

Honeywell’s New Communications Boost Productivity for VIP Transport

One of the best ways to improve productivity in the 
workplace is to improve communications. When people collaborate, they spend less time tracking down information independently and can make faster, smarter decisions. Honeywell has longtime experience in aiding communications to boost productivity. One example, is the new Mission Communications Terminal (MCT)... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/june/three-ways-honeywells-new-communications-boost-productivity-for-vip-transport]]&gt;. 

Honeywell Attended the Air Medical Safety Conference Hosted by HAI

Honeywell representatives participated in the 
Air Medical Safety Conference hosted by the Helicopter Association International (HAI) in Washington, DC in May. The conference included speakers from the United States Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Helicopter Emergency Medical Services (HEMS) operators, and HEMS helicopter manufacturers. Honeywell has three ways to keep your HEMS aircraft ready for any mission... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/may/3-ways-to-keep-your-medical-service-helicopter-ready-for-any-mission]]&gt;. 

Honeywell Hosted an Aviation and Telecommunications Workshop in Mexico

With the support of BendixKing and Diagnostics 
Solutions International, Honeywell offered a one day workshop held in April, in Mexico City. Topics included Honeywell portfolio, connectivity products, customer support, and HAPP/MSP services. If you would like to be invited to future events in your region, contact me at the information below.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Deta Adams
Sr. Customer Support Program Manager
Cell: +1 256-508-2708
Email: Deta.Adams@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Deta.Adams@Honeywell.com]]&gt;
Need immediate support, click below link?
Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
