<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201710_Global_Email_FeedbackWelcome_mih.201710_Global_Email_FeedbackWelcome_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Online Assessment Launches This Week – Feedback Welcome!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

FEEDBACK WELCOME

Dear Aerospace Colleague:
One of Honeywell’s top priorities is to improve the customer experience. Your candid feedback in this survey – along with feedback you provide through OEM and industry surveys – is crucial in guiding our improvement efforts so we focus on improving things most important to you. We have hired an independent research company, Corporate Executive Board (CEB), to conduct an online assessment. Look for the assessment to arrive via email this week.

Your participation in the assessment and the open feedback you share will help us learn more about recent experiences with Honeywell and what is most important when it comes to customer service. We appreciate your timely participation in the assessment, which will remain open for two weeks.

Based on the recent feedback we received from past surveys, we’ve taken action to:



	- Improve your digital ordering and technical support experience through the MyAerospace Portal  &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

	- Provide 24/7 global support, technical personnel visits, and technical expertise for Honeywell products when and where customers need it

	- Enhance communications, create consistent tools, and simplify policies to reduce customer effort so it’s easier to do business with Honeywell 

	- Improve the GoDirect services dashboard, the industry’s most complete portfolio of aviation services and applications

	- Reduce past dues, improve on-time deliveries, offer more exchanges when timely repair turnaround is at risk, and improve our warranty process for more detailed and timely adjudication



Rest assured, no one will attempt to sell you anything as a result of participating in this assessment. The findings will be used to make changes to improve your experience with Honeywell only and the identities of participants will be kept completely confidential.

Beyond our surveys like this one, if you ever have feedback you would like to provide our team, please contact us at AERO@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AERO@Honeywell.com]]&gt; day or night. We would like to hear about your experience with us.





Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
