<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202012_Global_C&amp;PS_Duncan-Announcement_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell and Duncan Aviation - new repair and exchange support</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 Honeywell is pleased to inform you of a new repair services agreement with Duncan Aviation that will enhance support for our business aviation and commercial helicopters customers. Under the agreement, Duncan Aviation will manage the repair and exchange for specified Avionics Content, Flight controls, Electronic Flight Control Instruments, Air Data and Attitude Heading Reference Unit on Legacy Platforms. This covers more than 2,000 Honeywell part numbers on nearly 100 fixed and rotor wing aircraft platforms, building upon the existing authorizations in place with Duncan Aviation as a licensed Honeywell Authorized Service Center and Channel Partner.

 Duncan Aviation has more than 60 years of experience in the market, with complete Maintenance, Repair and Overhaul (MRO) facilities in 
the US and strategically placed regional shops that can provide services 24/7 worldwide. In addition to global coverage, this agreement enables immediate access to parts once Duncan Aviation will maintain an inventory to support our customers globally.

 What To Do Now 



	- Prepare: Review the impacted parts list &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Authorized%20Product%20and%20Platform%20Duncan%20Agreement.pdf]]&gt; and your Authorized Supplier List (ASL). If Duncan Aviation is not already on your ASL, start working to add them as a new supplier.


	- Immediate action for cores: All cores that are part of the list should be shipped immediately to Duncan Aviation at 4001 N. Park Road, Lincoln, NE, 68524, USA.  


	- New repair orders (excluding cores): You can continue to place/status repairs orders (excluding cores) through the Honeywell facility per ROCAP´s capability on the aerospace.honeywell.com portal. 




	- AOG orders: You can continue to place/status all AOG orders through the Honeywell AOG team at aerospace.honeywell.com portal or call 1-800-601-3099. 




	- Technical Support: You can continue to access Technical Support through the Honeywell Hub at aerotechsupport@honeywell.com or call 1-800-601-3099. 




	- Exchange/MSP Avionics orders: You can obtain status and place all SPEX Exchange and MSP Avionics orders with Honeywell Aerospace Trading (HAT) at DL-AERO-HATSalesAmericas@HoneywellProd.onmicrosoft.com or call 1-866-825-5428. 



What You Can Expect Next

 Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. During the following weeks, Honeywell will send more information about this agreement and impact to your operation. If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact. 

 Yours sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
