<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201809_BK_Global_Email_KI-825 &amp; IVA-81D_Dealer_mih.201809_BK_Global_Email_KI-825</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>[Updated Information] ONTIC Licensing for Urbana, Ohio-Based Displays Product Line</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
UPDATED INFORMATION | September 20, 2018
ONTIC LICENSING FOR URBANA, OHIO-BASED DISPLAYS PRODUCT LINE 
 
In March 2018, Honeywell Aerospace announced an exclusive licensing agreement with Ontic, a subsidiary of BBA Aviation, for the manufacturing and servicing of our Urbana, Ohio-based Displays product line. This includes products sold through Grimes Lighting and BendixKing. 
 
 What is the Change? 




	- This agreement ends both Honeywell’s production and repair work for these displays, which are produced in Urbana, Ohio and repaired at both Urbana, Ohio and Renton, Washington.

	- This affects 23 displays and their associated dash numbers. Part Number List &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Displays_LRUList-Customer_Notification_091418.xlsx]]&gt;



What customers are impacted? 




	- This affects 610 D&amp;S and commercial customers.

	- View the list to see the customer list and the PN’s that they have procured in the past 2 years.

	- The customer email &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/index.php/email/emailWebview?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiTnpobVpqZzJNalF4TkRaayIsInQiOiJENmxtM3FQVGV4eXRVZVk3SWZOVXFiVUtVNGs0NGVSVkszZXd6ZnNTMkQ5ODBjSCtnNzF1dTR3YjdDT1F0VnZESFVIRlM2enJyV29VUEZDQjRSNnZoY2drQVFGaGhpOXFyXC95c1dSY1dJOEd3NDh2bENpdndtMmZFd1FRd1dpUlcifQ%3D%3D]]&gt; communication is provided for your reference.




What dates do I need to know? 

New Incoming Original Equipment Orders:




	- Effective Friday July 20, 2018 orders for these displays will no longer be accepted by Honeywell.

	- Effective Monday July 23, 2018 orders for these displays should be placed with Ontic.



Existing Original Equipment Orders: 




	- Existing orders due before January 2, 2019 will ship from Honeywell with a Honeywell certificate of compliance.

	- Existing orders due after January 2, 2019 will ship from Ontic with an Ontic certificate of compliance.




Original equipment information: 




	- Honeywell will make every effort to fulfil orders placed between July 3, 2018 and July 20, 2018. However, some long lead orders may require a novation agreement to Ontic. In this event, Honeywell will work closely with all parties to coordinate that activity.



Repair Orders: 




	- Repairs currently performed at Renton will transition to Ontic on August 10, 2018.



	- Effective August 13, 2018, repair orders should be placed with Ontic.


	- Repairs currently performed at Urbana will transition to Ontic November 1, 2018.



	- Effective November 2, repair orders should be placed with Ontic


	- Honeywell will make every effort to fulfil orders placed by the above dates. However, some circumstances may not allow for repair completion by these dates. In this event, Honeywell will work closely with all parties to coordinate the repair completion via PO novation.

	- The production and repair benches will physically move starting Nov 1, 2018.

	- There is a build ahead program for existing orders. When completed, the CBMs/CSPMs may be asked to contact their customers to see if the customer will allow for early shipment.



What does the customer need to do? 




	- Effective July 16, 2018 new orders will need to be placed at Ontic, per the information below.

	- Update their Authorized Supplier List (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier location as an approved supplier.




Ontic Engineering &amp; Manufacturing Inc. 
 20400 Plummer Street 
 Chatsworth, CA 91311, United States 
 Cage Code: 45934 
 DUNS 
Number: 155389224 


Direct email for inquires: displays@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:displays@ontic.com]]&gt;
Team Members: 





Name
Title
Email Address


Stephanie Cook
Customer Service-Factory New
stephanie.cook@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:stephanie.cook@ontic.com]]&gt;


Timm Harmon
Technical Sales Manager-Factory New
timmothy.harmon@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:timmothy.harmon@ontic.com]]&gt; 


Jack Lecka
Customer Service
jack.lecka@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:jack.lecka@ontic.com]]&gt;


Bill Nolan
Technical Sales Manager- MRO
bill.nolan@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:bill.nolan@ontic.com]]&gt;


Chris Muklevicz
Head of Sales, North America
Chris.Muklevicz@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:Chris.Muklevicz@ontic.com]]&gt; 
Phone +1 818 725 2352





How will we support AOGs? 




	- Honeywell will support AOG shipments through October 31, 2018.

	- Ontic will support AOG shipments starting November 1, 2018.

	- AOG Phone Number: +44 (0) 333 666 6842.

	- Ontic will coordinate with Honeywell, if needed, to support your AOG during this transition period.

	- Customers have been asked to plan accordingly and communicate with us to identify a proactive approach which will minimize AOG issues during this timeframe.




What do I need to know? 




	- CSPM/CSM/CBMs need to be able to respond to customer questions. See FAQ’s/Talking Points &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/FAQ_and_TalkingPoints-Urbana_Ontic_Licensing_062818.pdf]]&gt;.

	- Understand that cut off dates that are identified above.

	- CSPM/CSM: Identify if any additional communication is required. If so, take the appropriate action (phone call, call from director or VP, etc.)



 Should you need any additional information, please contact Jeff Baker &lt;[[mailto:jeff.baker@honeywell.com]]&gt;.


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/T3ZQS0h0v000BIG20qjdGX0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
