<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_Greenhouse_Covid-19_email_operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Our Ongoing Customer Commitment During COVID-19</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell HGuide Customer: 

 We know many of our valued customers and partners such as yourself are assessing the impact and the disruptions caused by the COVID-19 coronavirus and have evolved the way you work in order to accomplish your mission. Our thoughts are with your employees and their families at this very difficult time. 

 As you continue your operations, we want to share what Honeywell is doing to ensure we are meeting our HGuide customers critical needs: 

 1 – Even while working remotely, our employees remain available to assist you with new and existing orders. While taking precautions at all our sites and complying with local government initiatives, our production staff continues to manufacture and service deliver products. Our engineering team remains available to provide remote assistance in integration and use of our products. 

 2 – Our HGuide manufacturing and inventory is operating and ready to fulfill your delivery needs and ensure you continue meeting your own customers’ demands. 

 3 – You can reach us. We are eager to connect with you at your convenience – simply email HGuide sales &lt;[[mailto:hguide.sales@honeywell.com]]&gt; or email HGuide support &lt;[[mailto:hguide.support@honeywell.com]]&gt;. We want to understand what you are seeing in the market and what your customers are telling you so that we can help jointly overcome this challenge. 

 We are very focused on protecting the health and safety of our employees while maintaining the ability to keep serving you. 

 For ongoing information on how we are responding to COVID-19, please visit the Aerospace FAQ page &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/aero-covid-19]]&gt;. 

 Stay healthy, stay safe, and take care, 

 Chris Lund 
 Honeywell HGuide Business Leader</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
