<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202006_Global_Internal-Comms_Supplier-Comms_Auto-PO-for-VMI_Operational.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Honeywell Process Change Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Supplier, 

 Effective the weekend of June 6, a revision to the auto-PO process for VMI Flex/2.0 will be implemented, affecting only VMI orders that have active DPAS flow down. 

Why are we implementing these changes? 

 As part of VMI FLEX/2.0 continuous improvement, we are refining the scope of parts that will significantly reduce the number of POs Honeywell triggers to our VMI Flex/VMI 2.0 suppliers while reducing the administrative burden suppliers may be experiencing. 

 What do I need to do differently? 

 Please continue to follow the steps below as part of the standard process:
 

 	- Suppliers should maintain a sufficient quantity of parts at or above VMI bin levels 	- Suppliers should create sufficient POs to cover the current Honeywell forecast through the replenishment lead time (typically 14 days) 	- Suppliers should acknowledge the VMI FLEX PO quantity and provide the date the materials are expected to hit the Honeywell dock 	- Suppliers must always review and ensure compliance with flow down requirements in all VMI FLEX POs. 

 Who do I contact with questions? 

 Please refer to the available FAQs &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Honeywell_FAQ-VMI-Flex-Auto-PO.pdf]]&gt; . If you have any additional questions or concerns regarding this enhancement, please create a case within the Case Management tool in HASP. You can do so by logging into HASP then clicking this link &lt;[[https://scc.honeywell.com/irj/portal/createcase]]&gt;. You can also navigate to HASP&gt;Support&gt;Create Case, select “VMI” category and, finally select “Other VMI Issue” sub-category when submitting your case. 

 Thank you for your partnership to ensure on-time delivery to our mutual end customers.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
