<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_Global_Employee-Comms_Supplier-xCarrier-HASP_Email_Operational.Email 1 -</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Important Honeywell Process Change Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Valued Supplier: 

 We appreciate that you have been leveraging the Honeywell Aerospace Supplier Portal (HASP). The intention of the portal is to provide our suppliers a “one-stop-shop” to easily access pertinent information that makes doing business with Honeywell more efficient. It has come to our attention that while you are using HASP, the xCarrier shipping portal within HASP is not being used. 

 Please carefully read the information below and the process changes related to the use of xCarrier for all suppliers doing business with Honeywell effective Friday, February 21, 2020.


 What is xCarrier? 



	- xCarrier is the only Honeywell Aerospace approved inbound shipping method available.
	- xCarrier is a free web-based application that does not require any software to be downloaded.
	- xCarrier will allow receipt of supplier shipments as noted below:


	- Domestic – 10 days ahead of the delivery date
	- International – 12 days ahead of the delivery date




If you have used xCarrier in the past, recent enhancements have been made to support ease of use: 



	- Creation and printing of shipping labels with a “Click + Print” process.
	- xCarrier is a free web-based application that no longer requires IT engagement or configuration.
	- The application was moved to a new server with increased space to improve the speed of using the portal.


Why do I need to use xCarrier? 



	- Reduces Honeywell shipping costs by selecting the “best price” carrier per transportation route.


	- This prevents Honeywell from having to impose the costs of shipping to our supply base. This allows Honeywell to invest savings from shipping costs in the creation of additional tools for our suppliers such as xCarrier.


	- Provides Honeywell visibility to incoming supplier shipments using Advanced Shipping Notification (ASN).


	- Having visibility helps Honeywell better manage inventory while preventing having to ship materials back to suppliers when received sooner than requested.


	- Provides the ability to obtain freight data on volume, frequency, and cost of logistics activities.
	- Reduces calls to/from Honeywell Buyers regarding shipment status.


What do I need to do differently? 



	- Effective Friday, February 21, 2020, Honeywell is requiring all suppliers to use xCarrier as the only approved inbound shipping method for all inbound shipments.
	- Even if you have an approved expedited order, you are required to ship through xCarrier.
	- We will not allow the use of any other Honeywell shipping methods such as freight shipping accounts.


How do I access xCarrier? 



	- xCarrier is easily accessible through the Supply Chain portal at SCC.Honeywell.com.
	- If you have an ID, you simply log in to start the shipping process.
	- Step-by-step xCarrier training materials are located here &lt;[[https://xcarrier.honeywell.com/xcarrierdocs/HASP%20-%20Dashboard%20Overview%202018.pdf]]&gt;.


Who do I contact if I have questions about using xCarrier? 



	- If you have any questions about the xCarrier shipping tool, we encourage you to contact your dedicated Fulfillment Specialist or you can send an email to the Aerospace xCarrier support team &lt;[[mailto:AeroXcarrierSupport@honeywell.com]]&gt;.



We will be monitoring our suppliers’ use of xCarrier after Friday, February 21, 2020. Your feedback is important to me as we continue to make changes to improve our processes. We will be launching a survey specific to the use of xCarrier in mid-March to understand what is working well and what challenges you may be experiencing. 

 Thank you for your partnership to ensure on-time delivery to our mutual end customers while adhering to Honeywell approved processes. 

Bob Buddecke
Vice President, Chief Procurement Officer
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
