<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201911_Global_HoneywellForgePTMD_KK.Honeywell Forge now includes PTMD</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>PTMD migrates to Honeywell Forge [Product Update]</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Honeywell Forge now includes Predictive Trend Monitoring and Diagnostics (PTMD)
As part of our digital transformation strategy, we are migrating our Predictive Trend Monitoring and Diagnostics (PTMD) solution into Honeywell Forge, an analytics platform for storing, accessing, managing, and serving events and policies. The platform also enables you to set thresholds, alerting conditions, and upload your own and/or third-party analytics. There is no additional cost associated with the transition to Honeywell Forge.

We will be reaching out to our existing PTMD customers to start this migration throughout the remainder of 2019. PTMD users will still have access to the legacy PTMD application tentatively until March 31, 2020. 

What is changing for PTMD users?  
 

 	- PTMD customers will experience a new and improved UI application which will retain all of the existing features, along with some new ones. 	- Customer migrations will start November 2019, with planned completions in early 2020. 	- We will provide a 90-day migration period for users to continue to access the legacy PTMD application. 

 
Will this impact my existing work and preferred features?
 

 	- No. All existing PTMD features will remain, just with an upgraded look and feel. 	- Users will be provided a new URL at time of migration. 	- User login credentials will not change.   

 What’s next? Regional PTMD focal points of contact, along with the PTMD management team will be available to assist in the change and provide training and support as requested.

If you have questions or comments about the migration of PTMD to Honeywell Forge, please contact Krasimir.Koychev@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Krasimir.Koychev@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.
© {{my.year}} Honeywell International Inc.    This message was sent to {{lead.Email Address:default=NA}}. If you don&apos;t want to receive these emails from Honeywell in the future, you can edit your profile &lt;[[]]&gt; or unsubscribe &lt;[[https://explore.honeywell.com/Unsubscribepage.html]]&gt;. Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/privacy-statement/ps-german]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://www.honeywellsafety.com/DE/Contacts.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
