<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Global_C&amp;PS_Wellington-Wiper_Email_Operational.Wellington Wiper Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about Honeywell&apos;s Wiper Business</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

Honeywell continually evaluates its operations and products to determine what is best for customers and our long-term growth. After a thorough evaluation, we have decided to sign an exclusive perpetual licensing agreement for our wiper business to Ontic Engineering and Manufacturing, Inc., a long-term partner. 

Ontic is a valued partner that is committed to produce and service the wiper models. We have established a dedicated transition team composed of functional experts and leaders to manage the transition process. This team will work to ensure that there is no break in service or shipments during this transition period. 

Customers are asked to establish Ontic Engineering on their approved source list for the following wiper part numbers. View Wiper Product Line Part Numbers. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Wiper Part Numbers.xlsx]]&gt; 

Ontic Contact Information: 

Company Name:               Ontic Engineering and Manufacturing, Inc.
 Address:                            1176 Telecom Drive 
 City, State:                         Creedmoor, North Carolina 

 Postal Code:                      27522 

 Country:                             USA 
 Cage Code:                       8G4X8 

 DUNS Number:                 11 736 2367 
 Contact Name:                  Javier Hernandez 
 Contact Email Address:     javier.hernandez@ontic.com &lt;[[mailto:javier.hernandez@ontic.com]]&gt;
 Contract Phone:                919-956-4323 

We will continue to keep you updated, providing directions on activities that 
will need to be completed within the coming months. We are working to give you the quality and service that you deserve. 

If you have any questions, please engage your Honeywell point of contact. 

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
