<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202010_Global_BGA_Forge_GoGo-Termination-Notice_Email.202011_Global_BGA_Forge_Go</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reminder: Gogo Policy Change - Invoice Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>CUSTOMER UPDATES AND NOTIFICATIONS
Dear Valued Customer, 

 This is a reminder that Honeywell was recently informed by Gogo that they are terminating our single bill agreement. After November 30, 2020, you will be receiving two separate invoices, one from Honeywell Forge and another one from Gogo.

 We apologize for this inconvenience but please note we are working tirelessly to provide you with a seamless transition with no interruption in your service. We are still committed to providing you with our dedicated customer support for both Honeywell Forge and Gogo Service. Our team is here to help you every step of the way through this transition. 

 HOW DOES THIS IMPACT MY EXPERIENCE?


	- The voice number to the aircraft will not change.
	- Gogo will begin billing directly for their voice and Short Burst Data services. You should work directly with them for activation, call records and billing disputes.
	- Honeywell’s invoice will no longer include both these charges.
	- Honeywell Forge will continue to support you with troubleshooting and any other inquiries you have. Connectivity can span multiple components; we remain dedicated to you.


FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS (FAQ)


	- Will my services be the same with Gogo? 
 You should have received an email from Gogo Customer Operations with a link to complete an online Subscriber Service Agreement. Gogo will invoice you based on your plan selection. Concerning Datalink (If you subscribed), you should subscribe for Short Burst Data through Gogo. Subscription and billing are being managed by Gogo, but you should select Honeywell as the provider on the form.
	- Will my overall costs be affected? 
 After November 30, 2020, the overall bill from Honeywell Forge will be reduced by the amount of the Gogo services previously charged. If you subscribe to Datalink SBD through Gogo, Honeywell will reduce the datalink subscription price by $74.95/ mo annualized on your subscription.
	- When does this change occur? 
 December 1, 2020
	- Will my Datalink service be impacted? 
 As long as you subscribe to the SBD with Gogo, your datalink service will not be impacted and will function as it does today, otherwise your service could be impacted and would be limited to VHF only.
	- Do I get to keep my current phone number? 
 Yes
	- Do I have my same contact for overall service support? 
 Yes, you will have your same Honeywell Forge support person. We will continue to troubleshoot the overall system and be your single point of contact for support.
	- Will I notice any disruption to my service with Honeywell or Gogo? 
 This is only an administrative change, not on-wing. There will be no disruption in your service.
	- Who do I contact if I need support completing my service agreement? 
 Gogo Customer Operations can be reached at 303-301-3278 (option 1) or by emailing bacustomerservice@gogoair.com &lt;[[mailto:bacustomerservice@gogoair.com]]&gt;.
	- How will my experience change?
 Starting with the December billing cycle (12/1-12/31/2020), Gogo will be invoicing you for your Iridium Voice and Short Burst Data services. If you have non-Gogo services, those services will continue to be invoiced by Honeywell Forge.


Have any other questions? Contact our dedicated support team or call: 1-888-634-3330 Ext 7 or email sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:sales.honeywellforge@honeywell.com]]&gt;. Our #1 priority is to maintain a best-in-class customer experience for you.

 Sincerely, 
 Honeywell Forge</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
