<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202008_Global_ATR_ECS-Performance_Email.A/B Test.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Monitor Cabin Air Quality (ECS Check)</subject>
    <textOnly>MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace]]&gt;    |    Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;    |    View in browser &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;  Forward to a friend &lt;[[{{system.forwardToFriendLink}}]]&gt;

In a recent informal survey &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/press-release/2020/05/honeywell-survey-reveals-passenger-preferences?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_atr&amp;utm_content=ecs]]&gt; conducted by Honeywell*, 72% of passengers said they are more concerned with the air quality on an airplane than in an airport (28%). 

 Did you know that Honeywell Forge has tools that help airlines address Environmental Control Systems (ECS) performance before it causes serious problems?
Request a free trial of our ECS Performance Check



 






Learn more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/ecs-performance-check?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_atr&amp;utm_content=ecs]]&gt;
ECS Performance Check FAQ
How Can Airlines Improve Air Quality?


 


With its hundreds of elements and dozens of sensors, the Environmental Control Systems (ATA 21) is highly complex system. With Honeywell Forge &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/forms/honeywell-forge-airlines?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_atr&amp;utm_content=ecs]]&gt;, our advanced data analytics platform, airlines get an accurate picture of the ECS status across their entire fleet. Even more important, the predictive and prescriptive analytics will alert maintenance departments for potential failures ahead of time.


 


How Does the ECS Performance Check Work?


 


Honeywell Forge combines critical data from airline systems with flight data from the aircraft. Flight data can be delivered in real-time which enables airlines to react quickly to predictive alerts and avoid operational disruptions in the form of unscheduled maintenance events, delays, and cancelations. 

 The ECS Performance Check is part of the our data analytics platform and works in three steps: 



	- Aircraft Data – Air system data, fault messages, maintenance history.
	- Advanced Analytics – Algorithm to predict problems and alerts maintainers.
	- Performance Check – Provides outlet temperature, airflow, humidity data.





 


What’s the value to airlines?


 


Problems with ATA Chapter 21 are a common cause of delays**. Honeywell has validated its predictive analytics for ATA Chapter 21 with several airlines across different platforms: Airbus A320 and A330, Boeing 777, and others. Airlines can improve air quality by more monitoring ECS performance across their entire fleet.

 Benefits of ECS Performance Check include: 



	- Improved air flow and fresh air system performance
	- ECS Packs performance monitoring
	- Proactive maintenance policy setting
	- Fleet overview of ECS performance
	- No additional hardware or sensors


As Part of Honeywell Forge Connected Maintenance, ECS Performance Check can reduce operational disruptions due to unscheduled maintenance as well as cut costs due to premature removals (NFF rate).


 


What is the Free Trial?


 


The Free Trial is available to all Honeywell Forge customers. The data integration projects will be prioritized on a first-come, first-served basis. If your airline is not a Honeywell Forge customer, please reply or click below to explore the options when it comes to ingesting ACMS and flight data.
Want more info?


 


Simply reply to this email and we&apos;ll get right back to you! 



 






Reply to get more info &lt;[[mailto:krasimir.koychev@honeywell.com?Subject=ECS Check]]&gt;
* This informal and anonymous online survey, captured via SurveyMonkey, had 732 respondents split nearly evenly between North America and Asia, with a small number from elsewhere. The majority, 75%, were ages 25-44. Surveyed travelers fly equally for business and pleasure, mostly on domestic routes. 

 ** Our data shows that problems related to ATA 21 are among the top 3 most common causes for Airbus A320, Boeing 737, and 777 delays. It is also a significant contributor for delays on Airbus A330 and A350. 

 Note: Some Honeywell product concepts are currently under development. No testing has been done specifically as to protection against COVID-19. As with all of our products and services, Honeywell will adhere to its commitment to integrity and compliance within its global supply chain; meet relevant legal, scientific and industry standards; substantiate claims; and obtain necessary regulatory approvals as products progress through the development process.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/honeywell_aero]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.instagram.com/honeywell_aero/]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;      &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellDefense]]&gt;       
   
© 2020 Honeywell International Inc.  &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; 
300 S Tryon St Suite 500, Charlotte, NC 28202   
   
 Subscription Preference &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/AERO_Preference_Center.html]]&gt;  |  Terms of Use &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/terms-and-conditions]]&gt; |  Privacy Policy &lt;[[https://www.honeywell.com/en-us/privacy-statement]]&gt; |  Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
