<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Global_Email_GoDirectFlightPlanning_TM.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Six Thousand of Your Flying Friends Agree – Plan, File and Fly with Our App</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yJOzBIINlH0&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
Greetings {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}, 

Have you tried our new GoDirect™ Flight Planning experience? If you have, you’re in good company, because more than 6,000 flight plans have been successfully filed using the new flight planning engine since the launch in March. 

As with any new software program, we’ve been on a steep learning curve and constantly 
looking for opportunities to make your experience better. From your feedback we’re continuously making improvements and rapidly squashing bugs, issuing new patches every two weeks with eight patches already released since launch.

If you haven’t had a chance to use the new experience yet, try it and tell us what you think. Planning is now faster, easier to use and more accurate than ever before. It uses intuitive tools that you can access via website and the electronic flight bag. And you have 24/7 access to real live flight planning specialists and licensed dispatchers if you need them.

Interested in some hands-on, dedicated training? Our flight ops team is here for you. Let us set up time to walk you through everything that’s new. Our experts are ready to answer your questions. 

We want to thank you for being a GoDirect Flight Planning customer. Your feedback is critical to our ongoing development and improvements, please let us know if there are things we can do to improve the flight planning experience for you. 

GoDirect Flight Services
(888) 634-3330
flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
