<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>May 2016.May 2016 email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - May 2016</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.honeywellaidc.com/pages/SiteLanguages.aspx]]&gt;
NEWS | Business Aviation
HONEYWELL HAS 2020 VISION ON MANDATES COMPLIANCE SOLUTIONS

FANS 1/A+, PM-CPDLC, ADS-B OUT and TCAS II Mandates
Most operators know something about these by now, but staying on top of the various implementation deadlines, geographical requirements and required aircraft upgrades can be challenging. To make it easier to put mandates and compliance requirements into focus, we have developed Mandates At-A-Glance infographics which provide the overview, deadlines and Honeywell upgrade options. FANS 1/A+ &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/FANSataglance]]&gt;   PM-CPDLC &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/PMCPDLCataglance]]&gt;   ADS-B Out &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/ataglanceadsb]]&gt;  TCAS Change 7.1 &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/tcasataglance]]&gt;
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/Mandates]]&gt;
FLIGHTSAFETY INTERNATIONAL NOW HONEYWELL&apos;S FACTORY ENDORSED TRAINING PROVIDER
Our new partnership with FlightSafety will enable Honeywell to better meet your unique maintenance training needs, regardless of the size of your aircraft fleet, specific aircraft you operate or location. Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/FlightSafety International Training.pdf]]&gt;
HONEYWELL AND NASA TACKLE SUPERSONIC SOUND POLLUTION

Honeywell Aerospace is working with NASA’s Armstrong Flight Research Center to study the most effective way to visually inform pilots flying supersonic jets about sonic booms, a loud noise caused by current aircraft traveling faster than the speed of sound. Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/press-release-listing/2016/april/honeywell-and-nasa-tackle-supersonic-sound-pollution]]&gt;
HI-RES TOUCHSCREEN DISPLAY RECEIVES GULFSTREAM CERTS

Honeywell&apos;s latest edition of next-generation control display units for business jets—the CD-830—received FAA supplemental type certification (STC) for the Gulfstream GIV and GIV-SP aircraft on March 31. The CD-830 flat panel display unit now offers full touchscreen functionality with enhanced visibility and, like its predecessor the CD-820, provides graphical interfaces for video, critical weather graphics and a preview mode to show active leg changes prior to waypoint insertion. And the CD-830 improves on the -820 by cutting six pounds of weight per unit.
APP GIVES PILOTS PREVIEWS OF COMING APPROACHES

A new app from Honeywell eliminates surprises by giving pilots a highly accurate preview of the runway and surrounding terrain – long before they begin their approach. Introduced in spring 2016, the Flight Preview app provides a useful, practical and intuitive iPad tool that lets pilots know what they can expect during one of the most critical phases of flight. Learn More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[http://www.aerospace.honeywell.com/flightpreview]]&gt;
ATTEND ONE OF THE 2016 OPERATORS CONFERENCES

Honeywell has scheduled numerous Operators Conferences throughout the Americas, EMEAI and Asia Pacific. For more information contact you Regional Customer Support Manager. Link to Conference Schedule&gt;&gt; &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/Q0AX0bI0QT2qX0Z8G002bw0]]&gt;




CONTACT TECHNICAL AND CUSTOMER SUPPORT &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/G7I0XE200b0OQ0Gq00000Z0]]&gt;
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; 
This message was sent to name@website.com.
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
