<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201801_Global_Email_GoDirect_FlightPlanning_TM.201801_Global_Email_GoDirect_Flig</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Filed Flight Plan - New Feature - GoDirect Flight Planning</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Customer,

You filed a flight plan, performed your preflight, set up the FMS, loaded the passenger luggage, and prepare to start the engines. You call ATC and receive an IFR clearance completely different than your filed flight plan route. Don’t worry, it’s common to receive ATC clearances with new routes, so we created a new feature to make your life easier.

New for GoDirect Flight Planning Customers

When our team detects a filed flight plan route that is different than your ATC cleared route, we automatically generate a new summary flight plan and recall number for you. No need to manually change the FMS, just uplink the new recall number. New recall numbers will have a “Q” prefix and won’t clutter your review flight planning page on our website. Just a reminder plans are also available in the full flight plan format. 

By providing you with both your original datalink recall number and the new Q number, you will be able to quickly uplink the flight plan which aligns to your ATC cleared route and still view your filed flight plan documents. 

This feature is available right now for all flight planning customers, but the full benefit is gained by bundling our subscription with datalink service. To get started immediately, make sure you have set up flight plan auto regeneration notifications on flightservices.honeywell.com. 

To setup help, contact us at flightservices@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:flightservices@honeywell.com]]&gt;, or call flight ops at US toll-free: (888) 634-3330 or at International +1 (602) 365-7020. Our Honeywell Flight Services representatives will assist in setting up your notifications to enable this new service. 

Thank you,

Honeywell GoDirect Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
