<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>June 2016.June Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Business Aviation Newsletter - June 2016</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.honeywellaidc.com/pages/SiteLanguages.aspx]]&gt;
NEWS | Business Aviation
AOG PROPOSE TO CLOSE SURVEY DESIGNED TO ENHANCE CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE

Honeywell has been introducing new apps and channels to enhance your experience interacting with us. We are introducing AOG Propose To Close Survey to ensure we have provided a complete resolution of an AOG situation before closing your case. Completing the survey is the final phase of the AOG process and takes only moments to complete. Click the button below to learn more.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/AOG Survey Infographic 1.pdf]]&gt;
HONEYWELL TECHNICAL MANUALS NOW DELIVERED ONLINE


Honeywell technical publications distributed in paper format will be transitioned to a downloadable online delivery solution only through the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/]]&gt; portal. This transition to online is good news for you and every Honeywell customer. With it, we can keep important information accurate and up-to-date and more efficiently answer your questions. With online access to publications you have access to the automated notification system to alert you when there are newly released or revised documents to view or download. In addition, we are proud to play our part in being a good environmental steward.

In order to transition paper publications to online access we will email the contacts at each company who have the active paper publications on their account. In cases where email address for the contact is not available, we will mail a letter to the contact at the shipping address on file for the publication. In both cases, we require a response in order to verify information and transition the publication(s) to online access on the MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/]]&gt; portal. If you have any questions or concerns with this transition please do not hesitate to contact the publications team at pubs@honeywell.com &lt;[[pubs@honeywell.com]]&gt;. We appreciate your support in our efforts to better serve you while “going green”!
HONEYWELL MARKS 40 YEARS OF AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE SERVICES

Honeywell is celebrating four decades of providing maintenance service plans for airplane operators and owners of business jets. As one of the world’s leading manufacturers of engines and auxiliary power units, Honeywell has designed a program implemented by industry specialists based in more than 180 service centers across 30 countries worldwide. Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/press-release-listing/2016/may/honeywell-marks-40-years-of-aircraft-maintenance-services-that-reduce-downtime-and-costs]]&gt;
DON BATEMAN, INDUSTRY ICON FOR SAFETY, RETIRES 

Don Bateman, Honeywell’s living legend of aircraft safety, retired in May after a distinguished 56-year Honeywell career that is credited by many for saving more lives than anyone in the history of aviation. Read More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/news-listing/2016/may/don-bateman-retires-after-56-year-honeywell-career]]&gt;
ROUTER SOFTWARE UPDATE BOOSTS IN-FLIGHT CONNECTIVITY PERFORMANCE
Honeywell releases AvioIP software update 3.0 for more reliable in-flight connectivity. Learn More&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/press-release-listing/2016/may/honeywell-boosts-in-flight-connectivity-performance-with-cabin-router-software-update]]&gt;
CONTACT TECHNICAL AND CUSTOMER SUPPORT &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/G7I0XE200b0OQ0Gq00000Z0]]&gt;
 


© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.



 &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;





 



This message was sent to name@website.com.
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
