<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>D&amp;S Comms.D&amp;S UFR Letter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell launches Universal Flat Rates for Repair &amp; Overhaul services</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell launches Universal Flat Rates for Repair &amp; Overhaul services
On February 1, 2014, Honeywell will move from pricing based on Time and Material to Universal Flat Rate (UFR) pricing, which will enable customers to pay a flat rate for the Repair &amp; Overhaul services that Honeywell provides. The change will: 



 - Make it easier than ever for you to use Honeywell’s global network of repair and overhaul services. 
 - Improve the start-to-end repair process by eliminating the need for quotes and other administrative steps, resulting in faster turnaround times. 
 - Provide pricing visibility so you can plan and budget your repair needs, while eliminating financial surprises from the Repair &amp; Overhaul process.


Frequently asked questions about Universal Flat Rate pricing
What is included in the UFR price?
Included are normal repairs and minor modifications that don’t affect form, fit or function. As of the Feb. 1 launch, about 70 percent of R&amp;O services are covered by flat rates.
What if the service I need is not yet covered?
We are adding new part numbers to the UFR pricing model all the time, but if the service you need isn’t yet covered, we will charge on a Time and Material basis as in the past.
What is not included in the UFR price?
The only exceptions to UFR pricing are parts that have been damaged beyond normal wear and tear. For certain applicable part numbers, Honeywell Defense &amp; Space offers UFR pricing for MODs/Upgrades that include a part/dash number change.
Where can I find pricing for the flat rate covered parts?
Pricing can now be found online at MyAerospace.com &lt;http://MyAerospace.com&gt;
Why doesn’t my invoice have details on labor and materials required for my repair?
The new UFRs cover all labor and material required for the repair. The service report included with the return of the part will have additional details.
How can I reduce the quote process time requirements thereby reducing my overall repair time?
If you simply include the established Universal Flat Rate price on your Purchase Order (PO) sent with your part, repair can begin immediately. No separate quote approval will be needed. By including the UFR on your PO you are approving repair to begin. This approval includes authorizing minor modifications.
What about credit terms?
If you have established credit terms with Honeywell, you can arrange for repair and overhaul services quickly and easily by visiting the new and improved MyAerospace portal &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/&gt;. Click on “Universal Flat Rates” and follow the instructions.  If you do not have credit terms established, you will be asked to provide payment before we begin work on your unit. 



 






Honeywell Aerospace
1944 E Sky Harbor Circle, Phoenix, AZ 85034
Toll Free: 1-800-601-3099
International: 602-365-3099
www.MyAerospace.com &lt;www.MyAerospace.com&gt;
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
