<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201803_EMEAI_Email_IntuVue_mih.201803_EMEAI_Email_IntuVue_Integrated_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Take Bad Weather by Storm. In 3-D.</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
IntuVue™ 3-D Weather Hazard and Avoidance System 
More accurate weather detection at longer ranges
Dear valued customer,

As the global climate continues to change, weather conditions become more variable and occurrences of extreme weather are increasing. Conventional 2-D weather radars are no longer enough to provide pilots with the required situational awareness to make more informed routing and maneuvering decisions.

It’s time that you switch to a fully automatic, 3-D weather radar – IntuVue™ RDR-4000 –for vastly improved weather detection and predictive hazard warnings compared to conventional 2-D radar. Here are some of the compelling reasons for retrofitting IntuVue™ RDR-4000 in your aircraft:



	- Greater safety and lower costs with predictive hail, lightning and windshear detection, and Minimum Operation Performance Standard (MOPS) certified enhanced turbulence detection &amp; alerting capability

	- Quicker rerouting due to longer-range weather hazard detection and better situational awareness

	- Reduced pilot training costs and workload as the radar automatically and continuously scans the airspace up to -80 to +80 degrees in front of the aircraft, from 0 to 60,000 feet and up to 320nm ahead

	- Fully automatic and does not require manual adjustments to the system or antenna for operation



Discover why it makes absolute business sense to retrofit IntuVue™ RDR-4000.  






DISCOVER IntuVue™ RDR-4000 &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/Email_RMU_INTUVUE.html]]&gt;






Sincerely,

Team Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
