<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>MARK VI.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MK VI EGPWS Terrain Database Release Notification Ver 601</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}


 


Honeywell has just released Service Information Letter D201802000012 detailing 3 new regional MK VI EGPWS Terrain Databases - version 601. This version is an update to previous version 488 and adds a number of new airports, runways and obstacles while improving terrain mapping and resolution.




The databases and supporting documentation such as Service Information Letters, Certificates of Conformance, ATP Matrix file can be downloaded by visiting ads.honeywell.com &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/]]&gt; (Login required). EGPWS database search tools and change info are located there (no login required), look under the Search tab and the change Info tab. A Letter of Acceptance (LOA) document is located under the Documents Archive tab for applicable configurations. A Release Statement, located under the Updates tab, my be referenced to confirm the current status of the LOA.




Database download and Media creation capability for all EGPWS products now available in the OneNav+ Tool, Version 1.21.0 (No License Required), Additional OneNav+ features are being developed for EGPWS databases and will be available in 
future releases.




Please click here &lt;[[mailto:dsa@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWS MK VI Query]]&gt; if you have any technical questions concerning the database.




The URL www.egpws.com &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/pages/enhanced-ground-proximity-warning-system]]&gt; will take you directly to the new Honeywell EGPWS page.  From there you can view product Information, or jump to the EGPWS Technical Data Site &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/myportal/aero/new_egpws]]&gt; (login required) or the Aerospace Software and Database Services site &lt;[[https://ads.honeywell.com/?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRoju6vPZKXonjHpfsX76%2B0sWaC0lMI%2F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CSMBgI%2BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFTLTEMbFpwrgEWhM%3D]]&gt;. We encourage you to visit the website today and explore.




Please click here &lt;[[mailto:myaerospaceportalissue@honeywell.com?subject=EGPWS MK VI Website Query]]&gt; if you have any questions concerning operation or access to Honeywell websites. 







Best regards,
The Honeywell EGPWS Team



If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/TbZQj0h0o000BIu20qjdGX0]]&gt;
This email was sent by: Honeywell
21111 N 19th Avenue Phoenix, AZ 85027 USA
© 2018 Honeywell International Inc &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/Home.aspx]]&gt;
View Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;
View Our Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
