<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201710_Global_Email_ServerUpdate_mih.201710_Global_Email_ServerUpdate_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Advance Notice: iMDS and Vibralog Server Move</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear valued customer/partner,

We are informing you that Honeywell will be moving several of our servers in November and your access will be interrupted. Please note the details below and we appreciate your patience as we continue to upgrade our services.

What is changing? 
iMDS and Vibralog servers will be physically moving from San Diego, CA to a HON Data Center in Phoenix, AZ.

When?
The move will occur between 6 a.m. PST on Nov. 8 through midnight PST on Nov. 12. Downtime is anticipated to be between 72 and 96 hours. Please note, you will not have access to the servers during this time period.

What level of backup coverage is in place while the system is in transit?
A full system image backup will be conducted before the equipment is transferred, in addition to regular system and data backups.

Will the system performance be any different from this new datacenter?
The same equipment will be used at the new datacenter. At the new facility, the network connection will be faster. Applications will operate at the same speed, but may transmit data faster over the Internet.

Will the service available from the HON team be any different?
The HON team will continue to provide service and support for the servers via remote access to the servers. Any physical interaction with the servers will be performed by HON personnel at the data center.

Vibralog Users:
If you are using an IP address to connect to the Vibralog web page or an IP address to FTP flight data to the Vibralog Server, please contact Ben Schnur (Benjamin.Schnur@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Benjamin.Schnur@Honeywell.com]]&gt;).

iMDS Server Users:
If you are using an IP address instead of the server URL to identify the destination for a registered Facility PC-GBS, please contact Tom Zingale (Thomas.Zingale@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Thomas.Zingale@honeywell.com]]&gt;).

This can be checked at a registered Facility PC-GBS by navigating to the “Tools” menu, under the “Data Movement General” settings, as shown below. If you encounter an issue following this process, please contact Honeywell C&amp;PS (Deta.Adams@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Deta.Adams@honeywell.com]]&gt;).</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
