<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20183_MASCOTransition_LG.20183_MASCOTransition_Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Sky Connect Manufacturing and Service Changes</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
SKY CONNECT MANUFACTURING CHANGES
Dear Customer,

As part of our normal business process, Honeywell continually evaluates ways to serve you more effectively. We have decided to license the manufacturing and servicing of our Sky Connect® product line to Masco Service Corporation. This impacts product line manufacturing and services operations at our Deer Valley, Arizona site. Honeywell will remain the design and manufacturing authority with all parts continuing to be labeled Honeywell.
 
The part numbers affected by this message are listed in an announcement attached to this 
email &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/SkyConnect_MascoCommunication.pdf&gt;. This change is effective immediately and customers should contact Masco to order these products at the address below: 
Masco Service Corporation 
Contact : Coby Sisco 
850 S. Dooley Street 
Grapevine, TX 76051 
Phone: (817) 481-8205; Fax: (817) 488-8918
We expect the transition to be seamless for you. We have established a dedicated transition team with leaders from Honeywell Aerospace and Masco Service Corporation to manage the transition process and ensure customer needs are met. 
 
We view this exclusive license agreement with Masco as a benefit for you. They have an excellent reputation as an industry leader in aircraft instrument, avionics, and accessory service and support. We believe they are well positioned to provide world-class customer service for our Sky Connect customers. Masco is currently a licensed repair facility for Sky Connect products. 
 
Honeywell is committed to the helicopter industry and all Sky Connect customers as part of its overarching Connected Aircraft focus. Sky Connect has an aggressive roadmap that will bring continual improvements and unique connectivity services to current and future customers.
 
In the meantime, if you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Honeywell contact or click contact us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/contact-us]]&gt; for support. 





Honeywell Aerospace Customer &amp; Product Support 
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q00oI0G002000QQXh7Z0]]&gt;   
 
 Please 
click here &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/a0200q0oDQ0400ZXzIZ1F3G]]&gt; to subscribe to our email communications.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
