<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>D&amp;S Comms.D&amp;S UFR Phase II Customer Letter 07.05.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace R&amp;O Purchase Order Process</subject>
    <textOnly>Please discard if you have existing repair and overhaul (R&amp;O) contracts with agreed to pricing.






Dear Honeywell R&amp;O Customer, 

At Honeywell, we are constantly looking for ways to simplify and improve the repair and overhaul experience for you – our customer. With that in mind we are changing the way we communicate unfunded R&amp;O purchase orders received that are subject to universal flat rates* (UFR) or Time &amp; Material (T&amp;M) pricing. 

Here are the steps to take prior to shipping your repair unit to Honeywell:

1)    Log into the customer portal at www.myaerospace.com &lt;http://www.myaerospace.com&gt;
 

2)    Select the “Online Ordering” application 
 

3)    Select your account from the dropdown menu, click on repair part type, and enter or search for the part number
 

4)    Enter the UFR pricing amount on your purchase order and include with your repair unit or email to aerorepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:aerorepairs@Honeywell.com&gt;. That’s it!
 

5)    If pricing is not available, enter an unfunded (zero dollar) amount on your purchase order and include with your repair unit or email to aerorepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:aerorepairs@Honeywell.com&gt;. 
 

6)    Once the unfunded purchase order is received, T&amp;M pricing is applied. You will receive an auto-generated email requesting you to amend your purchase order so we may induct the unit. 
 

7)    Once Honeywell receives your funded PO, we will begin processing your repair unit immediately. No further action is needed from you.
 

8)    When your repair is completed, we will include a copy of the Café/Service report in the shipment. This report is also provided to units returned as “No Fault Found”, along with a “Test Teardown &amp; Evaluation” fee.
 
 

Here’s a sample of the email message. 

In order to induct and process your unit, please
amend your PO with the T&amp;M pricing.  


When you reply to these email messages, please use the “reply all” email function so we may continue to capture your Reference Case Number listed in the subject line. The reference case number helps maintain a record of all customer and repair communications associated with the unit. 


If we don’t hear back from you, we’ll send you a reminder after 5 calendar days. If we failure to receive any response from you after 10 calendar days, the repair unit will be returned to you in an “As Is” condition. 


If you have any questions, please contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager. 


Best regards,

Honeywell Aerospace 


* Universal flat rates include all minor modifications, overhaul rework instructions, and service bulletins that do not require a change of material number -- at no extra cost to you. Honeywell does reserve the right to reject repair materials under the flat rate program if deemed to have ‘excessive’ repair requirements and/or are beyond economical repair.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
