<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_06_June.2019_June_Edition</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Biz Av News - Primus Elite Enhanced Features Certified for Lear 40/45</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
BUSINESS AVIATION NEWSLETTER
June 2019
PRIMUS ELITE ENHANCED FEATURES FAA-CERTIFIED FOR LEAR 40/45
The Lear 40 / 45 community has been waiting for this news: The FAA has issued the Supplemental Type Certificate for Primus Elite Enhanced Features installation on your aircraft... 





LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/june/primus-elite-enhanced-features-certified-for-lear-40-45]]&gt;
Honeywell ‘Tool Man’ focused on customer service

Field Service Engineer Clark Rodgers grew up with a wrench in his hand. He was one of those kids who loved to tinker with mechanical things, he remembers, comparing himself to “Tim the Tool Man” on the “Home Improvement” TV sitcom... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/june/honeywell-tool-man-focuses-on-customer-service]]&gt;.
Honeywell will expedite your ADS-B retrofit at an affordable price
Honeywell is offering expedited upgrade paths for operators needing ADS-B Out on their Primus II Radio-equipped aircraft... Learn More &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2019_ADS-B.html]]&gt;.
Honeywell will be hosting nine more regional Operators Conferences this year

We hope you&apos;ll join us to learn more about the products, services and technical information which are critical to your flight department: July 18, Orange County, CA and Minneapolis, MN; July 30, Bogota, Colombia; Aug 1, Houston, TX; Aug 12, São Paulo, Brazil; Aug 14, Cleveland, OH; Sep 25, Santiago, Chile and Toluca, Mexico; Nov 5, Scottsdale, AZ. Register &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt;.
Honeywell focuses on cybersecurity
With the 
number of connected devices growing by leaps and bounds, it’s no surprise that information security is a top priority for government regulators and companies in nearly every industry. The aviation industry is no exception... Read more &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/blogs/2019/may/aerospace-industry-focuses-on-cybersecurity]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
