<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Americas_GDT_No-excuses-sell-more_Email.GDT No Excuses Sell More</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Selling aerospace parts online is real. Why aren’t you? #NoExcuses</subject>
    <textOnly>GoDirect Trade is the revolutionary new approach to selling Aerospace parts. You may think that “online sales just won’t work for our market.” Sorry to say, there were people at Kodak, Toys-R-Us and Blockbuster that felt the same way. Our team has listened closely and we’ve created a site that addresses your concerns: 

I adjust price depending on the customer



	- On GoDirect Trade you can customize the price customers see by creating price tiers. So if you have a few key partners that get smoking deals, that’s what they’ll see. You can even block those that you don’t want to see price.


My customers don’t shop online



	- We’ve got 5500+ customers that beg to differ. And in 2019 they spent over $5.5M on our site. Best of all, about 50% of those sales were incremental for our sellers.


I want to know who saw my product



	- GoDirect Trade provides analytics to every seller to determine who’s looked at your part, who put it in the cart but didn’t check out and what they’ve searched for on the site.


It costs too much




	- For a limited time we’re letting you list with a free-of-charge 6-month subscription. No payment required. Zip, nada, nothing. After the trial, subscriptions will be as low as $500 per month. There’s no obligation to continue after the trial.




 So now that we’ve eliminated the excuses, jump on board. Launch your e-commerce storefront within minutes and see why Forbes, The Wall Street Journal and Yahoo! Finance are all talking about our marketplace.

Ready to get started? Watch this 30-second video to learn how, then click the button below to launch! 
GoDirect Trade - Launching a Storefront in 3 Easy Steps &lt;[[https://youtu.be/qtDwqcJeQVY]]&gt;
LAUNCH A STOREFRONT NOW &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/customer/oauth/login/user_type/customer/deeplink/bWFya2V0cGxhY2UvYWNjb3VudC9lZGl0UHJvZmlsZS8=?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=seller_wizard]]&gt;
Best Regards, 

 Tony Perillo
New Business Development Leader
GoDirectTrade.com &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Seller_Wizard]]&gt; (powered by Honeywell)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
