<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202104_Global_Internal-Comms_HASP-Portal-Enhancements-for-VMI.HASP-Portal-Enhanc</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>HASP Portal Enhancements for VMI</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell is constantly seeking ways to create efficiencies in our processes and the tools we use to collaborate with our supply base. Please take a moment to review the recent changes to the VMI portion of the Honeywell Aerospace Supplier Portal (HASP).

 Planning Schedule Forecast Improvement

 What Changed?


	- Honeywell improved the reliability of the planning schedules forecast by more closely aligning to the VMI PO screen consumption forecast.


What Should Suppliers Do Differently?


	- No new actions are needed at this time but please continue to do the following:


	- Take note and respond to changes in the planning schedules forecast.
	- Continue to utilize the Planning Schedules for longer-term planning and the VMI PO (consumption forecast) for near-term replenishment planning.
	- Notify your dedicated Honeywell contact of any forecast changes that affect your ability to satisfy the planning schedules forecast.




VMI Purchase Order Screen Improvements

 What Changed?


	- The minimum stock quantity (MIN) will no longer be included as demand in the first weekly bucket to the extent that Total Stock On Hand covers the MIN. Previously, 100% of the MIN was shown as a forecast requirement in the first forecast bucket.
	- Improvements were made to the forecasted consumption accuracy by eliminating minor demands that were forecasted by other Honeywell sites.
	- Improved the calculation of the Suggested Order Quantity. The value now displays:


	- Suggested Order Quantity = (Past due consumption + current week demand + next week) – (total stock + open PO qty).




What Should Suppliers Do Differently?


	- No new actions are needed at this time but please continue to do the following:


	- Take note of any potential impact on your planning and replenishment processes.
	- Notify your dedicated Honeywell contact of any questions or changes that affect your ability to satisfy the consumption forecast.




Thank you for taking the time to understand these changes. We hope you find them beneficial.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
