<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202012_CH_EMEAI_TPA_Sales-Announcement_Email.202011_EMEAI_CH_W&amp;B_Email1_DT</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>TP Aerospace appointed as the Exclusive Distributor for B737 Classic Wheels and Brakes Honeywell products</subject>
    <textOnly>In order to better serve our air transport and regional market customer’s needs, we have recently appointed TP Aerospace as our Exclusive Worldwide Distributor for B737 Classic Wheels and Brakes Honeywell parts. As such, all future orders for these product categories will be placed through TP Aerospace. 

 As a trusted Honeywell partner, we want to make sure you are aware of the appointment of TP Aerospace, so you can connect with them to facilitate any customer requests for wheels and brakes for B737 classic platform. We would recommend adding TP Aerospace to your list of suppliers at the earliest opportunity. 

 This partnership also guarantees that you will always have immediate access to parts and components, in case of an unexpected need, once TP Aerospace will maintain an inventory to support customers globally, besides simplifying the supply chain and logistics operations. 

 Honeywell will continue to maintain current contractual obligations on Boeing 737 Classic, but the remaining network and non-contractual customers should approach TP Aerospace directly. As our contractual obligations on Boeing 737 Classic expires, these will also be served by TP Aerospace directly. All future orders for these product categories will also be placed through TP Aerospace.  

 Should you have any other queries regarding part numbers and products eligible in this agreement or the appointment of TP Aerospace, please contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager or TP Aerospace at sales@tpaerospace.com &lt;[[mailto:sales@tpaerospace.com]]&gt;.
Yours sincerely, 

 Maria Sanchez 
 Customer Business Director
CONTACT US &lt;[[mailto:sales@tpaerospace.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
