<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_Americas_GDT_Email_Jackpot_amr.A/B jackpot subject line.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>You’ve hit the jackpot with a free subscription</subject>
    <textOnly>GoDirect™ Trade &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_content=Seller_Wizard]]&gt; creates a bridge between you and thousands of customers that have found a more efficient way to search and purchase parts. We’ve eliminated time consuming RFQs and made your inventory available 24 x 7, 365 days a year. NOW is the time to launch and here’s why: 






	- We’re offering you a FREE 6-month subscription. If you don’t love it, your subscription will expire automatically and you’ll never be charged a penny. If you do love it, you’ll pay a monthly fee (starting at $500 per month) depending on your needs.








	- With our Storefront Wizard, it takes five minutes to set up your digital storefront. Just load a banner/logo, attach storefront terms and conditions, then select the way your customers can pay (ex. credit card, PO). That’s it.








	- Since we’ve launched a year ago, we’ve already processed over $7M in online sales. Over half of these sales were from “new customers” that our storefronts had never sold to before. Don’t miss out on your piece of the pie. 





Be part of the online revolution. Launch your e-commerce storefront within minutes and see why Forbes, The Wall Street Journal and Yahoo! Finance are all talking about our marketplace.
GET STARTED &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/customer/oauth/login/user_type/customer/deeplink/bWFya2V0cGxhY2UvYWNjb3VudC9lZGl0UHJvZmlsZS8=?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=seller_wizard]]&gt;
Best regards, 

 Tony Perillo
 New Business Development Leader 
 GoDirectTrade.com (powered by Honeywell)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
