<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Apr_MC.202004_BK_Dealer_Newsletter_Apr_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>BendixKing Dealer Newsletter April 2020</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;                               Dealer Newsletter - April 
2020

NEWS BRIEFS

BREAKING NEWS:
AeroCruze 230 Awarded EASA Certification
This approval opens the doors for over 35 airframes to upgrade their KFC 150 autopilots to increase efficiency and safety within the European general aviation markets. Read Announcement&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/blogs/2020/april/aerocruze-230-receives-stc-from-easa]]&gt;

 Please contact your BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt; with any questions. 

BendixKing Partners 
of the Year Announced
BendixKing named three Partners of the Year this week based on their commitments to the quality of the BendixKing brand. Scandinavian Avionics was named our Global Partner of the Year. Duncan Aviation is our Partner of the Year for the Americas, and Hawker Pacific is our Asia-Pacific Partner of the Year. Congratulations to these partners, and we thank them for their hard work in supporting us over the past year. Find Your Repair Partner&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/repair-partners]]&gt;

OTHER NEWS:
AeroCruze 100 Support and Repair
Mid Continent Instruments is our exclusive source for AeroCruze 100 and xCruze (formerly TruTrak Vizion) autopilot repair and support. Please find their contact information on our website &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aerocruze-100]]&gt; for both their Kansas and California locations. 


FEATURED PRODUCT
INTRODUCING AEROPANEL 100 INTERCOM/AUDIO PANEL AeroPanel 100 is a convenient slide-in replacement for the BendixKing KMA 30. The music and Bluetooth capability provide unsurpassed audio flexibility throughout your airplane, and the 30-second digital recorder lets you play back any missed communications. AeroPanel 100 makes it simple to control audio throughout the aircraft including two music sources, 6-place intercom, and multiple audio inputs. Product Page&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeropanel]]&gt;


NEW VIDEO SECTION ON DEALER PORTAL
 &lt;[[https://bkdealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Videos/]]&gt;



CUSTOMER WEBINARS 
Upcoming: 
April 30, 2020 8pm EST 
“AeroVue Touch Integrated Panels” Join Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and Simon Williams from BendixKing discuss the award-winning AeroVue Touch, including the panel planning process, installation tips and whether the AeroVue Touch might be the right choice for your next panel upgrade. Register Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/1272090279735663875]]&gt;

On-Demand Webinars: 
“Automation and the Flight Envelope.” SocialFlight’s Jeff Simon and BendixKing’s Andrew Barker and Mariellen Couppee explore the levels automation, autopilots and aligning with 
the phases of flight. View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/eYb46FKXAzoM4dQwP2Up4w]]&gt; Access code: 850409

Who’s tracking your flights and how to protect your privacy? Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and 
Roger Dykmann from BendixKing discussed this and more in “Privacy in the Age of ADS-B”. 
View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/xsDShFJY2Z3WQnUTwE9qZU]]&gt; Access Code: 902384

“Five Hours from the U.S. to France in a Bonanza” What? How did Jeff Simon from SocialFlight and his sons accomplish this? Find out the details and how the AeroNav GPS navigator kept them on course.
View it Here&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/4XAGurqui4LZPWY8RBScb4?]]&gt; Access Code: 253747

SALES BULLETINS
2020BK-01 Over The Counter (OTC) Equipment Sales

2020BK-02 AeroCruze 230 Autopilot

2020BK-03 MST 67A (Trade-in Rebate) Upgrade to MST 70B 

2020BK-04 Dealer Demonstration Equipment Promotion

2020BK-05 RDR 
Weather Radar Upgrade Program

2020BK-06 CAS 66/67 TCAS II Change 7.1 Upgrade

2020BK-07 First Time Sales – Incentive Program

Complete list of 2020 Sales Bulletins &lt;[[https://bkdealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Documents/]]&gt; (must login to view)

Find your nearest BendixKing Area Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;


SIGN UP 
FOR DEALER NEWSLETTER
Were you forwarded this newsletter? Contact Lamonte &lt;[[mailto:lamonte.macon@honeywell.com?subject=Please%20opt%20me%20in%20for%20the%20BK%20Dealer%20Newsletter]]&gt; to get on our Dealer Newsletter list.


We have a new section on our Dealer Portal 
for videos. These short-form videos offer four-minutes of subjects from how to use the dealer portal to product overviews. These will be continually updated on the portal and we will include the updated list on each monthly newsletter.  

The Dealer Support Videos are those are specific to our dealer network, while the Product Support Videos provide product overviews - perfect to forward to your customers and sales teams! 

If you have any feedback or need further information, reach 
out to your regional Sales Manager &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team]]&gt;

DEALER SUPPORT VIDEOS
BK Confidence Plan: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/xxLjXmUArZH45mT3Yd69Qg]]&gt;

PRODUCT SUPPORT VIDEOS
AeroCruze 100 
affordable autopilot: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/2WJK3urHijfSkmHsWPmnXS]]&gt;

AeroFlight / KI 300 attitude indicator and KA 310 autopilot adapter: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/KnR5z6UWxJSxCc9kxKFbr8]]&gt;

AeroNav 900 GPS navigator: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/bNaefwRc3ga4ePq9azShaM]]&gt;

AeroVue Integrated Flight Deck: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/tN4jmhgxhs3vVd5Pu3cr5W]]&gt;

HeliVue Touch touchscreen PFD/MFD display specific for helicopters: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/zfo8D42iDFqpPTnpPhicCA]]&gt;

AeroCruze 230 touchscreen autopilot: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/Wotxp12uYggtjrDqR2AN2C?]]&gt;

AeroPanel 100 audio panel: View Now&gt;&gt; &lt;[[https://watch.honeywell.com/watch/ZuhUyoDWgDVAQRiiNRnvFr]]&gt;

Note: Current List and Links as of April 23, 2020




SHOWS &amp; EVENTS

Due to state and local governments current restrictions on public gatherings, in-person events and shows for April and May have been postponed or cancelled. 

We’re coming up with ways to keep in touch with you in some non-traditional ways, such as the product and support videos (mentioned above) created by our sales managers and participating in virtual shows, special edition online magazines and events. 

May 2nd, 2020: In lieu of the cancelled Great Alaska Gathering show, Alaska Skyways &lt;[[https://www.alaskaskywaysmagazine.com/]]&gt; magazine will publish a special digital magazine on behalf of the Airmen’s Association. Look for the BendixKing ad!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
