<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Airbus Survey Improvements 11.22.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell. Building on your feedback.</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;













 
 

 Honeywell. Building on your feedback. 












Round 2.
Building a better Honeywell starts by listening to an accomplished group of experts – you, and people throughout the industry like you.
The thoughts you share with us don’t end up forgotten in a drawer somewhere. They’re acted on. They become policy. They’re turned into a way of working that works for you.
Here’s the second of three updates on customer-based initiatives launched by Honeywell. Keep watching. And let’s keep talking. Together, we’ll build the most responsive company in aviation.








Communicate! Quickly. Accurately. Now.
What you told us: &quot;Getting information from Honeywell takes more time than customers have to spend. Responses are slow, and even simple questions take forever to resolve.&quot;
What we’ve done: Honeywell has set our sights on communication perfection. Our goal is to resolve 90% of customer inquiries within 48 hours. By next month.
To reach that number, we’re using every tool we’ve got. In some cases, we’ve gone back into training to make sure we’re covering the basics. We’ve cut red tape by combining, rewriting, or eliminating redundant communications. Every step of our process has been examined to speed up the way we share critical information with you.












AOG ASAP!
What you told us: &quot;Honeywell needs to start treating AOG situations with the urgency they deserve.&quot;
What we’ve done to correct the problem: For starters, we’re putting more Honeywell boots on the ground, increasing AOG support by 30%. A single-point-of-contact has been created to eliminate handoffs and confusion. Add to that a team that’s on-call any hour, any day, and you’ll find we’ve created a more comprehensive program.





What’s on your mind?
Let us know. You can share your thoughts at customerexperience@honeywell.com &lt;mailto:customerexperience@honeywell.com&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
