<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2019_03_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Hernadez_2019_03</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 Thank you for pausing from your busy day to read this email. Its purpose is to keep you in touch and informed about Honeywell-related news and developments such as the opening of the Honeywell Service Center in Brazil later this year. 
I am always available, so don’t hesitate to contact me for assistance. -- Robert
Did You Know?

Customers and technology intersect for Honeywell field service engineer

The intersection between customers and technology is a very comfortable spot for Honeywell Field Service Engineer David 
Heilman. He’s a “people person” who thrives on solving technical problems... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2019/march/customers-and-technology-intersect-for-honeywell-field-service-engineer]]&gt;.

Honeywell had a robust presence during HAI HeliExpo 2019

Honeywell&apos;s helicopter business showcased a wide range of engines and hybrid propulsion, avionics, connectivity and services solutions during 
the three-day event. One of the most anticipated announcements during the show was Honeywell&apos;s 21st Turbine-Powered Civil Helicopter Purchase Outlook. According to the forecast &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/press-release-listing/2019/march/honeywell-forecasts-4000-new-civil-helicopter-deliveries-over-next-five-years]]&gt;, North 
America leading healthy global market poised for 3 to 4 percent annual growth rate in deliveries, with light single-engine models being the most-desired product class, driven by demand by law enforcement agencies.

Honeywell is opening a service center in BrazilHoneywell will be opening repair center for avionics products later this year in Sao Jose Dos Campos, Brazil. Additional information will be coming soon.

Technical solutions at your fingertipsMyAerospace hosts articles to help business jet and helicopter operators solve technical issues &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/services-and-support/support/technical-support]]&gt;. For example, if you&apos;re having issues logging into Aerospace Software &amp; Data Services to download your navigation database, find out how to resolve it. Log in to the MyAerospace Technical Knowledge Center &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/account/login?returnUrl=%2FRedirects%2FSSO%2Ftechnical-knowledge-center]]&gt; and then search for article number 11138. 
Honeywell met with customers during Aero Expo Week
Honeywell hosted a reception during Aero Expo Week, in Toluca, Mexico. Approximately 120 customers from over 60 companies met with Honeywell specialists from Customer &amp; Product Support, Sales, BendixKing and the helicopter business to discuss products, services and issues. These events are a great place to network with Honeywell representatives and industry professionals. There&apos;s probably one in your area so check out the calendar and register &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2019/january/2019-operator-conferences]]&gt;! 

DU-875 LCD displays deliver better pilot experience for 
Jet-Care

“Honeywell’s DU-875 liquid crystal displays provide a better flying experience,” according to the chief pilot of Spectro | Jet-Care... Read More &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/case-studies/2019/january/du-875-lcd-displays-deliver-better-pilot-experience-for-jet-care]]&gt;.
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

Robert Hernandez, Jr
Customer Support Manager
Office: 602-365-2974
Mobile: 602-317-8915
Email: robert.a.hernandez@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:robert.a.hernandez@honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
