<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202003_Global_Internal-Comms_Supplier-Coronavirus-Government_Email_operational.E</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Notification of prioritization for DPAS-rated orders</subject>
    <textOnly>March 23, 2020 

Dear Aerospace DPAS Supplier, 

 It is our shared great privilege to be part of an industry that is critical to infrastructure, transportation, national and homeland security, preparedness, and defense. Most critical among our obligations to our customers is the obligation to fulfill orders under the Defense Priorities and Allocation System (DPAS), pursuant to the Defense Production Act. 

 This letter serves as a notification and reminder that you and your applicable sub-tier suppliers are required to prioritize materials and production and deliver DPAS-rated orders in these challenging times, in accordance with applicable law and pursuant to recent guidance from the Department of Defense. 

 You will recall the DPAS system is used to prioritize government programs and contracts throughout the supply chain to support critical military, energy, homeland security, emergency preparedness, and infrastructure requirements. Under the guidance of the Department of Homeland Security and the Department of Defense &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Defense Industrial Base Essential Critical Infrastructure Workforce_3222020.pdf]]&gt;, companies, contractors, and employees in the commercial and defense aerospace industry are 
designated as Essential Critical Infrastructure Workforce for the Defense Industrial Base, and have a special responsibility to maintain normal staffing and work schedules necessary to meet contract requirements. This specifically includes personnel performing under DO or DX rated defense contracts &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/DIB Memo Final Coord Copy for Sig 20 Mar 20 1750.pdf]]&gt;. 

 Together, we must maintain support for our United States Government customers who need our products and services now more than ever. We continue to be inspired by the resilience of our supplier partners as we face together the challenges of the coronavirus (COVID-19) situation. Thank you for all you do to ensure the health, safety, and welfare of your employees, while simultaneously supporting this critical work. 

 Sincerely, 

 Bob Buddecke
 Chief Procurement Officer
 Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
