<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Amer_BGA_MSP-Avionics_Email.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Releases New Extended programs under MSP Avionics</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 We understand that a big area of concern for our operators is product obsolescence. MSP Avionics has a wide offering of optional programs that provide customers an alternative option to expensive upgrades. These programs allow enrolled operators that experience a failure to exchange the obsolete part for an upgraded one.

 As you know, we currently offer Extended programs for DU-1310, DU-1080, DU-875, and Phase III. We continuously work to develop a broader coverage to help customer prepare for obsolescence. As a result, we have expanded our offerings!



	- CD830 Extended Program &lt;[[https://honeywellprod.sharepoint.com/:b:/t/AERO_Sales/EcqEigM95CdIptXfldxLOWkBhLPwmYAydtx0ii5PmIdeSg?e=dCJCiy]]&gt;: Control Display Units 810 and 820 are facing obsolescence, CD810 is currently out of repair capabilities and CD820 will no longer have them by the end of 2020. MSP Avionics is now offering an optional Extended program allowing an unlike exchange to CD830.
	- ED800 Extended Program &lt;[[https://honeywellprod.sharepoint.com/:b:/t/AERO_Sales/EZBYD3WhQ_ZAltSJGegBjOYB0ZkxlWC5hEo9LTeWP6EaQg?e=YxKCj0]]&gt;: Electronic Display 800 (ED800) is obsolete and going out of repair by the end of 2020. MSP Avionics is now offering an optional Extended program allowing an unlike exchange to CMA6800.


We would value the opportunity to discuss these options in more detail. If you would like to find out more, please send us an e-mail &lt;[[mailto:MSPAvionicsSales@Honeywell.com?subject=Learn%20more%20about%20CD830%20&amp;%20ED800%20Extended%20Programs]]&gt; and we will keep you informed.
LEARN MORE &lt;[[mailto:MSPAvionicsSales@Honeywell.com?subject=Learn%20more%20about%20CD830%20&amp;%20ED800%20Extended%20Programs]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
