<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202004_Global_Internal-Comms_MX-Supplier-Letter_Email_Operational.Email 1 - MX S</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell is here to help - Act Now</subject>
    <textOnly>April 2, 2020 

Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Valued Supplier}}, 

 In spite of the challenges we are facing together due to the coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak, we continue to be inspired and motivated by the resilience of our employees and our supplier partners. The health and safety of our employees, customers, and suppliers are always our top priority. 

 It is a great privilege for all of us to be part of an industry that is critical to our economy. As such, we understand that business continuity shall be safeguarded, to the extent allowed by the applicable laws, maintaining support for our customers who need our products despite the COVID-19 pandemic. As one of our valued suppliers, your partnership is crucial in making this possible. With that, we would like to note the following:



	- We declare (i) your company is a supplier of airtransport parts to Honeywell; (ii) such parts are deemed critical to a essential industry sector, which continuity is essential to the society; (iii) your company is considered strategic and essential for the maintenance of Honeywell operations;
	- Although the statements herein refers to the value of your company as a critical supplier for Honeywell and does not intend to be a binding legal opinion about the applicable laws in place, we highlight the exceptions to the inmediate suspension of activities expressly allowed by the decree published on March 30th, 2020 on the Mexican Federal Official Gazette (“AGREEMENT by which 
extraordinary measures have been established to address the sanitary emergency generated by the SARS-Co V2 virus” / “ACUERDO por el que se establecen acciones extraordinarias para atender la emergencia sanitaria generada por el virus SARS-CoV2”):


 “II. Only the following activities, considered essential, may remain in operation: (…)


 b) Activities related to public safety and citizen’s protection; in the defense of the national integrity and sovereignty” (…);

 
 c) Activities of the fundamental sectors of the economy: (…) transportation services of passengers and cargo (…) logistic (airports, ports, railroads) as well as activities which suspension may imply irreversible effects for its continuation;

 
 e) Activities needed for the conservation, maintenance and repair of the critical infrastructure which ensures the production and distribution of essential services; such as: (…) public transportation, (…), among others that can be listed in this category” 

 Honeywell is here to help, and we want to understand how your operations are being impacted by the COVID-19 pandemic. Please let Honeywell know as soon as possible if you have any material concerns about maintaining your production and deliveries to Honeywell. This will enable us to support you as needed to identify and develop solutions for any immediate or longer-term challenges you may be experiencing. 

 Please contact us right away if any authority has told you, or tells you in the future, that you need to suspend operations. Call your local Honeywell contact or send an email to AeroSupplierCommunications@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroSupplierCommunications@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. 

 We are all in this together. Again, thank you for all you do.

 Sincerely, 

 Sergio Pérez Torreslara
 Sr. Director, Strategic Sourcing Latin America
 Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
