<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201811_CPUseMyAerospace_lg.201811_CPUseMyAerospace_email_Channel</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Download New Guidebook and Submit Electronic Orders</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Honeywell Partner, 
 
Honeywell channel partners are members of a carefully selected and outstanding group of partner companies chosen because of their unique market reach, bias for growth, and a strong record of performance, integrity and compliance. Our ongoing work to refine our channel partner framework has created an environment for excellence that: 


	- Identifies and standardizes global best practices.
	- Enables our channel partners to follow a consistent model with a systematic and programmatic approach.
	- Operates with a global mind-set, while aligning and adopting to the regional and local customer base, markets and opportunities.


To facilitate and enhance the communication, productivity and profitability of this network, we created a new Channel Partner Guidebook &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Documents/Channel Partners/Channel Partner Guidebook.pdf?la=en&gt;. This guidebook consolidates the latest information into a single source, including:  


	- Channel partner expectations and responsibilities
	- An overview of the Channel Partner Scorecard, used to measure success
	- Information on the Honeywell Account Manager’s role and responsibilities
	- Training resources for the MyAerospace Portal and other Honeywell tools that foster efficiency and effectiveness
	- Details about co-marketing support available to partners and how to engage Honeywell’s marketing team
	- Information on the channel partner recognition program 


The guidebook is available on the Channel Partner Resource Center  &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us/channel-partners&gt;in the MyAerospace Portal. When using the guidebook, please reference the most current revision – it will be updated as needed and posted on MyAerospace.
 
This guidebook also outlines Honeywell Aerospace’s policy to use MyAerospace or Electronic Data Interface (EDI) tools to create orders for spares, repairs and overhaul. Effective January 15, 2019: 


	- We will no longer accept orders which are not created electronically through MyAerospace or EDI. 
	- Any order not entered electronically will be held at receiving until an electronic order is received.
	- Honeywell reserves the right to reject, and will have no liability for, orders which were not entered electronically. Adoption will be monitored and measured by the monthly scorecard.
	- Training and resource information is available on page 18.


What are the benefits of online ordering?


	- Improved performance ratings on the scorecard for cost-to-serve
	- Timely, seamless flows into the repair cycle
	- Order paperwork and documentation is 100% accurate, eliminating holds and delays
	- Immediate confirmation that the order has been placed


What is my action?


	- Read the new Channel Partner Guidebook &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Documents/Channel Partners/Channel Partner Guidebook.pdf?la=en&gt;.
	- Contact your Honeywell Account Manager if you have any questions or would like information about EDI solutions. 


Thank you for your business and continued support.



Sincerely,
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
