<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_CPS_Cosmos-Move_Email_Operational.Cosmo Move Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Coon Rapids, Minnesota Move Notification</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer, 

 As Honeywell advised in 2019, we have decided to optimize our operations and close our Coon Rapids, Minnesota facility by Q1 2021. The transition teams are engaged and details for all move phases are being incorporated into the overall project plan. As a reminder, the product lines affected by this transition include: 



	-  Commercial Inertial Reference Units (IRUs), Data Acquisition Units (DAU), Yaw Damper and Flame Sensors are moving to the Honeywell Clearwater, Florida site. (In process- partially moved)
	-  Digital Analog Adaptor (DAA), Air Data Computer (ADC), Air Data Management and Fuel Probe repairs are moving to the Honeywell Deer Valley, Arizona site. (Not started)
	-  We are also taking this opportunity to better align Control Sensor Products (CSP). This will move from our Golden Valley site to the Honeywell Clearwater, Florida site. (Complete) 



The fourth move involves the Air Data Inertial Reference Unit (ADIRU), Displays, Micro Inertial Reference Systems and 777 Fault Tolerant (FT) ADIRU &amp; Secondary Attitude and Air Data Reference Unit (SAARU) and supporting equipment moving to Honeywell Clearwater, Florida. 

 Original Equipment and Spares (Part 21)
 At this time, there is no change to how original equipment (OE) and aftermarket spares orders are ordered. During the course of this fourth move, Honeywell will be co-producing at both the Coon Rapids and Clearwater facilities.
 
Status of the Clearwater facility Production Approval Holder (PAH) System. 



	- The Honeywell Clearwater, Florida campus is in the process of obtaining their Part 21 production certification from the FAA. 
	- The initial FAA site survey was conducted the week of February 17, 2020. 
	- Until the Clearwater site receives their Part 21 production approval certification, they will be working under the direct supervision of the Coon Rapids production certificate. 


	- Coon Rapids oversite of all Clearwater work will occur.
	- Units will be shipped to Coon Rapids for induction into the Honeywell Production Approval Holder (PAH) system. 
	- Coon Rapids will certify (ie: 8130) and ship to the customer. 


	- Due to the COVID outbreak, FAA certification approval process/time we recommend that the Honeywell Clearwater Commercial Operations be established on your Approved Source List for the OE/Spare and repair hardware that is identified on this Part Number File &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Coon Rapids Part Numbers.xlsx]]&gt;. 


	- This will allow you to seamlessly order and receive these products from Honeywell Commercial Aviation. 




Information for Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 
 Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts. (Note: The Honeywell Clearwater Commercial Aviation campus spans the city line between Clearwater and Largo.) 


            Honeywell Name for Repairs:             Honeywell International Inc.
                                                                        
Clearwater Commercial Service Center 
 
            Honeywell Name for OE/Spares:        Honeywell International Inc.
                                                                        
Clearwater Commercial Operations
 
            Address: 
                                             13051 66th Street
                                                                        
 Plant 4
            City, Statue:                                         Largo, Florida
            Postal 
Code:                                        33773
            Country:                                              
 U.S.A.
            Cage Code: 
                                         65507


 Repair Unit Shipments (Part 145) 



	- View the list of impacted parts: Part Number File &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Coon Rapids Part Numbers.xlsx]]&gt;


OR


	- Access MyAerospace Repair Site Capability &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; list available 24x7.








Product Description


Repairs: Last receipt date at Coon Rapids



Repairs: First receipt date at Clearwater
 


New OE/Spares:  Establish Clearwater on the Approved Supplier List (ASL)




Micro IRUs, 777 FT ADIRU &amp; SAARU


July 17, 2020


July 20, 2020



-No change until Part 21 PAH is in place. 
-A separate notification will be sent at that time. 
-Establish Clearwater on the ASL prior to July 20, 2020.  








 Repair Order Processing 
To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions: 

 Existing Repair Orders 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Coon Rapids. 
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification. 
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity. 


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;. 




New Repair Orders 



	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the new location. 
	- Part numbers received on or before July 17, 2020 will be accepted at Coon Rapids. 
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Coon Rapids Last Receipt Date’ to Clearwater for repair. 


	- A PO/contract modification may be required. 
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity. 


	- The Repair Site Capability list will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs. 


AOG Support 
 There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware. 

 As we move closer to the next transition phase, we will be sending out additional communications specific to those product lines and part numbers. If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 

 Sincerely, 

 Honeywell Aerospace
 Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
