<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201709_EMEAI_Email_CPDLC_Mandate_mih.201707_EMEAI_EMAIL COMMUNICATION_CPDLC MAND</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>IMPORTANT: SESAR Data Link Services Mandate</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {{lead.First Name:default=Colleague}},

As a key component of the Single European Sky, the European Community has mandated the operational use of the Data Link Services (DLS) for aircraft flying above 28,500 feet. 
With a considerable portion of your investment in DLS upgrade recoverable 
through INEA funding, there has never been a better time to invest and get mandate compliant. Calls 2017 could be the last opportunity to submit projects and get them completed by the deadline 2020.


&quot;Protected Mode” Controller Pilot Data Link Communication (PM-CPDLC) by Honeywell &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/cpdlc_sesar_product_bulletin2.html]]&gt; has been identified by SESAR as a key technology in modernizing air-ground information exchanges and to open the door to future 
SESAR driven concepts. Our solutions are mapped through upgrades, STC, TC and platform centric upgrades for all major aircraft platforms. 
Honeywell has a comprehensive product portfolio providing data link solutions for many platform 
variations and these include:


	- 
Communication Management Unit / Functions for various aircraft types

	- 
Radios for various aircraft types

	- 
Cockpit voice recorder with datalink recording



What’s more: Loans available for funding Data Link upgrades 
The European Investment Bank (EIB) is collaborating closely with the SDM to further support Pilot 
Common Project (PCP) deployment and assist the timely deployment of technological improvements and complementing grants with other innovative financing mechanisms. Existing EIB financial products can be tailored to support a large number of borrowers sharing a business case to meet a wide range of financing needs via intermediated loans. 
 
Next steps
Remember, November 30, 2017 is the deadline for project proposal submission, and there’s not much time left. So, hurry up and get in touch 
with us &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/cpdlc_sesar_product_bulletin2.html]]&gt; for details on Honeywell’s suite of Data Link solutions. Also, download our informative SESAR Bulletin with details of funding, loan products and application process.
 
Warm regards
 
Richard Brand
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
