<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>StandardAero.JetWave for Falcon.JetWave Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>RE: Watch Netflix at 30,000 Feet on Your Falcon Jet</subject>
    <textOnly>   &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;                                                            &lt;[[http://standardaero.com/]]&gt;
FAST AND RELIABLE IN-FLIGHT CONNECTIVITY FOR FALCON 50 AND 900B/C/EX BY STANDARDAERO


Are you tired of slow connection speeds and putting your life on hold when you travel? So are we. 

Luckily, you don&apos;t have to any longer with Honeywell&apos;s in-flight internet upgrade, JetWave,™ available for Falcon 900B, 900C, 900EX and Falcon 50 by StandardAero.
               
                                                                                     
 JetWave is Honeywell’s new game-changing, high bandwidth cabin communications hardware, offering speeds up to 15 Mbps and world-wide coverage* so that you and your passengers can stream your favorite movies or TV shows, conduct HD video conferences, browse the web and more -- all at the same time.


It was created for business travelers, airlines and others so that you can do what you want when you want, even when you&apos;re flying at 50,000 feet. And, thanks to the JetConneX Ka-band service exclusive for JetWave, you&apos;ll always receive one of the fastest connection speeds in the industry.

So what are you waiting for? Learn more about JetWave and see for yourself why so many business jet operators have already made the switch to fast and reliable in-flight internet!
LEARN MORE &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/fast-and-reliable-in-flight-connectivity-for-falcon-50-by-standardaero]]&gt;
*Excludes polar regions.
© 2016 Honeywell International Inc.
&lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt;   &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;   
Terms of Use &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com/terms-conditions]]&gt; | Privacy Policy &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/privacy/pages/en.aspx]]&gt; | Contact Us &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/contact-us]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
