<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201709_Global_Nurture_ADS-B_mih.201709_Global_Nurture_S1-1_ADS-B_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Fly Commercial or Upgrade to ADS-B Out? You decide.</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

Dear Aircraft Operator,


The 2020 ADS-B Out Mandate requires transponders to meet the DO-260B standard – Extended Squitter and operation on radio frequency 1090 MHz. 
 

And you won’t be flying without one!

 As 2020 approaches, experts predict product availability will contract, while costs and installation lead times will increase significantly – by as much as 30 percent or more. 
 

Avoid the uncertainty, save money, time, and the hassles by upgrading today!  



HONEYWELL HAS CERTIFIED ADS-B OUT UPGRADE SOLUTIONS 
FOR THESE AIRCRAFT 
 FANS 1/A and TCAS 7.1 CERTIFIED UPGRADES ARE ALSO AVAILABLE



Challenger 601 1A/3A

Gulfstream PlaneView Cockpits 
G350 / 450 / 500 / 550



Global 5000 &amp; Global Express
Gulfstream IV / IV-SP / V


Learjet 40 /45 &amp; 40XR / 45XR
Citation Sovereign / III / VI / VII /X


Falcon F900 Series, F2000 Series, F7X (EASy)
Textron Cessna Citation Model 550 and 560 (Ultra, Encore, Bravo, Excel, XLS)



Falcon 900A / B / C / EX 
(Non-EASy)

Hawker 800 / 1000 4000


Legacy 600 / 650





The aircraft listed are subject to change. Additional components may be impacted or required. Contact your Honeywell representative or preferred service center for specific upgrade configurations for your aircraft. 



 Honeywell has affordable and certified ADS-B Out solutions that provide compliance with minimal impact to your aircraft during the upgrade. You’ll be back in the air quickly. 







LEARN MORE  &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2017_ADS-B_Upgrade.html]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
