<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Cross SBU.Honeywell Customer Pricing Report 01262016</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing Honeywell&apos;s Customer Pricing Report</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.youtube.com/honeywell]]&gt;
 &lt;[[https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475]]&gt;
 &lt;[[http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt;










Honeywell’s Customer Pricing Reports.
Information and prices organized for only the products you use. 
Honeywell’s new guide to aftermarket products is right on time and right on the money.  

Creating your own, Customer Pricing Report is simple:



 




Just log into the Honeywell MyAerospace portal &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.com/]]&gt;,
 and request your report based on your customer account number.  

 




The Customer Pricing Report can be customized with up to 1,000 unique part numbers, and provide current prices for published parts. Or request a pricing report based on your last 2 years of purchases.
Within 24-hours of your request, we’ll notify you by email that your report is complete and available for downloading for 30 days through the portal.


Along with the products and prices you’ve asked for, Honeywell’s Customer Pricing Report includes Price Modification dates so you can easily identify changes. As well as new data fields including Airworthiness Eligibility, Manufacturing Cage Code, and Special Notes.  
Try it for yourself. Go to the portal for more information on what Honeywell’s Customer Pricing Reports can mean for your business. And – as always – if you have questions or comments, contact us at MyAerospacePortalIssue@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:MyAerospacePortalIssue@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
