<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201911_BK_Webinar_AeroFlight-SocialFlight_amr.A/B test Invite 1.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join us for a webinar Nov. 21 at 4 p.m. Eastern: BendixKing AeroFlight KI 300</subject>
    <textOnly>Webinar:
 Ditch the Pump: FAA Regs &amp; Tips for Electronic AI Installation 

 Date: 
 Thursday, November 21, 2019 – 4pm ET 

 Mechanical vacuum systems and gyros have been the weakest link in general aviation aircraft for decades. Electronic Attitude Indicators, such as BendixKing&apos;s AeroFlight KI 300 &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/products/aeroflight]]&gt;, make it economically possible to remove mechanical gyros and the entire vacuum system, improving reliability and safety while increasing the useful load of the aircraft. However, understanding the FAA regulations is critical to making sure that you have a plan that will work for your aircraft and your budget. 

 Join BendixKing Product Marketing Manager and avid pilot, Steven Pearce, along with SocialFlight President, Jeff Simon, an A&amp;P/IA mechanic, as they discuss the regulations pertaining to electronic attitude indicators and vacuum system removal, as well as the AeroFlight KI 300. 

 Topics include:
 


	- The Evolution of Attitude Systems
	- PFDs vs AIs
	- The regulations of replacement
	- Avoiding pitfalls during your conversion
	- AeroFlight KI 300 
 
 Produced in association with SocialFlight.com &lt;[[http://www.socialflight.com/search.php]]&gt;, your webinar registration includes FREE access to information on over 10,000 aviation events, destinations, airport restaurants, contests and more listed on SocialFlight.com, the SocialFlight mobile apps and Local Aviation Event Planner.
REGISTER HERE &lt;[[https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/275594091871253003]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
