<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Pro Star Aviation.Intro Email.ProStar Intro Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The ADS-B Out STC for Your Aircraft is Here</subject>
    <textOnly>     &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;                                                    &lt;[[http://prostaraviation.com/]]&gt;
Facebook      &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/HoneywellAero]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/HoneywellAviation]]&gt;                                                              Facebook      &lt;[[https://www.facebook.com/Pro-Star-Aviation-LLC-181065918611760/]]&gt; LinkedIn      &lt;[[https://www.linkedin.com/company/pro-star-aviation]]&gt; Twitter      &lt;[[https://twitter.com/prostaraviation]]&gt; YouTube &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/user/ProStarAviation]]&gt;
The ADS-B Out STC for Your Aircraft by Pro Star Aviation and Honeywell



Pro Star Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out STC
Did you know that only 1 in 10 operators have yet to find a solution for their aircraft to meet the January 1, 2020 ADS-B Out deadline? Fortunately, with Pro Star Aviation’s ADS-B Out approved maintenance list STC for your aircraft featuring Honeywell&apos;s Primus® II Radio System, you can ensure your travel plans in 2020.



Pro Star Aviation&apos;s ADS-B Out AML STC covers:



	- Bombardier Global Express
	- Bombardier Challenger 601
	- Bombardier Learjet 40 &amp; 45
	- Cessna Citation 550, 560, 650 &amp; 750
	- Hawker 800 &amp; 1,000



Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio System
When you upgrade your existing Honeywell Primus II Radio and add a stand-alone GPS receiver, you’ll enjoy a cost-effective solution combined with the latest configuration to meet the ADS-B Out mandate. Fly with confidence with Honeywell&apos;s Primus II Radio equipped with a Mode S Transponder and receive:



	- Increased aircraft positioning accuracy with full, WAAS capability

	- 
Reduced separation and highly accurate departure and arrival times


	- 
Surveillance in areas that do not currently have radar coverage 


	- 
A clear view of vehicles and runways in order to avoid collisions or delays 


	- 
More efficient spacing and optimal routing in non-radar environments




ADS-B Out Resources
In just a few short weeks, you’ll receive more information about the STC, the solutions offered and how Pro Star Aviation can equip your aircraft with a solution to comply with the ADS-B Out mandate in 2020. Avoid delays and learn more about the ADS-B Out deadline to see how Honeywell&apos;s integrated solutions can help:




	- The Ins and Outs of ADS-B DO-260B Compliance &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2015/october/the-ins-and-outs-of-the-ads-b-do-260b-compliance]]&gt;


	- The ADS-B Mandate: What You Need to Know &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2015/february/mandates-automatic-dependent-surveillance-broadcast]]&gt;


	- The ADS-B Deep Dive &lt;[[https://www.mygdc.com/assets/public_files/gdc_services/pilot_services/presentations/ADS_B_Deep_Dive.pdf]]&gt;






Pro Star Aviation
Based in the Northeast United States, Pro Star Aviation is an FAA Part 145 Repair Station specializing in business and corporate aircraft. Capabilities include; aircraft maintenance, engine service, avionics repair and service, avionics installations, structural modifications and  STC development service. Our company specializes in the following; Special Missions/ALE projects, Cabin Entertainment systems, Avionics Installations, Engineering and STC ODA &amp; DER services.
Privacy Statement &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Privacy]]&gt;     © 2016 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;[[http://www.honeywell.com]]&gt;     Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;[[http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
