<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2017 Helicopter Newsletter Q2.201704_Global_Email_HeliNewsletterQ2_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell&apos;s Helicopter Newsletter for Q2 has landed!</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
QUARTERLY HELICOPTER NEWSLETTER
Q2 2017
THE Q2 EDITION HAS LANDED!
In this edition of the Helicopter Newsletter, we will retrospectively look at 2016 as well as look ahead to the remaining months of 2017. Overall, we remain cautiously optimistic that 2017 will be stronger than 2016. Through our discussions with industry experts (OEMs, operators, channel partners), we are beginning to see signs of stabilization and in some locales and missions, positive growth.

While some areas of the industry remain constrained, we are hopeful that new OEM deliveries in 2017 will reflect some level of positive growth over 2016 levels. On the Aftermarket side, our customers are seeing increased levels of interest/quotes, which in time, will cascade into increased levels of orders and bookings.

Here at Honeywell, we firmly believe that we are only as good as our team, so we encourage you to learn more about our channel partners, DSI as well as Truth Data. Lastly, as the ADS-B Out Mandate compliance date nears, we encourage you to learn more about our Bendix King solutions.



Regards,

Rick Angelo
Director of Strategic Marketing: Global Commercial Helicopters
A Retrospective of 2016 and Looking Ahead at 2017 
 
Our editor had an opportunity to sit down with Rick Angelo, Global Director of Strategic Marketing for Honeywell Aerospace. A 20-year veteran of the Aerospace industry, Angelo has worked in a number of Marketing Research, Strategy and Business Development roles for Honeywell, Bell Helicopter and Heli-One... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/may/a-retrospective-of-2016-and-looking-ahead-at-2017]]&gt;
Honeywell and Truth Data Offer One-Stop HEMS Solution
 
Honeywell and Truth Data are working together to provide an affordable and complete solution just in time to help Helicopter Air Ambulance (HAA) operators meet the FAA Flight Data Monitoring (FDM) mandate... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/may/honeywell-and-truth-data-offer-one-stop-hems-solution]]&gt;
HUMS Legacy Defines Honeywell Partner DSI 
 
The legacy of Chadwick-Helmuth is alive and well at Diagnostic Solutions International (DSI), a Honeywell channel partner specializing in Health and Usage Monitoring Systems (HUMS). Chadwick-Helmuth pioneered the then-new technology of vibration test and measurement systems in the 1950s and developed the first Vibration Analysis System for Hughes Helicopter in the early 1960s... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/may/hums-legacy-defines-honeywell-partner-dsi]]&gt;
Honeywell Receives STC for Onboard VXP System
 
The Federal Aviation Administration has issued a supplemental type certificate (STC) to Honeywell that enables installation of the VXP Vibration Monitoring and Rotor Track &amp; Balance system on Airbus AS350/H125 helicopters, and allows real time notice of system alerts through the Sky Connect Tracker III Iridium satellite communications system... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/april/honeywell-receives-stc-for-onboard-vxp-system]]&gt;
Product Spotlight: Sky Connect Tracker System 

SKY CONNECT TRACKER III is the industry&apos;s proven solution for lightweight satellite communications. Worldwide tracking, 2-way messaging, and telephone services are combined with flight data monitoring capabilities to meet new mandates... View the new infographic. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/~/media/aerospace/files/infographics/n40-1915-001-001-skyconnect_portrait_ig.pdf]]&gt;
Product Spotlight: Aspire 200 Satellite Communications System
 
The Aspire® 200 Satellite Communications System is Honeywell&apos;s smallest Inmarsat SwiftBroadband system enabling simultaneous voice and data connectivity at rates up to 650kbps on all classes of aircraft... Watch the video. &lt;[[https://youtu.be/3xZh2dd65h8]]&gt;
Honeywell Forecasts 3,900 to 4,400 Global Helicopter Deliveries Over Next Five Years
 
In its 19th annual “Turbine-Powered Civil Helicopter Purchase Outlook,” Honeywell forecasts 3,900 to 4,400 civilian-use helicopters will be delivered from 2017 to 2021, roughly 400 helicopters lower than the 2016 five-year forecast... Watch the video. &lt;[[https://youtu.be/KzG3PoRj9no]]&gt;
ADS-B Solved for Helicopters
 
Helicopter operators may find themselves muttering a few choice words as they watch the clock tick down to Jan. 1, 2020. That’s the date their helicopters need to be equipped with ADS-B Out technology mandated by the FAA if they want to keep operating in U.S. ADS-B controlled airspace... Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2017/may/ads-b-solved-for-helicopters]]&gt;
Subscribe to the Honeywell Aerospace Newsletter
 
Simply provide your email address and we’ll drop you a line when we have updates. Some of our newsletters are monthly and others are quarterly. You can unsubscribe through the email anytime.  
   CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/newsletter]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
