<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202009_Global_HCE_Datalink-providers_Email.Email 1</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>5 Reasons Choosing the Right Datalink Provider Matters</subject>
    <textOnly>Your flight department needs accurate and reliable global communications between your aircraft cockpit and ground-based network. What are key things to look for when choosing a datalink communication provider? 

Here are 5 reasons to consider Honeywell for a Datalink Provider



	- You get the support you need – Honeywell provides 24/7 datalink service support with highly experienced and technically trained staff.
	- Your connectivity experience should be best-in-class – Unlike other providers, Honeywell uses all networks wherever available and uses the highest VHF connection speed available. This means in most of the world your aircraft will utilize the best connection and have redundant connectivity, giving the pilots peace of mind and better experience.
	- Your hardware and aircraft are supported – With Honeywell, your datalink solution is supported on all types of aircraft data-communications hardware. 
	- It’s compatible with all third-party flight plans 
	- Honeywell continues to develop and innovate – it’s not just datalink. We are constantly looking for ways to make the service work harder for your flight department. 


Honeywell Forge does this and more with our datalink offering. Our team leverages more than 30 years in the industry and greatly reduces workload for your pilots and dispatchers. Our flight data specialists are available to help you around the clock. Whether you need to request information, forward a message or troubleshoot – we’re there for you, by phone, email, text or ACARS message. 

Contact our team &lt;[[https://www.aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt; for a hassle-free trial today.
Start a Trial &lt;[[https://www.aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/connected-aircraft/business-aviation/flight-services?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=20_honeywellforge_bga]]&gt;
Honeywell&apos;s Datalink is compatible with third-party flight plans. Here is a list of vendors we are integrated with: 
 






Skyplan 



RocketRoute


ForeFlight


Jeppesen




Air Support

FlightPlan.com

Navtech


GDFS



Universal
UAS
HONEYWELL FORGE GIVES MORE PILOTS ACCESS TO DIGITAL ATIS INFO 

The latest version of our datalink software is able to translate digital Automatic Terminal Information Service (D-ATIS) information for display on the pilot’s flight management system or electronic flight book screen. Honeywell is the only datalink provider that offers both ARINC and SITA ground networks as standard worldwide offering.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
