<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202007_Americas_GDT_Sell-More_Spark_Email.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>A Spark Your Company May Need</subject>
    <textOnly>More than two thirds of shoppers are buying online for the first time and more than half are spending more online. Read Now &lt;[[https://www.digitalcommerce360.com/article/coronavirus-impact-online-retail/]]&gt;.

 You can count on GoDirect Trade to keep your aircraft flying. We are an online aerospace marketplace, powered by Honeywell that has over 75 active storefronts and $2B of quality listings for sale. We see ourselves as an extension to your business that can help you gain an additional revenue source. 

 Below are two services we can offer you today that can spark your growth with zero upfront costs. 

 The ability to reach a large group of customers virtually will become even more critical than it’s been in the past. List your inventory and sell to over 7,500 buyers across 3,000+ companies. For a limited time only, we are offering a no-obligation 8-month free subscription. 

 VIRTUAL CONSIGNMENT SERVICES

 With our Virtual Consignment Service, Honeywell Aerospace Trading &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/hat-consignment-services]]&gt; (HAT) sells your inventory through GoDirect Trade. Once the customer provides the list of parts to sell, GoDirect Trade will list the product, and HAT will field all inquiries and manage the entire sales process. Inventory is physically kept at your customer’s site.
CHECK IT OUT &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/hat-consignment-services?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Sell_More]]&gt;
LAUNCH AN E-COMMERCE STOREFRONT

 Or, you can launch a storefront in less than five minutes because it’s only three easy steps. The best part about this option is that we offer all customers a FREE, no-obligation 8-month storefront subscription with unlimited listings and transactions.
SIGN UP &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/customer/account/create/?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=Sell_More]]&gt;
Stay healthy, stay safe, and take care, 

 Lisa Butters
General Manager
GoDirectTrade.com &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=email&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=User_Growth]]&gt; (powered by Honeywell)</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
