<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201702_EMEAI_STC_Alert_CD-830_NJM.201702_EMEAI_STC_Alert_CD-830_NJM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell | STC Alert - CD-830</subject>
    <textOnly>STC Alert: CD-830 Touchscreen FMS Control Display Unit



Dear valued partners,

Honeywell is pleased to announce the availability of Supplemental Type Certificates for the new CD-830 Touchscreen Control Display Unit (CDU).
The CD-830 is a direct plug-and-play replacement for the now obsolete CD-810 / CD-820. This high resolution display offers full touch screen functionality with enhanced visibility and is compatible with NZ-2000/2010 and IC-800/810 Flight Management Systems (FMS).
Honeywell’s 4th-generation CDU provides significant benefits compared to previously released display units. The latest design increases reliability, reduces weight, provides improved cockpit aesthetics and touch-screen display technologies that are proven in the cockpit environment to enhance the human-machine interface.
A number of STC’s have been developed to support this upgrade, please refer to Honeywell Service Bulletin (HSB #2017-27 REV-A &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/~/media/aerospace/files/brochures/2017-27-cd-830-rev-a-control-display-unit-for-business-aircraft-bro.pdf]]&gt;). For those operators currently using the CD-820, Honeywell is offering a US$10,000 trade-in credit. Click Here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/cd-830-touchscreen-fms-control-display-unit]]&gt; for more details and to download the Service Bulletin and Product Brochure.
As part of our commitment to our dealer network, we are offering marketing support for this campaign through joint-branded communications to your affected customers. Should you want further information, please contact me or our new Channel Marketing Manager, Nick Maynard (nick.maynard@honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Nick.Maynard@Honeywell.com]]&gt;)
Should you have any further queries, please contact your Honeywell ASM. Alternatively, please do feel free to contact me directly.
Marc Parizot

Aftermarket Program Manager,

EMEAI






FIND OUT MORE  &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/cd-830-touchscreen-fms-control-display-unit]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
