<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ADE.Knowledge Center.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Portal:  Quick Answers to Technical Questions</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com]]&gt;
MYAEROSPACE PORTAL | QUICK ANSWERS TO TECHNICAL QUESTIONS
QUICK ANSWERS TO TECHNICAL QUESTIONS
Looking for a quick technical answer?  Search our online technical solutions and learn how similar issues have been resolved across the fleet.
 
We are continuously improving your online experience and have now updated the Technical Knowledge Center on the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;. This update, based upon customer feedback, improves your access to technical solutions, troubleshooting information, and case history with Aerospace Technical Support.
 
The updated Technical Knowledge Center provides you with solutions to common technical problems, accessing the latest support videos, publications and operational alerts. You can also search your open technical cases, closed cases, or create a new one.
 
Navigation is simplified and intuitive with a refreshed and consistent view.  You can quickly sort by aircraft or product types and filter by resource type.  The technical resources are maintained and updated by Honeywell service experts with new assets being added regularly.



For quick access to technical solutions, access the MyAerospace Portal &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt; and choose the “Technical Knowledge Center”.  

Click here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/myaerospace-updates]]&gt; to get the latest MyAerospace Portal news.  Would you like to be part of the next MyAerospace Portal enhancement? Sign up here &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/myaerospace-updates]]&gt; to participate in our next user research study and help us improve it, together.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
