<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2018_05_C&amp;PS_CSM_Emails.Malone_May_2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Customer Connect</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Customer Connect

Dear Honeywell Customer:
 

Hello, it’s LaCretia again with some news from Honeywell that can help you with your everyday activities. This information will help you get the most out of our products and services. I’m here to assist you with whatever you need, so please don’t hesitate to contact me for further assistance.
Did You Know?

Honeywell’s continued focus 
on improving the customer experience has driven a number of improvements in recent months. We’ve been listening to you and many of these enhancements are directly related to your input. Read more. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/2018_05_CPS_CSM_Emails_LandingPAge.html]]&gt;

Field Service Pro Stands Behind Every Honeywell 
Engine 

Ryan Goldstein has your back. A senior field service engineer with more than 25 years’ experience in aviation repair and maintenance, Goldstein is often the first point of contact for customers with propulsion engine or auxiliary power unit questions or issues. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/news-listing/2018/may/field-service-pro-stands-behind-every-honeywell-engine]]&gt;

Recent Operators Conferences Held Around the World
Honeywell Aerospace hosted Operators Conferences in United States, China and Chile. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/pages/recent-operators-conferences-held-around-the-world]]&gt;

Upcoming Operators Conferences
Operators Conferences are being scheduled in all 
regions - join us to learn more about Honeywell products and services that are critical to your flight department. Read more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/events-listing/2018/january/2018-operator-conferences]]&gt;
If you need additional customer support, I am your point of contact. Please reach me at:


 

LaCretia Malone 
Direct: 480-592-4598 
Mobile: 480-307-2819
Email: LaCretia.Lever@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:LaCretia.Lever@Honeywell.com]]&gt;

  &lt;[[mailto:LaCretia.Lever@Honeywell.com]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
