<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>FMS Newsletter 2014.October 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Direct-TO Newsletter - October 2014</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Direct-TO Newsletter
October 2014 Issue
Honeywell Pilot Gateway - iPad and iPhone App Now Available &lt;http://107.23.57.149/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/October%202014/Pilot%20Gateway%20App&gt;

The Pilot Gateway App is now available in the Apple App Store.  Building on the success of the Pilot Gateway website, the app brings additional functionality to iPhones and iPads...


The Radar Corner - The RDR-4000 3D Volumetric Radar:
The Beginning Part 3

This month’s article concludes Direct-TO’s look at the RDR-4000 Human Factors Study and examines how participants performed in the task simulator...


Go Direct™ Briefing - RNP Minima Values on RNAV (GPS) Approaches &lt;http://107.23.57.149/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/October%202014/RNAV%20GPS%20and%20RNP&gt;

Honeywell has received multiple reports of an “RNP 0.3” minima selection displaying instead of LNAV or LNAV/VNAV when loading an RNAV (GPS) approach...


Agusta AW139 - Full Time DME Presentation Issue for AW139 Phase 7 &lt;http://107.23.57.149/sitecore/content/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/October%202014/AgustaDME&gt;

An issue has been discovered on some AW139 helicopters in which the fulltime DME display will show only the onside distance and station ID on each PFD...


Tools of the Trade - BendixKing KSN 770 &lt;http://107.23.57.149/Pilots/Newsletters/2014/October%202014/KSN%20770&gt;

Since 1959, BendixKing has been building reliable solutions for aircraft, with many thousands of legacy products still in use today...


Learn More &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/O0i0g8gX0200ZQqE0i0G24I&gt;

Technical Publications, Videos, news, events, and other resources for pilots can now be found on the new Honeywell Pilot Gateway.  Click Here &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/O0i0g8gX0200ZQqE0i0G24I&gt; to get started.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2014 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
