<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201903_Global_BK_Channel_Newsletter_MC.201903_Global_BK_Channel_Newsletter_MC</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>March BendixKing Channel Newsletter</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;
 

BendixKing Channel Newsletter | March 2019
&lt;[[http://www.bendixKing.com]]&gt;
Channel Partner Program
 The Channel Partner Program &lt;[[https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Dealer-Newsletters]]&gt;* contains a new table that explains the revenue goals and associated benefits for each tier level in the program, as well as an introduction of our new products. Please take note of some key changes to the program:



	- Line Replacement Units (LRU) discounts vary by tier level,
	- The annual rebate is no longer part of the program, and
	- New products for experimental aircraft have been added.


Co-Op Program
 Here is the 2019 BendixKing Co-Op Program &lt;[[https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Dealer-Newsletters]]&gt;*. The earning periods for Co-Op credits earned remain semi-annual, but we have extended the claim period this year from 3 to 5 months, allowing more opportunity to use your Co-Op credits to your advantage.

 Authorized Repair Partners
 We are pleased to announce 
the addition of Jet Avionics Equipamentos Aeronauticos as a new Authorized Repair Partner &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/pages/repair-partners]]&gt;. 

Changes in Sales Regions
We have added a new sales manager, Simon Williams, and realigned some of our sales regions. Please visit sales team &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/sales-team?mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiWldNNE5HSXhZV1kzTkRjdyIsInQiOiJyckJNdm01SVVIRDNZWWozdGVGaXhZUmxyeDJXa0I4VkgxdUpKeTdocGZNSTRQRXd4SXBGY2Vkb1M2WDlkbXVqbVBMU3plamNFcmlISUFtNTdpUGdXdz09In0%3D]]&gt; to see the changes that we’ve made.

 Technical Support Update
 Here is a customer question that we recently received.

 Question: GPS Rollover occurring April 6th 2019 - will it affect my BendixKing GPS Navigator?

 Answer: No, the GPS Week Rollover Event will not affect any of the BendixKing GPS 
products listed below (all part numbers and software levels):



	- KSN 765/770
	- KLN 94
	- KLN 89/B
	- KLN 90/A/B
	- KLX 135/A
	- KLN 35/A
	- KLN 900


We want 2019 to be another growth year for both you and BendixKing. We will continue to provide new products, offer marketing support and develop new business relationships to make this year a success for all of you in our channel network. 

 You can find sales bulletins posted here &lt;[[https://dealers.bendixking.com/Dealer-Portal/Sales-Bulletins]]&gt; or on www.myaerospace.com &lt;[[http://www.myaerospace.com/]]&gt;.
 Contact us at support &lt;[[https://www.bendixking.com/en/contact-us]]&gt; for technical support or visit us at www.bendixking.com &lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/]]&gt;. 


 *Can be found in the dealer portal under Dealer Resources / Channel Programs &amp; Newsletters</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
