<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202005_Global_C&amp;PS_Announcement_A_Email_Operational.Email 5: Wave 4 Anniston Tra</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Anniston, Alabama - Wave 4 Cutover Reminder</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 

 Honeywell Aerospace recently provided an update regarding our Anniston site closure. In that communication, Honeywell provided the complete cut-over schedule and instructions on how to prepare for the upcoming transition. A copy of that communication can be found here &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Original Honeywell Annison Communication.pdf]]&gt;.  

 This notice is to remind you of the upcoming ship-to changes required before October 3, 2020 for Wave 4 part numbers. Repairs Site Capabilities &lt;[[https://aerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated on September 30, 2020, to enable updates prior to the October 3 ship-to change.

 The part numbers affected in this transition can be located here. &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Honeywell_Anniston_Impacted-Parts-by-Wave_82020.xlsx]]&gt;

 To minimize delays, please follow these guidelines and actions:

 New Repair Orders

 Shipment to the new repair stations for Wave 4 part 
numbers begins on October 3, 2020. Honeywell Repairs Site Capabilities will be activated to facilitate shipment to the new repair stations on September 30, 2020. Anniston will no longer induct Wave 4 parts for repair after October 9, 2020. 




	- For Wave 4 units received in Anniston after October 9, 2020, the orders will be forwarded to the new repair station. The Honeywell Customer Service team will request an updated PO with the new repair station address to ensure the 8130 tag matches the repair station on your Purchase Order.
	- Units received in Anniston after 1November 3, 2020 (30-days since October 3, 2020 cutover) will be returned to the sender, for routing to the proper Honeywell Repair Station.


EDI Order Management Impact (AeroXchange, B2B Aero): 

 For customers using EDI/M2M order management solutions, the option to create orders for the new repair station will be available on or before 9/4/2020. Please note that the link between EDI/M2M orders created in Anniston but requiring transition to the new repair station will be 
disconnected. These orders will need to be completed manually with any remaining actions administered through the CSR organization (AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;). 

 Unfinished Anniston Repair Orders Moving to New Repair Station: 

 A small number of repair orders that started work in Anniston will need to be transferred to the new site for repair completion, once the equipment moves to the new repair station. These units will go on hold once received at the new site, to seek Customer preference on finishing repair at the new repair station. 

 There are 2 options for addressing these impacted orders, your Honeywell Customer Service Representative will reach out if your orders are impacted: 




	- Provide an updated/new PO with the new site address.


	- Honeywell Customer Service Representative will provide a list of orders that need to be updated.


	- Provide e-mail approval to allow work completion at the new site under the Anniston PO.


	- The Honeywell CSR will use this approval to clear all units on hold for revised/new PO and ship from the new repair location under the original Anniston PO. Please note: 8130 tag will be from the new repair station, not Anniston.




What to do now?




	- Ensure the new repair stations identified in the Transition Wave list are qualified on your approved supplier list and update the Part Numbers in Wave 4 for shipment to the new repair station starting October 3, 2020. 
	- Anniston will no longer receive units after October 9, 2020 for Wave 4 outlines, they will be forwarded to the new repair station for processing.


 If you need to conduct an on-site audit, please email Norman.Dubay@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:Norman.Dubay@honeywell.com]]&gt; to request an audit. 

Authorized Supplier List (ASL) &amp; Quality Information 





Site 
CAGE Code
Repair Station ID
Address


Phoenix - Deer Valley
58960
FAA HQ7R766N 
EASA.145.4539 
Deer Valley QA Package &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Deer-Valley-QA-Package_FAA-EASA-AS9100-OpsSpec.pdf]]&gt;

Honeywell International Inc. 
21111 N 19th Avenue 
PHOENIX, AZ 85027 
US




Tempe, AZ 
59364
FAA ZN3R030M 
EASA.145.4136 
Tempe QA Package &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Tempe-QA-Package_FAA-EASA-CAAC-OpsSpec-AS9100.pdf]]&gt;

Honeywell International Inc.
1300 W WARNER RD
TEMPE, AZ 85284
US




Torrance, CA
70210
FAA DO3R456L 
EASA 145.4135 
Torrance QA Package &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Torranc-QA-Package_FAA-EASA-OpsSpec.pdf]]&gt;

Honeywell International Inc.
2525 W 190TH ST
TORRANCE, CA 90504-6002
US




 Transition Schedule





Product Line Description
Wave 
New Repair Station
Begin Shipment to New Repair Station 


Existing Dual Capability Valves &amp; Starters
1 &amp; 2
Tempe 
Aug. 21, 2020


Air Cycle Machines / Fan Blowers
3
Torrance
Sept. 7, 2020


Electronics
3
Phoenix – Deer Valley
Sept. 7, 2020


Remaining Valves &amp; Starters 
3
Tempe 
Sept. 7, 2020


Thermostats/Actuators
4
Tempe 
Oct. 3, 2020


Air Motors/Gear Boxes
5
Tempe 
Oct. 26, 2020




If you have any questions about this transition, please contact your Honeywell Business Manager, Customer Support Manager or other Honeywell representative. 


Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace 
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
