<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>20190815_Global_OdysseyRenton_KFK.20190815_OdysseyRenton_Email_KFK</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News About the Honeywell Renton, Washington Facility</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
Dear Customer, 


Honeywell Aerospace recently announced the transition of the Honeywell Renton, Washington Repair &amp; Overhaul activity to the Honeywell Olathe, Kansas facility. To minimize risk and customer impact, this transition has been planned with five moves. The first move starts in September 2019 and all moves will be completed by late February 2020. This communication addresses all move schedules tied to the Renton work transfer. 

A review of repair order history (2 years) indicates that you have sent in a part number for repair for at least one of the impacted part numbers. 

Repair Unit Shipments 



	- View the Part Number and Move Schedule &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Renton PN list by Wave 081419.xlsx]]&gt; file to determine the date that each part number will move. Locate the move sequence number and match to the ‘Renton Last Receipt Date’ identified in the chart below.


-- OR --


	- Access MyAerospace Repair Site Capability &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; list available 24x7.


Move Sequence by Product Line and Date 
**Please retain for your files**

 



Repair Order Processing 

To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions. 

Existing Repair Orders 



	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Renton.
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification.
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity.


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com.




New Repair Orders 



	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the correct location.
	- Part numbers received on or before the ‘Renton Last Receipt Date’ will be accepted at Renton.
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Renton Last Receipt Date’ to Olathe for repair.


	- A PO/contract modification may be required.
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity.


	- The Repair Site Capability list will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs.



AOG Support 

There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware. 

Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 

Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts. 


        Company Name: Honeywell International Inc.
        Address: 23500 West 105th Street
        City, State: Olathe, Kansas
        Postal Code: 866061
        Country: U.S.A.
        Cage Code: 22373
        DUNS Number: 614705783

If you have any questions about this transition, please reach out to your Honeywell point of contact. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace
Customer and Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
