<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Transition_Wichita_mih.201905_Transition_Wichita_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Wichita, Kansas Site Move Schedule</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;
HONEYWELL AEROSPACE WICHITA, KS MOVE SCHEDULE
Honeywell Aerospace recently announced the transition of the Wichita, Kansas Repair &amp; Overhaul activity to the Olathe, Kansas site. To minimize risk and customer impact, this transition has been planned utilizing a multiple move sequence. There will be four move sequences. The first move starts in late July 2019. This communication addresses all move schedules tied to the Wichita work transfer. Please retain this document for future reference.

A review of repair order history (2 years) indicates that you have sent in a part number for repair for at least one of the impacted part numbers. 

REPAIR UNIT SHIPMENTS 



	- View the PN and Move Schedule &lt;[[https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/Odyssey_MoveSchedule_update_050219_Final.pdf]]&gt; file to determine when each part number will move. Locate the move sequence number and match to the ‘Wichita Last Receipt Date’ identified in the chart below.


-- OR --


	- Access MyAerospace Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; available 24x7.


Move Sequence by Product Line and Date




Move Sequence

Product Descriptions
Wichita Last Receipt Date


1
Radar, SatCom
7/26/2019


2
Controllers, Flight Reference
8/9/2019


3
ComNav, CRT
8/30/2019


4
Flight Controls, EPIC, MAU, 486 Harvest, and Otto Repairs  
9/27/2019




REPAIR ORDER PROCESSING
To minimize issues or delays with the repair of your hardware, please follow these guidelines and actions. 
Existing Repair Orders: 


	- Honeywell will work to fulfill repair orders already on site at Wichita. 
	- Due to the nature of the repair and/or the timing of the receipt of the hardware relative to the repair lead-times, some repair orders may require a place of performance purchase order or contract modification. 
	- If a modification is required, your Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will contact you to advise and coordinate the activity. 


	- Watch for PO or contract modification correspondence coming from AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com &lt;[[mailto:AeroRepairs@Honeywell.com]]&gt;.




 New Repair Orders: 


	- To minimize delays to your repair, ensure that new repair orders are sent to the correct location. 
	- Part numbers received on or before the ‘Wichita Last Receipt Date’ will be accepted at Wichita.
	- Honeywell will send part numbers that are in transit and received within 7 days of the ‘Wichita Last Receipt Date’ to Olathe for repair. 


	- A PO/contract modification may be required.
	- The Honeywell Customer Business Manager, Honeywell Contracts Manager or Honeywell Support Representative will be in contact to advise and coordinate that activity. 


	- The Repair Site Capability list &lt;[[https://myaerospace2.honeywell.com/onlineordering/repair-capabilities/]]&gt; will be updated to allow for real-time queries about where to send your repairs.


 AOG Support 


	- There is no change on how Honeywell will support AOG shipments for this hardware.


 Update your Authorized Supplier List and Internal Systems 


	- Please update your authorized supplier list (ASL) and internal systems to include the new supplier information for these parts.





Company Name: 
Honeywell International Inc.


Address:
23500 West 105th Street


City, State:
Olathe, Kansas


Postal Code:
66061


Country:
U.S.A.


Cage Code:
22373


DUNS Number:
614705783




If you have any questions about this transition, please contact your Honeywell Customer Business Manager or point of contact. Our goal is to always provide you with the quality and service that you deserve. 

Honeywell Aerospace 
Visit MyAerospace &lt;[[https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;


If you no longer wish to receive these emails, click on the following link: Unsubscribe &lt;[[http://goaero.honeywell.com/u/hq0pk0I00Q0000GnZ020XI0]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
