<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201905_Global_GoDirect Trade_Seller_Nurture_Campaign_KK.201905_Global_GDT_Seller</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>GoDirectTrade.com: The End of Ghost Listings</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/sellers?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;
Ghost listings scare buyers and result in time-wasting RFQ’s!

You’ve seen the marketplaces claiming to have millions of listings and billions worth of inventory. Have you tried to buy one of those? Quickly? How many potential buyers have had to sift thru the multitude of ghosts to find the live listing? Too many!

GoDirect Trade ensures all listings have an image, quality document, and of course, price. Every listing is the real deal! Why is that important?



	- Accurate and informative listings give buyers the confidence they need to complete the order online with limited or no seller intervention


	- When every product listing is immediately available, buyers will return to the marketplace for their urgent needs


	- Buyers have a zero tolerance for risk. When they actually receive the product as described, they’ll start making more of their purchases online from sellers that make it easy for them


Become more efficient, be a seller on GoDirectTrade.com
Please contact us to learn more about starting your own storefront at our online marketplace. With over 2000 active buyers from over 700 companies, we can help you sell more online with no investment in expensive digital e-commerce technologies.






INQUIRE ABOUT OUR EXCLUSIVE OFFER FOR SELLERS &lt;[[https://www.godirecttrade.com/sellers?utm_source=Email&amp;utm_medium=Email&amp;utm_campaign=SellerCampaign]]&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
