<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2015-IDEF2015-EMEAI-Event.2015-IDEF2015-EMEAI evite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Us - IDEF 2015</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
IDEF 2015

 
 Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE
Join Us at IDEF 2015

Honeywell is delighted to be supporting IDEF 2015.  At the show we will be sharing our technologies and capabilities with customers and partners to demonstrate how Honeywell can work with Turkey to deliver solutions that protect, connect, upgrade and maintain both current capabilities; and next generation platforms.  As Turkey takes aim for the future we look forward to strengthening our strategic partnership with the Turkish aerospace industry and expanding our contributions to Turkey’s in-country engineering, manufacturing, maintenance and repair and technology development capabilities. Together, we can realize Turkey’s aerospace vision.

Join our leadership team to discover the latest news and to learn more about how our technologies enable our customers to realize the Possibilities of Partnership. Made Easy.

If you would like to book a meeting with a member of our team, please RSVP here. &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/2015-IDEF2015-EMEAI-Event_2015-IDEF-2015-EMEAI-Booking-form.html&gt;

 We look forward to meeting with you in Istanbul.

When: 5th – 8th May

Where: Tüyap Fair Convention and Congress Center, E5 Karayolu Üzeri, Gürpinar Kavsaği 34500 Büyükçekmece, Istanbul, Turkey

Booth: 221E

RSVP – Click here  &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/2015-IDEF2015-EMEAI-Event_2015-IDEF-2015-EMEAI-Booking-form.html&gt;
&lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/idef-2015&gt;
Learn More
 For more information about IDEF 2015 please visit the events page &lt;https://aerospace.honeywell.com/events/idef-2015&gt;.
Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2015 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
