<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201803_Global_Event_AEA_Dealers_mih.201803_Global_Invite3_AEA_Dealers_mih</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>LAST CHANCE: Connect with Honeywell and BendixKing at AEA 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en]]&gt;   &lt;[[http://www.bendixking.com/home]]&gt;
AEA INTERNATIONAL CONVENTION &amp; TRADE SHOW 
March 26-29
The 2018 AEA International Convention and Trade Show is right around the corner and we&apos;re excited to see all of our Honeywell and BendixKing dealers there. Please join us as we introduce new products, host training sessions and celebrate with you. See you there! 
 
 
   RSVP TODAY      
New Product Introduction Sessions
 
Honeywell and BendixKing are very excited to be participating in the new product introduction ceremony this year. Join us as we talk about our latest offerings in connectivity and mandate solutions.
Honeywell Training Sessions
 
Honeywell is hosting six total sessions geared to educate our dealers on three of our connectivity and cockpit upgrades. Click here &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DPXWW6S]]&gt; to see the full list and reserve your spot today. 
BendixKing Training Sessions 
 
Attention all BendixKing dealers! We&apos;re hosting three installation training sessions on the KI 300 AeroFlight Electronic Attitude Indicator, CNI 5000 ADS-B upgrade for CitationJet 525 &amp; 525A and AeroWave 100 Connectivity. View our full schedule here and reserve your spot today &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DPXWW6S]]&gt;.
Dealer Appreciation Reception
 
Honeywell and BendixKing dealers are invited to join us for cocktails and hors d&apos;oeuvres for an in-booth reception as we celebrate our accomplishments. RSVP today &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DPXWW6S]]&gt; to let us know you&apos;re coming.
For more information about our AEA 2018 plans, please contact Lisa Watmore (BendixKing) &lt;[[mailto:Lisa.Watmore@Honeywell.com]]&gt; or Jeremy Dingman (Honeywell) &lt;[[mailto:jeremy.dingman@honeywell.com]]&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
