<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>202002_Global_C&amp;PS_Eclair-Change-Management_Email-Operational.Eclair Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>News about your Honeywell ALF502/LF507 Turbofan Engine</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer,

Honeywell continually evaluates its operations and products to determine what is best for customers and our long-term growth. After a thorough evaluation, we have decided to transfer the ownership of our ALF502/LF507 Turbofan Engine to a long-term partner, CFS Aeroproduct LTD. As a valued partner, CFS Aero is committed to servicing the ALF502 / LF507 engine models and has established, strong relationships with the original equipment manufacturers (OEM) and operators. 

 Effective immediately, please start contacting CFS Aero for your ALF502/LF507 support needs. CFS Aero is a part 145 certified repair center for the ALF 502/LF507. They have been performing repairs prior to this transfer of ownership and are well-equipped to address your requirements. Honeywell will be supporting CFS Aero throughout the course of the transition. CFS Aero contact information is provided below. 


Part inquiries: Sales@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:Sales@cfsaero.com]]&gt;

Customer and Technical Support inquiries: turbines@cfsaero.com &lt;[[mailto:turbines@cfsaero.com]]&gt;

Website: www.cfsaero.com &lt;[[http://www.cfsaero.com/]]&gt;

We have established a dedicated transition team composed of functional experts and leaders to manage the transition process and ensure there is no break in service or shipments during this period. Our commitment to customer service does not wane during a transition. 

 Special Notes: 



	- T55 engines will continue to be supported by Honeywell. 
	- As of March 1, 2020, Vector Aerospace Engine Services will no longer be supporting ALF 502/LF507 engines.



 We will continue to keep you updated and will provide directions that will need to be completed within the coming months. We are working to give you the quality and the service you deserve. If you have any questions, please reach out to your primary Honeywell point of contact.

Sincerely, 

Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
