<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>201909_Global_IMU_i300 Customer Announcement_JRD.201909_Global_IMU_i300_Customer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Introducing Our Newest HGuide IMU: The HGuide i300</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/]]&gt;

NOW AVAILABLE: HONEYWELL HGUIDE i300 MEMS IMU


The HGuide i300 MEMS inertial measurement unit &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/navigation-and-sensors/hguide-i300-mems-inertial-measurement-unit]]&gt; is our newest, non-ITAR MEMS IMU. Its rugged design, small size, low power and weight make it ideal for countless applications including agriculture, AUVs, industrial equipment, robotics, survey/mapping, stabilized platforms, transportation, UAVs and UGVs.

For a limited time, you can try a Honeywell HGuide IMU or navigator before you buy*. 


PRODUCT OVERVIEW

The i300’s extremely small size (1 cubic inch), light weight (35 grams) and low power requirements (0.5 watts) make the unit ideal for a wide range of industrial applications. Learn more. &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/products/navigation-and-sensors/hguide-i300-mems-inertial-measurement-unit]]&gt;



TECHNICAL DOCUMENTS
Download the HGuide i300 brochure to read more about its key characteristics, performance grades and more. Download now &lt;[[https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/~/media/aerospace/files/brochures/n61-2009-000-003_i300-imu-bro.pdf]]&gt;.



WATCH THE i300 VIDEO

Learn more about the HGuide i300 by watching our video. Watch here &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BLJdx48jocc&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;. 





THE HGUIDE DIFFERENCE

The Honeywell HGuide inertial sensor and navigation team is here to help you solve your greatest navigation challenges. All customer inquiries are welcome and we look forward to helping you and your team. 

“Working with the Honeywell technical crew provides good access to all the help we need. They review our data and recommend ways in which it can be improved during flight because they appreciate how much accuracy matters to us. It’s very motivating.” - Dr Christoph Eck, Aeroscout 

--

TRY BEFORE YOU BUY

*Try before you buy program is subject to availability and execution of Honeywell’s bailment agreement. Limit one (1) product per customer. Customer must return unit in 30 days from the time the unit is received. Customers who do not return the unit within 30 days will be charged full MSRP at standard Honeywell terms and conditions.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
