<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>BGA Messages.BGA GTO Customer Letter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aerospace Technical Support</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;  &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;  &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;  &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;
Email Title
Normal 0     false false 
false  EN-US X-NONE X-NONE    
 
MicrosoftInternetExplorer4          
 
Dear Honeywell Customer, 

It doesn’t matter what the product or the name of the company is, when you call a business helpline that’s exactly what you want. Help. With quick and accurate answers to every question.  

That’s exactly what we want your experience to be every time you call Honeywell Aerospace.  So to make sure that’s the case, we’re reconfiguring our Technical Support processes and organization.  

Why are we changing?
We are responding to your survey feedback to have 
direct access to technical support as soon as you call. In today’s economy, customers require immediate technical support to quickly return their aircraft to service. 

What is changing to improve our responsiveness?
 
We’ve pulled the best of our Technical Operations Center (TOC) staff, Field Service Engineers (FSE), and Product Service Engineers (PSE) together to work as a single, cohesive technical support team. This team is called Aerospace Technical Support (ATS), and its focus is on quick turn support to keep your planes flying. 

What it means to you.
As part of our enhanced technical 
support process, customers in the Americas’ region now have 24/7 access to an entire network of product specialists instead of a single point of contact. This approach guarantees immediate access to technical support engineers as opposed to leaving voice messages or emails and then waiting for a return call or reply when you need them the most. 

No long waits or handoffs from department to department – just, quick, accurate, precise solutions.  If there is a specific field service engineer who you would prefer to work with, just ask for them by name.  If that person is available, you will be immediately transferred to him or her. 

We think you’ll like what you find when you turn to the new Honeywell Aerospace Technical Support network for help. Because we’re putting you closer to the person with the answers.  

Honeywell Aerospace Technical Support
 (U.S./Canada) 855.808.6500
 (International) 602.365.6500
 Email:   AeroTechSupport@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:AeroTechSupport@Honeywell.com&gt; 
These changes are applicable to North America at this time and will be applicable to the Asia Pacific Region on April 11.  Other global regional support 
models are unchanged at this time and customers should continue to contact the local Field Service Engineer or Honeywell Channel Partner representative for technical support until further notice. 

Thank you.
 Honeywell Aerospace

Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;    Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt;
© 2013 Honeywell International Inc. &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
