<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Editable version</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Order_Confirmation</letterhead>
    <name>Order Confirmation Editable</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Order Request Confirmation - We&apos;ve received your request for an order {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},



Thank you for your business! We are writing to confirm that we&apos;ve received your order, {!Case.CaseNumber}.



Order Summary:
___________________________________________________________

Order placed: {!Case.Order_Placed_Date_Time__c}
PO#: {!Case.Customer_PO_RO_WONumber__c}
Order #: {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}



Order Status:
___________________________________________________________

You can track the status of this order, and all of your orders, online by visiting Honeywell&apos;s Order Status.



&gt;&gt; Did you forget to attach your PO to the original request?

No problem. Just replay to this email and attach your PO.



&gt;&gt; Next time, put us to work faster by using the portal - 12 hours vs. a few seconds. That&apos;s the difference in confirmation times between ordering by email or using Honeywell&apos;s newly improved MyAerospace web portal! In the future, please visit www.MyAerospace.com to place an order, and within seconds receive your confirmation number, tracking data, and scheduled delivery information.



Questions?
___________________________________________________________

We&apos;ve connected all of your order details through the subject line of this email. That subject line was created specifically for you and is unique to this order.


So, please leave the subject line unchanged should you reply to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.



Thanks again! We appreciate your business,

Honeywell Aerospace



ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE

{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
