<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>R&amp;O Order Confirmation - Information is Missing</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>R_O_Order_Confirmation_Missing_Info</letterhead>
    <name>R&amp;O Order Confirmation-Missing Info</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Honeywell R&amp;O Confirmation - We&apos;re missing information (!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},


Thank you for your business! We’ve received your purchase order {!Case.Customer_PO_RO_WONumber__c}
and are anxious to get right to work on it.


But before we can start, we need your help. We need just a bit more information that
was missing from your order.


&lt;&lt; Insert Z107 task long text notes&gt;&gt;


What&apos;s next:

Once we receive the missing information, we&apos;ll induct your unit into the shop. Then
we&apos;ll complete a full analysis and verify the required repair. This typically takes us
3-5 days from receiving your missing information. If the work scope changes, we&apos;ll
contact you immediately.

Questions?
____________________________________________________________________________________________

We’ll connect all of your inquiry details through the subject line of this email. So, when
you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed
immediately to this case.


As you gather the missing information, here are a few answers to the most commonly
asked questions:


1. When will I receive an estimated ship date? – Once we’ve received the missing
information, your order will be confirmed and the estimate ship date will be available
on the portal.


2. What&apos;s needed if the work scope changes? – We&apos;ll need you to amend your
purchase order to match the updated work scope and price. Then just reply to this
email and attach your document. Your unit will be placed on &quot;hold&quot; until we&apos;ve contacted
you and received your approval and amended purchase order.


3. How much time do I have to respond before my part is returned? – 10 days
from when you receive the updated work scope. If we haven&apos;t heard from you, your
unit will be returned in “as is” condition.


4. I&apos;ve heard you now use flat rates for all your repairs. What&apos;s covered by a flat
rate? – Flat rates include any minor modifications, service bulletins, and overhaul rework
instructions that do not change the form, fit or function. The repair terms and conditions are
available on the Honeywell MyAerospace.com portal.

Honeywell reserves the right to determine the ineligibility of repairs under the flat rate
program if they are deemed to have &quot;excessive&quot; repair requirements and/or are beyond
economical repair.


Thanks again! We’ll be on the lookout for your email.


Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
For 24/7 AOG: 1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099, option 4.


ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
