<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Repair &amp; Overhaul Order Confirmation</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>R_O_Order_Confirmation</letterhead>
    <name>R&amp;O Order Confirmation</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Honeywell R&amp;O Order Confirmation {!Case.CaseNumber} {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},



Thank you for your business! We’ve received your purchase order {!Case.Customer_PO_RO_WONumber__c}
and are ready to start work on it.

&lt;&lt;Insert Z106 task long text notes&gt;&gt;

The estimated completion date for your repair is {!Case.Shipped_On__c}. This date is
based on Honeywell&apos;s standard turnaround time* for this type of repair.

What&apos;s next:

We&apos;ll now induct your unit into the shop. Then we&apos;ll complete a full analysis and verify
the required repair. This typically takes us 3-5 days from today. If the work scope changes,
we&apos;ll contact you immediately.

If the work scope changes from what&apos;s outlined on your purchase order:

We&apos;ll need you to amend your purchase order to match the updated work scope
and price. Then just reply to this email and attach your document.

Meanwhile, we’ll hold off on the repair until we&apos;ve contacted you and received your
approval and amended purchase order.

If after 10 calendar days, from when you received the updated work scope, we
don&apos;t hear from you, we’ll return your unit as is.


You can quickly track the progress of your repair via the MyAerospace.com portal,
using either your Purchase Order number {!Case.Customer_PO__c} or Sales
Order number {!Case.Sales_Order_Number__c}.

Questions?
_____________________________________________________________________________________________

We’ll connect all of your inquiry details through the subject line of this email. So, should
you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed
immediately to this case.


Thanks again! We appreciated your business.


Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
24/7 AOG: 1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099, option 4.


* Utilization of the flat rates acknowledges acceptance of Honeywell&apos;s repair terms and conditions (T&amp;Cs)
available on the MyAerospace portal. The T&amp;Cs include the incorporation of minor modifications and
service bulletins that do not change form, fit or function.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
