<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>SR#421957</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>Notification Email To Recipient For Government Compliance</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Functional Contributor Workflow Government Compliance</subject>
    <textOnly>Government Compliance,


Price agreement on the Honeywell RFP for {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Name__c} {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Description__c} (Site: {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Lead_Site__c}) was reached on {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Negotiation_Complet__c} with {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Customer__c}.



Honeywell must sign a Certification of Current Cost and Pricing Data certifying to the customer that the cost and pricing data from which the settlement price was obtained were accurate, complete and current as of the date that {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Customer__c} and Honeywell agreed on a price.



As a Functional Contributor you play an important role in providing Current Cost and Pricing Data.   Governmental Accounting Compliance current cost and pricing data should consider but not be limited to: changes in direct and indirect rate pools and bases, Forward Pricing Rates, Disclosure Statements, site disclosure statement, and Accounting practice that have not already been included in proposed direct and indirect rates and current rate trend reports.



As part of Pricing’s certification process, all relevant data is pulled by Pricing from the Compliance SharePoint site for inclusion in the TINA certification package.



Please advise Pricing if there is any known data that has not been posted  to SharePoint as of {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Negotiation_Complet__c} where the last internal approval had been received.  Notify {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Pricing_Analyst__c} that the “Current Cost and Pricing Disclosure” is current no later than {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.X2_Days_from_requested_date__c}.



Additional Comments: {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.comment__c}


&apos;No Updates&apos;  , &apos;Yes,I have Updates&apos;


Sincerely,

{!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Pricing_Analyst__c}

Parent Opportunity Number: {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Parent_Opportunity_Proposal__c}

Opportunity Proposal Name: {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.Opportunity_Proposal_Name__c}

P&amp;DR: {!Functional_Contributor_Update__c.P_DR__c}


“Cost or Pricing Data” (FAR 15.406-2 in accordance with definitions contained in 2.101) means all facts as of the date of price agreement, or, if applicable, an earlier date agreed upon between the parties that is as close as practicable to the date of agreement on price, that prudent buyers and sellers would reasonably expect to affect price negotiations significantly.  Cost or pricing data are factual, not judgmental; and are verifiable.  While they do not indicate the accuracy of the prospective contractor’s judgment about future costs or projections, they do include the data forming the basis for that judgment.  Cost or pricing data are more than historical accounting data; they are all the facts that can be reasonably expected to contribute to the soundness of estimates of future costs and to the validity of determinations of costs already incurred.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
