<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>RMA Template for Advance Exchange</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>ACT – RMA Advance Exchange</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support.  Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above.  If you wish to communicate with us further about this inquiry, you may reply to this e-mail -- please leave the Reference Case # within the subject line for quicker responses.

Honeywell Receiving: Please note that RMA &lt;type RMA #&gt; has been issued for P/N &lt;input part number&gt; in relation to Advanced Exchange Sales Order &lt;input SO #&gt;.  Please note that there will be no core return.



Dear {!Contact.Name},

Please find attached the requested Return Material Authorization (RMA).

For Honeywell to evaluate your return material, please download the Material Return Tag from My Aerospace portal https://www51.honeywell.com/aero/portal/Common/Documents/tag_V4.pdf.

Please complete and attach the Material Return Tag and RMA form when returning the part.



Returned part(s) must be received within 30 days of RMA issue date to avoid cancellation of RMA.   Credit will be provided once your return is evaluated and confirmed according to Honeywell terms and conditions.

Parts returned without a Honeywell authorized RMA, will be returned at customer expense.



Thank you, we appreciate your business!

Regards,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}

Honeywell Aerospace

Customer &amp; Product Support


Visit the exciting new options on our improved, easier to navigate Web Portal at www.myaerospace.com. You can now obtain real time price and availability, place orders and check order status online for avionics, mechanical, wheels and brakes products and exchange programs (SPEX), globally for all of our customers.

Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
