<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>MTO Quote on behalf of HAT</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Honeywell_New_logo</letterhead>
    <name>MTO – HAT Quote Template</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Quotation – Aerospace Trading Phoenix</subject>
    <textOnly>Referencing your new part order or price and availability request &lt;insert customer PO or quote reference&gt;, we are unable to provide the item as originally requested. However, we provide the following information on behalf of Honeywell Aerospace Trading:

Quote Date: &lt;Enter date of quote&gt;
Quote Valid to: 9 Days from quote date. Note: Items subject to prior sale
Part Number: &lt;enter part number&gt;
Condition: &lt;enter condition&gt;
Quantity Bid: &lt;enter quantity bid&gt;
Delivery: &lt;enter delivery lead time provided&gt;
Unit Price: &lt;Enter price per piece&gt; Extended Price: &lt;enter total price&gt;
Payment Terms: &lt;Enter terms from SAP&gt;
Shipping Terms: ExWorks Honeywell Facility
Warranty: Unless otherwise noted, units carry a one (1) year warranty.

Mail Purchase Orders to:
Honeywell Aerospace Trading
1800 W Rose Garden Lane
Phoenix, AZ 85027
USA

Email Purchase Orders to: NCHAT@honeywell.com

This quotation or any related sale is subject to US export regulations and requires the end use, end user, and end destination of the product. If the parts purchased are for your inventory, please state that the End User is your company. If the End User is someone other than your company, please provide the Company Name, City, and final destination Country of the end user to comply with export regulations.

The part(s) quoted herein are subject to prior sale. All sales are subject to the Terms and conditions of sale available by visiting the Aerospace Trading homepage at http://www.Aerospacetrading.com and selecting &quot;Terms and Conditions,” or on request.

Please contact Honeywell Aerospace Trading directly using the information below:

Phone: +1 6024361798
Contact: Lia Hanson
Email: NCHAT@honeywell.com

Honeywell Customer Support
http://www.MyAerospace.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
