<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Use this when there is a return request for SPEX order</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>HoneywellAerospaceLOGO</letterhead>
    <name>RMA SPEX</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Your case number is xxxxxxx.

RMA# XXX for SO XXX, PO XXXX, PN XXXX, SN XXXX, Qty XXXX, Invoice XXXX.

Attached is the requested Return Material Authorization (RMA). Please download the Material Return Tag from our portal:
https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/-/media/Files/Documents/Claims/Material%20Return%20Tag/tag_V4.pdf.

Place the completed documents in the same box as the product you’re returning, and attach the provided address label to the outside of the box.

If the returned Product is unused, undamaged and in a salable condition, Honeywell will issue a credit equal to the net amount paid to Honeywell by Customer minus transportation cost, handling charges and any applicable fees listed below:
· Tamper proof seal intact on the part and shipping container and less than 7 days - no restocking fee applies;
· Returns between 7 – 14 days (domestic) / 7 – 30 days (Int’l) - $1,100 restocking fee;
· Returns greater than 14 days (domestic) / 30 days (Int’l) - exchange price applies.

NOTE: If the tamper proof seal on the unit is broken, then it is not eligible for return/ credit customer to return the unit to core plant via core return tag which is received along with the unit.

We will take over from here and move the process forward:

1. Once we receive the returned product, we will examine it to confirm the reason for return. If validated, will issue a credit to your account and you will be notified via an email confirmation.

2. Product returned without RMA authorization will be considered an exchanged core and exchange fees will apply.

For future returns, please continue to follow the same process, including issuance of a new RMA, to ensure that the return is approved and credited to your account


Honeywell Customer Support
http://www.MyAerospace.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
