<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<HomePageComponent xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <body>&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;Welcome to the Honeywell Aerospace IDEA Exchange. &amp;nbsp;The IDEA Exchange provides a forum to allow ALL Aerospace employees to get involved and participate in the success of the business. &amp;nbsp;You can provide suggestions for improvements to products, services or processes that would help drive revenue growth, increase productivity or improve the customer experience. &amp;nbsp;In addition to submitting ideas, you can vote and comment on your favorite ideas to ensure they rise to the top.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;Here are some basic guidelines for submitting ideas to the IDEA Exchange:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;Make sure your idea is reasonable and necessary – if you are not sure or cannot articulate the value the improvement would drive do not submit at this time; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;you can always come back at a later time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;Search for your IDEA before you submit it – keep your community clean and productive by searching before you post. &amp;nbsp;Make a concerted effort to locate similar ideas and, if they are located, comment on them or suggest to merge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;Make Title meaningful - Titles like &quot;product improvement&quot; offer other members little insight to what your Idea is about. Include in the tile: product name, specific functions/business processes, and a brief notion of the issue/limitation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;Be clear and concise - When posting an idea, put other members in the best position to judge and respond to them. &amp;nbsp;Clearly state the specific issue your idea recommends addressing/enhancing. At the same time, make your post reader-friendly by keeping your idea to a few clear sentences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;If possible, picture it - Everybody loves colors! Make pretty pictures if you have the time. Conveying your idea visually allows community members to better envision your proposal and will lead to more promotions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; &quot;&gt;Be respectful - A successful community is built upon an open flow of dialogue. It is just as important to critique suggestions as it is to promote them. However, remember that we all seek a stronger more robust Aerospace environment and demeaning, insulting activity only serves to impede that effort. Always keep in mind, it&apos;s about Honeywell, not about yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;Arial, sans-serif&quot; size=&quot;2&quot;&gt;Ready to submit an IDEA? &amp;nbsp;Click on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/ideas/editIdea.apexp?c=09a3000000052pq&amp;amp;retURL=%2Fideas%2FideaList.apexp&quot; style=&quot;background-color: rgb(255, 255, 0);&quot;&gt;&quot;Post a NEW IDEA&lt;/a&gt;&quot;&amp;nbsp;to get started…&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</body>
    <pageComponentType>htmlArea</pageComponentType>
    <width>wide</width>
</HomePageComponent>
