<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>New MSP Renewal template provided by Jason Coolman</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>MSP Renewal</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>MSP Contract Renewal</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear,



In advance of the upcoming expiration of your MSP contract, Honeywell has posted your renewal MSP contract package to our aerospace systems portal.




Anticipating that you would like to renew your MSP coverage, please click on the following link to view and complete all company information where appropriate and electronically sign the MSP renewal contract:    https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/wps/portal/aero/myservices/home



Important Electronic Instructions:



Accessing the Renewal Contract – Use the above link to navigate to the portal and login.  Click  “Sign Contract Renewal” associated with the Tail coming up for renewal.



Navigating the fields to be completed – Once the contract is open you can utilize the Next button located on the side to advance line by line or simply click in the field you wish to fill in.



Gold Addendum – Please note it will be required to sign the Gold Addendum if you are or are not electing to enroll in MSP Gold coverage. Under the signature block on the Gold Addendum will be the ability to select the MSP Gold of your choice or to Opt out.


Not the Responsible Party to sign? – Open the contract and click &quot;Somebody else should sign&quot; in the lower right hand corner. This will open a page for you to input an email address to forward the contract to the correct person for signature.  Please note, they will not need access to the portal in order to sign the contract, it will be attached in the email.


Questions about the document or don’t wish to renew – Open the contract and click “I will not eSign this document” in the lower right hand corner.  This will open a text box in which you can provide details and submit back to the MSP Contracts Team.


Note that upon completion of all electronic non-Honeywell signatures, the document will automatically be returned to HON for execution.  If Honeywell determines a standard addendum is required (typically needed when the Registered Owner is not the signer on the contract), one will be forwarded to you in standard email format.

If you choose to manually sign your contract, print the document, obtain all signatures, then return to Honeywell - MSPContracts@Honeywell.com



Please note that all MSP reporting and payments must be current for Honeywell to process the renewed MSP Contract.
Thank you for your participation in our MSP Program and we look forward to providing you continued MSP service. If you have any questions, please direct your request to MSPContracts@Honeywell.com or call 1-800-601-3099/1-602-365-3099.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
