<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>used for conditional replacement</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>New_BK_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Service Parts Conditional Replacement--CSR</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>{!Case.CaseNumber} {!Case.Subject}</subject>
    <textOnly>Team,
We have a request for a conditional special order part request. Can you please help with this request?

Note: this form may be filled out electronically or manually. Refer to QMS 3-09-026 PS

Date


Requested By


EXT


Customer No.


Contact/Ref:


Customer Name


Unit Name


Serial No.

Unit Part Number

Mode Status


Manual, Page, Location

Part Number

Quantity


UM

ea

Comments


Service Parts Administration

Fill in below, if information is not know, direct this form to Purchasing or Production.

R/B Part Number (if applicable)

SPA Comments

List Price

Planner Code

UM

Delivery

Completed By

Date

EXT

*QUOTE VALID FOR 90 DAYS SUBJECT TO PRIOR SALE.*

Internal use only (below this line)

Purchasing

Provide vendor price and delivery in appropriate box, initial and return to Service Parts Administration.

Name

Price

U/M

Min OTY

Delivery

Date

EXT


Production Coach

Fill in the test thru-put in appropriate box.

Name

EXT

MD#

Can part be tested?

Test thru-put time

Fill in the manufacturing thru-put time in the appropriate box, initial and return to Service Parts Administration.

Delivery Lead Time- including test.

Date

Initial


Service Parts Administration

Fill in the lead time below based on the shortage part with the longest lead time.

Name

EXT

MD#

Shortage Fill Lead time

Date

Initial


Thank you,


{!Case.OwnerFullName}
BendixKing Customer Support Representative
Phone: U.S.: 1-855-250-7027
International: 1-602-365-7027
Email: parts@bendixking.com
Web: www.bendixking.com

*Please note that all Bendix King requests can, and should, now be submitted to &quot;parts@bendixking.com&quot;. This includes quotes, new orders, order changes, order status, export data (such as Schedule B/ECCN information), etc. Thank you, we appreciate your business!

Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time


--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

{!EmailMessage.FromName} 
{!EmailMessage.FromAddress} 
{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber} {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c} 

{!Case.Description}</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
