<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Notification of Solution assigned for Approval.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Approve_Reject</letterhead>
    <name>Notification of Solution assigned to you for Approval.</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Notification of Solution# {!Solution.SolutionNumber} has been assigned to you for Approval</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Solution.GTO_Approver__c},

Solution #{!Solution.SolutionNumber} has been assigned to you for Technical or Standards Review.  Please review the Solution according to the standards in AG-5218 and update the status.


Approver for Standards Review: Creator&apos;s Manager who reviews the Solution and after approval of the standards, sets status to Technical Review. If AG standards are not met, Manager to reject Solution and work with Creator for revisions.


Approver for Technical Review: Usually the PSE (but sometimes an FSE or TSE)with product responsibility and ownership of the knowledge base for the selected Supported Product.Often referred to as the “Primary” or “Secondary” on a particular Supported Product.


If you are not the correct Approver for this Solution, review the Supported Product that was selected - it may be incorrect.  If you know the correct Supported Product, please update that field and SalesForce will automatically update the Approver Information accordingly.


Solution Details:

Supported Product: {!Solution.Supported_Product__c}

Solution Name:{!Solution.SolutionName}

Created by: {!Solution.CreatedBy}





Click on the below link to view details:
{!Solution.Link}


Thank you, we appreciate your support!





Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or  use in our applications or systems at the present time</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
