<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Used for ATR customers being sent to the portal</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>ATR Send to Portal</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Please Use the MyAerospace Web Portal for Placing an Order</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Case.Contact_Name__c},

We&apos;re glad to hear from you!

There have been some changes to our spares ordering process since you were here last. Now, instead of emailing your request, you will log onto the MyAerospace Web Portal and simply follow the prompts to place your order. You can also view order status on the My Aerospace portal. Click here to view a short video on how to place an order on MyAerospace.

Why the change? Because this new system moves your request from ordered to filled to delivered faster than any email system ever could. The web portal gives you instant, written confirmation that your order has been placed and is being processed. It allows you to check and track order progress from any computer or Smartphone.

It’s important to understand that in shifting to this new streamlined process, Honeywell has completely disabled our email ordering system.
So please, log onto MyAerospace.com and resubmit your order.

We appreciate you taking this one-time extra step to order. Rest assured, from now on the portal will open a world of convenience, access, dependability, and speed for your company.

Thank you. We appreciate your business!
Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support

Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
