<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>New MSP Renewal template provided by Hoganson, Jeff</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>MSP Renewal New</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>Honeywell MSP Contract Renewal</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear,



In advance of the upcoming expiration of your MSP contract and anticipating that you would like to renew your MSP coverage, Honeywell has posted your renewal MSP contract for signature.



Please use the following link to view and electronically sign the MSP renewal contract: Agreement Link



***PLEASE DO NOT FORWARD THIS EMAIL – IF YOU ARE NOT THE RESPONSIBLE PERSON TO SIGN PLEASE FOLLOW THE BELOW INSTRUCTIONS***



Not the Responsible Party to sign? – You were identified as the correct person to sign the contract, however should another party be responsible please open the contract and click “Somebody else should sign” in the lower right hand corner.  This will open a page for you to input an email address to forward the contract to the correct person for signature. It is recommended you advise them that you have forwarded the form so they know to watch for the email notification.



Navigating the fields to be completed – Once the contract is open you can utilize the Next button located on the left side to advance line by line or simply click in the field you wish to fill in.  In addition, you will be directed to the next mandatory field to be completed by clicking the top right prompt.



Gold Addendum – Please note it will be required to sign the Gold Addendum if you are or are not electing to enroll in MSP Gold coverage.  Under the signature block on the Gold Addendum you must select the MSP Gold election of your choice or to Opt out.





Questions about the document or don’t wish to renew – Open the contract and click “I will not eSign this document” in the lower right hand corner. This will open a text box in which you can provide details and submit back to the MSP Contracts Team.



Note that upon completion of all electronic non-Honeywell signatures, the document will automatically be returned to HON for execution.  If Honeywell has determined a standard addendum is required (typically needed when the Registered Owner is not the signer on the contract), one will be forwarded to you in standard email format.



Please note that all MSP reporting and payments must be current for Honeywell to process the renewed MSP Contract.
Thank you for your participation in our MSP Program and we look forward to providing you continued MSP service. If you have any questions, please direct your request to MSPContracts@Honeywell.com or call 1-800-601-3099/1-602-365-3099.

Sincerely,
MSP Contracts Team.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
