<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Created for UFR Pricing Phase II project IT-14-044</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>UFR_Pricing</letterhead>
    <name>UFR D&amp;S Case Creation Temp</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>D&amp;S UFR funding mismatch PO#: {!Case.Customer_PO_RO_WONumber__c} , Notification #: {!Case.Case_OwnerId_After_Close__c}, Case Number: {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Customer,

Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace. Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above. To communicate further in regards to this inquiry, please reply to this e-mail with the Reference Case # within the subject line of the message.

We apologize for the delay, as we are unable to complete your request until we receive the information outlined below.

In order to proceed with induction of your unit PN {!Case.Product_Part__c}, we need you to provide an amended PO funded for the D&amp;S Flat Rate repair price of {!Case.UFR_Standard_Price_Amount__c} USD.

Also, please update your requested delivery date according to standard Turn Around Time (TAT). Please note that if you have a contract in place the contractual TAT requirements take precedence.

Please visit our Web Portal at https://myaerospace.honeywell.com to obtain real time price, availability and standard TAT of many Honeywell Aerospace products.

Please note that in if RAI policy applies and we do not receive a response, your unit will be automatically returned in “as is” condition (RAI) after 10 calendar days.

Utilization of flat rate repair prices on your purchase order indicates your acceptance of Honeywell’s Repair and Overhaul Terms and Conditions which can be viewed at https://commerce.honeywell.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/TermsAndConditionsDocsView?storeid=10651&amp;langid=-1

If this inquiry relates to AOG, please call us at 1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099.

Thank you, we appreciate your business!
Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web: https://myaerospace.honeywell.com


D&amp;S Universal Flat Rates (D&amp;S UFR)

Honeywell Aerospace launched Defense &amp; Space Universal Flat Rate pricing in 2014. Referencing the appropriate flat rate on your purchase order helps us to reduce overall repair time and gives you and the end users a tool to effectively predict, manage, and budget R&amp;O expenses.

Once Honeywell receives your funded PO, you will not be asked for further quote acceptance. Honeywell will automatically proceed with requested work scope and will send the unit back to you immediately after it is done with CAFE/Service report attached. This also applies to ‘not fault found’ units (NFF). In case of NFF you will be charged with Test Teardown and Evaluation fee (TT&amp;E) only.

Flat rate covers minor modifications, ORIs and service bulletins which do not require a change of material number. These will be incorporated without extra charges above the flat rate.


Honeywell reserves the right to reject repair materials under the flat rate program if they are deemed to have ‘excessive’ repair requirements and/or are beyond economical repair (BER).


Please note that purchase order funding has to match required work scope, otherwise repair will be held until amended purchase order is received and/or part will be returned.

All current repair and overhaul flat rates and conditions are available at Honeywell MyAerospace Portal: https://myaerospace.honeywell.com

If you have questions about Honeywell Universal Flat Rate program please contact Honeywell Customer &amp; Product Support team.
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
