<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Test - Template used for Opportunity Proposals</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Honeywell_New_logo</letterhead>
    <name>TEST - Opportunity Proposal Template</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>TEST - Opportunity Proposal</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell International Inc.
21111 N. 19th Ave.
Phoenix, AZ
85027
USA

Date: Month Day, Year

Customer Name
Customer Address

Reference: OPRO-XXXXXXX

Dear Mr.
Honeywell is pleased to submit this proposal response for the (product name) for the aircraft in response to your request for quotation dated Month Day, Year.

Pricing

Description  Part Number  Qty.  Delivery Year  Unit Price
Embedded GPS INS (EGI)  HG9873N02  4  2019  $138,500
12  2020  $143,500
12  2021  $148,500

Prices are in US Dollars

Delivery Schedule
Delivery schedule above is based on the assumption of 4 development units in 2019 with a further 24 production units in 2020-2021.

Payment Terms
Strictly 30 days from date of invoice
Terms &amp; Conditions Except for Warranty clause, Honeywell Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale shall apply. See Appendix A

Warranty
Warranty period shall be 24 months from shipment (Ex-Works Clearwater Florida USA). Pricing for additional periods of Warranty shall be quoted upon request.

Validity of Proposal
This proposal is valid for 8 months from the date of the proposal

This proposal is subject to final agreement between the parties, is not intended to be, and shall not constitute in any way a binding offer or legal agreement, or impose any legal obligation or duty on either Honeywell or the recipient.

Honeywell International (www.honeywell.com) is a Fortune 100 diversified technology and manufacturing leader, serving customers worldwide with aerospace products and services; control technologies for buildings, homes and industry; automotive products; turbochargers; and specialty materials. Based in Morris Township, N.J., Honeywell&apos;s shares are traded on the New York, London, and Chicago Stock Exchanges.

We trust that the enclosed meets your expectations and we look forward to receiving your comments or further instructions in due course. In the meantime, should you have any query then please do not hesitate to contact the undersigned.

Yours faithfully,

Customer Business Manager
Name and Signature

Tel :
Mobile :
Email :


Contracts Manager
Name and Signature

Tel :
Mobile :
Email :</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
