<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Email Templates For RegestrationCompletion</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>HoneywellAerospaceLOGO</letterhead>
    <name>RegistrationCompletionTemplate_Archive</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>MyAerospace Registration Complete</subject>
    <textOnly>MyAerospace Registration Complete

Dear {!Contact.Name},   

Welcome Aboard to MyAerospace.   

Here are just a few of our most popular tasks: 

Tools To Get Started  

Place Orders Fast
Honeywell makes it easy for you to order parts online. Whether you&apos;re looking for new parts, certified pre-owned parts, exchanges or rentals, you can find what you need using our all-inclusive search engine, check prices and place your order.
           
Track Orders Easily            
With our status application you can quickly check the status of your parts and repairs orders. At a glance you can see a summary of your active orders, and see where they are in fulfillment process and address any orders that are awaiting your approval.

Manage Honeywell Services 
With our GoDirect brand, Honeywell industries most complete portfolio of value added aviation services applications. GoDirect services ranges from GoDirect Flight Services, powered by Global Data Center, to our award-winning Weather Information Services, to service that enables reliable, high-speed in-flight Wi-Fi.

View Technical Publications   
Honeywell&apos;s comprehensive library of technical publications is available online. Our intuitive search engine lets you find the publication you need with part number, publication number, ATA code or keywords. You can choose to be alerted  when new publication is added to the library.

Get Technical Help 24/7       
The Technical Knowledge Center feature lets you find technical questions and view your organization&apos;s reported issues, anytime of the day and night. Our extensive library contains questions and answers on a wide range of relevant topics.   

Tips:
To get access to these applications, visit My Account
To download the latest training aids, visit MyAerospace Training

Note:

This email is being sent from an unmonitored mailbox. If you need further assistance, please contact a customer support team member at:

1-800-601-3099 US / Canada (Toll Free)
1-602-365-3099 International
Choose Option 7 (Web Support)

Thank You,
Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support Team 

© 2018 Honeywell International Inc.
Terms of Use    |   Privacy Policy   |    Contact Us</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
