<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>For D&amp;S R&amp;O quotes after 5 days</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>RAI DS 5 Days</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>D&amp;S Return As Is Notification - {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support.  Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above.  If you wish to communicate with us further about this inquiry you may reply to this e-mail -- please leave the Reference Case # within the subject line for quicker responses.



Dear Honeywell Customer,

We have not received a response for your unit within 5 days of issue. Therefore, unless we receive required information (quote approval, PO information, FR funding, repair details, payment in advance, etc) within the next 5 days, our Return As Is process will be initiated. And an invoice for evaluation and any non-recoverable time and materials required to troubleshoot your repair will be included if applicable.

To avoid having product returned in error, it is required that you follow the appropriate response path for all quote approvals and/or information requests.

How to submit quote approvals:

Preferred Option: To quickly process your order, go online at www.myaerospace.com. A short instructional video is available on how to approve or decline quotes.  You can also navigate to this video that is located on the portal by selecting the help desk tab, clicking on Tutorials, and then scrolling down to the order status videos.

Next Best Option: Direct reply back to the original quote email received from CPSQuotesApprovals@Honeywell.com

Caution: All other methods of contact such as direct or other generic email boxes cannot guarantee processing in time to avoid a product return.

How to submit requested information: (for example: PO information including flat rate funding, additional repair details, payment in advance if required)

Preferred Option: Direct response to original email received from Honeywell. Email box may vary based on repair center and location.
Caution: All other methods of contact such as direct or other generic email boxes cannot guarantee processing in time to avoid a product return.

Thank you for your time, your consideration and your continuing choice of Honeywell Services. If we can be of any further assistance to you, please let us know.



Sincerely,


Honeywell Aerospace

Customer &amp; Product Support

Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
