<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>For use 5 days after R&amp;O quote sent</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>RAI ATR 5 Days</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Did your Honeywell quote get lost in the email?</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Honeywell Customer, 

Thank you for your business. We look forward to working with you! 

A few days ago Honeywell Aerospace sent you a quote. In order for us to work on that request, we need your approval within five (5) days of this email. If we do not receive a reply within that time frame, we will box and return the uncompleted parts. Please review the quote information and let us know whether you approve the costs. Thank you in advance for your time.

If you have any questions, or if the quote information from Honeywell Aerospace cannot be located, please contact me directly by replying to this email. I am happy to assist you.

Included below are a few options to approve the project.
How to submit quote approvals: 

- Preferred Option:  Visit www.myaerospace.com. A short instructional video is available on how to approve or decline quotes. You can also navigate to this video on the portal by selecting the Help Desk tab, clicking on Tutorials, and scrolling down to the Order Status videos. 
- Next Best Option:  Reply to the original quote email received from CPSQuotesApprovals@Honeywell.com
- Please Note: All other methods of contact (including a direct or other generic email box) cannot guarantee processing in time to avoid a product return. 

If uncompleted parts are returned and you wish to have your unit repaired, please notify your Honeywell Customer Support Representative and they will be glad to assist. Please return the unit to our repair facility within 21 days, and we will honor the previous quote as well as waive the return invoice (if applicable). Please include the signed approval of the quote along with the returned unit. For necessary changes or quote updates, you will receive a new quote encompassing additional or modified repair actions. 

Please reply with any questions or clarifications. I look forward to hearing from you!

Sincerely,

Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
