<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>Lead Assigned Alert for Marcom</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Action - Sales Lead (and possibly a BRAVO $$$) For You</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.OwnerFullName},

A lead has now been assigned to you as lead owner.

Access your lead from the summary information below:

Lead: {!Lead.Link}
Company: {!Lead.Company}
Name: {!Lead.Name}
Product Information: {!ATR_Product_Information__c}
Lead Description: {!Lead.Lead_Description__c}

We are excited to let you know that our marketing efforts have led to a sales lead that we’ve initially researched and felt should be assigned to you as lead owner in SFDC to contact the customer and pursue the deal.

Please evaluate the lead immediately and, if it looks accurate, move the lead status to Sales Accepted Lead (SAL). If it is not, please change the lead status to Recycle or Disqualified.

Should your SAL become a Sales Qualified Lead (SQL) after a conversation with this customer, please change the lead status and convert it to an Opportunity.

Please update all necessary fields, including the “Next Steps” section, accordingly. The most recent communication from the customer can be found in the “Next Steps” section.

We are giving away random BRAVOs for those who act on these leads within 48 hours, and unfortunately reporting those who do not update this lead within two weeks (referred to as a “leaked lead”).

We look forward to hearing whether this is a legitimate revenue opportunity for Honeywell Aerospace, and winning it!

Thank you so much for contributing to Honeywell’s growth!

Please refer below for Lead Status Definitions:

Sales Accepted:
A lead formally accepted by sales upon which sales agrees to take action.

Sales Qualified:
A lead that has evolved into a qualified pipeline opportunity. These leads should be converted to Opportunities.

Recycle:
Leads that need to be passed back to marketing because they were not ready to buy, but the lead needs to remain active.

Disqualified:
Leads that are not appropriate or viable such as a no or incorrect contact info, not our target market, lead is from a student or job seeker, customer contact established and customer is not interested, Opportunity already exists. “Reason for disqualification” field on leads page is to be populated accordingly.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
