<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>Plymouth RMA Approved</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Approved: {!Case.Case_Number__c} {!Case.Subject} {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName} {!Contact.LastName},


Your returns request has been approved. You have been assigned case # {!Case.CaseNumber} for the following:


Part Number(s): {!Case.Part_Number__c}


Serial Number(s): {!Case.Serial_Number__c}



Quantity:{!Case.Quantity__c}



Sales Order Number: {!Case.Sales_Order_Number__c}



**Please do not issue a Debit Memo.** If you cannot process your return without issuing a Debit Memo, please email RMA-SSEC-MN14@honeywell.com with a copy of the debit memo.


If the unit is still under warranty, we will examine the unit for defects. Honeywell will repair, replace , or issue credit (at our option) items provided under this order which are not free from defects in workmanship and material under normal use and service if such items are returned to Honeywell within one year after delivery.


In preparation for shipment, please:

1) Pack units being returned in the original shipping container if possible, or other container that protects the units from ESD and mechanical damage. For MRAM products, the packaging must additionally provide protection against Stray Magnetic Fields (SMF) during shipment.*

2) Place a copy of this e-mail inside the packing box.

3) Mark the outside of the shipping box BOLDLY with the case number. (Case #{!Case.Case_Number__c})

4) Mail to:


Honeywell Aerospace - Plymouth

ATTN: QUALITY DEPT. MN14-1C05

12001 Highway 55

Plymouth, MN 55441


5) You may use the following carriers and account numbers for the return:

USA Returns: UPS (Ground Service - collect account 569503) or FedEx (Ground Service - collect account 055408106)

International Returns: DHL Express - (collect account 963188108)


* For MRAM products, it is recommended that MRAM shipping containers from Honeywell be reused. If this is not possible, the shipping approach should ensure that each MRAM part is a minimum of 4&quot; from each outer surface of the box. It is also recommended that a prominent label be attached to the outer box indicating &quot;Caution - contains magnetic field sensitive devices - open in appropriate environment only.&quot; Honeywell can provide such labels upon request.


Thank you,



Honeywell Customer Support</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
