<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Honeywell Blank Quote Sheet PROs BER &amp; Reminders</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>Honeywell Blank Quote Sheet PROs BER &amp; Reminders</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Production Return Quote {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Date: {!Today}

To: {!Case.Contact}
Company: {!Case.Account}
Phone: {!Case.Primary_Work_Number__c}
Fax: {!Case.Contact_Fax_Number__c}
Email: {!Case.Primary_Email_Address__c}

From:  AEROPRO@Honeywell.com

Disposition: Beyond Economical Rework Assessment

Purchase Order:  {!Case.Customer_PO_RO_WONumber__c}
Part Number:  {!Case.Product_Part__c}
Serial Number:  {!Case.Product_Serial_Number__c}

We have completed the evaluation of your production return unit.  It has been determined that the rework cost in order to return this unit to an as new conditional is beyond the cost of a new replacement unit. In order to close out this production return order, please select from one of the three options provided below.

Option 1: Scrap on Site

QTY: 1 (CSR: Enter Qty number)
Total Labor and Test: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Label Total $$)
Total Parts: N/A
Total Quote: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Total $$ for quote)

Option 2:  Return As-Is

QTY: 1 (CSR: Enter Qty number)
Total Labor and Test: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Label Total $$)
Total Parts: N/A
Total Quote: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Total $$ for quote)

Option 3:  Rework and Return part (Reference attached Cafe Report)

QTY: 1 (CSR: Enter Qty number)
Total Labor and Test: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Label Total $$)
Total Parts: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Parts Total $$)
Total Quote: $ 1,111.11 (CSR: Enter Total $$ for quote)

If Scrap on Site or Return As-Is are selected, we can help you with a purchase of a new part. Simply let us know and we will help facilitate that transaction within our organization.

To rework your unit, please provide an amended Purchase Order within 3 working days. Any PRO unit returned for rework should include a zero dollar PO with: Honeywell entity address, rework PO number, Honeywell P/N and S/N , Quantity, Bill to, Customer delivery address and Carrier and freight details.

Note: If no response received by the 10th business day from the date of this quote, units will be returned as is and invoice you the applicable test fee. All units deemed no fault found will incur applicable test fee.

For information on status and quote amount, please respond directly to this email.

Honeywell Customer Support
http://www.MyAerospace.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
