<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Tech Pubs CD Collection Access</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Access_Request</letterhead>
    <name>Tech Pubs CD Collection Access</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Request {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},


Your publication(s) {!Case.Publication_Number__c} are now available through the MyAerospace portal.

We&apos;ve made some changes to the technical publication web page since you were there last


To view your &quot;collection&quot; of documents:


1. Log on to the portal using your new user id XXXX and password then submit.

2. On the next screen click on the Technical Publication box. This will bring you to the Search Publication screen.

3.  Enter your pub number, #####, into the search field and click on search.

4. Click the &quot;View Collection&quot; link in the right column.

5. On the gray bar near the top of the page, click on Manuals. A drop down will appear, click on Collection Manuals. This will bring up all the publications for the collection you require.



For additional publications, click on &quot;Request this Publication&quot;

and submit to your shopping cart.



For Case Related Questions?


We’ll connect all of your order details through the subject line of this email. So, should you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.


Thanks again! We appreciate your business,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099


ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}


This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
