<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Technical Publications Subscription Renewal</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Renewal</letterhead>
    <name>Tech Pubs Renewal</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Request  {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Subject}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},

Please note that your current subscription will be expiring on DATE.   The renewal must be approved and paid in full before the expiration of your current subscription to retain access to Technical Publications,

You can now review, finalize and pay your invoice online by following the attached renewal instructions via Honeywell Forge.

The objective of Honeywell Forge Dashboard is to provide one location to administer subscriptions. Eliminates the need for customers to navigate to, and login to, individual sites for both. 


Actions needed:

·         Approve/Reject renewal invoice

·         Process invoice payment online

Note:  We have enclosed process steps for your reference.

If you are unable to finish the renewal process online, you can still choose to accept your renewal as normal by replying to pubs@honeywell.com
 Regards,


{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099

ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}

This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
