<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Tech Pubs GEM Orders Access</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Access_Request</letterhead>
    <name>Tech Pubs GEM Orders Access</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Access Request  {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Subject}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},

Your technical publication (publication no.) associated with purchase order (PO no.) for part number (part no.) is now available for immediate online viewing through the MyAerospace portal.



We’ve attached a simple “how to” guide to help you create your User ID and Password in case you don&apos;t already have one.

For Case Related Questions?

We’ll connect all of your order details through the subject line of this email. So, should you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.



Thanks again! We appreciate your business,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099





ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}





This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
