<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Requesting access to the Tech Pubs Portal</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Access_Request</letterhead>
    <name>Getting Setup on MYAEROSPACE.COM</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Access Request  {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear  ,

Attached is our registration guide to access MyAerospace.com. You can create your Honeywell ID by clicking on the link below.

https://ads.honeywell.com/login

Please note: After your registration, you will receive an email to confirm your email address and password. You may also be required to request access to GoDirect  and Technical Publication Services. For Tech Pubs access please also electronically sign and return the End User Statement we have attached for your convenience.





Your Tech Pubs Support Team

Have you encountered an issue? We are available Mon.thru Fri. 5 a.m.to 4 p.m. Mountain Time to support you. Please contact:

Technical Publications
For all service &amp; account related issues


+1-800-601-3099
pubs@Honeywell.com



© 2018 Honeywell International Inc.
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Contact Us

For Case Related Questions?

We’ll connect all of your inquiry details through the subject line of this email. So, should you reply, please leave the subject line just like it is to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.



Thanks again! We appreciate your business,



{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099





ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}





This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
