<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Technical Publications Quote</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Access_Request</letterhead>
    <name>Tech Pubs Quote</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Request {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},

Thank you for your interest in our technical publications! We’ve attached a copy of the quote for the technical publications you’ve requested.


&lt;insert technical publication (publication no.) and quote (quote no.)



We’ll connect all of your quote details through the subject line of this email. So, when you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.


How to proceed with your order with:



Purchase Orders
-  Reply to this email and attach your purchase order.


Check or Wire Transfer
-  Reply to this email and attach your payment confirmation.

Credit Cards
-  Payments are processed through a Honeywell agent. Please call us at 1-800-601-3099 and provide your quote or unique tracking number.



To proceed with your order, simply reply to this email and specify your preferred method of payment. Payments by credit card are processed through a Honeywell agent. 



Thanks again! We appreciate your business,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099



ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}



This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
