<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Technical Publications Web - Request for Access</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Tech_Pubs_Access_Request</letterhead>
    <name>Tech Pubs New Customer Setup</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Your Honeywell Tech Pubs Request is Missing Info  {!Case.CaseNumber}, {!Case.Subject}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!Contact.FirstName},



Thank you for contacting the Honeywell Aerospace Technical Publications Team. We’ve received your {!Case.Subject} inquiry, and are anxious to get right to work on it.



But before we can start, we need your help. We need just a bit more information that was missing from your request.

Signed New Customer Setup Form (Attachment)


Just reply to this email and include your signed form. To track our progress on your request, use this unique tracking number: {!Case.CaseNumber}.

For Case Related Questions?

We’ll connect all of your inquiry details through the subject line of this email. So, when you reply, please leave the subject line unchanged to make sure your response is routed immediately to this case.



Here’s the profile information we’ve gathered from your request. Please let us know if we need to make any changes.



First name   : &lt;Insert customer first name&gt;
Last name   : &lt;Insert customer last name&gt;
Username   : &lt;Insert requested username&gt;
Company name   : &lt;Insert company name&gt;
Phone number  : &lt;Insert customer phone&gt;



Thanks again! We appreciate your business,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Honeywell Aerospace
Technical Publications Team
Web: http://www.MyAerospace.com
1-800-601-3099 or internationally at 1-602-365-3099



ORIGINAL CORRESPONDENCE:
{!Case.Subject}
{!Case.Description}
{!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}





This e-mail message and any attachment(s) are for the use of the intended recipient(s) and may contain proprietary and/or confidential information, which may be privileged or otherwise protected from disclosure. Further, information contained herein, U.S. Export Control laws may control including attached files.  Any unauthorized review, use, disclosure or distribution of this communication in whole or in part without the express written consent of Honeywell, or the U.S. Government as required, is prohibited.  If you are not the intended recipient(s), please contact the sender by reply email and destroy the original message and any copies of the message as well as any attachment(s) to the original message.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
