<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Quotes - Repair</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>CSO - Quotes Repair</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support.  Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above.  If you wish to communicate with us further about this inquiry, you may reply to this e-mail -- please leave the Reference Case # within the subject line for quicker responses.
  
The information you requested is captured below.
 
Part/Product #:  
Description:  
Condition (Repair, Repair Mod, Overhaul, Overhaul Mod):  
Lead-time (Avg TAT in Days):  
Quantity:  
Stock (Y/N):  
Price:  
Est. Avg Price:  
Min Price:  
Max Price:  
NCFR / NFF (No cause for rejection or no fault found) Fee:  
 
&lt;Insert body of message here&gt;
 
This quote is an estimate and final price quotation will be provided after an analytical evaluation has been performed on the component by the Honeywell R&amp;O site. 
 
This quote is valid for the next 30 days and delivery is subject to prior sale.
 
This quote is NOT valid for military applications.  
 
Be sure to include the “end user” and “final destination” of product when ready to place an order.
 
For your convenience and faster service, please visit our MyAerospace Web Portal at http://www.MyAerospace.com to request a quote, place an order, get order status, make order changes, authorize a return, and much more.


 

Thank you, we appreciate your business!



 
 
Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web:  http://www.MyAerospace.com
 
 Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
