<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Help Doc for HON ID Registration</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Honeywell_New_logo</letterhead>
    <name>Customer Web Portal Registration Process</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Web Registration Steps {!Case.CaseNumber} {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Thank you for making Honeywell your GoDirect service provider. We appreciate your continued business!



In order to provide you with access to the myaerospace web portal you will need to create a Honeywell ID.



Please visit MyAerospace.com to begin the process. When you get to the website you will see a link for New Users. If you click on this link it will guide you through the registration process.



I have also attached a document which you can refer to if you have any questions or you can view the video tutorial by clicking on this link: Need Help? View Tutorial



One you have created your Honeywell ID, please contact the us so we can link it to your account and you will be able to view your aircraft SBB information.



If I can be of further assistance please don&apos;t hesitate to contact me.



Thank you,



{!Case.OwnerFullName}



Honeywell | Aerospace

FORGE - FSS and Connectivity

Email: fssaccounts@honeywell.com




NOTICE: The information contained in this e-mail and any attachments is intended for the exclusive use of the addressee(s) and may contain proprietary information.  If you are not the intended recipient of this e-mail, you are hereby notified that any form of dissemination of this communication is strictly prohibited.  If this e-mail was sent to you in error, please notify the sender immediately by telephone.



_____________________________________________________________________</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
