<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>EGPWS Communication to be sent on the AT Renewal after Invoice is finalized.</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>AT - 1st Step - EGPWS Communication &amp; Quote</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>EGPWS Communication &amp; Quote {!Account.Name} {!Case.CaseNumber}  {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName}



Please reference the communication regarding the upcoming changes to the Honeywell EGPWS Terrain Database Service.  Attached please find a Database Service Bulletin and Service Introduction document with a detailed explanation of what is changing and why. If you are not responsible for your terrain database(s), please kindly forward to the correct contact keeping us in copy.



Action Needed:

Attached is “EGPWS fleet form” with current AC information on file we believe to have Honeywell EGPWS Installed. Please verify the details under Aircraft Type &amp; Fleet Count and update with any changes.  Once AC Type and Fleet Count have been verified, please select the corresponding Terrain DB and provide the USER ID’s to ensure we link them to your account. Please note all regional databases are included for your MK(s).


Attached is a quote with the available options based on the aircraft count provided. Please let me know what option will best suit your operations. I will then send the service agreement to sign and return in order to set up the annual EGPWS subscription.




Option 1 - One free of charge update per aircraft
Cost for one additional release per year per aircraft if you go with Option 1
Option 2 - 6 updates a year for all aircraft






Regards,
{!Case.OwnerFirstName}

Data Services

Account Management Representative(AMR)

email: dsa@honeywell.com

602-436-6739


For 24-Hour/7-Day technical support, please contact ATS (Aerospace Technical Support) at 855-808-6500 for within the United States and 602-365-6500 for outside the United States,Fax 1-602-365-3343, or  email AeroTechSupport@honeywell.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
