<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Auto Finalize Inv Direct Customers Only (Final - customer never accepted)</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>AT Invoice Auto Issued by Default Direct</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>NavDB Invoice To Be Issued by Default {!Case.Account} {!Case.Sales_Order_Number__c} {!Case.Case_Number__c} {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

We have made several attempts to contact you regarding your annual NavDB service renewal. As of this email, we have not received your confirmation and acceptance of the upcoming service renewal invoice.

Due to the imminent expiration of the subject renewal, we are invoking the automatic renewal provisions in accordance with Article 2, TERM, of your Service Agreement.

Please find attached the final invoice covering the next 13 cycles of service which has been prepared in accordance with the Fee Schedule included with this letter.  Please forward it to the appropriate personnel for payment.

Payment must be received within the agreed upon payment terms to avoid interruption of service.

To register for your ONENAV+ license, please go to the website and download the most recent version of ONENAV+ program to your desktop. As a new user, or to renew your license, you will need to register to get the a license key. Please refer to the steps below to request a license.

Start -&gt; Programs -&gt; OneNav+ -&gt;OneNav+ Help -&gt; Getting Started -&gt; Registration and License -&gt; Registering OneNav+

We appreciate your business and look forward to working with you during this renewal period.  If you have any questions or if I can be of assistance to you, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Regards,

{!Case.OwnerFirstName}
Account Management Representative

602-436-6739

Fax: 602-822-7333

email: AISACCOUNTSERVICES@HONEYWELL.COM


For 24-Hour/7-Day technical support, please contact the Technical Operations Center at 855-808-6500 for within the United States and 602-365-6500 for outside the United States,Fax 1-602-365-3343, or  email AeroTechSupport@honeywell.com


{!EmailMessage.TextBody}</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
