<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>ATC database</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>ATC database</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>ATC database instructions</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Sir,

Regarding the CPDLC ATC database part numbers 69000767-506 or DM60001005-0015.  The FSA states on page 3 to get a FOC copy downloaded.  That statement is in error and is in revision.  There are no downloadable ATC part numbers.  The only way you can get one of these parts is to go to the Honeywell&apos;s website,  https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en  and go to “On-Line Ordering”.  That is our web eCommerce site where you can purchase these parts costing $975 (media fee to cover reproduction costs).  We will ship a CD to you.

We are sorry for delay and  confusion this has caused you.


Kind Regards,



Account Manager
Honeywell aerospace
Tel. 602-365-3099 opt 1, opt 1, opt 2

dsa@honeywell.com

For 24-Hour/7-Day mechanical or avionics technical support, please contact ATS (Aerospace Technical Support) at 855-808-6500 for within the United States and 602-365-6500 for outside the United States,Fax 1-602-365-3343, or email AeroTechSupport@honeywell.com

DISCLAIMER This message is intended only for the use of the person(s) (&quot;Intended Recipient&quot;) to whom it is addressed.  It may contain information, which is privileged and confidential.  Accordingly any forwarding, copying, dissemination or other use of this message or any of its content may constitute a breach of copyright and or breach of civil or criminal law and is strictly prohibited.  Any views held by employees do not necessarily represent the views and opinions of the company.

VIRUSES Please note that we do not, to the extent permitted by the law, accept any liability (whether in contract, negligence or otherwise) for viruses and it is your responsibility to scan the attachments (if any).</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
