<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>GNS What the customer needs to do in order to switch from XLS (8mb) to PRNAV (20mb)</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Plain</letterhead>
    <name>GNS Switch from XLS to PRNAV</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>GNS switch from XLS and PRNAV:  {!Case.CaseNumber}  {!Case.Case_Ref_ID__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

GNS PRNAV upgrade is only a software upgrade and can be carried out by any of the Honeywell Service Centers. Honeywell authorized Service Centers closer to you can be located on the Honeywell ASDS website under “Service Centers &amp; Pilots” tab.


Now, once you enhance the unit, there are 3 databases you can choose from:


- GPR which covers Worldwide with runway restrictions of 6500 ft and above (this info may vary cycle to cycle).

- GPW which covers CAN, USA, LAM, SAM with no runway restrictions (all runways available)

- GPE which covers EUR, AFR, EEU, MES, PAC, SPA with no runway restrictions (all runways available)


When you upgrade to the enhanced PRNAV, we offer an exchange of one 8MB PCMCIA card for one 20MB PCMCIA card (the card must be owned by your company and in good condition in order for the exchange to be valid). If you would like any additional cards, they are $475.86 each and under a one year warranty from the date of purchase.


Regarding your account, the PRNAV subscription is about $949 more per year than what you currently pay. We will upgrade the remainder of your account for free when you let us know of the switch and you will see the PRNAV pricing once your subscription renews. The process of downloading and loading the database is the same as what you do now. The only difference is that you will need to leave the 20mb card in the FMS at all times when flying.



Please let us know once the upgrade has been finished and we can update the account accordingly. Should you have any questions, do not hesitate on contacting us.


Regards,
{!Case.OwnerFirstName}


Data Services

Account Management Representative(AMR)

email: dsa@honeywell.com

602-436-6739


For 24-Hour/7-Day technical support, please contact ATS (Aerospace Technical Support) at 855-808-6500 for within the United States and 602-365-6500 for outside the United States,Fax 1-602-365-3343, or  email AeroTechSupport@honeywell.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
