<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Other - APAC HIS Customer Letter</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>CSO - APAC HIS Customer Letter</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Honeywell Aerospace
ZONE D&apos;ACTIVITES LA PIECE 16
1180 ROLLE
SWITZERLAND

Dear Honeywell Customer,

As previously communicated, Honeywell International Sarl (HIS) was established to better serve the supply of piece parts across the Europe, Middle East, Africa and India regions. We are pleased to announce we have expanded our HIS geographical scope to include the Asia Pacific region.

Over the next several months, the HIS entity will also assume responsibility for delivery of all new condition mechanical and avionics aftermarket piece parts orders currently procured from the Honeywell facility in Phoenix, Ariz. This transition only applies to supplier cage codes 7X000 for mechanical piece parts, and 58960 and 97896 for avionic piece parts.

Starting April 6, 2009, customers may begin ordering new condition mechanical and avionic piece parts using the HIS Cage Code SCY35. This new cage code encompasses mechanical and avionic - new condition only - spare parts. After April 6, 2009, we can no longer accept purchase orders for new condition mechanical and avionics piece parts that are placed at the Phoenix, Ariz., location using supplier cage codes 7X000, 58960 and 97896.

This change does NOT apply to the following items:

Mechanical:
o Complete Engine and APU (top level) assemblies
o Exchange units (APU and Engine rentals)
o Repair and overhaul orders
o RMA and Warranty for parts originally ordered from 7X000
o ITAR restricted parts
o Store front parts

Avionics:
o LRU end items
o SPEX™ (Spares Exchange)
o Consigned parts
o ITAR restricted parts
o EAR licensed parts

For your reference, a detailed list of HIS non-procurable parts and the new ordering process document titled &quot;HIS Order Entry Process for APAC Customers&quot; are included with this letter.

Please note that orders against cage code SCY35 will be shipped from our HIS Distribution Center located in Hemel Hempstead, United Kingdom. For these shipments, we kindly asked that you provide a valid customer carrier account number or freight forwarder with contact details to jirina.salkova@honeywell.com, no later than February 27, 2009.

To make this transition process as seamless as possible, please use the following steps as a guide to help with any system changes:
1. Set up new HIS cage code SCY35 in your system
2. Amend purchase order address to display HIS vendor details
3. Amend HIS vendor billing information
4. Amend HIS bank details in your system

After the transition is completed, all customer calls will continue to be routed to the 24/7 Global

Customer Care Center in Phoenix, Ariz. at:
· Toll-free number US: 1-800-601-3099
· Toll-free number Int.: 1-602-365-3099
· Fax number: 1- 877-484-2980

Our Asia Pacific customer account leaders, program managers and supply chain leaders will work closely with your procurement organization and program teams to ensure that each step of the process is well communicated and effectively implemented.

During this transition, we want to assure you that we have your best interests in mind. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact your regular Honeywell representative.

Thank you for your support as we work to enhance the way Honeywell Aerospace does business with you.


Sincerely,

Frank Kolmich (acting)
Vice President Airlines - Honeywell International Sarl
Pak Chin
Vice President Airlines - Honeywell Asia Pacific
Jeff Donnell
Vice President Business &amp; General Aviation and Customer &amp; Product Support - Honeywell International Sarl

Honeywell International SARL - Company Information

COMPANY NAME:  
HONEYWELL INTERNATIONAL SARL

COMPANY ADDRESS:
ZONE D&apos;ACTIVITES LA PIECE 16
1180 ROLLE
SWITZERLAND

(Note : All HIS invoicing will come from this address)

PURCHASE ORDER ADDRESS (to be included on the PO):
ZONE D&apos;ACTIVITES LA PIECE 16
1180 ROLLE
SWITZERLAND

SEND PURCHASE ORDERS TO THE Phoenix CUSTOMER CARE CENTER: (DO NOT SEND THE PO’s TO SWITZERLAND)

HONEYWELL INTERNATIONAL SARL
C/O HONEYWELL International, Inc.
Toll-free number: 1-800-601-30999
Toll number: 1-602-365-3099
Fax number: 1- 877-484-2980

Honeywell International, Sarl. DISTRIBUTION CENTER
Honeywell Aerospace
Unit 2-4 Chevron
Eaton Road
Hemel Hempstead
HP2 7DR.
United Kingdom

TAX ID (VAT): GB 907 5560 17

DUNS &amp; BRADSTREET NUMBER: 483642950

IATA ADDRESS: PRGHWCR

CAGE CODE: SCY35

BANK INFORMATION:
Deutsche Bank AG
17 AVENUE MARNIXLAAN
B-1000 Brussels
Belgium

USD Account:
Deutsche Bank Brussels
Account number (USD): 826-0024674-53

IBAN: BE53826002467453

BIC: DEUTBEBEXXX

CURRENCY: USD

FINANCE CONTACTS:
Eva Novotna – Head of Accounting
Phone: +420 234 625 582
E-mail: eva.novotna2@honeywell.com

Gwenael Rouy-Poirier - HIS Controller
Tel: 41 217 117 823 (Swiss)
E-mail: gwenael.rouy.poirier@honeywell.com

CREDIT AND COLLECTION CONTACTS:
Linda Lee – Credit Manager
Phone: +8610-8458 3280 ext 522
E-mail: linda.lee@honeywell.com

Alice Yap – Credit Manager
Phone: +603-7884 1948
E-mail: alice.yap@honeywell.com

QUALITY MANAGEMENT SYSTEM:
http://businesscontrols.honeywell.com/policies/Aerospace/Site-Level/HIS

QUALITY CONTACTS:
Graham Crighton – HIS Quality Leader
Phone (Switzerland): +41 21 711 7845
E-mail: graham.crighton@honeywell.com

Babette Poncato- Quality Analyst
Phone: +41 21 711 7838
Fax: +41 21 711 7889
Email: Babette.poncato@honeywell.com</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
