<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>First Standard Pricing Communication - Introduction</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Standard Pricing Customer Letter 08.03.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Repair &amp; Overhaul Standard Pricing</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










One price. No surprises. Great value.
Bringing you a new level of value, scheduling, and service.
Beginning August 31st, there’s a big change coming to Repair &amp; Overhaul services at Honeywell’s facilities – and it means great things for you. It’s called Standard Pricing. And just like the name says, it brings a welcome predictability to the cost and coordination of aircraft part repair and overhaul.
Here’s what’s different:
Until now, the cost of Honeywell R&amp;O work was based on the time and materials it would take to get each job done. A challenge with that approach is that it takes time for both of us to prep and approve the quote, impacting cycle times and tying up assets.

Honeywell Standard Pricing changes all that. Now, you’ll know exactly what the charge will be before you even schedule the work. And that’s just the beginning of the advantage Standard Pricing brings you.

Each repair still goes through a detailed analysis to identify work scope. But now the Standard Price will be available immediately and cover common repairs up to two times (~2X) the Standard Price. If your repair happens to exceed that amount, Time and Material pricing will be applied.

 











 
Here’s what it means for you:
The companies that have tried Standard Pricing give it glowing reports.


 - Up to 40% Faster Turn Around Time
 - And repair quote approvals are a thing of the past. That’s time-savings that over the year really adds up. 
 - Just add the Standard Price to your repair purchase order, and we’ll begin the work immediately.
 - Remember, Standard Prices will be updated annually.



 

 
Here’s how to bring Standard Pricing to your business:
We’ve designed a special Standard Pricing process for our best customers. Within the next two weeks, we’ll send you an Excel spreadsheet compiled just for YOU! On that list will be every product or service you ordered in the past year that’s now covered by Honeywell Standard Pricing, as well as the price.


 - Using the attached Excel file, find your new Standard Price.
 - Upload the file, and the price will be automatically added to your PO. Or, you can manually reference the price.
 - Send in your repair and PO, and we’ll go to work.












&gt;&gt;&gt; Find yourself with excess LRU assets as a result of our faster turnaround times? Honeywell would be happy to purchase your stock. Just give HAT a call at 866-825-5428 or email aerospacetrading@honeywell.com &lt;mailto:aerospacetrading@honeywell.com&gt;

It’s as easy, predictable, and valuable as that! So try it.
And take your Repair &amp; Overhaul operations to a higher level. If you run into any difficulties using Standard Pricing your first time through, we’re here to quickly help make sense of it.
Honeywell reserves the right to impose additional charges, on a time and material (“T&amp;M”) basis, for any accident, misuse, mishandling, corrosion, missing parts, underwater locator beacon/batteries, life limited hardware due to time limits, Beyond Economic Repair (&quot;BER&quot;), Foreign Object Damage (“FOD”) or other damage not related to normal wear and tear (collectively, “Abuse”).
Unless covered by an agreement in force between Honeywell and Customer, any services provided hereunder shall be subject to the Honeywell Repair and Overhaul Terms applicable to Customer, which can be found here &lt;https://commerce.honeywell.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/HonCatalogDownloadView?storeId=10651&gt;.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
