<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Embraer Ops Conference China 05.20.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Visit Honeywell at Embraer’s Operators Conference May 25 &amp; 26</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;









 
 

Embraer’s Operators Conference May 25 &amp; 26 – China
















We hope to see you next week 
 at Embraer’s Operators Conference 

Come see for yourself the new level of service we’ve built on your comments, feedback, and needs. We’ll be facilitating a key session, as well as gathering your thoughts and reactions to these new initiatives.

If it’s been a while, take a look at Honeywell. Stop by our session at the Embraer Operators Conference on May 26th, or read on to learn more.


You’re going to like what lies ahead...


 - Performance Accelerator – Introducing a Service Bulletin search so customizable, it’s like we built it just for you. Every service bulletin you need to see, and not a single one you don’t. With the all-new, online Performance Accelerator &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/THZQZ00030000I320q00GX0&gt;, select your own search criteria, and the Service Bulletins and upgrades relevant to your fleet are there immediately.

 - Check out the 74% faster MyAerospace portal! 
 It won’t take long, we promise. Recently, we made enhancements to improve internet performance globally. As a result, our MyAerospace portal is faster than ever in the Asia Pacific region. Check it out for yourself at MyAerospace.com &lt;https://myaerospace.honeywell.com/&gt;!





Embraer’s Operators Conference 
May 25 &amp; 26 
 Hotel St. Regis 
 Tianjin City, China
 

 Can’t make it?
 Don’t worry, 
 we’re coming to you! 
 In the next year alone, we’ll be at more than 60 OEM events and conferences – like the one in Tianjin City – ready to answer your questions and address your concerns.
In the meantime, learn about Honeywell’s portal enhancements that simplify your online experience.


 - Checkout our new GTO video. (Watch video) &lt;https://youtu.be/7KqbTtAj9dE&gt;
 - Find out how to download a Tech Pub&apos;s document using your iPad. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Download_TechPubs_In_IPad.mp4&gt;
 - How to get automatic email notifications on your order. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Email_Notifications_How_to.mp4&gt;
 - Check pricing and parts availability. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Search_for_a_Part_How_to.mp4&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
