<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>ATR Messages.ATR Bombardier Conference 05.19.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Visit Honeywell at the Bombardier Operators Conference May 26 – 28</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;









 
 

2015 Bombardier All Series Operators Conference
















We hope to see you next week
 at Bombardier’s All Series Operators Conference 

Honeywell Aerospace gives you the power to chart the perfect course for your fleet and your business, with innovative products that win the praise of airlines in demanding, real-life operations.

Come see for yourself the new level of service we’ve built on your comments, feedback, and needs. Visit our booth to check out our all-new, online tool, as well as tell us your thoughts and reactions.

If it’s been a while, take a look at Honeywell. Stop by Booth 9 at the Bombardier All Series Operators Conference, or read on to learn more.


You’re going to like what lies ahead...


 - Performance Accelerator – Introducing a Service Bulletin search so customizable, it’s like we built it just for you. Every service bulletin you need to see, and not a single one you don’t. Select your own search criteria with our new Performance Accelerator &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/THZQZ00030000I320q00GX0&gt;, and the Service Bulletins and upgrades relevant to your fleet are there immediately.
 - Aerospace Technical Support – Reach Honeywell technical experts 24/7, with just one number (1-602-365-6500). No long waits or handoffs from department to department - just quick, accurate, precise solutions to keep you flying.




Bombardier All Series Operators Conference 
May 26 - 28
 Sheraton Munich 
 Arabellapark Hotel 
 Munich, Germany
Check out the 
10 top things to do in Munich &lt;http://www.express.co.uk/travel/activity/576790/10-top-things-to-see-and-do-in-Munich&gt; 
 from the UK Express
 

Can’t make it?
 Don’t worry, 
 we’re coming to you! 
 In the next year alone, we’ll be at more than 60 OEM events and conferences – like the one in Munich – ready to answer your questions and address your concerns.
In the meantime, learn about Honeywell’s portal enhancements that simplify your online experience.


 - Checkout our new GTO video. (Watch video) &lt;https://youtu.be/7KqbTtAj9dE&gt;
 - Find out how to download a Tech Pub&apos;s document using your iPad. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Download_TechPubs_In_IPad.mp4&gt;
 - How to get automatic email notifications on your order. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Email_Notifications_How_to.mp4&gt;
 - Check pricing and parts availability. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Search_for_a_Part_How_to.mp4&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
