<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>CSO Messages.SECAN Transition Wave 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell SECAN Site Transitions - Vendome and Gennevilliers</subject>
    <textOnly>June 16, 2015

 

Dear Honeywell Customer,

 Honeywell has signed an agreement on 23 April to sell our SECAN legal entity to an affiliate of Quantum Capital Partners AG. SECAN today consists of two sites: Gennevilliers and Vendôme. This sale covers only the activities in Gennevilliers. The Vendôme site will remain with Honeywell.

Vendôme
 
 Our site in Vendome will continue to remain with Honeywell and become a new legal entity – Honeywell Aerospace Vendome – on 26 June.

How this change may impact you.   



 - Your current Repair &amp; Overhaul orders will be automatically transferred from SECAN to Honeywell Aerospace Vendôme as of 26 June. 
 
 

 - For any Quality questions, please contact your Honeywell Quality Manager or Victor Perou at Victor.Perou@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:Victor.Perou@Honeywell.com&gt;. 





 - Following the 26 June Vendôme transition, our Vendôme financial accounting information will change. To avoid any disruption in service, please update your systems as needed. The new remittance banking account information is below.


SAS au capital de 10.000 euro
 Honeywell Aerospace Vendome
 18 BD DE L INDUSTRIE
 41100 Vendôme
 487 674 640 R.C.S BLOIS-APE 3030Z
 Tel: +33 (0)2 54 77 71 05
Payment by bank transfer
BNP - Bercy PARIS 12
IBAN
FR7630004025110001057738368
Swift N °
BNPAFRPPIFO

Gennevilliers

We are pleased to say that we are on track to close the anticipated sale on 24 July 2015.

After 24 July, all Air Management System product lines (including heat exchangers and vapor cycle air conditioning systems) design and manufacturing, and repair activities will continue to be performed by SECAN. Together, we are committed to ensuring a smooth transition for you, our customer, employees and suppliers. We have established a dedicated transition team to minimize any interruption in service.

For any questions on Gennevilliers quality certification requirements ISO9001, AS9100, EASA PART21G, EASA PART145, NUCAP/PRI (special processes and NDT), or about the flow down of your Quality requirement, please contact Gilles Patry, Quality Leader, at +33140805985 or email Gilles.Patry@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:Gilles.Patry@Honeywell.com&gt;.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact your Honeywell representative or send an email to AeroCPSCommunications@Honeywell.com &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/c000200Q0qZI04GXW00tN00&gt;.

Yours Sincerely, 
 
 Heath Patrick
Vice President
Customer &amp; Product Support
Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
