<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Customer Experience (CX).Boeing 787 Fleet Team Mtg; July 19-23, 2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Visit Honeywell at the Boeing 787 Fleet Team Meeting, July 19-23</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;









 
 

2015 Boeing 787 Fleet Team Conference – Washington















Honeywell is geared up to take on a long list of activities for you in Washington.
We’ll be there throughout the gathering to share full details on the improvements we’re making to our 787 products (many of them as a result of your feedback). Honeywell staff will also be on hand for a panel discussion on topics critical to your flight operations.
Away from the main floor and scheduled meetings, the Honeywell Balsam Room suite will be open after hours on Tuesday to welcome you in for eats, drinks and great prizes.
Best of all, we’ll take every opportunity to visit with you throughout the meetings to hear your take on what’s working, what needs more work, and how we can make your business easier, better, and more profitable.
We’ll see you in Washington!

You’re going to like what lies ahead...


 - Performance Accelerator – Introducing a Service Bulletin search so customizable, it’s like we built it just for you. Every service bulletin you need to see, and not a single one you don’t. Select your own search criteria with our new Performance Accelerator &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/THZQZ00030000I320q00GX0&gt;, and the Service Bulletins and upgrades relevant to your fleet are there immediately.
 - Aerospace Technical Support – Reach Honeywell technical experts 24/7, with just one number (1-602-365-6500). No long waits or handoffs from department to department - just quick, accurate, precise solutions to keep you flying.




Boeing 787
 Fleet Team Conference 
July 19 - 23
 Hyatt Bellevue 
 Bellevue, Washington

Can’t make it?
 Don’t worry, 
 we’re coming to you! 
 This year alone, we’ll be at more than 60 OEM events and conferences – like the one in Washington – ready to answer your questions and address your concerns.
In the meantime, learn about Honeywell’s portal enhancements that simplify your online experience.


 - Checkout our new Technical Support video. (Watch video) &lt;https://youtu.be/7KqbTtAj9dE&gt;
 - Find out how to download a Tech Pub&apos;s document using your iPad. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Download_TechPubs_In_IPad.mp4&gt;
 - How to get automatic email notifications on your order. (Watch video) &lt;http://goaero.honeywell.com/R00q004I0G002000QVXw7Z0&gt;
 - Check pricing and parts availability. (Watch video) &lt;http://commerce.honeywell.com/wcsstore/B2BDirectMyAerospaceAssetStore/images/catalog/Search_for_a_Part_How_to.mp4&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
