<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Portal Communication.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Changes to Honeywell’s Order Process</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;

Honeywell Order Changes

Fast. Simple. Reliable.
You told us that’s how every Honeywell product order and delivery experience should be. And we heard you. So now we’re taking big steps to make sure that’s what you’ll find – 100 percent of the time.
Here are the tools we’ll use to accomplish that better level of service:

An all-new, high-performance portal that leaves email in the dust.
 This is not Honeywell’s old portal. It’s far easier to use, incredibly accurate, and constantly accessible. Instead of waiting 12 hours for confirmation of your email order, the portal gives you immediate confirmation. And rather than batching information for occasional updates, the portal displays real-time data for quotes, spares, OEM and repair orders. You can track the up-to-the-minute fulfillment and shipping of your order whenever you choose. Get quote approvals online. And watch your repair order as it moves through the shop with our new order health monitoring feature.

Client Service Representative support that’s more supportive than ever. For this one, we brought in the experts. Honeywell has partnered with Infosys – a world-renowned, award-winning customer response organization whose work has set new standards in customer satisfaction.

We’ll also soon unveil a new and improved, customer designed, quote form; as well as other programs and processes to make partnering with us easier, faster, and more satisfying than ever.
As you begin to use these overhauled ordering elements, let us know how they’re working for you. After all, comments from customers like you are the reasons behind our changes. And we welcome your thoughts on where we go next.
P.S. Let us introduce the all-new Honeywell portal to your team. Contact us at Portal2.0 &lt;mailto:MyAerospacePortalissue@honeywell.com&gt; to receive a schedule of our upcoming webinars.

Privacy Statement &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;   &lt;http://honeywell.com/Privacy&gt;| Terms &amp; Conditions &lt;http://honeywell.com/Pages/TermsConditions.aspx&gt; | © 2013 Honeywell International Inc &lt;http://www.honeywell.com&gt;</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
