<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Cross SBU.EGPWS Terrain DB Subscription Upgrade 07.30.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Streamlined Terrain DB Downloads. Only the data you need.</subject>
    <textOnly>&lt;http://aerospace.honeywell.com/services&gt;
 &lt;https://twitter.com/Honeywell_Aero&gt;
 &lt;http://www.youtube.com/honeywell&gt;
 &lt;https://plus.google.com/109803702550636260475&gt;
 &lt;http://www.linkedin.com/company/honeywell-aerospace&gt;










Dear Honeywell Customer,
Finding the easiest, quickest, smartest way to get from here to there has always been aviation’s goal. Now, Honeywell is happy to contribute to the progress with a completely redesigned Aerospace Database Services (ADS) website, affectionately renamed Aerospace Software and Data Services (ASDS).
The updated ASDS is worlds apart from the site you’ve been using. It features a clutter-free, easy-to-navigate design that quickly connects the information dots. But the best thing about ASDS is its functionality. We’ll soon be able to customize the EGPWS results you see based upon your fleet.
As you’re renewing your NavDB agreement, we’ll ask you to share some information about your fleet that will help us customize your downloads. Your input will help us to provide you with downloads that apply specifically to your fleet and the way it flies. And, it allows you to avoid time wasted sorting through data you&apos;ll never use.



 




See for yourself. Click on https://ads.honeywell.com &lt;https://ads.honeywell.com/&gt;. And find the quick, easy, and smart way to get where you need to be.

 




If you’re a new user to the database service or just need some help with registration, please contact us and we’ll get right back to you. We may be a bit slower after 5:00 pm (MST) and on the weekends.





 




Email: DSA@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:DSA@Honeywell.com&gt;

 






 




Phone: +1.602.436.6737, Option 5


 




And we’re not done improving. We’ve also developed an EGPWS subscription that will offer you Terrain updates 6 times per year! The subscription will give you the first download FREE. Then, by bundling updates 2 through 6, you’ll pay just $500 per aircraft for all five – just $100/download. 
 Click here for more details. &lt;https://pages3.honeywell.com/rs/641-QIX-912/images/EGPWS_SalesSheet.pdf&gt;
Best Regards,
 Honeywell Aerospace Services</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
