<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>Cross SBU.GAM SAP 60 day Wave 1 Letter 06.11.2015</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Honeywell Aftermarket R&amp;O Sites Upgrade SAP System</subject>
    <textOnly>Normal 0     
false false false  EN-US X-NONE 
X-NONE          
 MicrosoftInternetExplorer4                 
 
 
 
 

 
 
Honeywell Aerospace 
 1944 E. Sky Harbor Circle
Phoenix, AZ 85034


June 11, 2015
 

 

Dear Honeywell Customer, 

Honeywell is upgrading its Aftermarket Repair &amp; Overhaul (R&amp;O) sites to an enhanced version of SAP, an enterprise resource planning system. With the upgrade, sites will now be able to see the inventory and WIP at other Honeywell locations. We’ll be able to more quickly source parts for you and fulfill requests. 

In phase one, we’ll transition the following sites to the SAP solution in August 2015. 





Tempe - West Warner Road
1300 West Warner Road
Tempe, AZ, US 85284

 



 



Honeywell Int. SARL
c/o Honeywell Aerospace UK
Edison Road
Basingstoke, Hampshire, GB RG21 6QD





Wichita - CS ERB &amp; R&amp;O
7227 W. Harry
Wichita, KS, US 67209




AES CS Shanghai
430 Li Bing Road, Zhang Jiang
Shanghai, CN 201203 







 



 





At this time there are no changes being made to how you engage with Honeywell. Your Honeywell contacts remain the same. 

We will share more details on the timing of the transition and any specific changes over the next 60 days. 

Following the successful completion of this initial phase, the team will begin phase two to transition the remaining R&amp;O sites in Renton, Washington; Rocky Mount, North Carolina; Toulouse, France; Tucson, Arizona, and 
Singapore over to the enhanced SAP solution in October 2015. Details on the second phase will be shared with customers in August. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact your Honeywell representative or send an email to AeroCPSCommunications@Honeywell.com &lt;mailto:AeroCPSCommunications@Honeywell.com&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&gt;

Yours Sincerely,

Heath Patrick
 Vice President
 Customer &amp; Product Support
 Honeywell Aerospace</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
