<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Invoice Disputes - Payment Info</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>CSO - Disputes Payment Info</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support.  Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above.  If you wish to communicate with us further about this inquiry, you may reply to this e-mail -- please leave the Reference Case # within the subject line for quicker responses.
 
The Debit Memo reason is captured below.

Incorrect Price:  
Under warranty:  
Returned for repair:  
Charged sales tax:  
Returned for credit:  
Defective/rejected material:
Other (please specify):  
 
Purchase Order #:  
Invoice #:  
 
This Debit Memo is issued as a re-bill against the original invoice for the correct price.  The original invoice was credited due to the above reason.  THIS DEBIT MEMO IS PAYABLE.
 
Please refer to attached referenced documents.
 
Please reply with payment details to ensure your account is updated promptly and accurately.
 
&lt;Insert body of message here&gt;
 
For your convenience and faster service, please visit our MyAerospace Web Portal at http://www.MyAerospace.com to request a quote, place an order, get order status, make order changes, authorize a return, and much more.

 
Thank you, we appreciate your business!



 
 
Honeywell Aerospace
Customer &amp; Product Support
Web:  http://www.MyAerospace.com
 
 Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
