<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>ISC - RoHS Position</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>ISC - RoHS Position</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Case.Subject} : {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for contacting Honeywell Aerospace Customer Support.  Your case tracking number for this inquiry is provided above.  If you wish to communicate with us further about this inquiry, you may reply to this e-mail -- please leave the Reference Case # within the subject line for quicker responses. 
 
The Aerospace industry is considered ‘out of scope’ to the RoHS Directive and is not required to comply with the material restrictions included in the directive.  This email provides the current position of Honeywell Aerospace on the use of alternative component termination finishes, Pb-free solders and their subsequent assembly processes in response to regulatory directives such as RoHS. These directives increasingly restrict the use of certain hazardous materials including lead. Honeywell Aerospace understands the impact of these directives: forcing the move of our supply chain to lead-free materials and limiting the availability of traditional tin-lead materials. As a result, Honeywell Aerospace is investigating the use of lead-free component surface finishes, lead-free solder alloys for assembly and assembly processes with an emphasis on maintaining product performance and reliability given these material and process changes. Further, Honeywell Aerospace is actively participating on industry committees chartered to govern the introduction of lead-free materials into the aerospace market. An example is the Aerospace Industries Association Lead-free Electronics in Aerospace Process Working Group (AIA-LEAP WG).
 
Note: Applications designated as GEIA-STD-0005-2 tin whisker control “level 3” will maintain non-pure tin termination finish and will be negotiated as such.
 
For more information please contact us @ REACH.Aero@Honeywell.com
Yours faithfully,

Marjorie Baumann
Director of Product Stewardship
Honeywell Aerospace

 
 Due to government regulations and/or contractual limitations, all data and/or attachments containing export control information and/or containing details related to Space, Munitions and Missiles items is not authorized for entry or use in our applications or systems at the present time</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
