<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Lead Assignment Template for MARCOM Lead Team</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Logo</letterhead>
    <name>Lead Assignment template MARCOM</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Lead Assigned</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.OwnerFullName},

Please refer to Lead {!Lead.Link}

This lead has now been assigned to you as lead owner:

Please evaluate the lead immediately and, if it looks accurate, move the lead to Sales Accepted Lead (SAL). If it is not, please change the lead status to Recycle or Disqualified. Should your SAL become a Sales Qualified Lead (SQL) after a conversation with the customer, please change the lead status and convert it to an Opportunity.  

Please update the “Honeywell Response date” &amp; “Next Steps” field accordingly. The most recent communication from the customer can be found in the Next Steps section.

If you do not update the lead within two weeks, it is possible that it could appear on a leaked leads report to leadership.
 
Thank you so much for contributing to Honeywell’s growth!

- Marketing Communications Lead Team
 
 
Please refer below for Lead Status Definitions :
 
Sales Accepted:
A lead formally accepted by sales upon which sales agrees to take action. 

Sales Qualified:
A lead that has evolved into a qualified pipeline opportunity.  These leads should be converted to Opportunities.

Recycle:
Leads that need to be passed back to marketing because they were not ready to buy, but the lead needs to remain active.
•        Requirement may arise at a future date (e.g. due mandate).
 
Disqualified:
Leads that are not appropriate or viable such as a no or incorrect  contact info, not our target market, lead is from a student or job seeker, customer contact established and customer is not interested, Opportunity already exists. “Reason for disqualification” field on leads page is to be populated accordingly.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
