<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>User Management: User Creation</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Welcome to Nokia Salesforce CRM</subject>
    <textOnly>Distribution: New and Reactivated Salesforce CRM Users

Welcome to Nokia’s Customer Relationship Management Platform: Salesforce CRM

Dear Salesforce CRM User,

The Salesforce CRM solution is Nokia’s automated customer relationship management platform, consisting of integrated tools to improve sales execution and to achieve a better customer experience.

Call for Action:

Please take the necessary steps to ensure you are trained and aware of the processes and the CRM platform.

1. Please bookmark this  URL to log in to Salesforce CRM using Nokia Web Single Sign-On (SSO). Login at least once a month to avoid being deactivated.

2. Google Chrome is the recommended browser. If Chrome is not available, Mozilla Firefox or Microsoft Edge may also be used. Please do not use Internet Explorer

3.  Please review the  training materials and watch the quick reference videos to establish a firm foundation in understanding the Salesforce CRM tool and the sales process

4. Knowledge of Nokia’s  Sales Process and License to Deal (L2D) Policy and Process  is beneficial for sales opportunity management.

For more details about the Salesforce CRM benefits, please visit the  CRM Central Hub  for all Nokia Salesforce users.

What’s in it for you?

Salesforce CRM allows you to share, manage and analyze data more easily and to collaborate with customers and teams in real-time. Enhanced efficiency and reduced administrative burden is achieved by intuitive navigation and the user-friendly interface. Functionalities:

•	Account, Contact, and Lead Management
•	Opportunity Management
•	Forecasting
•	Dashboards and Reporting
•	Governance and Approvals
•	Collaboration and Efficiency
•	Einstein Analytics

Support and contacts

If you have any questions, please contact the following for:
•	Salesforce CRM questions (e.g. tool functionalities, sales process): Sales Process Champions and CRM Key Users  by markets and BGs
•Salesforce CRM access
•Other IT (non-CRM) log in issues: Contact Nokia’s IT help desk

Thanks for your continued engagement and support.

Regards,
Salesforce CRM Program Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
